OK so we can start with a second project of course.
And of course this one is going to be much much harder.
So I have the finished application right here.
So this is the final one I believe this is final.
Yeah this is the final one.
So take a look at all the components we are going to be creating.
So it's a you know a lot more work than the other one.
And of course after components we're going to use firebase.
We're going to get you our database and everything else so right now we have this.
But we're going to finish with this of course.
And at the end we get to push the project to hosting and get hosted in firebase since we are going to
be using firebase of course on the third one we're going to use something else.
But for now this is what we're going to be creating a Manchester City.
I don't know if you like soccer or football.
Depends you know the pen depends on your country you live.
So this is a football team from England.
So you know I wanted to do something fun you know something fun football team not a to do app or something
like that.
It's really boring.
So OK so this is what we're going to be creating.
So whenever the app loads we begin to do some kind of you know different animations that maybe would
reveal of course we going to use something else.
And when we scroll down we get that we'll transition.
And of course then we get you know a nice animation maybe the image it's too large.
And then when we go down we get again and we get to add user to the email user to the database for example
for a mailing list and going to type whatever whatever and whenever we roll of course there's one is
going to be stored on the firebase database.
Now then of course we're going to go to a different route.
So now we're going to be using routes whenever we go to the team.
We have a list of of course all the team.
And if we go to matches we get the matches with the table.
If we go when we get to apply a filter right here and this filter of course it's going to be pretty
easy because on the next one and the next project we will have a lot of filters.
You know a big section for filtering and of course we need to communicate with the database and get
the filtered data from the database.
With firebase we don't have that option.
So OK.
So of course we need a place where we can enter first the team or the matches right here for example
home.
We have a list of all the matches.
So we need a place so we can enter so we can create a sign in.
We're going to log in with.
We can log in with firebase.
Maybe I don't remember the user I've been using right here.
So yeah.
OK.
So after we log in we're going to go to dashboard if you want to you know go to sign and we are going
to prevent that if you're locked then.
And of course we prevent dashboard.
If you're if you're not Altham dictated so we're going to get the dashboard mattress where we can see
the matches.
We can click on the match to edit the match or we can of course add a new match.
So this is going to be doing a lot of forms.
Then players same idea.
We have a player and we can edit the player or we can of course add player.
We can be able to do that.
So OK players and of course we will store the images of the players inside firebase.
We can do a firebase uploading and of course we can't log out.
Right.
So you know a lot of things.
OK so the first thing you need to do is to create a directory where are you going to be hosting all
these files and my directory calls.
MC for Manchester City and.
OK.
So now what we need to do we need to create every act application so create then react then app.
And since I'm already inside the directory I can put a dot and press enter.
It's going to take a couple minutes and we'll be right back.
All right so everything was downloaded.
So now we need to of course install all the dependencies.
We just like the first project on the preview section I gave you some commands for yarn at or NPM install.
So I'm going to copy that and paste it right here.
So let me make sure I make this correctly on me.
There we go.
OK.
Let's go.
So OK so your an ad we're going to use material to you I'd just like with that before then.
The three the three E's.
It's something for the Sing's.
So we're going to use a library for you know for animations which calls re-act move and D-3 ease comes
with know react so we can indeed to use it.
Then of course the firebase connector we're going to use a third party library to upload files to the
database.
But we're going to do that later.
And then of course again re-act reveal and re-act router because we can use route routes.
So I'm going to press center.
It's going to take a while and I'll be right back whenever this is done.
OK so everything was installed so we have all the dependencies right here.
So the next thing we're going to need to we're going to need is to put the resources folder and begin
to put some icons on the public folder or the public directory so we can use the images and some team
logos right here.
They're going to possibly put it right now on this section you have the resources.
So download both Cips the one for the resources and the one for the images inside public.
OK so I've added the images directory.
Remember to download the Cyp.
And inside we have some team icons.
You know the icons that all the injuries of the teams so you need to use it because if not going to
have to do it yourself.
And now this took me a while.
What else.
We have the resources resources.
We have a pretty long CSSA And then of course we get images with some maybe a logo that we the pictures
of the players.
This is actually something I added just in case we can to use something else.
But the defense what else to keep them mid-fielder you're not going to really consume the images of
the players from here we're going to do it from firebase bed begin to do that at the end.
And of course some other images.
OK.
That's it.
So now what we need to do the same thing we did before I going to go right here to that.
SS You're not really going to use it.
I'm going to delete it.
The jazz going to use that one AB test.
Good bye.
Move to trash that index that says the SS are not going to really use it.
So we won.
In this day as I begin to use it logo going to delete it and then service workers good bye.
OK so I guess can it clear everything.
And I'm going to say hello whatever.
And then inside the index I'm going to register service worker.
The ledes deliver the import for the CSL and I forgot to the import on the app.
So import logo could buy and import APIs VSS.
Goodbye.
All right so now I'm going to run the development server.
In your case if you're using NPM it's NPM start.
If you're using Yorn just like me it's just Yohn start.
OK so it's asking me if I want to run it on a different port because I'm running the final one of the
three thousand.
So I'm going to say yes and later I'm going to change it.
But right now I'm going to say yes and it will start to develop in server on the three 001.
And we should be getting the you know the hill low on was done and there we go.
So.
Hello.
OK so we are ready to start coding.
So let's go to the next section and we will start with all the set up we can bring the routes and everything
else.