OK so let's start building our application.
So if you if you take a look at the final one we have some routes so we need to bring Briac Browder
to the equation and prepare the application to you know receive routes different routing.
So first we need to include the CSA.
So I'm going to go right here at the top and say import DOD for Slash resources for Slash CSSA for Slash
app that C S S Breguet.
So now again it seems we are going to be using routes these this file this app should be going to our
route files so the app that does instead of calling it up that just are going to call it routes and
touts know routes routes and no never update.
Sorry for that.
You know sometimes that routes and I can change of course because I have a theme installed.
It's the material theme.
So instead of index we have the upsy assess import app from app.
Well not really now.
Now we're going to get a route's file routes and from that forward slash and then routes.
All right.
So now if you remember maybe you didn't know this because you never worked with re-act router.
We need to wrap our application inside the browser router so we need to bring something from Briac router.
So gotta to go right here to the top and import open.
And then it's going to be browser and the Make It Right browser and then router and it's going to be
of course from re-act router Dom re-act router.
Dom right.
So now our whole application is going to be wrapped in this browser router.
So I'm going to go right here at the bottom create a function which is going to be our main application.
And this one is going to be returning just you know the browser Roder.
So it's return open and close but instead of here I make use of browser Roder now whatever goes inside
of browser Rohter is going to be our main application.
Since we have a file to manage all the routes are going to include the routes right here.
So at the end where we our main starting point is going to be up an app.
It's browser a router with the router inside.
OK.
So of course if we go right here you're still getting Kellow because routes it's equal to this component.
Of course we need to modify this a little bit.
Now what else inside routes.
Right here inside this file we will create all our routes.
Right now we don't have a route.
We just have the home so we can look pretty at pretty much more if I dress up for just to render home.
And then of course we're going to be adding routes.
OK.
So I'm going to remove this one from here we are not going to really use it right now and I'm going
to do this and I'm going to create just to function Konst routes equals And later are we going to receive
props.
So I'm going to put it right now.
We're not going to use it right now but I'm just going to leave it for future reference.
So just like the other component we just need to return something so we could return a Dave saying hello.
In this case and routes it's export default routes and when the application loads we are still getting.
Hello.
Let's get now on the main application to find one we can see that on every route.
Still we get the hetter the same header and the same footer.
So it kind of makes sense for us to create.
I hide or there a component to store the header and footer because begin can show it on every route.
So that's what we're going to be doing right now creating a component to store the header and footer
and we are going to create a high or there component to return a layout.
OK.
That's what we're going to do.
So first I'm going to go to source.
I'm going to create right now components directory not a file just a folder is going to be components
right.
Now inside the source directory again.
And you can actually you can put it outside the source directory.
It's completely up to you.
Doesn't really matter right now.
So inside source I'm going to put it out.
Yes.
No sorry.
We need to put it inside source.
But outside components or you can put it inside components going to create a directory outside called
h o c for you know high order components and these h o c pretty much is going to be the main layout
we can use on the application.
So now I'm going to create a file called layout that jazz and lay all that jazz is going to be or re-act
stateless component just reacts Nicholas components.
We are going to be receiving props later.
And what we do right here we just render something we say OK hello I'm going to say hello right here.
So now in routes instead of making a reference to that.
Hello.
Right now what are you going to be doing is importing that layout.
So import that layout from that forward slash a Tosi forward slash and the main layout and instead of
rendering something right here I'm going to say lay out and I'm going to say second line.
You can see why in a minute.
So now we are rendering the delay out.
And inside of the layer we have a second line.
So if I go right now in relo the application the only thing we get is hello and it's because layout
is just returning Hello.
We are not rendering the second line.
So what I'm going to do right here are going to go right here at the bottom and say this.
I'm sorry.
Props props that children and whenever you know we we load the application we get hello and we get second
line.
So if we go to a different route we are still going to get hello and then we can to get whatever we
have on that component.
That is the idea.
We will always render the header right here.
The footer at the bottom we don't have them yet.
And any sign in the mid in between of the header and footer whatever components are going to be passing
here through routes.
That's why we use a lay out and a high other component.
OK.
So we don't have a header and we don't have a footer.
We need to create them right now.
So I'm going to go to components.
I'm going to create a new directory called Hetter just like this and footer maybe underscore footer.
And inside of here I will start creating First the header that is going to be real simple so the header.
Yeah we could create a class or we can create a stateless app but for now just to be safe I'm going
to create a class so re-act classmates components.
OK.
So inside of Hetter we are going to be returning pretty much the header.
So from lay out I'm going to import the header import
import that header from that that force slash components for Slash header and footer for Slash and then
head or because we don't have an index.
So right now what do I do which is going to be I'm going to put the header component right here and
whenever of course the application loads or we go to a different route.
We will always have the header at the top and same thing later with the footer but could begin to do
the footer at the end.
OK let's get.
So let's create all the logic for the hitter we need to do something like this.
OK so for the better we're going to use the same material.
I bar with data on the previous project.
So I'm going to go at the top right here and start importing things.
So import it's up and then bar from open.
We need to do the at and then material the ice core and it's the same name.
Albar again if you remember inside of the bar we need the tool bar so import then tool bar from ADD
Materi core.
And you know same name in this case we are not going to use the material UI icons on this one and we
will have buttons this buttons.
So I will import import then button from add material to our core.
And then again button.
Very good.
Now we will use links because these are actual links.
So to use links and use reac rotor Dohm we need to import the link modules module from re-act Rotterdam.
So like.
And it's going to be from re-act then router and then Dohm forget you're going to use a CD logo.
And we have the CD logo inside icons right here I believe.
Yes UI icons.
We're going to do it later.
We're going to do it in a minute or so.
OK.
So first what we need to do.
I'm going to delete this and I'm going to return that abar from material to you.
I if you remember this abar need some configuration.
So the position just like before is going to be fixed.
So position equals fixed Frigga then going to use style opening close.
And I'm going to modify some of the default stylings.
The back ground color we can add that blue that light blue color is going to be you know hatchback 9
8 C 5 e 9.
That's the actual color.
Then again to add a box shadow are going to remove the box shadow unlike box shadow.
You know me shadow then it's going to be non of course koma are going to add a little bit of padding
telling pixels from the top and zero from the sides.
And one more thing.
The last one the border bottom and the border the bottom is going to be two pixels solid and it's kind
of a dark blue.
So it's going to be hash.
Oops sorry for that.
Or you go go go.
So it's 0 0 0 2 8 5 e that is it.
So inside of the bar we need that toolbar again.
So I'm going to open it close and make a reference to the material I toolbar we've imported at the top
and again of course we need to add some stylings.
In this case not a good one.
Not going to mollify a lot.
We're just going to give it a display of flex.
So this play and then flex and if we reload the application Well you know we kind of get it.
It's nice.
OK so inside of here inside of this toolbar container we need to add the logo.
So for now which is going to say def I'm going to add the style of the Flex grow because we are using
with flex on the parent.
So Flex and then grow.
And this one is going to be one very good and he's out of here.
We're going to be adding you know the logo.
For now I'm going to say Dave open and close.
And this one is going to get a class name of head or logo underscore logo.
And I'm going to put the logo in a minute right here.
OK.
So at least we get you know the word logo and it's on the same spot than this one.
So then of course we need to add the links and since we are using re-act Rotterdam we need to use link
from the top.
So I'm going to say link up when you make it right link open or close let me open and close.
Very good.
Now this link needs a property which is the two which is where we are going to go.
And I'm going to say two and they're rowdiest going to be called team and this is where we can see the
whole squad.
Next one can I create a new link and this one instead of the team is going to be the matches.
You know we can see the matches of the team and instead of here we can add the bottom from material.
I so open it close button Breguet are going to change the color to inherit and open it close.
And this one is going to be the team and I'm going to copy this one.
We're almost done going to copy the team and I'm going to copy this one which is going to be matches
up matches.
There you go and reload the application and.
OK.
We can get this now with the logo.
We need to do something else right.
Because right here we are now saying logo but on the real application we will use the logo maybe on
different parts.
At least right now we are using it at the top on Hetter and then on the footer.
So you know it kind of makes sense for us to create a reusable component where we can display the logo
with the background position and the link and everything else.
So let's go to the next section and Korea and start creating reusable component.
Our first reusable component.