All right so now we need to create this reusable component for the logo.
So just like with that before I'm going to go to component's create a new directory called you.
I am going to you know everything.
Nightcaps you want just you on.
And he said if you're going to add the first when we get to we're going to get a few right now we're
going to create a few on this project you know several components you can call instead of you you can
call it.
Maybe I don't know Minsk or misc or Eutelsat.
That's good too.
So this one is going to be icons and I call them using a plural right here because you might have many
many icons on your application.
In this case I believe we can have one but you know it's always a good idea to create you know a place
where you're going to host all the icons.
OK.
So this one of course since we need to return some react I need to import react from react.
All right.
What else we are going to use a link so we need to import import.
Open and close and then link from Briac Rotterdam so re-act router and Domm and that's it.
Now we're going to use the Manchester City logo if we go to resources and I go to logo's.
We have this Manchester City logo.
You know I like the logo.
So we're going to use it.
So ugly import em city.
Some like this logo resemble from open and close that for Slash that dot for Slash.
And then it's resources for Slash images for Slash Manchester City Oh yeah.
Images of sorry Logos then for Slash.
And then of course Manchester City logos.
There we go.
OK.
So now again like I told before this file might host several logos or different type of you know functions
or different code.
So I'm going to export Konst this concept called city logo.
So whenever we include this piece of code from a different component we just import the city logo and
we can get all the contents of this.
So this silly logo will be receiving some props.
OK.
So now I'm going to create a Konst we're just going to be a template just like this.
It's going to be just a justifiable.
Right.
OK.
So this template will be returning something called Logo going to created right now.
Now the thing is that sometimes maybe you want to import the logo and you want to bring the logo and
maybe you want to skip the fact that this is a link.
So maybe you don't want to return a link.
You want to return something that is not clickable.
So to make the we always need to make the components that were reusable components as versatile as we
can.
So I'm going to make a logic question right here and I'm going to check if Propst that link.
And we're going to be passing if it's a link or not.
As Probst we're going to return something if not we're going to return something else.
So what when we return.
Going to say return if this is not a link is going to be whatever template we have right here.
But if it's a link We're going to return something else.
So return open it close and what we will be returning is the link we are importing at the top right.
Makes sense.
So link make it right there we go.
Now this link if you remember we always need to worry that the link is going to go.
So I'm going to say to open it close and then I'm going to add props and then link to.
And this is probably are going to be passing from the parent component.
OK.
And he's out of here.
We're going to be returning whatever we have on the template.
So pretty much we always return the template but if we have a link we return it in linked form.
If not we return Chesed the template right.
I'm going to be adding a class name right here.
You know maybe a link logo something like that link logo.
And now we need to of course return this template.
So first I'm going to go to the header and include you know bring this reusable component from the header
so at least we get that wart with the like.
So import opening close.
And if you remember I believe I call that see the logo.
You'll see the logo right.
And then from that dot for Slash you I forward slash and then icons.
OK.
So now I'm going to make a reference to city logo.
Of course we're going to get some errors because we are not passing props at all.
We're going to be passing it right now.
But at least we get you know we get that logo.
So now this silly logo if you go go back to the icons.
This one it's expecting a props that link.
That's what makes that different.
That makes a difference.
So OK so I'm going to go to Hetter and are going to be passing some props on this CD logo.
So first we need a link to evaluate if this is true or not true.
We can also do something like this.
So if it's true this one is going to be a link
and of course you're at it.
OK.
So let's go back in Icahn's this one.
It's going to try.
So we are returning this.
BURNETT Right now we have an error because we are not specifying the two property right now of the two
it's probs that link to.
And we are not passing that you know that property.
So I'm going to say link to and it's going to go to home right.
Make sense.
So I was going to go to home.
So now we're going to get this one right.
So we get logo.
And if I click you know of course I'm not going anywhere but it's going to take us back to home.
That's good.
OK.
What else.
So sometimes you going to get a width and height for the for the icons.
So it kind of makes sense.
So I'm going to go to icons and this logo instead of just returning this I'm going to break it down
and add some properties.
First they're going to change the class name.
So class name equals M G cover.
So we can add that back front cover and then we're going to be passing stylings.
So now what do we do.
I'm going to be passing a with and we get it from Propst.
And then of course we have a height and we get it from probs dot height.
All right.
So now whenever we include a logo since this is a reusable component we need to pass the width and height
in it.
Of course maybe you're using it on the head or so you need a different twist and hide.
So we pass a dynamic dynamic data.
Right that's the idea of doing all of this.
So we need to pass with and with in this case is going to be 70 pixels.
What else we can add height and the height it's going to be again you know square image 70 pixels look
at you know at least we get something what else we need to be passing.
What else we are going to go to icons.
So we have the wit and the height we need to be passing the background.
In this case I want to see the logo.
So I'm going to say background background.
Open and Close.
I'm going to be passing some u r l because we will need to use some temporal strings and we use the
MC logo we are importing the top and then I'm going to say no.
Repeat.
This is just C Ss Pete.
All right I need to add a coma right here.
So now we have a dynamic width and height.
And of course this component is just for the city logo.
So we return a div with a CD logo.
That's the idea and I'm going to remove this and make it a little bit better.
There we go.
And if I reload the application will we get the Manchester City get the team and the matches.
This one should go to the right.
So let me double check why it's in the left.
OK.
I know.
I'm sorry for that.
It should be styles inside the header with the toolbar style and style.
Of course we were not using the flex property.
So we get the logo and it is the link and everything else it's a link to.
So very good.
We go to the team and if I click logo we go back.
So now whenever we want to add a logo with a link or maybe without a link we can always make reference
to this city the city logo from icons.
And that is it.
We don't need to do all of that.
All of this again we just include it.
And that is at.
All right.
So we're going to do the full arena.
So I'm going to go to header and footer and you file and this one is going to be footer.
I'm doing it right now because it's really pretty simple.
So this one react stateless components opening close and I'm going to change this.
Sorry I made a mistake.
Rename and capital F.
Same thing right here.
Capital F.
There we go.
So now the footer.
And if I check if I remove this for three maybe I can show you this later.
Why not right here at the bottom.
We just get you know a dark blue logo.
And you know what's next.
Really really really simple.
So instead of here instead of returning the div are going to return a footer.
There we go.
When we make the change right here at the bottom.
So this one will get a class name of B C K blue.
Pretty much what we did before.
Busy K blue and we need to add a logo so div opening close.
Class name and then footer logo and right here we going to do the same thing with did with the header.
Same exact thing.
Import.
We're going to bring the city logo.
Let me copy the name.
See the logo.
And then from dot dot for Slash.
You I for Slash icons.
So now again we just make a reference to see the logo opening close.
I could make this self-closing tak.
And then of course we need to pass the props.
So if you remember it is with with the Riego and to with for this one is going to be 70 pixels just
like the other one.
Same thing then the height 7 pixels.
We could pass the link and this one it's going to be linkable so we can say.
True.
And then the change to this true.
And the next one is going to be where he's going to go you know where we can link it to.
So link to equals home.
And that is it.
So after the you see the logo that fooler logo are going to create a div with the class name of footer
underscore.
And this claimers something like that.
And of course some dumb content matzos Manchester Manchester City 2018 all rights rights reserved.
You know the usual stuff.
And if I go to the home nothing happens because this one goes inside the layout.
It's going to go to lay out in Port footer from dot dot for Slash components for Slash and or footer
and then you know the footer.
Real Simple is stuff.
So far this is you know we know this footer and the pick up.
So that's what we're getting.
And of course the foot hurts below the head or because the head or it's up you know position fixed so
it's on top of everything.
But we are getting the flitter at least.
All right.
So in the next section we're going to start building pretty much what everything that it's related to
the home.
First we're going to do the animations with this and then we can move forward to manage to do the matches
and with the matches we will need to create a firebase account create a database and get it from firebase.
We are not going to use a dummy database.
So.
OK so let's go to the next section and start the featured.