All right so now we are going to be working on the animation you know the featured animation.
So if I reload the application you know we get that transition effect.
You know we're going to do that.
And of course we're going to use a library for this.
But first I have you know I have it right here.
But first we need to do something.
So everything it's happening and at home you know the route home.
And so far we don't really have a route.
We have a file that you know outputs play out and just a text.
So what we need to do first is to create that home route and to add the routes right here.
OK.
So first are going to delete the one that has a second line.
And I'm going to bring something from re-act router dumb so I'm going to go right here at the top and
I'm going to import opening close and first I'm going to bring switch and then I'm going to bring route
later are we going to be changing this when we bring out integration to our project.
Now it's you know it's go.
So from re-act broader Dom re-act router Dom and then instead of the layout to begin to use that switch
and inside of the switch we will put all our routes.
So switch open and close it right here we will put our route.
So so far we don't have a route.
We just have the header and footer and nothing else.
So I'm going to go to components.
I'm going to create a new directory called home an inside home.
We will put you know what we're going to be using in this case.
At home we have several sections.
We have the featured.
We have the matches.
Then meet the players and when a jersey so it kind of makes sense that inside of home we can have you
know several folders or directory with different things.
So the first one is going to be featured.
So I'm going to create a new directory and say featured right.
Inside feature again we have maybe several things so we will create an index that will host the different
files.
And when the animation starts we have two pieces of animations.
The stripes in the background and then the text and the player.
So I'm going to first create an index just so we can pass this one to the routes and then inside of
here we're going to have two different files one for the stripes.
So this one is going to be called stripes that Jesus and the other one is going to be called text because
we're going to host the text again.
You can use whatever name you want.
So inside of the index this one will just you know output the stripes and that and the text so we can
skip the class based components and make every act stateless components.
All right.
And this one is going to call it featured.
I always do that with the sliders at the top.
Call them featured.
That comes from from WordPress.
Back in the day saga.
So here now we are not going to import anything.
So the only thing we're going to do.
I'm going to return a div with a class name of featured and then rapper and he's out of here.
I don't know.
Some text from now.
All right.
So now this one.
It's the main view for this feature.
And it's inside home.
But the thing is that we don't have a home we have a feature but we don't have a home.
So now what do we need to do.
We need to create a file inside Home which is going to be the index.
So I'm going to say Index non-jazz and this one is going to be the route home.
So again react to Stigler's component and this one will be called home a copy home and paste home.
And the only thing we're going to be returning.
It's a class name and I'm going to give it a background S.K. of blue.
You know we're going to get that this blue background.
All right.
Now inside of here we need to output the featured container.
So import feature it from opening close that for Slash featured.
And of course we'll make a reference right here.
All right.
Of course if I go to our project and reload the page nothing really happens because we have everything
right here.
But inside of routes you're not making reference to this home container.
So we're going to go right here on top import home from that forward slash components forward slash
home.
All right.
So I got a copy.
And now what we need to do we need to pass a route we need to define a route for home.
So with re-act Browder we're going to use this route.
We've imported to the top so I'm going to say route and make it a self-closing tack since we can have
made routes I can to put exact.
And then I'm going to put render.
So inside of the render sorry components we could use rendering this case but component is actually
more accurate.
So inside components we will put which components we want to render at home.
So in this case is just home.
And then of course the path where you know where we're going to be using this route so is forced slash
because it's home.
And now the application loads and we have that you know that blue background.
So you know at least this works OK.
So again I have a lot of things open.
I'm going to close everything.
I'm going to open round again and case of home remember we are giving a back of blue.
All right.
So now we need to create the animations and we will start with stripes.
So I'm going to go to stripes and we can it use for this tripes a library for animations.
Let me show you the library first.
So it calls re-act move.
And of course we've installed this re-act move now reac move to use some easing you know to use the
Sing's library.
It uses something else calls D3 yse.
So we've already installed this.
Everything is on the documentation of course.
So this one calls we are moved.
And we can create you know a kind of enhanced animations.
So again if you check the documentation maybe it's not that good it's clear but it's a little bit confusing.
But when you get the basics you pretty much understand everything else.
So we are going to do something very basic right now.
And then of course we're going to do something with no group because it's a little bit more confusing.
So let me show you an example and we act move.
So right here let me show you the link.
Go to live examples code and undocks and if you go here you're going to get you know different options
documentation more examples.
And inside the communication you have two types of animations you have animate and node group with animate.
We can do animations of something like that.
Well for example something like this you know they are they look really really cool.
So with animate we can update you can we can animate single deps or single elements.
Let me show you this example.
So what they do actually we just import animate and D-3 ease with the name of the thing.
And what we do.
We just render an element.
We have it right here with the tag animate.
And of course in this case it's creating several elements.
And so it's looping and just returning several animated you know attacks.
Now we will have a key of course.
So what we need to do we need to set up a start and an update.
In this case we are using update but we could just use just a start or enter.
So inside the start we will put all them the starting properties of that deck.
You know maybe the scale the color or the rotation doesn't matter.
So then when the component updates we will get the new values and right here inside of a function we
just returned the div we want to animate with all the properties we want to change.
And this of course whenever they change here they will change here and they will change on the actual
element.
So this is the main idea this is how it works in a nutshell.
So you can animate single elements or you can animate groups.
And in this case a note group would be kind of an array or maybe an object with different think thinks
inside.
So it kind of works like this when it updates the computer and updates it shows the animations.
All right.
So we're going to use it again.
This is a little confusing.
And for example right here we have a start which is the starting point enter when whenever the elements
it's entering then when it updates we change the properties.
And when it leaves.
So it can react animations the featured re-act animations and you know a little bit different.
And you know this works really good.
So we're going to do it right now.
So I'm going to go back to our project and get it closed as and right here we are calling it features
inside of home and home.
Let's go to index a featured So we are just returning some text of course we need to do much more.
First we're going to do the stripes so I'm going to create a I'm going to call a component called Strypes.
We don't have this component we need to create it.
So we're going to go right here.
Import stripes from Dot.
Sorry dot for Slash.
And I'm going to call it Strypes just like that.
OK.
So this is Strypes of course.
It's not doing anything.
We don't have anything right here.
You can add it so we can create a class component so re-act class based components.
And of course it's going to be called Strypes.
We need to import the things and react move.
So import open and close and for the easy things you have many types of things.
I'm going to show you in a minute on the documentation but for this one we're going to use IIS just
like this said Polly and that out and then from D-3 is very good that import and he made just like this
from re act.
Let me find re-act OK animate up sorry move and then forward slash.
And we need to pass animate.
So this is the way it works.
So at the bottom on the container we can every turn at just a div with the class name class name.
Well not after completing with a class name of featured shows like this and Stripes are going to make
sense inside of here we just returned a function that will loop the state of something and returned
three different stripes.
So I get a call that show stripes opening close nothing else show stripes and let me fix it.
Show stripe.
Of course we don't have this function.
I'm going to save it.
I'm going to go to show stripes are going to create that function and this function the only thing it
does for now it just returns returns some GSX so I'm going to put just a div and say stripes mind.
Maybe we are not going to be able to see it but we can get it right here.
Strypes so at least we are returning something.
All right.
OK.
So let's go to the next section and continue with the stripes.
And you know finish me maybe finish the animation part.