All right.
So now what we need to do we need to render three different stripes.
Of course with different properties different rotations and you know different delay and everything
else.
So I'm going to go right here to the show stripes and what we will do we will map an array of objects
with all these properties.
We didn't have this we need to create this I'm going to go to St..
I'm going to open an array.
I'm you are going to open up state and we'll me do it like this.
And inside of here I'm going to say tripes now we Strypes is going to be an array of objects since we
have three stripes.
We need to add three different properties here three different objects open and close.
All right.
So of course inside of them them we need some properties.
So in this case the first one to just put background say back and then just ground and the background
of course is going to be the background color is when it's light blue.
This one is white and this one again same color than the other one.
So I'm going to open it close and the color is going to be in.
Oh sorry.
Nine eight.
See five eat nine.
That's a color.
So I'm going to copy the same background for the other one pasted and pasted right here and this one
it's white.
So once through one two three four five six there you go we just have a background for now.
Then of course we're going to change everything else.
Now instead of here inside show stripes we need to loop you know how many stripes we get.
We have four of course is going to render four different stripes but in this case we just went three.
So we start with a does that state that.
Stripes.
All right.
And I'm going to use a map and on each iteration I'm going to be passing a stripe and then the iteration
number the index.
Then I get the opening close and notice I'm not using brackets.
I'm using parentheses because we just want to return an element.
So in this case what we will need to do if we go to the documentation we need to return.
Let me show you the first one.
There's one there's one right here.
We need to return a new element calls animate and inside of this animate we need to start passing all
the properties.
All right.
So OK so I'm going to go right here and first I'm going to open it close and put the animate.
So then open it close.
All right.
Now we know that this animate returns something for example a div.
So I'm going to go and say div open it close.
Now this divide will have some properties and in this case we just want to add a class name for now
and it's going to be called Strype of course perhaps Strypes this one will be strike.
And of course we will have styles are going to put it right now and then I'm going to explain you a
little bit better.
So background.
I'm just going to say background.
That's it.
OK.
So now this animate needs some properties in order to work first.
So first since we are looping something we need to add a key so key opening close is that the iteration
number we are getting right here.
OK.
Now this animation needs to know if it if it's going to be starting whenever the element gets mounted
or render it or not.
So we have a property called show so show in this case it's true we want to animate as soon as this
you know generated.
OK.
So for this case we're going to be using a start property and then we're going to use an Enter property
you have more we talked about this we have more and more properties like Update leave or you know yes
Abdin a leaf but in this case the element is going to start and then it's going to enter.
There is no update.
So there is no on an manhunting unmounting.
So we just put the enter the start and enter whenever the page loads and whenever the element enters
that's it we don't need anything else.
So for now we just have one property which is the background.
So I'm going to say background right here.
Background and the background will start as white will always starts as white.
So one two three four five six.
All right then when it enters.
Of course with other ones for the first one the least in the in the last one we have a different color.
So we need to specify well from which color we want to change the element too.
So we're going to go to enter and say background and the background.
And this is kind of weird.
We could put stripes or stripe that back and remember we are looping this and these striped state you
know the stripes so we can x axis stripe dot background and get the color.
But we cannot pass it just like this we cannot do stripes and then background.
This is not going to work.
What we need to do we need to put it in square brackets.
Yeah I know it's kind of weird but that's the way it works.
So now when it enters everything is going to be white.
You know the first second and third stripe are going to be white.
But the first one is going to change the color.
The second one is going to remain wide because we have white and then the last one is going to be blue.
Of course if I go right here nothing really not nothing really happens.
We are getting this error.
So background it's not defined.
And this background it means this background you're kind of using of Barville to something that it's
not really defined.
We have background inside start and interpret no place else.
So in this case and this is how it works what it returns it's not going to be a dip.
So I'm going to copy and I'm going to copy right.
Undeleted going to cop.
So what does it because it's going to be returning a function.
So first we open brackets.
Now inside of the brackets we need to return a function.
So we're going to open just like this and I'm going to return just to function.
All right.
Now inside of this of course inside of the function we need to return some GSX.
So I'm going to say return just like this.
Open the parenthesis and return that.
You know I'm going to paste that depth.
We were using before.
We're going to be adding some things right here in a minute.
And then of course I'm going to add this.
So instead of here we need a way to pass to this function.
All the properties we are using inside animate in this case we just have the background.
Now we look at some other examples.
We're right here maybe you get something else maybe you get state.
Well state whenever we make reference to state inside of here we are making reference to the state right
here.
So inside start inside enter we get background so we can get it from that state state that start that
background.
But in this case we can make use of ESX and I'm just going to say in this case background why my same
background because we are animated background so if we were animating opacity we need to pass background
and capacity.
And if we are animating top top background and capacity.
So when once we pass them through here we can pass the new properties to the elements.
In this case we are doing so we are passing background.
So in theory if I save this we should be getting at least something and we do.
And you know we get the three elements.
If I inspect this I'm going to go right here and let me select this.
We get one stripe two stripes with a different color.
You know this one is the blue.
This one is still white.
And this one is blue.
So it's kind of animating them all right because they of course start as white.
Let me reload and see if we get it.
Well not that.
No not really.
So let's go back now this animation of course takes some time.
I'm going to close this.
And of course we need to define how much time this is going to take.
So I'm going to go to enter which is the last one in this case the one that actually does the animation
and we need to pass on this special property.
And only on enter that calls timing.
And on the timing we will define all the you know the delay maybe the duration of the animation and
everything else so we can set a delay.
We can I can put it.
I'm going to put 500.
We're going to do something else later.
But for now it's OK.
Then we have a duration now the duration is going to be of course Homan so much time is going to last.
So 200 it's going to be really simple you know really fast.
And then we can select the easing since we are importing at the top the D-3 East module we can pass
the Issing we want and of course if we reload again we see nothing because there's no actual animation
which is a change in the background.
Now we could see it but I'm going to do something else now on the original we are changing not just
the background color but we are changing the position.
You know how much of the left and how much this element is rotated by default.
It's just you know horizontal but we need to you know rotate this.
So again we just could get it from props we can specify right here.
What is the rotation for this one for this one and for this one.
And then the unmade will be animating this property.
All right.
So I'm going to go for a hearing and to start putting all the properties are going to say that we have
left and then I'm going to say coma.
Then we have a rotate which is how much is going to be rotating.
So rotate then we going to have a top where it's going to be positioned from the top because we are
rotating and then we're going to have the delay.
Right.
How much is going to take.
How do you let me fix it.
Delay Burguet.
And of course we get pretty much the same thing for all the other properties.
So I'm going to copy them and I'm going to paste them below here.
We're going to be of course adding something.
So they left for the first stripe.
It's 120 The rotate.
Going to rotate 25 and the top is going to be minus to 60 and the delay for now is going to be zero.
The first one waits no amount of time is just God is going to go right away.
The second one from the left is going to be three.
Then the rotation is going to be 25 the top minus 3 9 7 0 3 9 7 and then the delay.
This one is going to wait for the first one to show and then it's going to be animating 200.
The last one 600 the rotation is going to be 25 the top.
It's going to be minus 4 9 8 and then I know that this is boring but we are almost done and delay 400.
So now we have all these properties and we need to pass the properties to the actual animate.
So we're going to do that.
It's not going to be that hard work.
So all the elements they start with the Pasotti of zero.
I'm not passing this and just going to do it directly from here.
So I could take opacity just like this.
And it starts at zero.
All right.
Coma.
Next one is going to be the left position.
How much from the left is going to go.
So everything is going to start at zero left zero right.
So I'm going to go right here at the bottom.
And of course we have more properties we two of them again are just going to copy this and paste right
here.
The one now the capacity of course we need to go from zero to 1 so we can actually see the stripe.
And of course remember to put the square brackets and then we need to specify the left position.
In this case we are using the whatever we have inside the state.
So it's going to be stripe dot left.
If I reload the page nothing really happens because we need to pass the opacity property and left just
like that with background.
Now same idea same idea.
So I'm going to go right here and say that we are passing now a left property and then we are passing
and passing the property.
Then we copy the name so opacity coma.
Now again.
The Stiles we need to pass this opacity and to pass the left of the left it's not going to be that simple
and it's going to look a little bit weird.
So what we use and see if we can get something on these you know on the on the left what we're going
to do we are going to animate with transform.
So I'm going to go right here at the bottom you're going to say transform and this one are going to
be using template strings going to close this.
So going to put rotate and we don't have all the values right now but we will use rotate.
So I'm going to put 0 0 degrees of course.
Then of course we're going to be adding this.
Then translate translate and inside of translate.
Of course we need to pass the left and the top you know the X and Y.
So in this case going to use 0 pixels and 0 pixels from the top and I get to go back to the first one
because we do have this property which is the left you're going to say left right.
I'm using template strings.
That's the only thing I'm using.
And now we get something different.
If we load the application OK at least it's doing something that is good.
So now we need to achieve the rotation and the top you know transition.
So we do have this.
So we have the rotate the top and then begin to do the delete.
So I got to go right here at the the actually the actual tack the animate and after the left are going
to put rotate which is going to be equal to zero and then top which is going to be equal to zero as
well.
All right.
Now we need to pass the new properties right here.
So again going to copy this one at the top.
Go right here at the bottom and instead of zero is going to be Strype dot rotate.
All right.
And the same thing for the other one but the other one is going to be instead of rotate.
It's going to be top.
All right.
So now we have the rotate and the top property of course we need to add them right here.
So I'm going to be adding after the left rotate and top and then coma and of course we need to use them
inside the transform so the rotate is going to be equal to rotate.
That's correct.
And then we have the top and top again just like the left.
It's going to be equal to top of a mini mistake.
Let's go back to top.
I got to.
There you go.
I'm going to reload the application and you know we can get it a little bit fast.
But we can we're going to get that transition.
Now that thing right now is that they are all the animations are happening after 500 milliseconds.
They are all happening at the same time and that's why it's a little bit faster than than the other
one.
All right.
So first we need to specify I did late so I'm going to say delay that's that.
That's my first mistake.
DeLay should be a little bit slower.
OK.
Now it's a little bit slower but they're all happening at the same time and I need for this animation
to animate the first one then the second one and then the third one.
That's why we are passing a delay right here.
So instead of making a reference to a delay on the timing we say Strype dot delay right.
And that's going to save it just in case a reload it and we get the same animation that is good.
Right.
And it wasn't that hard.
It's kind of hard to understand what is going on when you when you see this.
But then then you realize this is simple it just create a new property starting properties.
You put the new ones and then you pass it to the you know to the function and the actual elements.
You know it's really really simple.
All right.
And that is it.
I'm going to tell you one more thing that might be useful for you in the future.
Going to do.
Coma.
And then you have access to events.
So whenever this element it's changing or it's done any mating or whenever it's doing something you
have different types of events right here and you can check this on the documentation.
So for example if this animation triggers I want to know when when the when whenever the animation it's
done after the animation is done I want to maybe run a different function.
I don't know whatever.
So we can call and and inside and we can do console log animation and finished or something like that.
Everything is on the documentation right.
Animation finished.
Or go to console.
And of course it took me a little while to open it.
So animation finished.
All right.
So we get it three times because we have three different elements.
And remember that we are inside the map so that it said that that is the Zed with the stripes.
So now we are going to be animating the text and you know showing the player.
This of course is a passerby with a simple animation.
All right so let's go to the next one and start with the text.