OK so let's animate the texts.
So for the application we can see that we have four times of types of animations.
We have the number then the first text then the second text and then the player.
So this is what we're going to be doing.
And now it's going to be much much easier because we know how this works.
So on the other one is going to be a piece of cake.
Right.
So we have a component.
We do have a component to host all this animations and we have it inside text of course we have and
it nothing right here.
So we're going to need a real class based component Riak RACC.
And this could be a stateless component.
Yeah it could be a stateless component doesn't matter.
You can do that which is going to create a class right now.
So first we need to import all the animated related stuff the dependencies for animations we have in
stripes.
So I'm going to copy go to text and paste it.
All right.
So of course scene within featured.
We need to render the text below Strypes so import than text from that for Slash and then text right.
And of course we need to make a reference right here text.
So I'm going to go back to text now inside text.
We need to render a wrapper.
Where are we going to be containing all of this animation.
So the class name for this will be class name and then featured and then text and inside of here we
will render four types of Funimation's so I will run four different functions.
So the first one is going to be called this animate.
I don't know first why not animate and then first which is going to be the number not going to do number.
So made number first is the actual text first to get made number right.
So I'm going to copy the name of the function I'm going to go right here and just create a function
rhyme.
We just run a function.
Now this function will return some GSX.
So we need to use parenthesis instead of square brackets.
What we return is going to be that animate tack we were using previously and what we do we return a
function with the actual.
Just like with it before the Notkin explain it again.
You know go back to the previous section.
So we were trying to function in this case open it close and we return some function.
Now from this one we will get all the props like opacity or rotate and background and everything like
everything else.
But we're going to do it later.
Of course we need to return some sex so opening closed.
And I will be returning just a dip in this case.
I want a class name for featured And then number that's the class of this one.
And of course we need to attach the styles with all the animations and everything else.
So in this case I'm going to say style Sorry style equals and leave it empty.
We don't have the properties so far and then are going to say just three I'm going to go back.
And of course cannot the structure undefined because we are not really passing anything that's good.
Now of course we need to pass all the properties to the animate tack.
So I'm going to say this one show it's true.
We want to show it.
So true.
And then close it and then we have a start and then enter.
So I'm going to say start equals something.
Now we will do two things.
We will add capacity and rotation.
So opacity equals zero then a coma and then rotate equals zero.
So the starting point point it's zero.
Then of course when it enters We want to do animations.
So opacity again we change it to 1.
And remember the square brackets.
Then what we want to do we want to rotate and we want to rotate 360 degrees for rotation.
And then of course we always need to add the timing and note is that right now it's working.
So timing that timing we have to ration in this case I'm not going to add a delay just duration just
like this.
And it's going to take one second and then the easing the ease we will use the one at the top which
is the same one than the other one is pulling out.
Right.
So now we are using opacity and rotation.
So I'm going to copy capacity pass it to the function and then rotate.
And then again pass it to the function.
Now of course inside styles we need to make a reference to this of Pasotti.
So we will say just opacity and the rotation it is a transform just like the other one.
So Tran's form open close and we will use template strings.
So again we will I will do a translation.
Real simple translate and open and close and it's going to be two 60 pixels coma 1 70 pixels.
Now there's no point of doing this.
This is the starting point where this number is going to be positioned pretty much that that is it.
And then of course we have the rotate on the closes and the rotation we do have a rotation value.
So rotate y opening close and we need to pass the property so open it close rotate and you know it is
done.
I'm going in a little bit fast right now.
So the rotate degrees and we do get it.
No we get that animated number.
All right that's good.
All right let's fix the problem with the font.
I'm going to go to Google font and it's because we never include this inside of the project.
Sorry for that.
So Google and fonts.
So I know this is boring but you know part of the process.
Are they going to do rubato.
And and.
OK.
And the other one is the same one than the other project the writers like this font.
I don't know why so rebozo customize than light medium and that's it.
We don't know the other ones.
So I'm going to copy Blinkx go to the index.
Pasted right here save it and if I go back while we do have all of that you know the number.
So now we need to create the first animation for the number for the search for the text the first text.
So this is animation.
I'm going to go back to text.
We just need to do pretty much the same thing with different values instead of the animate number.
I'm going to call it this animate.
And then first.
All right.
Just run the function.
Now we don't have a function to go right here.
Animate first opening close and we will return some GSX.
Now the animation looks like this one so I'm going to copy and paste it.
Now if you can sell it.
Could we do just maybe a loop and loop some properties.
Well yeah you could be told it could.
You know I'm doing this way we did that with stripes.
All right.
So again we just need that number the first we return of course something different and different instead
of a number.
It's going to be needed first.
Now we do have a past city and the transform We do have a translate but we don't have rotation so I'm
going to remove it.
And of course we're going to use different properties and instead of three we will say Lee.
All right.
So instead of rotate I'm going to rotate and I'm going to do it again rotate.
We will use the x and y axis so there's two values.
So X with some values and then of course why.
So I'm going to say why with some Ballis now the values for x which is the default are going to position
the number on this place.
If I put 0 they're going to go right here at the top.
But I need to put them right below the number so.
OK.
So I'm going to delete it and the numbers are 5 0 3 and have done this of course 5 0 3 and 450.
So now we need to animate the X and Y because they're going to go from here to here.
You know this is the starting point.
And then again going to go and stop right here.
OK.
So the X are going to wrap everything in square brackets and I complete.
And it's going to be 2 7 3 2 7 3.
Again I totally already done the math and the y 450.
There's actually no need to use the Y we can use for 50 but we need to actually pass it right here.
So it's the same value.
So now we are using an X and Y and I'm going to change the duration instead of one second is going to
be 500 and same easing in other translation.
I'm going to use template strings to use x and to use Y.
Right.
Of course we need to be adding pixels right here at the bottom at the end and then an opacity we need
to pass this property so x and y.
If I reload the application there we go.
We get it right.
So since this one was very simple let's do the other one the championship which is going to be pretty
much the same thing.
So same process going to create a function does that animate and then show.
I don't know.
Maybe animate second instead of show makes sense second.
All right.
And we pretty much do the same thing before if you want to create a loop to do this.
You totally can you can manage everything through state.
So I'm going to copy this one from within the animate going to copy and I made a mistake right here
and to this one and put some penances.
All right.
So animate instead of like is going to be championships championships.
That's the first change.
Cham peenemnde chips.
Raggatt.
So they really are the champs they want the up to 18 title.
So they really are champions.
So instead of featured first featured second right and capacity and transform We will use pretty much
the same thing.
The only thing it's going to change right here are the values.
Everything else stays the same.
Now I'm going to go to X. It's going to be 5 0 3.
Same position on the X.
But to 7:3 same position on the X right.
This is good.
Now if you notice this when it's below league.
So now we need to change the y axis 2 5 8 6.
And then of course 5 8 6.
That doesn't change.
So we're going to reload the application our application and we are not getting it.
Let me see what I mean.
Of course of course get reloaded and we can get it.
Now the problem is that you know if we take a look at this one first comes leak and then comes comes
championship championships.
So we need to achieve this and we can do it through delay delay and timing right.
So I to go and say the lay open it close and you know not too much.
And if I reload it we get it right.
So we are almost done the only thing left is just a player and it's just an impasse in effect.
All right so let's add the player visible.
We just need to do an animation with the positive.
So this dot animate and then of course player open costs.
So a player is going to be a function that is going to be returning some assets at this point.
This should be really easy for you.
All right.
So any player will be returning something so I don't want to type all over again.
I'm going to copy paste.
So again show true and capacity.
We didn't need the x y so I'm going to delete the x y and just leave the opacity and the delay is going
to take you know.
This one shows at the end.
Sorry I'm a little bit sick.
So sometimes my throat.
Just so time delay.
Eight hundred.
Right here in my country right now in my country it's winter so everyone can get sick.
And that's really a bummer.
So feature player of course we need to change this and the style is just a pastie and other transform.
I'm going to you know put the default positioning of the actual image so to 0 1 and that's the key.
We didn't have a word right here.
We have an image so we need the background image so we can put it right here.
So everything it's on resources and resources we do have this image feature player and it's too large.
Maybe we can trim and trim that down but does it matter right now.
So we're going to include it right here at the top.
So we say import featured and then player and this is something you will need to do in real life.
Sometimes the designer maybe you know maybe you don't.
Sometimes the designers or the people that will be creating the design for you to create right here
on the team version they will give you the images and sometimes the images are really big.
They are kind of a not very safe to to use on you know a loading environment because you're going to
be loading images from the web.
So you know if there are really heavy.
Right.
So let me.
There you go.
Feature player so they're really heavy.
So sometimes you will need to use some software maybe Photoshop or I don't know whatever software you
want to use to trim down the size.
This one the feature player.
It's one megabyte.
It's too much too much.
I'm sorry for that I forgot to trim that down.
But in real life if you go to production you need to trim it down.
All right.
So now we do have an image so I'm going to need to go right here the bunkroom at the bottom and pass
the Eurail of the image right.
It says background open it close and it's you are all open close and we just pass with templates strings.
Real simple.
The featured player and of course koma
and there we go you know we can get it.
This is my belief this is my mistake because I'm loading a component before the actual text after the
test.
So we got an e-mail number first and then second and then players.
This is my mistake.
The player should be loading first because he's going to go you know behind of all of this text.
Say if I reload it like go again.
There we go.
We can get it.
So we have the same animation.
So this is it you know this was not a lot of work a lot of this was you know copy paste but you know
this is the kind of complicated thing to understand and all.
Returning the function y at right here we don't need x y.
So why return after you do it one time.
It's pretty obvious right.
You can repeat this and create really complex animations.
And of course remember to always check the re-act move.
Now we will do more animations.
Not this one but we're going to do something like this and we're going to do this.
And then on the team I'm sorry the matches we will animate list with that.
No group right here no group.
We will use that one to animate this thing.
All right.
So let's go to the next one.
I'm going to give you the code of course you can find the resource the code for this section and begin
to move forward and do the next one the matches.
And this one is going to get really interesting here because the matches they need a database they need
you know the name of the teams they need the logos they need the they.
How much how was the how the match.
Our team won or something like that you know we need that kind of information and that information comes
from the database.
And we don't have a database so we will need to create a database with firebase feet some information
and then you know do all the set up in our project to connect to the data to firebase to retrieve the
data.
All right.
So let's go to the next section and start of that.