All right so let's start building the matches.
Now this is not going to be that simple is going to be a little bit long because we need to do a lot
of things.
And one of the things we're going to be using that of course throughout the whole application.
So we're going to do this which is this is a reusable component.
We're going to see a lot of this right here.
So it kind of makes sense for us to create a reusable components so we don't have to write the same
code several several times then we need to create a database.
And then of course we need to create this tiny component so we can get that data.
And you know create all this results.
But first we will need to create the matches component create the reusable component right here the
matches and everything else.
So that's the first thing we're going to do going to go back to our application and I'm going to go
back right here.
Got to close this.
They've featured and everything else because we don't really need it in the x and the stripes.
I'm just going to leave home right here.
So we need a new directory were we going to be hosting this inside home.
We're going to call this matches.
So Majerus contains two different sections the index and then the actual blocks you know and the blocks
are this once it's going to create two files inside matches the index digests and then another one called
blocks.
So block is that.
Yes.
All right.
Let's get.
So now inside index that genius right here inside the x that is of course the only thing we need to
do right here is to return a stateless component because we will return the tag at the top the blocks
right here.
And then just attack at the bottom.
Right.
OK.
So it reacts.
They list components.
And of course this one I'm going to call it matches matches home because it's the matches from home.
Right.
OK.
So of course we will need to import blocks but we're going to do it later.
And on this one the only thing we're going to render is just Divx which is going to be a wrapper class
name and then home matches matches underscore wrap her all right inside of here.
I will add a container because this is centered in the middle so there is a class called container.
We can use just like a bootstrap class name and then Container container.
Now right here on this component we will have a div with attack.
You know just like this.
So check that we're going to have the blocks and then at the bottom we're going to have a tack which
is going to be a link and that's when it's not a link.
And this one it is.
That's why we use reusable components.
So we need to pass props.
Same thing with it with the previous project.
OK.
So I'm going to save it.
And of course we need to bring the matches to home.
So I'm going to go to home and inside home we import import import matches.
Why not mattress from that for Slash and then matches.
Right.
So I'm going to make a copy and make reference to this.
But of course if I go back to our application we can ever get nothing so far because we are you know
not really rendering anything.
We get this.
But for course we're going to do it right now.
So first we're going to create that reusable component.
So I'm going to go to matches and the reusable component is going to be inside you.
I now this component the TAC is not super important so I'm going to stored inside a common file called
Minsk for Muslims.
So inside misc we will you know return this component.
So of course we will use some GSX so import re-act from react to it and we will be using linked link.
So import that link and then from re-act router.
No it's not the medium of the comp..
This is why import re-act router.
Dom.
Very good.
So I'm going to export Barville a function called takk.
Right.
So this function will be receiving some props.
And then of course we return something's on just going to go ahead and pass prompts just like we did
in the previous project.
This task will return a template which you know some dip whatever date doesn't matter just going to
call it tech and it's out of here we will make.
We will check if the tag it's a link or not.
Again same thing with the default.
So if and of course if we have props that link we didn't have this problem so hard to get it created
in a minute.
Else we're going to return something else so if we don't have the proper link we will return the template
and if we do so we can return return some other GSX wrapped in a link right.
Makes sense.
Open and close like OK.
So the link and then go and going a little fast because we all did this on the on the priest on the
first project and it is really simple.
So in this one we will have a prop called link to which is actually the actual reference.
The H the direction you know the location where we're going to go.
And of course at the end we will just return the template we have right here.
So in theory if I include this from a different component we should be getting a div with attack inside.
So I going to go to the mattress and I'm going to import a tack from and it's going to be done that
for Slash the dot for Slash you I for Slash and then Misc..
And if I make a reference right here to tack take it out for the full import as tag was not found.
OK.
This is my mistake.
I am importing Ptak without this because maybe you don't know this when you export something like this
with not export default and we imported right here this doesn't know what to look if we do this because
we are importing something that it has the export default we do do not have the export default.
It's because we have many many exports.
So we need to import one of all of the file.
In this case we just import tag.
That's why we get no mistakes and we get the TAC key right.
OK.
So I'm going to go to the matches and now this task will have special properties of course.
So I'm going to go to tack.
We're going to go right here.
I'm going to add a VC K which is going to be the background.
And in this case it's going to be hash tag then 0 1 7 3 1 right.
I'm going to add a size property which is going to be 50 pixels 50 pixels and then a color with I don't
know white that white makes sense.
So white one two three four five six.
There you go.
So this tack will have some text.
So instead of making a self-closing attack I'm going to say tech and inside will be saying matches.
Now the stack has a background a size and a color.
So we are passing that as props.
So inside of misc instead of this components we need to catch up props.
All right.
So I'm going to go to a template and what we get to do.
Of course we return a div with some properties to do this.
So what we do we add this tile property to this to this element.
So we do have a background.
I'm going to say background.
And this one it's equal to props that became the thing we are passing as props.
All right.
I'm going to put koma.
I can get font size font size and then remember we have this size.
So it's prop's that size.
Now coma we have a color.
So it's color and I'm going to be adding props that color we do have that props and then we can add
whatever property we want.
In this case I'm going to be adding some padding five pixels and 10 pixels from the side to display.
It's inline block in line and then loops block what else.
Oh and the fun family fun family is going to be righteous.
So right it was very good.
So I made a mistake right here.
Righteous right.
So now if we rendered this it will render all the props and the padding and everything else so we can
get it.
You know it's it's nice going to get it Briger let me do this.
Now if I deleted we get this core bracket because we didn't have a text and we are not defining the
text as props I'm defining this inside of here so we could do we can pass prop's the children to fill
the inside of this deck so props that children right and reload it.
And we get matches.
That's good.
Now I'm going to show you something else just in case right now you're just passing.
We are just passing background on size and color.
What happens if I want to pass something else.
Maybe I want to add some special property just to the style of this one and I can not add this style
right here.
So what we can do we can create a special property that has some success you know some other CSSA properties
for example I'm going to say at an open close and are going to be passing just an object with some things
inside.
So I'm going to say maybe I don't know that color is red just like that's colored.
No I'm defining the color red here and I'm just really finding it right here inside of this property.
So now inside of misc what I could do I could do coma and do.
Dad dad dad dad dad props dad ad and whatever we have inside add will be added to the end of all of
this properties.
So the car red right here will override the color red right here.
And we will get a color red.
So inside of the property you can pass you know some cost to more specific stylings.
And if you think about it this is what we do with material you I we added style and that style it's
actually a property from Matile you I'd not real style but we can override some default stylings with
our own own custom Starling's and this is very very useful.
All right.
What else.
So we have mattress and then we have the blocks going to remove this.
I don't need this.
There we go.
OK.
So we have mattress we have the Block.
And then we have a tack.
If I go to the original it's just attack with a small font.
But this one it's a link.
If I click it we go to the matches right.
So what do we need to do.
We need to pass the link property just like we did on previous project.
So I'm going to start all over again.
Can I say tack open and close the text on this one.
It's see more matches right.
And again I'm going to be passing some properties.
Copy this.
I don't want to type it again so b c k of the background.
It's instead of blue it's going to be white the size instead of 50.
It's going to be 22 and the color is going to be that blue.
So I'm going to copy from here.
All right.
So if I do this we can get it you know this is get we can get it but it's not a link.
So we need to pass the property link true just like this.
True.
And that link to property if not we're going to get an error.
I'm not sure if I made the link to the last link to it without clicking is linked to.
So if I open it close this one is going to go to the scene just like this.
Let me make it right.
The team we didn't have this route.
We will do it much much later.
So if I go over we can get the link right here.
And if I could get we go to our route of course that doesn't exist yet but we will get the top and we
get the bottom.
So now the only thing we need to do the remaining thing for this component.
It's the blocks.
But before we do the blocks we need to set up firebase.