Right.
So now what we eat it's firebase.
So let's go to right here to the browser and we will search for firebase something like this.
And of course the first firebase dash Google you get that one.
So for this you will need a Google account.
So if you don't have a Google account you need to create one.
Right.
So whenever you go to Google you know enter firebase.
If you're not authenticated you need to log in everything else.
And let me change this to maybe and or something like that because it's in Spanish.
OK.
So I'm going to get this maybe in English if of course you're in Spanish spoken country again in Spanish
but you can't get it.
So right here at the top you're going to get go to consult.
I'm going to like it.
I'm going to go to my council and I'm going to get two projects.
You're not going to get anything if you don't have firebase projects.
And I get the test one because I'm on the incorrect place this is the correct account I was using the
incorrect accounts or for that.
So for example right here we have the second practice test.
This project belongs to this one.
So all my database and everything else is hosted on this project by default with firebase.
You get some free projects that you can run.
You can upload and see it in right here just like Heroku.
So this one belongs to this one but of course I'm not going to use this one.
Of course this one it's a new test.
I'm creating a new course on the side.
But you know it's going to take a little bit more time.
So what we need to do right now we need to add a new project to create a new project so I'm going to
click on that project and mine is going to call AM city you know McIvor makes sense and can only letters
numbers and spaces and there's characters.
All right.
So we cannot do it like this.
We can do it like this.
MC And of course is going to give you a D.
You can select it you know the country doesn't matter.
I'm just going to say except and it will create a project.
It's going to take a couple of minutes.
Right after it's done your new project is ready.
I'm going to click and continue and you're going to get this you know this end point right here and
you get to get a lot of things with firebase authentication.
We will use authentication of this one database.
We will use it storage.
We will use it in hosting.
We will use it.
So we get to use the first four.
Now how can how can we create a database.
And that's one.
OK.
If you scroll down.
Oh.
Oh I'm sorry.
This change actually it was different.
So I got to go to database and you're going to get this right here and this is actually new because
they've released a new new product called Cloud Firestar you know it's in beta.
So we are not going to use cloud for store of course.
Could it go right here the time at the bottom and or choose real time database real time database create
a database now and this again this is new.
Actually we didn't have this before.
So it gives you the the option to run into different modes start in locked mode.
This one was the default in the past or in test mode lock mode.
It means that the users cannot read and cannot ride unless they are authenticated on the on this you
know this project.
If they are not then sign in or sign out they don't have the correct tokens.
They can not read or write from the database.
And if you start in test mode we have true and true.
So anyone can read and anyone can right now for now because we are just testing and developing.
We need this structure.
True and true.
When this goes to the to production of course we need to change this.
So I'm going to click Enable and remove this one.
And then you're going to get.
Of course you're going to get this database.
And this is the actual database.
It's empty so far it's empty.
We will add some things here.
So if you go to rules later inside the rules you can change that read and write to falls or maybe only
if it's authenticated you can do this.
So I'm going to go to data and right here we need to add some data but first we need to connect to our
project you know make a connection between this far based project and our project right here.
So we will need to do some configuration.
Now how can we get the configuration and the keys and the password we need to connect this project.
If you go to a project you get start here you get three different options and it says at firebase to
your web app.
So I'm going to look at and it says at firebase do you wake up and it's going to give you the API key
the domain and all the other configuration you need to start your project and they give you this.
But of course we are not using.
We are not going to use this.
We just use this passports.
Now I'm going to leave this here and I'm going to go back to our project.
I'm going to close some things there's a little bit cleaner.
OK.
So inside source are going to be adding a file that it's going to be doing.
The connection between the server and our project is going to go to source and add a new Fylde called
fire base that yes it can call this whatever you want.
Does the name it's not important.
So inside firebase we need to connect with our project.
OK.
So first we need to import firebase.
Why.
Because we downloaded a dependency called firebase that it's in charge of doing all this connection.
You know it's the kind of the SDK.
Now the SDK suffered some updates.
It was different in the past.
Now we need to do it on a different way.
It's still going to work if we use the old way.
You might find some documentation with the old way of doing things.
But now if you want to skip the warning messages we're going to do it just like this.
I'm going to show you in a minute.
So first we need to import firebase from the firebase and then firebase and slash app.
This is the first thing now and this is on the documentation and it makes no sense but this is how we
need to do it then we need to import just like this and we open close.
And we pretty much do the same thing.
Firebase app.
Right.
So we are importing You know the app properties and everything.
Everything we're going to use from app.
All right.
Later we're going to be using a database you know the database property so we need to do import firebase
and database later are we going to use the storage so we need to import firebase storage and you know
we need to do a lot of things.
So at the bottom right here we need to bring all the configuration in everything we have right here
so I'm going to copy bar config and everything else and I'm going to paste it right here.
And since we are using a six I'm going to say Kunst config.
All right.
So now we need a way to start our application.
How can we do this.
Right here we have firebase initialize app and then config.
Copy this.
I'm going to paste it right here at the bottom and that's it.
Now what we need to do we need to include this file from within you know our main application.
So far this file has no relation with our project we didn't include this file in our you know our project
our app.
Right.
So that's what we need to do first.
All right so now we're going to do a network request to get some data from the database because that's
the idea we need to populate this component right here.
This one with some information from the database but our database it's empty so go to database and you
can see this.
No.
So what are we going to do.
I've added as a resource.
Jason file so we can imported and generate a database so we can have you know some kind of real information.
Later of course we will create an admin and point so we can add the matches dynamically into the database
but we will do that that later.
Now most of the times when you do a web page or a project with the server you start for that with the
server first and then you move up to the front and front and that's what we're going to do on the next
project.
But I wanted to start with this first because you know it's a little bit more fun.
So OK so instead of here just download what I give you as a resource is I believe it's ambs city something.
Just download it and then when you want it to go do go right here to the dots and import Jason are going
to do that right now.
All right so after importing that file this is how it looks.
You can get the mattress which is what we're going to be using right now.
Then a database with all the players and the matches and the players are the ones we can add dynamically
from the admin.
Then we have a position with the position table.
You're not going to do this one.
I can explain you why later.
And then we have promotions.
And this is going to be the e-mails e-mailing list.
We do at home.
We're going to do later.
And then of course a list of all the teams and inside you know the name of a team and the thumbnail.
But can he be using from the public folder.
And we're not going to do this one.
Maybe I'm going to do it as a bonus but much much later.
All right.
So now we have some matches.
This is what we need to load.
We need to make an at per request and get the matches from the database.
Right.
OK.
I'm going to go back to my project and right now we have this file.
We are not including the file.
So as a testing purposes just to make sure we are connecting with the database I'm going to go right
here and import the file right here.
So whenever the application start we will do that.
Network request from this file but in real life we will do it from within the matches.
Right.
OK.
So inside of firebase right here.
Can it go at the bottom.
I'm going to create a viable where we going to be connecting with the database and I'm going to say
Konst just like this and it's firebase D.B and this is my name.
You can put you know database or whatever is that you want to call it.
And right here we need to call to a method called firebase dot database.
So firebase that database and that's why we are importing database at the top because we need to use
this method.
So we use firebase which is the thing we are importing.
And then we use the database.
So now in the future when we want to make a network request to firebase we don't have to do firebase
that database and then do everything else we just export fire DV and that's it.
We just you know creating an alias that that's what it is.
So now to access the database we need to pass a reference of what we want to get what we want to break.
In this case is the matches going to go you know to ref open opening close and are going to say matches.
Now the ref needs one more method.
It uses the once method and then everything that's on the firebase documentation.
So what we get is the value.
Right.
OK.
And then of course this will return a promise.
So we'll do then opening close and then of course we will return something else.
And this is the code we are going to get back.
So this then will return a snapshot could be response is actually a response but in firebase lingo they
call it snapshot.
Now if I do a log and I cancel lot what do we get back from the database as a snapshot we're going to
go back to home and reload and it's at least the application is not breaking.
I'm going to go to inspect console and we get this data snapshot.
And this is the console log again right here.
So if I open it we get a lot of things index key matches the no children you know we get a lot of information
but not know the information we want which is the actual data.
So for this instead of the snapshot we need to bring the bow.
So whenever we bring back all the application will reload and there we go.
We get all the matches and let me show you the structure of this structure.
It's a little bit weird.
We get you know the I.D. which has this I.D. and then you know all the information but it's kind of
an object with keys and objects inside.
It's a little bit weird.
We didn't get an array with objects we will need to transform this structure to make it work.
In our project we're going to get there.
But now at least we know that if we connect to firebase with the config and everything else we are connecting
and we are able to make a get request and they will then we will be making a post request.
So now we are connected.
That is good.
That's the first step.
All right.
So let's go to the next section and we will start.
We're going to we're going to deliver this.
We're going into this and we're going to start bringing the blocks.
We're going to start doing the blocks.