OK so let's continue with this.
Now inside the firebase Well there's actually another way we can to use this.
I just did this just to make sure and to show you how this works.
But we are not going to really use it like this so I'm going to go to the index and the lead that firebase
import later when we use the authentication we can do something similar but not just like this.
So inside firebase I'm going to delete this because we are not going to really use it.
Now I want I want I want to export you know available with all this logic.
So I'm going to go right here and create an export export.
So this is just like the misc file with it.
Right here we are just creating viral and exporting something.
So I'm going to export this firebase right.
And I would export more things first begin to make it we're going to make a request to get the matches.
So middle of this are going to get the matches.
All right.
So going to create a viable called firebase matches something like that you can call this whatever you
want.
So barbus matches and this one is going to be equal to that firebase DVH which is firebase that database
and then DOD and are going to make are going to use that reference to matches matches of reference we
have on the database right here.
We have this matches.
So if we wanted to call players we will need to use players and positions and everything else in this
case we just want matches.
So now I can export firebase matches just like this far as firebase matches.
And from a different file include this and it will make a reference to firebase dot database dot ref
that matches and there's no need to ride all this.
You know all of this again.
Right.
That's the first thing.
So now where do we need to.
Where are we going to be making this request.
You know the request for these blocks.
Well we have a component for that inside matches inside blocks.
So I'm going to go two blocks.
This is what is going to be a re-act class based component called Gluck's at the top we need to import
several things.
First we need to import opening close.
And we need to import that fire firebase matches from that that for Slash that are for us one more time
and it's going to be firebase.
So now if we make a request to this when we were able to connect to the database and bring the data
we want that's the first thing.
All right.
So inside the renter for now I'm not going to do anything but we will store the matches through state.
So matches open it close and then that's all right.
So inside of the render what we will do we will render a div with the class name just like this class
name of home matches and inside of here I will just say this show matches something like this show matches
opening close and pass the reference to this state that matches when you have this function going to
create right now.
So you know for now this function is going to do anything first begin to make the request.
So show matches equals to a function that returns some GSX later we will be looping all the matches
we get from the server and returning you know a deps for now which is going to return a div with match
whatever doesn't matter go back and the application should be reloading but it's not because I'm not
including blocks on the parent matches right here on the index.
So I'm going to go to index import blocks from that forward slash blocks and I'm going to make.
I'm going to add the tag right here blocks.
So now the application in theory should be reloading.
And we get match.
All right.
So this is what we get from our function show matches.
So now we need to make a request to the server.
And this is going to be a little bit weird.
So first I'm going to do it on the component.
Did mount everything.
Everything is mounted.
We will do river quest and where we have the information about the matches we will set the stage with
the new state of matches since we are importing firebase matches at the top.
I'm going to put firebase matches.
That's the first thing.
Now add one more thing.
If I'm talking too fast or maybe too slow for you at the bottom.
On the other player to me at the bottom in the left you have a button to play the BDO in a slower tempo
or to go a little bit faster.
You know do that the whole time.
All right.
So we are making a request to far based matches but we need to do a little bit more right here in the
database.
We have 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 maybe 12 entries with the matches and right here we just have sex.
So there's no need for us to retrieve all 12 because we just need six so we can use a method from the
you know the firebase the ref and get a limit to last.
So this is what he's going to do.
It's going to bring the last six.
In this case we just need six.
So going to do that and we need to use the once again just like with that before once it's going to
be bad.
And then of course this will return the promise.
Inside it will return a snapshot.
Just like with that before it's now shut the closes not shot right here of course we can do console
log is now shut.
And then of course dot.
And at least we get to see if we get something back.
And I got we get it when we can get the information but we can not use the information just the way
it is.
You know with a key and then the object inside of an object we cannot do this.
We need to convert this into an array of objects.
And if you notice this is a string.
It's the ID of the actual entry.
We have the ID here and we don't have it inside.
But sometimes we will need the ID inside of the actual object.
So we will need to kind of a convert this resoled into some something else.
So what we can do we can create a function that converts this and we can host it inside your tails.
And then Mintz told you that mistake.
It's going to be really useful.
So inside Misc. we're going to create a new function.
Let me make this better.
And the function you can put whatever name you want.
I'm going to click export first do the export than it cost and I'm going to I always call it firebase
and then Luper the Firebrace Luper will be a function that at the end will return something and it will
return a bit be receiving that snapshot as arguments.
So what we do we just need to loop the snapshot first to create Barville with then with the data and
it's going to be empty at the beginning after the loop.
This data will contain all our records in the way we want.
So what we do we do not snapshot dot and we do enter a for each and this is a method of firebase give
us for each something like this.
Each opening close so we open and we rerun a function.
So this for each will be getting a child snapshot and all of this is on the on the documentation of
firebase.
Now on each loop on each snapshot which is actually each entry of the of the array or the you know the
result we can do something else.
We can grab some data and push it to data in the way we want.
So I'm going to access data are viral and then I'm going to do push just like an array.
And what I'm going to be pushing is going to be the entire object now in entire object.
We just want two things all the data we have right here and we want to push the idea as well.
So I'm going to I'm going to go right here and say that that child snapshot dateable I'm accessing the
snapshot and putting inside all the values we have inside for each key.
Right.
And then I'm going to create a special key called ID and I going to say child snapshot dot key.
So we are getting that key and we are pushing a value called ID with the same name.
That's the idea.
Real simple this is not you know react to firebase is just standard Javascript.
And at the end when this is done we will return this data.
Right.
This is the idea.
So now I'm going to go two blocks and import this function import open and close and it's called firebase
Luper and we will include it from dot dot for Slash the dot for Slash.
And then you I and then Misc..
So now whenever we get this a snapshot and not about the whole snapshot we can create a viable called
I don't know whatever is you want to call it maybe matches if we are working with matches equals that
firebase Luper.
And we will be passing that snapshot we get.
So whenever we get the snapshot is going to go to firebase Luper Firebrace Luber is going to do that
logic and it will return an array with object objects which is what we want.
And if I do a console log and then mattress and reload the application you know we get it the correct
way where we want the array with the 0 and then of course the ID inside anality.
For me the rest of the information we have a lot of information about the match frank here we will be
using this later.
All right.
So that is the first thing.
Now we have the firebase Luber.
Now if you notice right here we have Manchester City it's Manchester City against Brighton referees.
Harry Potter sorry for that.
It's against Brighton.
So you know it kind of makes sense that this is the maybe the the last game.
So if I go right here it is not it's not the last game.
So what it does this let me go back to our project this limit to last it drafts the last six.
So it starts from the bottom one two three four five six.
And this is the first key.
Now on the right here I cannot put the first of the six right here.
This should be the last game.
So what do we do.
We need to reverse the array.
And from firebase we cannot do that.
I can not make a request to far based and get it ready directly from the database.
We need to do it on the front and that is one of the things that you know that's how Firebrace works.
It just gives you a simple database and you know simple simple API but you can do whatever you want
just like I don't know a Ph piece of or something like that on the Apache server.
So it doesn't matter.
Going to delete this.
And what I'm going to do are going to did this that said state for now said state open it close and
it seems we have new mattress are going to say matches.
Now again I need to reverse the array.
The first one goes to the last and the last one go to the first.
We just turn the remote right around.
So I'm going to create a function inside Minsk.
For now I'm going to say this I'm going to go Minsk.
Could it go right here at the bottom.
And again create a function to reverse.
You're right again again this is standard javascript not react so reverse array equals to actually actual.
All right which is the array we get after we process with firebase Luper.
And of course it's just a function that returns something.
So I'm going to create a viral called reversed array some like that.
And this one should be let out Konst doesn't matter.
So reverse array equals to an empty array just like with it before.
So now I'm going to do a for a good old for an VAR or let you know I equals.
And this is what we need to do we need to grab the actual array just like this.
The actual rate we need to calculate the length.
So it's Lenk just like this minus one.
And then of course it's equal to I greater than zero.
And then we do I minus minus minus.
Right.
Yes.
I'm really glad is 6 game to 2 and all of this because after a while this gets a little bit confusing.
So we grab that reversed array just like this which is this marble we have right here and we do the
push open and close and we push the actual array.
And the key which is the eye we are going back Portes right here.
So at the end we do reversed array and we returned the reverse array return.
All right.
That is it.
So now of course we need to bring this function into the blocks just like we did with Firebrace Luper
And now instead of returning matches with an empty array just like I'm doing now we do reverse array
and this returns matches.
We can do this before the setting state of.
But you know that's cool.
So if I reload the application of course I get nothing.
I'm going to go right here to the render and console log this that state.
Right.
So we get the new state of mattress and I mean a mistake it's returning a function.
This is actually my mistake.
Return reversal rate it's because reversed a rate.
This is my mistake.
I'm returning to the actual function and not you know the BHARMAL.
So now we get a array of sex and Brighton.
It's not the first one it's how does it feel or how town against Manchester City.
So we just reversed everything that we're simple.
So now we have the database ready to pass it to.
You know the show matches the show matches it's going to loop the list of matches and create all the
blocks right here.
So let's go to the next one and do all the you know the front and for the blocks.