So finally let's create the blocks right here.
So I'm going to go two blocks and on this function we do loop you know the all the list of matches we
get from the server.
Let me close the log.
And of course return a block.
So in this case just going to do this.
We don't need so and show matches.
We are receiving this the state that matches.
So I'm going to say mattress.
OK.
So if we do have matches we're going to go and do something if not we get a return.
No we didn't this many many times before.
So I'm going to access matches I can and do a map.
And of course on each iteration I will return some GSX.
And again Notice I'm using parenthesis.
OK.
So the map will return a match.
So on each match we will return a div with a class name of item class name item.
And inside I will return a div with a class name of wrap her or something like that.
I believe proper Yes.
Now if we stop for a second and we think about this this block this one we have right here we could
use a block like this in different components maybe in different places so we can make sense that this
could be reusable component.
And that's what we can do.
I'm going to go to you.
I could create a new file that calls matches underscore block that yes and it's going to be just a single
block not the whole blocks.
OK.
So inside Majerus block this is going to be a re-act stateless components.
And I'm going to change name to matches matches and then block Breguet.
So right now we are not going to you know return anything just block.
So inside of block we need to of course import this reusable component called match's block.
So import matches matches and then block from the data for Slashdot that force Lesch you for Slash and
matches.
BLOCK So now I'm going to go right here.
I'm going to make a reference to this div because right now we just have a div and I'm going to be passing
the match on each iteration so I'm going to go right here at the bottom and say of course match equals
match match equals match.
So now the match just blog will be receiving a prob with the match.
If we will know the application.
We get block Block block blocked six blocks.
All right.
So inside Majerus block we're going to go right here and if we do console log just like this and I can
select the props we are getting.
And of course we are Depass to probs do the console.
It's a little bit low con. We get an object with a match and then the object.
So what I can do I can use some a little bit of destructuring and I can do OK with the match Orion and
when it's once it's loaded.
Of course I need to do cons lock match when it's loaded instead of giving me match with an object inside
it.
With all the information we just get the information.
So now I can run I can return this component just making a reference to match and the name or match
and the ID and everything else.
I'm going to go here.
And now what we need to do we need to start building all the you know the kind of the front end of this.
So class name and the class name the wrapper of this is match underscore block that is it.
Now if we take a look at the original we have a date and then we have the Block 1 and then the block
to the top and the one to the bottom.
So OK.
So I've removed it.
So on the top we will have a div with the date.
This one contains a name a class name of match and then date date.
And instead of the date we will of course return match that date.
Now sometimes if I go to the server and go to matches we have a property called the date right here
date but we have one that it's going to be called Match final.
Now sometimes the match of course didn't start because it can happen in the future.
That didn't play the game or writing the game didn't start.
So if it's just final No we will display a message of match not played yet or something like that.
And of course the match was played which is we have final Yes we will just show the date.
That makes sense.
So I'm going to go right here and first thing going to say OK you match that final final.
It's true we will output match that date if we're not going to return something else and I'm going to
close this for now and I'm going to be returning match.
Not played yet.
Cohen is pace and I will attach the match dates and you know when this is going to be played.
Match date and all the games we have.
They are pretty much in the past so they were all over the place.
So we get to date forgive get going to Close's So now what do we need to do.
We need to start with a rapper.
With the first block and the second block.
All right.
So I'm going to go right here and say Dave opening close so we get the class name of match match and
then wrap her match.
There we go.
OK.
So we have a top and a bottom.
So for each we have a.
So day of class name I know that is the boring part.
And Heino I know.
So then match top.
Now if we take a look in the left we have something in the right.
We have a different block.
So we do have a div with match left and right.
So class name is going to be left and the other one is going to be you guessed it right.
OK.
So in the left we have something in in the right.
We have something else now in the left.
We have a Nikon which is the icon of the team and the Manchester City you know the name of the team.
So I'm going to go and say Dave I'm sorry with the class name and this one is going to be called I can
if I check the database on each.
Each match we have the local teen thumbnail which is the name of the thumbnail inside of the public
images and team icons.
We're not fetching the images from the server.
And of course on the other one the local sart local thumbnail and we have the a way thumbnail which
is going to be Manchester City for local or for a way you know while we have only have Manchester City
always have much history.
Let's get.
So I'm going to call this an inside of the icon I'm sorry upside of the icon.
I'm going to set the style and I'm going to be passing the background image so background just like
this.
Open it close we'll use templates strengths.
Right.
So it's your L opening close and the location it's images for Slash team icons forward slash and then
of course we pass the local thumbnail because the first one is always local so open and close.
We do match DOD local C T H and B.
Right.
And then it's always the PMG so that PNB and that is that if I save it in theory we should be getting
at least something and we do.
Let's get what else.
Then we have the team name.
So we're going to go at the bottom open close Dave with a class name and a class name for this.
It's team name make sense team name and the only thing we do it's for the local.
So we do match local.
So instead of top this could be local match local and then match away something like that and I'm going
Tuesday of course it's match local and we get the name right.
Manchester City Liverpool Burgert.
So now we need to put you know the right so inside of the right.
If you notice maybe this one if the result is not defined We're going to put this dash and that could
happen.
So we're going to say if match that final final which means that the you know the game didn't start
we're going to put the match which is true.
We're going to put match and result and then local and this result.
It's of course on the database resoled local right here if not of course we're going to put that cash.
So open close dash.
All right.
So let's check it out.
So we have a dash and the local resoled.
All right of course they made a mistake here.
Maybe the date is wrong.
But that's good.
What else we need to put away.
So the weight instead of match top is going to be match bottom makes sense.
You know the opposite class name and then match and then but we are almost done guys and we have pretty
much the same thing.
So I'm going to copy and paste the only difference is that now instead of local is going to be a way
right and they match local no match way and rissoles local No resoled way.
All right.
That is it.
Got to reload it and we can't get it.
That is good.
Very good.
Now if I go to the final one below the application I scroll down.
We have the you know the sliding effect.
So that's the last thing we're going to be adding because this is ready.
OK.
So I'm going to go back to blog and we will use Riak reveal.
You know it's a very simple transition.
We are not used re-act move while doing all that code just to do that makes no sense.
So I'm going to bring the slide from re-act reveal import and remember we've already installed this
on a package that Jason re-act reveal we do have it right here.
All right.
So import slide from re-act reveal react reveal and we bring a slide.
Real simple.
And inside of slide instead of returning this item we will return we will return a slide right and make
sense and go to the bottom close and slide.
All right.
That is it.
So now of course we want to slide it from the bottom.
So you say bottom just like this.
And since we are looping and returning an element we need to give a key so key opening close match dot
ID.
And if you reload and scroll down same result very good.
And of course this one is link you know the tag everything.
So everything looks nice.
So the next section is going to be the.
This animation going to do a more animation and then we're going to go back to the database to enter
you know enter they are the user e-mail to the e-mail.
The mailing list or something like that to win a jersey.
And after we finish the home we're going to start building the back.
And right we can do authentication and everything else.
So if you're not interesting interested on this on this component and this component you just can go
move forward get the code from Get have or actually get it from the last section where we do this.
I'm going to give you that code and now I'm going to give you the code for this one and you can just
you know put it on your computer do your own or NPM install and get it from this point and you start
watching the authentication process with firebase and everything else you can totally totally do that.
No problem.
But this is done.
This section is done.
So let's going to move forward and go to meet the players at home.