All right so let's create the media players section.
So I'm going to go right here to our project and this of course is going to be one more component inside
home.
So it kind of makes sense for me for going to go home and create a new folder and a directory called
I don't know meet the players or meet players.
That makes sense right.
So many players will have two different components which is the index and then we have two different
sections which is going over you know the main layout in the right and the main layout with the animation
in the left.
So inside the player's index the genius and the other one will be called cartes.
Now the cards we can have a meet to make a reusable component because the original figure and the final
one if I go to the team we get the you know the same cards we get from from from home.
So we get to make sense again.
For us to create a reusable component so we didn't have to repeat a lot of code.
All right.
So from cartes for now I'm not going to do anything inside of the players.
I need a re-act class based components.
You're going to see why I'm using a class based component and this one is going to be called Meet the
or meet players.
Just to sum it up mid players and then meet players forget.
So if you notice in the background we have kind of a tiny PNB is a sprite.
So we're going to repeat it and create this background.
And this of course is in resources and images right here resources images and I believe it was called
stripes.
There we go.
We have you know this.
So we're going to bring it so we can attach it to the background.
I'm going to go and say import the stripes stripes from that that for Slashdot for Slash one more time.
And then of course resources for Slash images for Slash and store right.
Yes.
There we go.
What else are we going to use tax right here the in the right.
We use the tax we've been using before that reusable component.
So we need to import it as well because we're going to be using it import Takk from DOD for Slashdot
that forward slash you I.
And then from the misc file.
Right.
Miscellaneous.
Now we will have a state.
For now I'm going to leave it empty.
Going to say state and then we're going to talk why we are using a stake right here.
Now on the return we're going to be returning for now just a class a container of course with the class
name of home meet players something like this.
All right.
Now this container has the background with the stripes.
So I need to pass the style and the background with the you know the image so background.
And then we use Collen template strings.
And I'm going to say that the background is going to be white by default and we're going to be using
that pride as well.
And I'm going to open and close and use that.
Tripes I believe I called the strypes stripes and of course by default it's repeat.
So we can generate dat and repeat the background.
If I put something inside of here me go back put something inside of here and save it.
Of course we're going to get something but first we need to go to the index of home and require and
import this meet players.
So we're going to go here in Port meet for years players from that forward slash meet players and since
we have an index there is no need to put in X than meet the players.
No standard stuff right here.
Nothing new.
And of course we get you know that line of code with the background Burguet.
OK.
So let's go back to meet the players.
I'm going to remove blocks because are not going to use it.
The source firebase you know a lot of components we don't really need right now mask goodbye and matches
goodbye.
I'm just going to leave to meet the players which is the index and then cartes.
All right.
So here we need to do a lot more going to do lead and create a dev with a class of container because
we need to center everything.
So it's container and inside of here are going to add one more wrapper.
So Dev because his obsession flexed flex and he's flex right here.
So class name opening close and this one this class KOLs home meet players we just know pretty much
the same thing in this.
I'm going to copy and paste and then wrapper.
So instead of here whenever the app loads.
Of course now we get nothing.
But now we're going to get something like this you know a default to sites in the left.
We'll have the animation in the right.
We'll have the you know the text.
So I'm going to create a container for the left and a container for the can you know the right so diff
opening close the class name of this one is going to be home card and then wrapper and right here we
can have the card that begin to be creating in a few minutes.
And then this one which is the right side.
Class name opening close home text and then wrapper.
All right.
And right here we're going to get the text real simple and if we reloaded we have cart and we have text
that is good.
Now inside of the home text wrapper we need to add the text the same component we have right here.
But of course with different properties.
So I'm going to add the first tack when I say dev opening close and I'm going to add a tack right here.
The meat to it right.
There we go.
So instead of here we need to keep the put the wart meat.
This is the first tack.
So meat right.
Of course we need to be packed we need to pass some properties in order for this work.
If you remember is the background I'm going to close this so that we can see everything the background
and the background has does that blue color.
It's 0 1 7 7 3 1 0 1.
There we go.
Then the size I'm going to say its size and it's the font size.
So 100 pixels then we say color and we find the color of the you know of the text.
So once you have three one two three it's white and that one should be getting something at least.
Now we need to add additional CSX information so I'm going to use that and again you know concatenate
the styles with the props.
If you remember this weekend it did this before.
So the display for this one.
This play will be in line and then block.
And I'm going to add a margin bottom of tiny pixels.
We need to do pretty much this on all the tacks right here.
All right so get we get meat.
Now the next one will be pretty much the same same idea than this.
So I'm going to copy this.
I'm not going to copy this.
I'm going to go at the bottom and say Meet D and save it and we got the.
Then the players and players Oh sorry for that.
Meet the players.
And we get beat the players.
That's good.
Now again this is a lot of space.
So I'm going to go back I did this just to you know show you this.
But you know I see it in a lot of space just for you know two or three things so I don't really like
it just get to do this.
Sorry for this.
I'm going to take one minute or less.
Almost done and then the ad and then we go a little bit better.
You know and this one could go right here as well.
So this one was done and was done.
I'm sorry if this I don't regret it anyways.
All right.
Almost done.
There we go.
So OK.
So now after me the players we have.
But in so an action so we can click here and we go to the team.
Right.
So we need to bring a button.
Same thing that's attacked but the tag is going to be a link Tac.
So at the bottom we're going to say Open of course and again we use takk.
Now the TAC will pretty much contain the same thing in there.
But we're going to change some values.
So I'm going to say attack and the background instead of blue is going to be white.
So one two three one two three.
Right.
The size.
It's not 100 pixels much smaller 27 pixels.
The caller will have that blue color so I'm going to copy this one from the top and paste it.
Now of course we need to add all the other properties.
And on this one I'm going to put it like light like this.
So link if you remember to make it linkable we need to pass a boolean true and then we need to pass
that link to property.
I believe it was linked to.
I always forget this.
I'm going to go to you.
I was Minsk and it's the link to property.
There you go.
So linked to.
And we're going to go to the route the team.
So Forth slash the team.
All right.
I'm going to add that we're going to add more things just like we did with apps going to copy this one
go over here at the bottom and at it we are still using the inline block.
I'm going to add more margin Bunim and I'm going to add or I can add a border.
You take a look we have a blue border.
So are going to go with the bottom and say border.
And we're almost done one pixels.
I want pixel solid and we can use this bluish color.
So dark and blue and the text for this one it's me at them here.
Whatever doesn't matter.
All right.
So we get it.
And if I click this I open a new tab.
I did it on purpose so he get the team very good.
So now the only thing left is going to be the carts and this one will be you know really really simple
not not at the heart.
There is a catch anyways and I'm going to tell you right now.
So you can be excited on the front for the next session so we can create an animation right here we'll
include that karst with the animation everything else.
Now the thing is that if the web page loads right here that animation happens in the bottom.
So whenever we reach here the animation will be done then we have done animation.
So we are now going to see animation.
So we're going to chain they react move to create the animations and we are going to use re-act reveal
as a callback to you know for years whenever we reach here Riak revealed will tell us to run to try
and function or run the animation and react move will do the animation.
So let's go to the next section and do the do the animation right here.