All right so like we use book before we need for re-act reveal to tell us or to communicate to the cartes
component that you know this section was revealed and we need to trigger the animation if you remember
with React move.
We have the state of show which is true or false.
So pretty much when the animation starts all with the page loads that show under-react move is going
to be false.
But when we reach here re-act reveal will change the state to true and the animation will trigger.
That's the logic.
So first I'm going to do this first.
OK.
I'm going to go right here and say import reveal right.
We need to use re-act reveal right here reveal.
And it's from.
And react react.
Dash reveal reveal.
Very good.
Now I'm going to reveal from Briac reveal.
So can I do this.
All right.
And now what do we need to do.
We need to wrap everything.
No.
This whole section inside this re-act reveal.
So I'm going to go right here and say reveal open and close ups open and close.
They're going to copy child this cut zcode we're going to remove it and put it inside of re-act real.
If I select everything right click for my selection it's going to make it a little bit better.
So now this reveal contains this on reveal property whenever this is happening we can trigger a function.
So I'm going to say on reveal just like this reveal equals to a function opening close and we will trigger
a different function you know kind of a callback.
So for now I'm going to say console log revealed so we can actually see it on the browser right here.
So let me go right here on the top and I'm going to go to cons. Now it is that we are not getting you
know this comes from blogs.
Maybe you can delete it later.
And if I scroll down as girl down there we go we get revealed.
Now the rebill appears whenever this part of the code you know the first part of the component rebuilds
to the screen.
So in addition of Henri reveal we have a different property that calls for action.
So this fraction it's from zero to 1.
So we can pass to a fraction.
How much of this component should be revealed on the screen in order for the you know re-act reveal
to trigger that on rebill callback.
So in this case I'm going to use 0.7 of course all of this is on the documentation so I'm going to try
again.
Going to go right here the top reload the application going to go below and you know it gave us the
bill pretty much after we have the whole component on the you are right on the screen.
So instead of doing a cons like what we will do will change the state.
So I got to say right now show equals false.
So whenever the application state is start starts show it's equal to false and right here what we do
we change that.
This data set stayed open close and then show it's equal to true.
So now whenever we called the to the component that it's going to be ruling this animation we will pass
the state of show which is false.
But when we get on reveal we will get the true and the animation will we'll run.
Makes sense right.
Perfect sense.
So now we don't have a component to rule this.
We don't really have it.
We have the file but we don't have anything else so let's create that one are going to create a react
class based component.
And this one open mistake.
Our classmates component.
And this one will be called home cards something like that.
Now in-home carts we will use will be using different things.
For example the money made from re-act move and that the D-3 ease.
So just because I'm lazy I'm going to go to Strypes inside feature and copy from here shortcut.
So easy pull out same thing and animate from re-act animate.
Now if you notice on the original we are using this thumbnail.
So we need to bring that player image.
So import and that player calls are to mehndi is a Argentinian player from the that for Slashdot that
for Slashdot or for Slash resources images just like this.
Then players for Slash and they believe it's the name of the player.
And then we got we get the image on this component for now this is good of course to create the animation.
We will need a state.
So I'm going at it right here and this show and this is one way to do it.
So this is going to be this that props because this component will be receiving some props and are going
to say there's the props that show now right here.
I didn't change the name of the class.
Sorry for that.
For now I'm going to return you know card whatever.
So this component is going to get a props which show which is true or false.
So this show will change to true or false.
And from misc No.
From meet the players we need to make a reference to this card.
We didn't include it on this component so I'm going to go right here.
Import and home cards from that forward slash and then cards home cards the name of the component.
OK.
So now we are including this so we need to make a reference on the actual code.
So we're going to go and say home cards and then close it.
If you remember we are we need to pass this show property.
You know we need to pass this props and it's this that state that show initially will be false but when
it changes we'll be receiving a prompt change.
OK.
Let's get we are we are on the good track.
So now what we need to do we need to return the actual animation.
If I go right here we get just card.
So I'm going to go at the bottom and create a function this that show.
You could put this with whatever name doesn't matter.
And he made cartes Kratz no cards right.
So now we'll create a function that will loop through all the cards or maybe through loop three times
because we need three or four cards and it will you know render some some component some elements.
So I'm using again parenthesis not curly braces and what we'll do we will loop through this that state
that cartes.
Right.
So how many cards do we need.
Let's check the fine one.
We have one two three and four.
So what do we need to do.
We will need to create a state with carts right here with an array of elements with four different elements
with different properties so I will create just four because we need four cards.
Now the animation the only thing we need to animate is still left at the bottom right.
This one is to you know bottom zero bottom 20 bottom know 40 and then 60.
So that's what we need to do.
So just from start we need a property with Bonham and then a property with a left right.
So the bottom for the first one in are going to do this right now.
Point out the bottom for the first one is going to be 90.
The second one is going to be three on the left 300 are going at the other ones Bunim 60 and bottom
left 200 something for the other ones.
So bottom 30 and then 100.
And then bottom zero and this is the first the first one.
Bottom zero and left zero.
Now what you can do.
You can create a function maybe a loop and just change the numbers dynamically you know plus 30 or minus
30 or something like that doesn't matter.
This is just one way to do it.
So right now I'm going to do.
I'm going to loop the cards not.
Cards and generally the animation with the with this property.
We kind of already did this with the animate move with the react.
So I'm going to enter this.
That state DOT carts just like this that map and this map will be returning just one card and the iteration
number.
And then of course we will run a function and return some GSX just like this.
All right.
Now this one will return an animate tag from from re-act move.
Animate opening close.
If you remember what we need to do is return a function.
So we open it close.
We will use some destructuring inside and then we will just returned the function with the actual elements
always do return open and close.
And this one will be just a def and we will come back to this later.
I'm going to say just dip for now.
Now the animate going to go right here at the top.
The Man-Made it's using a left and a Bunim And of course since we are looping something we need to add
key.
So we add key with the iteration with the index.
Right.
If you remember we are using show.
So we use this that props that show.
And this that prompts that show let's get in now.
Think about it.
There's no two uses.
OK.
So there's the props that show very good.
So now I'm going to go to start equals and we need to pass a prop..
The first one is left starts at zero.
The next one it's but him and it starts at zero.
Right.
OK.
And then we have an enter and the Enter would be where are going to go.
On this one we do have a left.
We do have a button on the left one is going to be whatever we get from the state on each iteration.
So it's going to be card that left the other one is going to be card dot right.
Oh sorry bought them.
And then since this one is the one that it's going to be doing the animation we need to add the timing
property so timing.
All right.
So we will need to add to duration and duration.
Half a second.
And the ease it's going to be Pawley.
Let me find it right here.
East Point out forget.
We're almost done.
Now we need to pass the left just like this.
And the bottom because these are the properties we are using for this element and right here we need
to pass this style opening close and the need to use the position we are going to change this to position
absolute.
That's why we're using the top and left and bottom left and bottom and absolute and we're going to use
the left coma and then the bottom and then said I'm going to go to our application and we can get it
you know I'm going to reload it.
And there we go.
So OK let me go back.
Oh goodness.
All right.
So we started very low.
There we go again.
Girls girls girls grow and then you can see the transmission right here.
Of course we didn't have a card.
That's going to be the next step creating a component of reusable components where we can you know create
a player cart.