Write so let's create the player cart.
So again we are going to use it I'm going to use the play cards inside of the team.
Same same same components.
So we're going to make it reusable component.
All right.
So I going to go here and go to you.
I create a new file player.
And then the card.
Yes.
This one is going to be a re-act stateless component.
Did it work.
Reacts the last component and it was like going to change the capital player card.
All right.
So this play your card and right now we're going to make a prefixed information is going to be always
this player on the 4 on four images if you want later you can fetch the players from the database and
just bring four and loop through the four players.
But for now I'm just going to have you know hard code the information.
So this player will be receiving this card will be receiving always some props with the name of the
player the number and everything else.
Right.
Makes sense.
So what it will be returning is going to be a class name with play your card and then wrapper.
All right.
So now we're going to look at that just like that's going to go to carts and from here I'm going to
import you know these components so import and it's going to be play your card from and then that for
Slash.
Oops.
Not that not three dots for us.
And it's you I for Slash play your cart right.
So since we have the player card we're going to go right here at the bottom and include it by the components.
That's what the thing to do.
Now of course we need to pass the props maybe later.
And actually we're going to do it on the team.
We're going to be rendering that card.
And from the server we will fetch a list of all the players.
So it's always the same component rendering different name different images and different number.
And of course we have the you know the position of the player but that comes from the database I can't
worry about that later.
So the player card receives a number which is in this case 30 whatever.
Doesn't matter the name which is going to be Nickolas and then the last name of the player.
And in this case.
Yeah.
There we go.
Then we have a background which is a background image that we're going to be using.
And if you remember we've imported that at the top right here.
So I'm going to put it right here.
So now this player card this component is reusable components will be getting all the props right here.
So now the only thing we need to do is just finish the template.
So I've got Dave opening close and am going to remove this.
We get to get a class name off and it's player card.
T t h him B for you know short thumbnail.
I got to put it right here.
So now a little bit prettier.
All right then we need to set the style for this with the background so background just like this is
going to be equal to we will use template strings and I'm going to use that you know a kind of a grayish
color.
It's not white.
You see it.
So the color it's a hash then EF 2 EF 9 and then f f.
All right.
And then of course we need to pass a u r l opening close.
We pass that Propst b c k we are passing from the parent component B C K opes b c k that will go.
So now at least we get the thumbnail.
All right.
It looks weird but you know it works.
It really works.
It is alive.
All right.
So at the bottom they've open it closed and we pass a class name of player card info.
Right.
Makes sense to cart the player info.
And on top we have the number of the player and at the bottom floating.
We have the player name.
So Dave opening close the class name its player card number and the number it's of course from prompts
we get from prompts Propst that number.
Next Dave open it close.
The class is now going to copy this class name.
It's going to be player card.
And then of course names just a name.
And we'll have have the name and the last name.
So we have two different props one with the name and one with the last name.
So we'll use two pants props that name.
And at the bottom we will use the last name.
So it's props.
That last name and that is when we are done with a player card.
So if I reloaded.
We are not getting it.
Maybe I made a mistake right here.
Let me just all check.
All right so for this it's name or no number.
You saw this and you say dude your mistake.
Well yeah I did.
All right.
So we got the name and the number.
Very good.
Of course it's always the same player.
But again just like I told before from this one you could make a network request functionalist up by
at least four different players random players.
And then you go fetch it from here just do a loop and look for different players or you can pass the
whole list of players.
You can do whatever you want right here.
I'm not going to spend a lot of time because this is not too important for this application.
We still need to do a lot of things on this app.
So but this one it's pretty much done on the next one we're going to start with this with a jersey.
So this is fun.
Again we have a transition really simple but then we have this.
So right here we will start using forms we will need to create a template for forms for form fields.
We will add symbolic Deshaun and we just show you for example if I type whatever at gmail dot com.
Does a matter I'm going to say and roll and we get a confirmation and then it goes away.
If I use a mail I've already already on the database you're going to say already on the database because
the database right here and promotions we have a list of all the users that you know registered for
the mailing list.
So again there's one looks simple but it's not that simple.
We need to do all that logic.
But after we do all the form fields all the logic and the reusable code for forms and everything else
we are going to be using them on the admin side of the page.
So this section it's really important for us.
So let's go let's go to the next one and do this.