OK so now we will create the wind and Jersey and the jersey animation and then we will create the n
roll impact with you know with a form.
OK.
So we're going to go back to our project and go back right here to our goat code and instead of home
of course we need new components in U.S. and then we call this promotion because of course it's to receive
promotional emails.
Kind of makes sense.
So inside promotion we will have pretty much two different components.
First it's going to be the index that we're going to have the animation container which contains the
top animation.
So just going to call it any mention of capital and a animation could be promotion animation makes a
little bit more sense.
But that's one.
And then of course we get the end roll.
So I'm going to say and roll that is first we will start from index.
So this one could be Chester react stateless component because you know the only thing we get into right
here is just make reference to the animation and the role so react statelets component are going to
change just to promotion and then promotion.
All right.
So the wrapper of this are going to wrap everything into a class promotion and then wrapper.
And I'm going to add some stylings and we're going to do it on the CSSA I'm going to do it just from
here style open and close and a background.
Monique Fix's style.
There we go.
It's a background of white just a black and white Nothing really special.
So one two three one two three.
Now everything is kind of centered so I will create a class name of container's same thing we did before
and it's sort of here of course we need to put the both components in a Jersey Jersey and the unrolls
so I going to go to the roll and the and roll which is just an animation.
We are not going to use react.
React.
Move.
I'm going to use just react reveals a very simple animation.
So we could do we had we could create a re-act stateless components.
I don't know just name two promotion animation not just animation because you know anything could be
an animation.
So we just return some you know some constants.
So we're now going to say animation as matter.
And of course this component this index the index of promotion.
It's not being included.
We're not including that.
So first I'm going to import this promotion animation from.
And of course animation and I make reference to this right here and there we go.
And now of course from the index of home we need to call this index of promotion.
So I'm going to go right here.
Import promotion from that forward slash.
And then we go to promotion.
All right.
Going to make reference to this.
There you go.
Promotion.
That and are going to go back to our application and we should be getting at least a minimum stake right
here when we don't check why import promotion from promotion.
Well this actually looks nice.
It's because I did it on the roll.
Sorry for that guys.
Got to close it.
You know we're getting calls all the old ones I've been mistaken that place all the code of the code
inside and roll.
So we get information that is good.
Get.
All right.
So now we need to start creating the animation and this one is going to be real simple.
We're going to use re-act reveal and I'm going to import soome from re-act reveal.
So re-act reveal and slash and then the name of what we're going to be using which is soome.
All right.
Now we will use an image of a jersey and everything isn't resourced so we have that image in resources.
So import levels like that and I get a call in jersey from that that force last one more time one more
time and then resources forward slash images for Slash and the jersey just like that.
OK.
So I'm going to read everything into a class name of promotion animation.
All right.
So we have two sides in this animation.
We have the left and we have the right so we have to get a container for both first one class name left
made this very simple.
And then of course the other one is going to be you guessed it the right one.
So right.
So in the left we will get some text you know when a jersey just like this.
So I gave the class and left.
Whenever we get a div and it's pen just like this of course we're going to get all the styling everything
it's on the CSSA So when a.
And below this we will put Jersey just like that me.
There you go.
Jersey.
All right.
They are very expensive so you know.
So can we get it with Jersey.
That's very good.
All right.
So what else I want to animate this with assumed fact.
So I'm going to go right here and we're just going to do this right now.
We will put some end in sight of the soome.
We will you know put everything else.
Let me go here.
Ryan going to go up.
OK.
There you go.
We get it when we go up again.
Scroll down and we get it you know really or the symbol of this moment.
Next is going to be the year right.
So they make this nice and again we will use assume.
So I'm just going to bring it right now.
So soome and instead of here we get that image.
So we will pass a div just a div with a style and a background.
Ryan real simple so open it close and we will say background.
It's going to be equal to.
And again template strings.
R l.
We use that jersey we imported the top Jersey and of course at no repeat.
Right.
And of course I made this already too gravidarum and make it at a position back you know just to get
the image right here.
You know the right size and everything else.
So let's try again.
If we lower the application and you know we get the same animation start again.
All right.
You know that's nice.
So now we're going to go to the next section and we will start doing all of this.
And this is not that simple.
It's not just an impact right.
We can it create a template for the inputs.
So we will add utility to you to the UI elements we will add a file that will rule all the inputs we
will need to add validation we will need to connect to the server check if the user is already on the
mailing list and to give a message if they are already already on the mailing list.
So again we need to do a lot of stuff.
So let's go to the next one and start this.