All right so let's create the input and everything else so everything is going to be on the inside and
roll.
So I'm going to go to and roll.
Let me just close some other things.
They have opened right here.
I don't need them.
They're just kind of in the way.
So anyway.
Not going to do you any more that it's done.
So I'm in the index of promotion.
I'm going to bring in roll.
Of course this one will be class based component.
We need to use the state to you know to work with the actual input.
So it's going to be a controlled component.
So re-act stateless sart react class based components Burguet so I'm going to call and roll that is
get it now from here we will of course import some other things.
But for now I'm just going to import fade from Briac reveal we're going to use that fading effect.
So re-act reveal and of course for Slash and inmate in the name of the effect.
Right.
And is the first thing now instead of here what we will do we will create of course the title everything
else.
But the input needs to be controlled so we need a state to control everything through state and what
we will create.
If you maybe you come from a different course with me we will create a file that will render all the
inputs that we have inside state.
We have declared insights state don't worry if it does confuse you.
You know don't worry they're going to do everything is step by step.
So first thing going to create a state now inside the state we will have all the logic of the form.
So first I want to store.
We have our forms so form error.
So it's going to start as follows.
That's the first thing.
Then of course if we get success if the form gets you know submitted and everything goes OK.
We have a message so form success for now is going to be empty when the applications start.
Then we need a place where we or are we going to be stored all the elements of the four.
Right now we just have one but we could have maybe a name a password or something else.
So inside the key form data form just like this and then data will have all the inputs that we need
in this case we just need one.
So it's going to be called email and the name it's really important if your input it's email.
This should be e-mail.
If it's a name it should be name.
So this is like the name of the input inside a email right.
Same thing.
So I'm going to open it close now instead of this email we'll pass a bunch of attributes a bunch of
key value pairs.
We need to generate this input.
So the first one is going to be with what kind of elements we get you know we want to get.
So it's going to be element and the name for this is just a name pre-text right.
OK.
So then of course that element has a value.
And when the application starts it's going to be empty.
So we get an empty value.
Now each each element could get a configuration you know when you create an input you need to give it
a name maybe a placeholder and maybe it type well inside config begin to store all this configuration.
So the name again is just like the H Tim L name when you create an input NHT mail.
So email input.
That's the kind of the name of this type.
Well it is an input but it's not typed text.
It's going to be a type of e-mail.
All right then we're going to add a place holder just like this.
And it's going to be Enter make it right.
Enter your e-mail.
All right.
And that is it for now.
Of course we will need to add some validation.
So of course I'm going to create a place where we're going to be hosting our validations.
So this one whenever we submit it needs to be required.
We cannot submit something if you know if we have an empty value.
So it's going to be required and then we just pass a boolean and there's one.
Now what else we're going to be checking if this one it is an email.
So if we do have true or validation it's going to check that we have a valid e-mail you know regular
validation and HMO.
So Como and I are going to go below the validation and we can add an attribute saying that it's valid.
So whenever the application starts we don't really have a value.
So it's going to start as false it's not valid.
All right.
And of course after we do some checking before we submit the server we're going to change changes to
it.
True.
All right.
And of course if we get an error message from validation I'm going to add one more.
So it's going to be called a validation message.
And again the Whenever the application starts starts empty.
So what is the point of doing all of this now inside of the render will start creating all this you
know its template and the input.
And we weren't going to pass.
We're going to create reusable component and we're going to be passing this data.
So that component will read this and it will return an input with everything we need.
That is the idea.
And later maybe.
And we're going to be using it later when when we create the admin section of the of the web page we're
going to use that form data file that we use eval component.
All right.
So I'm going to go to the render and I'm going to start doing everything now.
Again if you notice on the original one who might just show you if we scroll down we get this and we
get a fading effect effect.
So I'm going to wrap everything inside faced the same fate we have right here on the top right.
So inside of here of course we need to add some HDMI mail.
So the device is going to be a class name of and roll just like this and roll wrapper.
Sense.
Then of course we do have form.
So I'm going to create a form.
Now whenever we submit a form we need to call to a function to access this just like this and of course
whenever the form gets submitted we need to run a function and pass the event.
So I'm going to say event and we didn't have a function.
I'm going to create right now and we are not going to do anything right now.
So I'm going to call it MIT and then form and what we will do we will pass the event of you know submitting
a form.
We don't have this function going to go right here and say submit for opening close so we can skip any
messages.
All right.
Let's get we are on the good track right now.
Of course we have a title so we'll create a div just a div with a class name and roll title and it's
going to be enter your e-mail.
All right.
So then I will create the container of the you know the actual input and this one will be a class of
class name and then end roll input.
All right.
OK so now what we can do.
Let me see what we get so far in Reloaded.
And of course we get nothing because we need to include add.
Sorry for that.
Import and roll from that for Slash and roll.
And now of course make reference to this.
All right.
So that's what you get.
Enter your email.
OK.
So now right here the bottom we should be getting an input right a form field but of course how can
we create it.
We need to create that use reusable component so I'm going to go to you I'm going to create a new file
called form fields that jazz.
So this form fields is just going to be a stateless component component just though it's going to be
we're going to be returning just to function and that function we will do some checking and return some
GSX.
That is the idea.
So I'm going to say import re-act from Briac because we need to return's GSX right.
So I'm going to create a function Konst form field just like this form field equals we will receive
some props.
And then of course we will do some checking and at the very end we will be returning you know some GSX
so I'm going to open and close and pass it off and say I don't know form for now Porterfield frigate.
So now the Konst forum feel we're going to be exporting this export default form field.
So again it's just a re-act stateless component.
So I'm going to go back to enroll and of course import form fields.
So import and I believe I call this form fields.
Right now I believe so.
I'm notcher from feel so from Dad forward slash slash.
Then one more and you I and then form feels very good.
So now if I make a reference to Ford Field right here just like this we should be getting that form
field text and we do we get it.
So that is get now this form fill we will pass to this to this component.
The information we have for this input for e-mail and this form field will check what kind of input
we have the old configuration and it will return an input with all this you know information.
Now we might have many types of inputs.
So this form field will be deciding what kind of you know component or input will be returning.
Right now we just have one bit on the future.
We can add much more or so inside in our Roll we need to pass everything as props all the other what
form fill needs to create that form.
All right.
So inside for IFILL We will start passing all the props.
So I'm going to make some space some room right here and we're going to be passing an A and A D.
So the ID is the name of the the name of the actual input.
So we call it email then we need to pass the form data.
So I'm going to say form data just like this equals.
Does that state that form data that e-mail or at.
And then we have a change property.
We're going to maybe do it later.
That's fine for now.
So now this form if you will be receiving an ID with e-mail which is the name of the key right here
and then the four data inside.
All right.
I'm going to go back to form fields now inside form fields.
We will have a template and then we will return this template so we're going to do this and create a
function called render and then template.
We didn't have this function.
So I'm going to copy the name of the function and I will you know create the function right now.
Konst render template.
Open and close and then of course we will do something right here and it's Kunst.
All right.
So now whenever we start we make a reference to this we have a template and the template starts empty.
So that form template equals no equals to nothing.
So if we get a mistake or something is wrong at the end will return nothing.
Instead of you know maybe just some array I'm T-Ray or something like that.
Just nothing.
All right.
And then what we will do we will add a switch and the switch will we will will check what kind of input
we have in email.
You know if it's a simple text or it's a text area or user selects or whatever doesn't matter.
So I'm going to add a switch open and close just like this with the form data.
Remember we have a form data at the top.
Oh I didn't do this search for this we are passing props from that to this component.
So we are right now getting IDM form data.
So I will use destructuring instead of the keyword prompts.
Right.
Just like with it before.
So with the form data just like this and the actual ID.
So now if I do switch I can pass form data dot and element.
So if I go back to one roll we know that the form data element it's input.
All right.
So where we will be checking it what kind of input we are getting from this form elements.
Right.
So Romulo here open it cause it's a switch just a Gudel switch.
So if the form temp is the case.
Sorry if the case the case is impaired just like this.
We will return something.
And of course we need to add a break.
This is just a switch so we need to have a break.
If you're at a break we will have a sign that something is going to break for us.
And then at the end we have a default and we would just return the form template going to say that the
form template that we have at the top it's still null and default.
There we go.
And that is it.
So if we don't have a case we are not matching in case the default is still the form template input
and at the very very end of this function we just return the form template.
Just like this.
So if we have no match the template is going to be null.
So this whole function will be will be returning nothing nothing at all.
All right.
So if we do have a match in the case if it's an input and we do have a match right here with input what
we will be returning is a form template with some you know some code inside.
So I'm going to say form template equals and I'm going to open and close and right here is just some
S.J. insects right here.
We will return an input weird something whatever.
All right.
So now in theory if I go to our application we get that input with something.
So we do have a match and right now we need to return an input text.
All right.
So I'm going to go right here.
Dave going into this.
And inside of the div. What do we need to do is to send back an input input.
Right.
Of course with the input we have a lot of configuration.
First if you remember inside of the input config we have the name the type and the placeholder.
So right from the start we could do dot dot dot form data access that form data and then pass the config
and everything will be passed.
As you know a regular attack of the impact.
So if I check out the Riego we get the e-mail.
Let me do an inspect right here.
Inspect there go.
So let me make it a little bit bigger so we get that name which is the one we have on the confect the
type again same on the confect and the placeholder.
And now what we can do for example if you have a different form we just include form fields.
We just copy this or we pass it to the other components and then just include the form fields and there's
no need to create the input and do all the logic.
Every time you want to add an input you just create the state and that's it.
Good idea.
All right.
Of course every input has a value.
So again to add value opening close and I'm going to say this one it's the form data that value right.
Of course whenever the application starts the value is going to be empty.
Right so now let me just close as for now.
Whenever we change we type something inside of the input nothing happens.
I'm typing and nothing happens.
And this is because we need to trigger a function that the text the onchange on the input.
And it will update the state of this email.
Since we are passing the value right here whenever this component updates.
You know this is State updates we will be passing a value right here and the form field will return
a value right here.
So we will see the Chaser's right here.
So let's go to the next section because this one went too long already and start you know adding what's
next on this component.