All right so let's go to all the logic of our updating form.
Because right now if you type something.
Nothing gets updated.
All right.
So now whenever we type something we want to trigger a function right here so we can update this estate
with the value.
That's we want to do so of course as you know whenever we attach an onchange function on the input we
can know what the user is typing.
So I'm going to go right here and create a function called on change.
All right.
So this change takes an event.
And of course it runs a function.
We don't have a function so far.
So for now I'm just going to save this and I'm going to go back to n roll.
And of course nothing is going to work with that.
So inside the form field we will you know lead the application know what is the function we want to
run to update the state.
So I'm going to call.
I'm going to pass a prop with the key word change.
Now this change of course we will we will we will it will be receiving an event you know the event we
are passing right here is going to get received by this change.
So instead of a band I'm going to call it element and again explain you why in a minute.
So whenever we trigger this function this change of function what we want to do we want to run a function
called update form and we didn't have this function.
We will create it.
This will create the function in a minute.
And of course we will grab that element that will be passed from here which is the actual event and
we will pass that element to the update for.
We don't have this function.
I'm going to put it right here and say that we want to update a form.
All.
So now again we are not passing anything whenever we trigger this function from form fields.
Nothing is going to happen.
All right.
So what are we going to be doing.
We're going to be triggering this change function and we're going to pass two things we need to pass
two things.
I'm going to pass an object with the event we are getting right here.
And in addition I'm going to pass the ID of the element.
Remember that right here at the top we are passing we are receiving this prompt the ID of the elements
because whenever we trigger this update form we need to know what form field with which element on the
form data we want to update.
For example if you had another one right here called Name another input what how would the application
is going to know which one needs to update the email or the name.
So that's why we are passing an object with the event and the e-mail.
All right let's go below.
So again we we go to this function if we go to the update form.
It's going to be receiving the event and the ID.
All right.
So inside update form of course we don't have we don't have any logic so far so we can get at it right
now.
So on the update form we we will be receiving an element just like this.
So if I cancel log the element just like this.
Of course we should be getting something.
So let me reload the application.
And change is not defined so I might call a change the update form just let me make sure are up of course
right here at the top on the form fields are not bringing the change prop so change.
There we go.
So now it should be working.
So I'm going to bring the console and on the console if I type something you know we get the actual
event and the name and the ID of the impot where we are typing something.
So now from within the event we can get the value or the the characters that the user is typing begin
to do that.
OK so I'm going to go back to enroll.
Going into this and we're going to start doing all of this logic.
So what do we need to do.
We need to create a copy of this form data.
Remember it's not good to know mutate the state directly.
So I'm going to create a viable Konst new form data just like this form data that it's equal and I'm
going to do it just like this because right here we have form data not in camel case.
So from data.
So this one is going to be equal to a copy of whatever we have inside form data.
So I'm going to say that that Dudd this that state that form data.
All right so now we have a copy of this.
So all the changes that we're going to do right now we're going to do it on this copy and at the very
end this form data it will be equal to this form data.
So then we will update the whole state.
Right.
So then we need to make a copy of the elements so we can mutate that elements.
So Konst new element equals to open and close and then we do that that new form data that we can grab.
Always that copy right now and we copy inside of here the elements in this case is going to be e-mail.
So how can we copy the elements.
Remember that inside elements we're getting the idea.
So I'm going to go right here and say element that ID.
So now inside new element we will get a copy of this state of this email state.
Right.
So now of course inside element we have the event if you remember and inside the event we have the value
and you know the characters that the user is inputting inside the input.
So I'm going to access new element just like this new element dot and I'm going to enter the value.
I'm going to enter this value and I'm going to say that this value is equal to Element dot target dot
of sorry elements an event that target just like this that value.
So after we do this this new element will contain the value that the user is typing right here.
All right.
That's the first step.
Then of course we will add some validation but we will do it on maybe on the next video.
So OK so now what we have is the new element with all the new values when we need to update right now.
So what we will do we will get this new elements and we will update new form data.
So I'm going to grab you for form data just like this new form data.
Sorry.
Square as core brackets and are going to access the element Id just like with it right here.
And we're going to said that the new front data elements Id just email it's equal to new elements.
So now we are pretty much updating this new form data Barville the state of this era and at the very
end the only thing we need to do right now since we have the new state of e-mail we get to set this
state and update this state and of course since this is the main state it will be reflected right here.
All right.
So we're going to say this.
That said state opening close and I'm going to say that form data now now the new state of form data
it's called new form data.
All right get out I'm going to close it.
So I'm going to reload the application and if I type something now we get the value.
So everything is here.
So this f f f is going to be de-value right now inside the actual state.
So much much later when we submit a form we will have a value on this estate.
We will evaluate what whenever we have informed data and we will make the request.
Of course we do have some validation and we need to change this valid to true.
If we do have a valid value.
Right now this is not valid.
This is an email so we can not submit this.
We need to add some validation right.
So to add some validation to this.
OK so let's add some validation.
So again the validation is something that we're going to be using on different forms different sections
so it can have it's May is a good idea to create a reusable component.
Or maybe it's just a global function where we can you know check if the input is valid.
So we have validation right here.
We will come to a function.
It will check the validation and it's going to check if it's if it's required.
You know if it devalues not empty and if the if we have e-mail it's going to check if the value is a
valid e-mail.
But it's the whole idea.
Very very simple just to function.
So inside you I am going to store everything inside mints this time it's a mistake.
Since this mistake we will have a function called validate and we will pass it through there.
So for now it's going to go right here at the bottom and say export then Konst and then validate and
it's going to be equal to something.
And then of course we will return something right.
Very just to function.
So now I'm going to go to enroll now will you call this validate function so we can use it.
So import opening close then validate
that for flash that that force slashed at that 4 slash you I for Slash and then misc.
All right.
So now we can use this date function.
So how are we going to use it.
Okay.
Very simple.
I'm going to go right here.
The bottom and after we update the new state of the elements are going to you know pass through the
actual validation.
All right.
So it seems we have the new value inside this new elements before we update the state.
What I can do I can create a variable called valid data.
You can call this whatever you want doesn't matter and that's valid data will be true or false.
Or maybe an array or maybe something this one will host you know the data that says if the element is
valid or not valid or if we have an error message.
All right.
So I'm going to call this function and I will be passing all the values we have inside new elements.
That's why we did it on a different variable.
There are many ways to do this right now and this project we're going to do it this way on the next
one we're going to change some things.
It's going to get a little bit easier.
All right.
So today it's going to be returnable the data will be equal to whatever we get back from validate.
So now if I do console log opening close valid data and I type something let me bring the console.
There you go.
I type something we get of course undefined because this function this misc function is not returning
anything.
Right now we can add some things now from and roll whenever we call the bonneted function.
We are passing the new element with the file with the updated value.
So if I go to validate this one will be receiving an element.
All right.
Now this element contains all the data we have of that elements in this case.
All of this.
So what we need to check is the validation what which validation rules we have for this one and we will
be accessing the value right.
All right.
So we have validation and value.
I going to go back to Ms.
I'm going to create a viable called error.
So at the end if the input it's valid we will return an array because this array will be containing
what we're saying if the input is true which is this which is valid or false if it's not valid and the
second argument the second position is going to be a message we're going to be adding a message must
be a valid email.
Please enter a valid email or you know something like that.
So the first position will be true which is you know if it's true valid or false.
So by default it's true that it's the default.
And then I get a pass an empty an empty message.
So of course there's no match with the with the elements and with the form fields we have right here
with this read there's no match we'd require or e-mail.
We will assume that the e-mail that this impot this element needs no validation at all.
That's why we are returning that the input is valid.
True and no error message.
Now of course if we have validation we need to do it.
So first we're going to do e-mail I'm sorry we're going to do require we're going to check if the value
it's empty or not.
All right.
So we're going to go right here and this is going to be very simple.
We're going to enter elements OK.
Then we enter validation just like this and then dot and we check if they're required it's equal to
true.
So if it's equal to true we will run some code and we will modify this error this arrival if we really
need.
All right.
So I'm going to say Konst ballot equals and I need to trim whatever value I have inside elements I'm
going to say element that value that trim.
And this is not reacting to standard javascript.
I'm going to trim it and I'm going to evaluate if this value is equal to nothing.
Of course this will return true or false if it's empty will return.
You know it's true if not false or they're going to say Kunst in a say message equals and we will be
adding a message if ballot it's false.
Of course if it's empty it's false if not empty is true.
So if we do have a message I'm going to I'm going to return just to string just a text so I'm going
to be adding some template strings right here.
I'm going to say if ballot it's equal to false.
Notice I'm using this at the beginning.
You're going to return a message just like this.
If not we are not going to return anything.
Just an empty string.
But right now I'm going to say this field is required.
You know very simple message doesn't matter.
And at the end after we do all this logic about it it's going to be true by default or false and message
is going to be equal to a message or an empty string.
No this message or an empty string.
So when we return it's the actual error right here.
So going to say return.
So are you going to say error.
It's equal to.
And if it's not bounded we will append an array will change it to an array would be valid we have right
here which is true or false.
And the I'm sorry in this case falls because we are doing a check right here and the actual message
that we get.
If the element is not valid.
If not or is it still going to be equal to error.
The default which is true and empty.
And this at the end at the very end we just return the error.
It does get looks nice.
So now I'm going to go back to n roll and write here we are updating the violent data so Barlett data
you go.
Well let's see what you get really made a mistake right here.
Ms error is not the find.
That is my mistake or rather there we go.
All right.
So I'm going to go right here and if I type something we get true and we get empty.
And that is good because we have what caracter.
It's it's not empty.
Now if I delete it we get falls and this field is required.
So now we have an array saying telling us that the input if it's false if it's valid or not and if we
do have an error message.
So we have an array inside of this and rollbar all this valid data.
So now what we need to do is we need to update the state.
Remember right here we have a ballot and we have a validation message.
So we need to convert this at this.
The keys and values to the actual form data.
So since I have it inside valid data right here the array I'm going to delete this and I to say OK.
So new elements dot valid is going to be equal to whatever I get from valid data and the precision number
zero of that array which is true or false.
And the validation message same thing new elements dot and a have it right here on the day the message
is going to be equal to whatever I get from ballasted data and the position number 1 which is the actual
message or empty.
Right.
Makes sense.
So now of course if I can slog console log new form data and from data that is get when me type something
and I inspect this email elements we get that the devalue it says it's valid.
True.
And the validation message is nothing.
If I delete it inside the state of e-mail we get an error message validation message and valid false.
So now what we can do whenever the application renders with this date with the latest state we can check
if we do have a validation message display the message.
And then of course later when we submit the form if the is input it's valid for us.
We will not do anything and we will update.
We will actually show a different message or maybe you know something else we will not submit the form
because the element is false.
All right so let's add this validation message.