All right so now we have the required validation.
But we have one more which is the email validation right.
So we need to add it to Misc..
And you know at the validation.
So I'm going to do this before because that requires connection can it can in global.
And the e-mail it's a little bit more specific.
So we're going to do that validation first.
So we do pretty much the same thing if we do have an NLM element that validation that email.
We will do something.
Now I will add as a resource just a javascript file with a regular expression a regular expression is
going to be using to check the email so you can get it from there or you can just go to the web and
find directx for a validation email.
This one is really really simple.
You have another and you have other publications with regular expressions.
They are much much longer.
This is one it's really simple.
So again we are just testing the element that value to check if we had we have a.
Real simple.
And then of course we will add a message so we can say Konst message equals and we use template strings.
Same thing with it right here so I get a copy of this and they're going to paste it right here.
So if the element of course is not valid we have an error.
This is going to be this or maybe MUST MUST be a valid email get the end of course just like the other
one I'm going to copy this and I'm going to paste them here.
If it's not valid Google returns about it and the error message if not error.
Very good.
Right.
So we are pretty much done.
Real simple real simple.
So now we can check right here.
If we do have an e-mail so I'm going to type something and we can to get the must be a valid email.
And of course about it false if I add an e-mail and say gmail dot com whatever.
And check the state of this.
Everything is going to be valid true.
And we have no validation message.
Very very simple.
Now of course what we need to do now is we need a way to render that error message.
Of course if the empire is not valid you know kind of makes sense why why are we doing all this.
So OK so we're going to go back to n roll.
So and roll will have a key you know form data e-mail each input will have a validation message and
we are passing all of this data whenever we render the form feel.
So this from will be receiving.
If the elements it's valid or not and it will be getting that error message if we do have an error message.
So what we can do we can catch it here and render the error message display the message below the input
or not of course.
So I'm going to go here at the bottom and it create a function called show error and it's just a function
just a function.
All right of course we don't have this function we need to create to write here.
So I'm going to go right here to the top before render a template and I'm going to say cons cons or
egos and show error.
All right.
Same same name of function.
Very good.
So no this is just going to be a function.
And at the end what we will be returning is same thing that is just a template with another message.
So I'm going to say let error and then message something like that.
You can choose whenever you want doesn't matter.
So this one is going to be a div just a div and I'm going to add a class name so class name and it will
be error level.
Now instead of here we need to return an error message.
If we do have an error message so I'm going to be attaching some code and some validation you know some
check before we add an actual message.
So I'm going to access form data dot and I'm going to access validation.
So if on this import this form data this element we have some validation then OK this is going to go
true.
So we move forward but I also want to check if the form data it's not valid.
So if form data is not valid then I want to you know display that error message.
Of course if we are the elements it is valid and it has validation doesn't matter.
We are not going to return anything very simple just logic.
So what we would do well we'll be returning is deformed data dot and whatever validation message we
get right here on the state of the actual elements right here.
So I'm going to copy the names so I don't have to type everything and that's it.
So at the end of the function the only thing we're going to be returning is return and then error message.
Right.
All right.
So let let's see how it goes.
So all right I'm going to type something and go away.
Maybe type it and delete it.
This field is required.
Of course we're going to do some things to clear if we hold out.
You know we go outside the input and everything else doesn't matter right now.
So the most important thing is that we are getting the error message.
We don't have a valid email.
All right.
And if I add a valid e-mail gmail dot com something like that doesn't matter.
Dot com the error goes away.
So we are on the good track right here.
All right.
So what else we still need to do a lot of things.
What happens if we try to submit the form.
We need a way to loop through all the unroll elements that make sure that they are valid and that we
do have a value.
And then of course we need to send the e-mail to the database store the e-mail to the database.
But for what it's going to be doing is going to be looping through all the elements we have right here
and form data.
We'll be rechecking if they are valid and they are good to go and if they good to go of course we can
create a new object with just a key value pair you know email and the name because we can not submit
all of this to the server.
We just need to submit the key value pair ride.
The usual way.
The normal way.
OK.
So of course I'm going to be adding a button right here at the bottom because we don't we have so far.
So I'm going to go and say button and of course this well this one B and roll or something like that.
And of course we need to attach a known click event listener so open and close.
And of course we pass the event and then we run a function which is the same function we have right
here pretty much the same thing.
All right.
So now whenever we click on the button we will try to submit the form.
Right so we got the roll.
So if I click on the button the page is going to reload.
And this is you know the usual how would the forms work and in h d m l b click it and we go to the server.
So make a request so the page loads but I don't want this I don't want this behavior I don't want this
to happen.
Of course since we have the event we can block it.
Usual HDMI out.
OK.
So on the submit form of course we will be receiving an event just like this.
And I'm going to say event and I'm going to do the famous prevent default just like this.
We all know this.
Of course we will be doing at the end is just submitting an object with a key and a value right.
So I'm going to create a function I'm sorry a barbel that is going to be hosting this data to submit.
Pretty clear.
And this is going to start as an empty object then I'm going to create a new Marvel called form is valid.
So this one is going to be true or false.
So at the beginning before we start checking the Farmall it's going to be true so I will we will assume
that all the inputs are valid right now.
So now what I need to do.
I need to go through all of the elements inside form data and check if they have a value.
I'm sorry if they are valid.
True.
That's the one thing we need to do because if they are valid true they are good to go.
They are good to be part of data to submit if not of course everything fails.
So I going to create a 4 because right now we have one.
But in the future we will have maybe more.
So it's a good idea to create a 4.
They're going to say let key in and we want to loop the state does not state that form data.
All right.
So instead of here what I want to do on every loop inside of data to submit.
I'm going to add this.
I'm going to say data to submit equals.
Sorry date of mid and the name of the key.
So on each loop of this data form data I'm going to grab the key in this case it's email and I'm going
to push a new value to the data to submit chess with the key.
And then of course that key has a value and the value is going to be this that state that form data
whatever key we are looping.
And then of course the value.
Right.
So at the end.
And let me again show you console log data to see if I made this because maybe you're not used to do
it do something like this even if you have more experience you know what can happen right here.
So I'm going to type.
I don't know just an email whatever.
And if I click it and roll we are looping to the state of data we are creating a key with the same name
of the key we have right here.
This one e-mail and we are pushing the value of whatever we have inside to that key as way out and we
get e-mail and Francis we had a name is going to be name and whatever value we have a name a last name
whatever value we have on last name and this ultimately is going to it's going to be what it's going
to go to the server.
Now if I delete this and I click it we get an empty space so this one should be false.
So we need an additional check right here right now.
The only thing we are doing is you know putting the value inside data.
I the key data it's the key and the value part.
But we need to do one more check.
We need to check if the form is valid because later we're going to check if this is true or false.
So I'm going to say form is valid.
Going to make a reference to this to this viral and are going to change it to False.
If the element it's not true.
So this that state that formed data that key to access to key and are going to check if that element
is valid.
All right.
This one you know we're going to get an error maybe later.
What if we have more inputs more elements right here because if we just check for this maybe on the
next iteration it's going to change.
But this one is not going to change it's going to be true and we could have the previous one could be
false.
So it's always a good idea to check if this element is valid and if the form is still valid.
So I'm going to say and form is valid.
All right.
So either way we are going to still get data to submit.
But before we submit anything we're going to be asking the application and I'm going to do a Nel's right
here.
Let's open and close.
We're going to check if the form is valid.
So if the form is valid we want to cancel log data to submit.
If not I'm going to do console log no error or something like that.
So let's try again it go at the bottom go can we go at the bottom and go you know put a valid email
going to enroll and we get the e-mail and the key value pairs.
So we are good to go.
What happens if I delete everything I can to enroll again and we get our set you know that works.
All right.
No we're good.
So now at the top if I go back to the state we have two elements right here the form error and then
of course begin to do for success.
So if we do have a form error we have a form error.
We're going to change it to true.
And at the bottom we will display an error message.
So we're right here if we have an error going to say this is this.
That said state opening close just like this and then form error.
And there's one going to be changing this to true and at the Bunim before before the button are going
to add some you know some error message.
So if we do have a does that state DOT form error ups or in error that form error and this is true what
we want to do we want to display a div with an error message.
If not we are not going to do anything.
Not at all.
You're not going to buy anything.
So this and then make this a little bit prettier div will have a class name of pro-level just like before.
Error level.
And I'm going to say something is some thing is wrong.
Try again.
Right.
All right.
That's right.
Now of course have submit we get something is wrong.
Try it.
Now it's time to start typing.
We're going to get to our message.
Something's wrong.
Try again.
It must be an e-mail e-mail.
So this comes from the validation.
And this one is the error form.
So we need a way to clear that form error to clear this whenever we start typing again.
So this is really simple.
I'm going to delete the form data right here and the only thing we need to do is to set state form error
back to false.
Whenever we turn new values false that is it.
Well let's try again and go with it and roll.
Something is wrong.
And if I type something we just get the validation error message.
All right.
So that is good.
Now what happens if we put no valid email name roll we submit the form.
What happens after we submit the form.
We should be getting a success or a message.
And of course we should be clearing this impot you know this email impot.
So let's do that right now.