All right so if you're able to place this e-mail this user on the database on the Frisbee race database
I want to display a success message and clear the impot So we're going to do that right now.
So the bottom just going to go right ahead and create a div just a div with a class name just like this
with success just like this success and then underscore all this court level and instead of here I will
put whatever message we get from this state state DOT and then form success just like this.
Remember at the top we have a forum success with an empty value.
Of course the application if we save it will reload and of course we get nothing because success equals
nothing.
All right.
Now of course if we are able to submit the form because that date and the form is valid at the end we
will run a function that will clear all this out.
So I'm going to say this dot and I'm going to call it reset form success.
All right.
We don't have this function we can create right now.
So I'm going to go right here and reset for them success.
So this function will be pretty straightforward.
The only thing we're going to do just like we did with the update we're going to copy a make a copy
of new form data reset everything back to zero and you know update distinct risible.
So I'm going to copy this one just you know get a copy.
OK.
So now we have a copy of form data.
So what we will do we will loop all the elements inside form data and we will set the value to nothing
devolved to false and we will clear the pollination message.
Right.
Makes sense.
So on the 4.
Just like before.
Let key in and we loop the new form data I can access new form data whatever key we are in inside the
loop and then are going to access value and set it to nothing.
Right.
I'm going to copy this one because you know it's pretty much like and valid and valid instead of nothing
is going to be false.
So we are just resetting everything back to zero going to copy this one and this one it's going to be
validation message and this one will be equal to nothing.
So now inside you form data we have the new state with everything out right.
So what we would do we will this.
That said state opening close and to do this we will grab that form error we have and we will just make
sure that it's equal to false right the form data it's equal to the new form data.
And then remember that we have a success a form success message right here at the top.
So what we will do we will make a reference to that form success and I'm going to say congratulations.
We're going to do a little bit more later on this one because we have a different case but for now this
one will work can grab two lessons.
Right.
So let's see this.
Oh congratulations.
Right.
So I'm going to go over here but I'm going to add whatever and roll and we get congratulations and we
are able to clear you know the state of this know what we need to do is to clear this congratulations.
We need to remove it.
So at the end of this I will just create a different function so this that success message or could
be you know clear success message or something like that.
I'm just going to call it like this doesn't matter.
And the success message we will read and run a time out to clear everything.
So OK.
Real simple.
So we'll do a set.
Time out.
Open and close we will run just to function and it will run after maybe two seconds and the only thing
that this one is going to do is does not said state opening close and we will change form success.
Back to nothing.
Make sense.
So let's try again and go to the bottom whatever e-mail you're going to do and roll.
Congratulations.
And it goes away.
So everything works.
Now later when we make this request we're going to do that right now when we make this request firebase.
All right.
If the user it's already on the database we need to return back from the server with an error.
You know the user is already on the database.
So on this forum success instead of showing congratulations.
We will show already on the database if the user it's already on the database.
So we're going to do that.
So right now there is one thing missing.
What is missing is this cause a locked data to submit.
Instead of doing this we will be adding this to database so let's do that right now.
So if we go to firebase to the database everything right here we're going to see something that says
promotions.
Now inside promotions of course we have many users.
We've added a few with France's different variations on the delete some of them.
It you know sometimes the database whenever we make actions right here it's a little bit slow when you
know it's free.
So I'm going to leave this Francis at gmail can handle this one.
And I'm going to I can really just eat just Francis can delete everything else.
So I'm done.
Yeah.
Yeah I went to the lead and I went to this one well as well.
So the only email the only guy we have on this e-mail list and the promotions it's friends is at gmail
that the only email that we have.
Now let's go back to our project and we need to go to firebase you know to that firebase file we have
right here and bring that table you know that document right here the promotions.
So OK so first going to go right here at the bottom and then will create again just like we did with
mattress of Barville to host the promotions.
So Konst then fire base promotions equals to firebase D.B and the RAF opening close promotions.
So this name equals to this name right.
If you make a mistake right here nothing is going to work.
OK.
So now we have a viral that enters that database.
So of course I'm going to export it.
OK.
So I'm going to go back to enroll.
And we need to import this of firebase.
Ryan makes sense.
So I'm going to go at the top and say import and I believe it was called foreign based promotions.
I have sometimes I have memory problems comes with the job.
From that that forward slash them for Slash.
One more and then firebase right.
So now we can use Farnaby's promotion to promotions to make requests.
Very good.
I get to go at the bottom wherever we have the form is when they're going to come in this one.
And you know this one.
All right.
So we need to do two things.
The first request is going to be checking if the user it's already on the database so we can enter promotions
and begin to try to match the e-mail that the user is entering right here right here.
And check if the user it's on the database if it is we're going to do something.
And if it's not going to do something else.
All right.
So I'm going to go right here and say OK first make a reference to fire based promotions.
So how can we check if the e-mail is equal to something.
First we need to or there or the information by child so we use the order by child method that you know
this is this comes from Firebrace and we say that we want to search by the email key later we're going
to get some error message some warnings actually.
And later much later I'm going to tell you how to fix it.
Resample.
So first we are the right e-mail ones we order by e-mail.
We say that we want to find the one that it's equal to.
And remember that we have data to submit that e-mail.
Then we use that once and we save value.
And then of course this will return to promises on the Close's will return a promise.
So what we can do we can do then.
And if you remember we receive a snapshot.
So let me bring a snapshot right here.
And then of course we can run a function right.
Kind of makes sense again.
All right.
So right here we will receive this snapshot.
So I'm going to say snapshot dot Bell and I'm going to cancel so we can see what we get from the server
console log and then snapshot how Burguet.
So let's go back so fight type Frances remember ribaldry have Francis Jamail on this database.
I'm going to put it right here.
I'm going to enroll.
And the response is going to be this one right.
We can it we can get it.
So let me try again.
Let me update this right sorry for that.
It's a little bit slow.
So OK so we go back.
So I make this request.
I'm ordering my child and I'm bringing whatever result I can get back on the database that matches Francis
at gmail dot com and of course we are getting our response.
We are getting this ID and e-mail Francis So we are finding a match.
So what happens if I type something else whatever.
And Gmail overcome doesn't matter.
I'm going to enroll in what we get is no because that e-mail this e-mail doesn't exist on the database.
So what we can do right here instead of doing of course cancer look what we can do we can do and if
we choose if and else and if the value it's no it means that you know it's not in the database.
So we can push it to the database but if we get something different to Noul we're going to do something
else.
So.
OK.
So right here I'm going to say if SNOP short short sorry song and copy.
So snapshot that bell opening close equals no we're going to do a push.
We're going to push that to the database.
How can we push it really really simple.
I'm going to say fire based promotions that push open and close and I'm going to be passing the data
to met which contains the email and the e-mail and the value of e-mail.
Right.
And then of course if the user it's already in the database we need to do something else.
So what I'm going to be doing or going to doing I'm going to do this reset form success just like this
but this time I'm going to add an argument.
So this what is going to be false.
And the other one of course if you're adding a user to the database it's going to be the completely
opposite.
The complete opposite.
True.
All right so now this reset for success will be receiving right here a value you know.
True or false.
I'm going to call that type.
So if rates of course if it's true it's congratulations because we added the user to the database but
it's false.
If it's false we can add a different message.
Something like already on the database so I'm going to go right here to the Whenever we set the state
of this.
So type if it's true.
Congratulations.
If not already on the database something like that resample.
All right.
And that is it.
You know I know it looks really simple.
So let's try.
Let's see what happens.
So going to reload the applications go back and remember that we have Francis and G.M. that come.
So I'm going to try with Francis Jima that come and we get already on the database.
And of course we are clearing the error message the impact.
What happens if we add another one.
So and roll.
And congratulations.
And if we go too far base we are getting the value right.
We are storing it.
So let's try me one more Steve and G-mail that come in and roll we get.
Congratulations.
And if I try Steve at gmail dot com again
already on the database so everything works.
So later I'm going to tell you how to fix this.
It's just a warning it's still going to work.
We need to add some properties right here to some rules to the database to get rid of this error message.
But don't worry about this right now.
All right so we are done with this components.
Right.
We are.
You're done.
There's no nothing else.
So if I check the final a final one the other thing is just a disclaimer.
So I'm going to just add some of it.
That's the only thing missing right now.
And of course we need to add to that with the class name because we have a different font.
So class name and the class name it's and roll disclaimer.
And again a pace that larm Epsom and a five year low the application.
That's it.
Everything works very good.
So if I check again find one this is the last component inside home.
And we did a lot already.
So we have a lot of files already.
Look at all of this and this is going to get much bigger.
So OK so what are we going to be doing next.
So again just like that before we are fetching everything from firebase but we're kind of manually adding
this to the database.
So on the next section we're going to start with the log in part of the application we can add a log
in a user not a because not anyone can.
We're just here we're going to add a log in we're going to add some user to the database manually.
And of course if the user slot.
And we're going to create that authentication and begin to check the routes the user is able to enter
some routes and everything else.
And we will create and not been route.
So only administrators can enter that route so we can start dynamically adding matches players and some
other things.
So on the next action we start with the sign sign up with the authentication part of the project.