All right.
So let's keep going with this.
I was going to I was going to do the site info and then the using information.
But again they are just like the products in the magic of magic category.
And I wanted to do something a little bit more fun.
So what are we going to be doing is that whenever we click on the product we're going to get.
Of course the information about the product and everything else and where we click and of course we
get the thumbnails and everything else right.
And then after we're finished this we're going to go directly to the card logic and you know adding
everything to the user card.
And then of course make it the purchase.
So let's begin with this.
If I go to guitars right here this is the one we made previously.
And if I go of course go to bew product nothing happens.
But if we remember and I go to Mongo DVH on this entry we have three images so we can work with that.
If you don't have this please try to go to the admin and add maybe at least two images at least two
images if you're going to add more.
That's cool.
All right.
Let's begin with this.
So what do we need first.
First we need a road where we can render by catching the idea.
Right.
OK.
So I'm going to go to source.
Let me close everything else.
And we're going to start this on it's own component.
I'm going to create a new folder and this one will be called Product singler.
And of course we will get an Index index that as instead of they're going to press enter and this is
going to be a re-act classmates component.
And now of course I'm going to say product right here.
We're going to make some changes of course and I'm going to go to route's because of course we need
to include it inside.
ROBERTS So I'm going to import and I'm going to call the component product just like this.
And that page could be product detail or something like that.
It's completely up to you.
And there's when it's inside components for last and that product right I'm going to copy the name I
got to replace and that's for with a product page.
And of course and then we need to include it.
And this one will be kind of a public scenario so I'm going to copy and paste it.
And the your L is of course is going to change.
So I'm going to change the component and the Ural is going to be something like I don't know a full
force would be something like product or part of detail that makes sense.
Yeah.
So I'm going to call it product and then detail.
And of course we need to catch DJT.
If you remember we need to call in and the name of what we are going to be catching in this case is
the idea SOGA are going to save it and in theory we've already added this part of detail.
So if I go here of course let me go back to be Tarz if I go to the product we get a dashboard.
This is my mistake because of course this is a product detail and we are setting this to false ride.
So this one it's a public just like shop and home so it should be Nouel at least we know that the logic
with the preventing route is working.
So I go to the product and we get products.
All right.
So let's go to the index.
And of course we need to include a lot of things right here.
We're going to divide everything into three or three different components which is this is the main
one.
And then we're going to have the we're going to get the left with the image and then the right side
we're going to do first the right and then the image because this one has a light box.
So we have a little bit more logic right there.
So I'm going to go right here and say first I want to include the page top.
This is the page up.
They weren't Would it be before right here.
So we will really have this.
So I'm going to imported the import page top from Dot dot dot for slash your tails for Slash and then
page top right.
OK.
What else we need to connect because whenever we get the ID of this product connect whenever we get
the idea of this product we need to of course go to fetch the information.
So it's from react and then redux.
OK am I going to go right here and we're going to say of course we need to import actions.
So for now of course we are not going to import anything because we need to create the actions and we
need some user actions and some products actions.
So for now we are good now.
I'm going to do.
I'm going to grab the connect connect open and close and then wrap the actual component.
All right now we're going to use Map state props.
So I'm just going to go right now and say map state prompts and we will use the products so products
and then products right here.
All right.
And of course inside of the connect Burguet.
So let's begin with this.
First we need to fetch the information about this product on the server later are we going to do some
changes.
But for now we are just going to fetch the information.
So a component did mount open and close and we can open it.
So I'm going to say Konst ID equals and to get the ID from the Paramus is this that probs that match
that prompts that idea.
Remember we kind of already did this.
So then of course I went to dispatch in action which is going to be the you know the get product detail.
First I want to console log the console log that and getting the correct ID you know that we are getting
the ID so I can inspect are going to go to bew product and we get the idea that is get our Burguet.
So of course we need to create this patch and then of course go to the reducers So we need to go to
actions.
And this one is going to be a product action Zangana open actions and save the index.
Okay.
So inside product actions we need to create a type which is going to be a get product detail just like
that.
So lets do it right now going to do a coma and then get a mic get it right get for product underscore
detail and then and again to create it.
Right now we can create a clear product detail.
Remember we told you that whenever we fetched information story redux and we go outside we should clear
the state of this global state because if we enter again we're going to see a flashing information of
the previous state.
So I'm going to create it right now.
We're going to start with clear than product and that detail.
All right.
Pretty good.
So now I'm going to copy this and I'm going to do this at the top.
So export export function and we're going to call it get product and the detail and with this one we'll
be getting an ID and then of course we need to do something.
Now if you remember on the server we already have this information.
Let me find it I believe we call it good product by ID or something like that.
So our articles by ID.
So this is one we are using right and we are listening for Crace and we need to pass a type of single
if we want to get a single one.
All right.
So at least we know what the route is so we're going to carry the request Konst request equals ASIO's
that get and then we just pass the same you r l which is product server just like this forward slash.
And its going to be products my ID right.
So its actually articles by id write articles by ID so articles by ID.
So we need to pass the query string so its all the closes its ID equals to whatever ID we get from the
from the arguments and then the type so ampersand and type.
And in this case its a single right.
That is it.
Then of course we need to catch the response response.
The Rigaud opening close and what we need to return is the response so Im going to say return responds
that data.
All right.
Now again the information comes in the inside of an array.
Right it comes inside of something.
So I'm going to do I want to get whatever we have inside and just put it inside of that.
So whenever we get the information on the index we could just make a reference to the Propst product
and the name of what we want to bring.
Right.
OK.
So this one is good.
We need to return to type.
So type sorry return we do the type of course open close and then payload Collen right.
So the type its get product detail and what we will we will send it whatever we get back from the request.
So we need to add these types because we really need to add them.
So I'm going to go again to copy and do both.
So right.
So export Export Konst and the first one was get product detail right.
Let's do that one.
So get product detail and then we close it.
And the same thing for the other one.
So export Konst clear product detail and then include your product detail.
All right so now we get the types Burguet.
So of course if I go to Protech actions I made a mistake right here and they put a comma.
Now when did you go to the producer Ron.
We need to do to catch this types from the reducer So let's go to the reduce or so product reduce or
of course we need to import the types I'm going to copy this once and then paste it at the top.
Very good.
So now on the get product detail we just create a case recopy the type get product Gitau going to go
right here at the bottom and say if the case is that we get a product detail we want to return that
Dudden state coma and we want to return something that has the detail.
So the key for this is going to be Prod. detail.
CONAN And whenever we get inside action that payload now we get to meet or go like it like this a little
bit more.
If we get the case that we want to clear the plot the product detail we pretty much do the same thing
so clear product detailed case clear product detail and we just returned pretty much the same thing.
The difference is that this time the action that the load is going to be nothing.
We are not going to get anything inside of the payload is going to create a function right now.
So we can get it out of the way to go at the bottom and say export function and clear product detail
open and close and we just return a type of clear product detail the type of the top and the type clear
product detail and the payload could be anything you know could be an empty array could be an empty
object or just going to say empty string.
So now we have two functions.
So again we go to index and Im going to require them from the actions right.
So important open and close and then get.
I have I here get part of the detail and just to avoid typos Im going to copy the name.
All right.
So then of course we need to required from dot dot for Slashdot that for Slash and then actions and
then products of product actions.
All right.
We are kind of ready to go.
So we need to first dispatch to get product detail right.
Whenever we do component mounts we do get the ID.
So I'm going to say this that prompts that dispatch and we passed the get product detail with the actual
ID.
So now the page is going to reload and of course nothing happens.
But if we go here we should be getting that product detail and we do state products product detail and
we get you know the three images and everything else we now have this is the only entry with three images
so we know that this is a one.
OK.
So now we get it.
Now of course look at this.
If I go to home and I check in again the product details stays there.
Right.
We still get it.
So if I go again to that post until we finished a network request that product details stays the same
always stays the same and whenever it's done then it's going to go and replace it for the new one if
you're going to a different ID.
That's why we do clear product detail and what we're going to be doing whenever this component and mounts
component will and mount we will trigger that part detail.
So there's not a problem that this patch and this action is instant.
It's actually very very quick because we are not making a request of the server.
We are just modifying the store and that's it.
So now instead get part of detail inside the actual product the detail we get all the information about
the about the components.
So let's try to build something right here so we can at least get something.
So going to delete products and first thing and add the page top we've included at the top.
And if you remember we need to pass a title if not nothing going to is going to get us played.
So title equals and then product detail Okay.
So then I'm going to wrap everything inside of a container.
All right.
Now the thing is that the first time the page loads we will not and we are not going to get anything
called prok detail.
So of course we need to ask if we do have something so this that props that products just like this
dot and then private detail.
So there's that props up products that detail if you do have something we're going to do something if
not we're going to return no or what you can do.
And I'm not going to do it right now to save time.
I'm going to return loading.
So right here we could show that materail you I circle or progress.
I'm not going to do it.
So we can save a little bit of time but you know this is how we do it.
So instead of if we do have some information I want to show something on the screen.
Right.
So I'm going to show a wrapper of class name and then product then detail and then wrap her.
And instead of here we will get two sites left with images and the light box and the right side with
the info.
So div class name of the left and this one we're going to be the actual images whatever.
And then in the ride we will get the.
Of course the data we can do right now.
So class name right.
OK.
So in sort of here and we're going to the info of course we're going to do a couple more things.
But you know we can if we can get it we get images in left and then the info in the center.
I'm pretty sure I made a mistake with this should be container right.
That's why it's all the way to the left.
OK so now we got it in the center.
So then part of detail wrapper.
Everything looks nice.
Of course when we start adding things we're going to modify the sizes right here but that's good.
So first we're going to do the info one.
Right.
So for this one we need a new component to get a pass I think is Propst.
And then of course we can show the information.
So this component I'm going to create Right now I'm going to call it prod info or something like that
would AFO prod and info and then that G-S.
All right to save it so would prod and info.
The only thing we need to do is to catch the prompts and display some Jande sex.
So this one could be a reactive state stateless component just like this.
And I'm going to call it prod and foe with a capital P.
So we are good.
So of course we need to import a lot of things and right from the start we will need a button.
We have buttons right here.
So I'm going to import my button from Eutelsat and then button.
All right.
Actually it's button we will use Fonte awesome icon.
So import phantasm font.
Awesome icon from that weird name for it.
Awesome and re-act for awesome.
OK now let me try try to go to the find one so we will get this icons.
If it's a free shipping we can it show something.
If not begin to show something else.
Of course then we have an X.
And we can have some something else if we're going to import three different icons.
They're going to say import and I get to create the first one and then just we can copy and paste of
course.
So import a and then truck from at and it's Fortt awesome.
And this is the one the free solid.
So a truck.
All right.
And that's it I'm going to copy this one because it's pretty much the same.
The only thing that changes is the name.
And then we add check because we get checkmark or simple enough going to copy.
I'm going to paste and I'm the last one.
It's times all right.
So we have to get all the icons.
There are no more imports for this section.
So instead of the Prod. info we will be getting props right.
Right.
OK.
So now the bottom what I want to do on the actual one and whenever we render something we have three
different places we have you know the description the title and this.
Then we have a place where we show the price and we can add a card and then we have the specifications.
So what I want to do instead of here just instead of just returning everything I want to retry and return
three different functions where we can you know split the content.
So I get inside the return inside of the div..
First I'm going to put the title.
So it's prop's Oh sorry.
Let me make it right to access the title.
So proud props that detail.
And you know now that I think about it we could you know store this Konst detail equals props that detail
so we don't have to make a reference to props.
We just can say detail and that is it.
So whenever we called a detail we access the brand and art we access the name.
I remember that then we have the name of the the actual article no fender what Fender Stratocaster or
what what we're going to be using.
So props out sort detail dot name and in future we should be getting something let's double check.
Of course we need to include it.
So I'm going to go to the top and import Perrott info.
We call it info signed copy prod info from that forward slash and then Prof ampho.
And of course we need to when to put it right here and we need to pass a prompt.
If not of course we are not going to get anything.
Sorry forgot to do this.
So I'm going to call.
I'm going to put two things.
The first one is the detail.
You know what we need to pass to the component so this that prompts the products dot and then prod detail.
Which is what we get on the read of the store later much later when we are pretty much done with done
with this.
We're going to do the Add to Cart.
So we need to kind of a trigger function that adds this item to the cart of the user.
So I'm going to call it out to cart and then add to cart.
And this one is going to be equal to a function.
Now this function will be getting the ID of the element and then I'm going to say this dot at current
just like this.
Add to Cart and we make it ride.
So add two and then cart and then handler open and close and we just pass the ID and passing the ID
from the child component because we are sure that we handle only one information because maybe later
you're going to get I don't know some other data right here maybe you going to get something else.
So again it's better to pass the ID for get idea from the child.
All right.
So we get the title.
I have an s r g.
Two fifty five.
So that is get we get the title or nothing.
We are getting the data correctly at least right.
So then we have a description going to do something very simple.
I'm going to put it put it a paragraph then detail dot and then description and we should be getting
the description OK.
So we get it.
Let me see the.
All right.
I'm way past the time.
So this is get we get the title and we get the text.
So let's go to the next section and do everything else is going to be really really simple.