Write so let's keep going with this.
We need to add this.
I'm going to call it product tax.
This one tax you know attack then actions so get the you know this and maybe later we could get more
actions maybe contact us or something like that.
For now it's going to be very simple.
And then we get the specifications.
So I'm going to go here at the bottom and I add just the function which is going to be show show then
prod and then tax.
All right.
And we're going to be passing whatever we get back from detail Ryan Ryan so detail this detail which
is equal to prod and then detail.
All right.
So I'm going to go at the top and create this show Prod. stack just like this.
We're going to get something and then we do something and we're going to be returning of course some
sex.
So we need to open and close that we will be seeing the details.
I'm going to say detail now I'm going to wrap everything inside of a container class name of product
product underscore tax and right here some of the simple some of the articles.
They have shipping.
So if we do have shipping we can show this.
If we don't have any shipping we are not going added Of course because it's not free shipping.
So maybe you are buying something.
I don't know that worth maybe $10 or $20 so there's no shipping for that of course.
So shipping detailed shipping if we do have something we get going return.
If not the original nil.
So here I'm going to add DIVX and I'm going to add the tags and they are all pretty much the same.
That's why I'm telling you this one is going to be easy.
There's a lot of copy pasting.
So the name of the attack of course the class name call stack.
And the first thing we will get the font awesome icon so font awesome icon opening close.
Now the icon of this one is going to be the truck.
Remember the shipping.
So F-8 truck right.
Then we have the text.
So Dave and I are going to add the class name of tack text and this one should be saying Free Shipping
Free Shipping.
And since we have it on two lines I did something simple.
So free shipping and of course I'm going to add a second line like it's holding something very simple
and then and return.
All right.
So let's check it out.
Show PRUD stock.
It's not that fun.
I made a mistake with this.
It should be canceled because this is the functional component.
It's not a class.
And right here I'm making it a track us string.
So it should be available.
All right.
OK.
What is next.
We have the availability.
You know if it's available or not and there's two ways you can do this are going to do one way and then
I'm going to tell you a different way you can do this.
Of course we can attach a different conditionals if we have detail available.
We can do something now if not we can show something else right.
We can know this.
So for this one I want to pretty much show the same tax on going to copy and paste and make it a little
bit better.
So if it's available I want to show the fake check.
Right because we get a checkmark right.
And instead of here is going to say available
in store we get rid of this and store.
Of course if it's not available I'm pretty much showing the same things.
I'm going to copy paste and change the icons and everything else.
And now I'm going to tell you maybe a different way to do this.
So this one should be five times just like this and it's going to be not available not available preorder
free or other only.
So of course we're going to reload the application and we get the available in-store because this element
is available right now.
Instead of doing this because again we are doing a lot of more code.
What you can do is just put a conditional of detail available instead of the icon to show the check
or show the Times and the same thing with the context.
Right.
If you have if you get the the available true you showed this.
If not you show the other one you just put the same conditional on different spots.
So you can get rid of the you know redoing the tags and everything else.
All right.
That's one way to do it.
OK.
So let's keep going.
We get the actions.
It's the number and the actual button.
So I'm going to go at the bottom and create a new function.
So this one is going to be called show prod and then actions open and close and we pass the detail right.
So on the create function.
So it's going to be Konst show productions and then we are going to do something.
So this action is just renders the cart ride the cart button and the price.
Now we didn't have the special bond and because it isn't special.
We're going to talk about that in a second so detailed we pass this.
And then of course we'll return a dev with a class name of product and then actions.
Now on this one we will show the price and that's why it's simple enough so we get a class name off
price just like this.
And then of course we attached a price.
Right.
Makes sense.
So detail dot price.
Let's see if we get that at least so we get the price.
All right.
So let's go to the bun create a death and this one it's going to be the cart so we're going to have
a lot of fun with this.
So we need to add.
Now if we think about this the button looks a little bit different than the other ones.
That's one thing and the thing is that this is not a link.
This is a burn net whenever we click it.
We need to fire a function that adds to the cart.
And whenever we add to the cart of course we need to go to the My Account added to the users to the
user account on the server.
Right.
So we need to do a lot of things but for this when of course we need to trigger a function.
So first I'm going to import my button right here at the top.
And we didn't we don't have this button.
We need to create the bun.
All right.
So I'm going to type I'm going to close it just like this and I'm going to pass the time.
Remember that with the type we got things so as to card like.
All right.
We will need to create a type a button with this type.
Right.
So then I'm going to attach a different prop which is going to be run action.
What's going to happen whenever we click this.
So what is going to happen is that we run in a different function.
Right.
Just a different function.
And this one is going to be something being added later.
All right.
For now just going to say console log
at to cart whatever.
OK.
So we need to go to buttons right here and we need to create the Add to Cart link.
Right.
All right.
Let's do that right now.
So let's add the case are going to do.
Case off.
And if we get at card link we do something with this.
And of course never forget the break.
So what we will be returning again is just the template and the template is going to be very very simple
because it's just a button with a class you know a div with a class that has an unclick on it.
And with unclick we just run the function that we are passing as a callback right.
So class name.
And then I believe we call it at Codling when we use the same thing.
And then of course we need to attach the on click.
So on click equals open and close and we run whatever we're getting from prop's ride and then run action.
This is the name of we are passing the prop you're passing run action and then we will trigger this
OK.
So instead of you're going to copy the you want awesome icon and we will use the same thing.
The FAA shopping bag.
And then add to cart.
All right and we get it.
Let me go to inspect the console and if I click it we get to cart.
All right let's get it works.
Later we are going to be doing this logic.
All right.
Well let's go back to private info and finish unfinished part info.
So then we have the specifications.
I'm going to go at the bottom and say show Pernod and then specifications and we will pass the detail
around.
All right.
Copy the function just like before going to a concert.
The name of the function.
We run something.
And then of course we do something and we need to pass the detail right.
OK.
We will be returning some GSX.
So I'm going to delete this and put the parenthesis.
All right.
So Dave we add a class name of product underscore specifications and then we need a title.
Let me just show you the final one.
We get the title and then just the frets.
Right.
So H-2 is going to be an age to tag and then specifications.
And just going to call specs.
Right.
We have it better.
So Dave.
And now for each one we will add a day of class something class name item and right here we will have
a strong.
Because as you know the name of field than Fretz open and close and after the strong we do for its detail
and then we have the conference detail.
All right.
We're going to copy same thing and we have the word for now we just get two categories the wood and
the frets of course in real life.
You're going to get a lot of things right.
You can get a lot of this a lot of this.
OK.
So detail and remember that would we get an idea.
So we need to enter word because we are getting getting it from the server like this and then enter
the name.
All right let's check it out.
So we got 24 hours.
And this is older right.
Because this is the baby time.
And it's not an R.G. to 5 it's a different name just made this up.
OK.
So we get all the detail.
Everything works OK.
So now what we need to do we need to create the light box and for that we need to do a little bit more
logic and we are going to be using a dependency we've already installed this.
Let me see if I can find it.
I don't see it has to be here.
React images I don't remember right now but it's just that it's just a light box right.
It's just a light box really really simple.