All right.
So let's do the images this and then of course we'll attach the light box.
We need to do a few things.
OK.
So we're going to use this dependency and it was we asked images.
So if I go to Google and do re-act images I'm going to open it from get have and of course we get everything
else.
So this is a tiny example.
What we do of course we put a box and inside of the images we have the property images and we need to
pass an array with objects and with the Source property.
So right now our structure actually benefits that so we can use that but it's not really safe because
the light box is going to be creating it's going to be an outside component is going to be a reusable
component inside tills because we might use it later.
Right.
But that's why this is our reference.
Let's go back to our project and I'm going to close the package that Jason and I are going about going
to go back to the index.
Now what we need to do we need to create a component that is going to be rendering images.
So I'm going to go to product are going to create a new file called Perrott Perrott EMG.
Yes of course we need to including at the top.
So import them to import Prod. EMG from that forward slash and then prod MGE.
Right.
Of course we need to go to the problem G and create whatever it is that we need to create.
So this brought in is going can be a Cosbys component because we need to use the state so re-act class
based component.
And we're going to call it Prod. EMG Burguet.
For now we are not going to do anything.
Let's go back to the parent component.
We need to include this right here inside of images.
And like I told before don't take this as a reference but I'm going to do.
I'm going to do a div I'm going to add a style.
Again it's this is not responsive so I'm going to say with an attached just a fixed width with 500 pixels.
Now I'm going to make a reference to this proud detail.
And of course since we are getting images right here inside the detail they're going to be passing the
detail of the of the of the actual product so detail equals and right here at the top.
We are not using this.
So it's this props that products that Perrott detail.
All right very good.
So of course now we need to go to detail and catch all these for make sure this information is going
to go back to a proud image.
Sorry.
So instead of Prod. image I'm going to go here and create some state.
So state open and close and right from the start begin to get to light box like box and I'm going to
set it from the default to false.
Now remember that whenever we want to include the box in open the light box we need to pass that is
open.
So this is going to be a true or false you know value.
So right from the start it's going to be false then we need to set the image position.
So again to say image and that pass.
So whenever we click on on an image right here this could be the first image the second the third one
or the fourth.
So whenever I click on the third the Lightbox will open on the third right or maybe the fourth.
We are clicking the fourth.
So this is where we're going to be handling this by default we open at zero which is the first image
on the on the on the list and then I'm going to create a different which is going to be light box and
that images I get told before this light box needs this structure in order to work.
We can get it but we need to process this a little bit more.
So I'm going to go right here.
The bottom I'm going to catch this.
You know this proud detail that we're getting inside props this detail.
So I'm going to do a component will mount so a component will mount up sort of component that mount
you shouldn't use component will mount will be excluded on the next portion of react.
So what do we want to do now on this case.
We are going to get some images with the properties of right here with the you know an array of objects
with the public I.D. and the you are l.
So the only thing that we need is the u r l but we are going to include the light box as an outside
component as a reusable components.
So we always need to send one property right since what we care is the you are l right here passing
just an RE with D or else no source no nothing just an array with you or else.
All right.
So I'm going to go here.
I'm going to do if I open and close and if we do have images if this prompts that detail detail that
images and if we have more we have more than one then we want to do this because if we have only one
M.F. image there is no need to attach it in any dye box or do any logic right here.
So if we get a length of greater than zero then we want to you know convert the array and everything
else.
So so if you have more than one image then we want to create a light box like light box.
Let me do it right.
Light box images.
This one is going to be an empty array and we're going to be pushing the Your else right there.
So this that props that detail that images you can create an alias so you don't have to do this that
props that detail that's completely up to you and I'm going to do it for each.
So for each.
So on that for each.
We will catch the item on each iteration and we will.
We will do.
We're going to get that source that you well and we're going to push it to light box images.
So I'm going to go say like books images that push open and close.
Now the key for this is you are out.
This is the key.
OK.
And enter item and say I want to push that.
You are l into our New You are right.
So once we are done I'm going to do this not set state open and close and I'm going to pass the Lightbox
images right here.
So we are using the same name so I can do this.
All right.
So of course I'm going to do a console log this state and I'm going to go back to our project and if
I inspected we're going to get just the array of objects that I'm sorry the array of you know your else.
OK.
All right let's get one now we can begin to use this later of course this lightbox images.
Now.
First I would like to start doing the all the the layout right here so we can get at least something.
So on the previous section on the info right here we did this what you can do.
You can do something else.
You know very similar.
You can create a concert you can bring the detail from there and then you can say this when it comes
from props.
So now you have a viable that calls detail that contains the props that detail right a different way
to do it.
So I'm going to create a class name with a container of product underscore image underscore container.
All right.
Now at the top you can get the main pick and this one it's always the first image on that right.
Right.
OK.
So we're going to create a container div class name main pick.
And inside we will just put a div with a background image.
Right.
OK.
Now the first pic is the one that needs to come up you know comes as props now might happen that we
don't have an image with that image.
It's like the the other ones the sorry image not available because we don't get it.
So we need to check if we do have a real image to play.
Because if not we are not going we are going to be displaying nothing.
All right.
Just like it happens right now.
OK.
So I'm going to say style equals to open and close and I'm going to say background.
Now the background.
It will be equal to your L and I will be passing the Ural and then I'm going to say no real Pete.
Now I'm going to hand I'm going to create a function to handle the you know show the correct image or
show the other one the you know not found.
So I'm going to call this this render render and then card and then image and as it's of no value I'm
going to be passing whatever we get in detail which is this one.
And that images are going to pass the array of images we get from the parent you know from this one
from the detail not the one we are doing inside like books images.
OK.
So we don't have this function going to go and created right now equals to open and close.
And of course we will need to return a value right.
So what we need to do is to check if we do have an image.
If we we have something inside of that right now going to create an if then else.
So if has to be images dot because we are passing the images arguments right here so images dot and
then we check the length and if it's greater than zero it means that you know we have something.
So what I'm going to do I'm going to do.
Return
images the precision number zero and do your L because this is a background of poverty.
We just need your help.
Nothing else.
Now of course if we don't have the image I'm going to return open it close and images forward slash.
And remember that we have that image not available.
So Image not on those core available that P and G.
Just like with before with the carts it's pretty much the same thing.
Let me just it again of course we are getting the first images image because whenever we bring the data
out of this we do have images.
So this is the first one.
If I go to a different one that it's not available we get nothing.
Let me show why and should check why maybe the the route is incorrect but we know we are attaching these
images image not available PNB.
I know it's the same stick with it before I did before.
So I'm going to copy the name because the name is incorrect and I'm not changing the names because I've
already give you all the files everything else.
So again I cannot go backwards.
Sometimes when I make mistakes I need to fix it with you right here.
So Image not available.
All right.
Now we should be getting something at least and we get it we get it.
Let's get.
All right.
We're going to go back.
Going to go to New Product.
Just going to reload just in case it's OK.
So now for example later when we click here when you click on that image I want to open the light box.
So I need to fire that light box.
You can be using in a couple of minutes.
So I'm going to attach this on click function.
So I'm going to go here and say whenever we do anon click and let me fix the one at the top.
There we go.
Whenever we do an unclick
I'm going to do something.
And what am I going to do.
I'm going to do this.
Dad handle and then lightbox.
So this function is the one there's that handle.
There we go.
This function is the one that it's going to be deciding what do we need to open.
If you want to open at zero position or maybe the second position or third position and everything else.
So of course this function is not ready yet.
We're going to create it in a minute.
All right.
Now again we need to pass that position you're going to see of course we're going to discuss right here
pretty much the same thing and you're going to get it of course at the bottom.
We have more images.
We can have two three more five or 10 whatever is that you attached to that you know place the product.
So for this one we will create a new container called class name.
Main thumbs.
All right.
So this one again is going to be a function.
But now we need to render all the remaining images we can not just skip this one and show the other
images.
So again we can process this in a function.
So this does it show.
And then thumbs and we are going to be passing whatever we get back from the detail.
Let me make it ride thumps.
OK.
So let's create the function and return some GSX going to do it right here.
He calls to open and close and that's it.
OK.
Now we need to create a function.
Let me check the time.
We are OK.
So OK on shoat thumbs.
Pretty simple stuff.
We need to of course loop the information.
We get all the detailed images.
But if you remember we already have something inside the component will mount.
We have the Lightbox images.
So what we can do we can check the light but like box images check if we have a more than one right.
And if we have more than one we want to of course show the remaining all the pictures but the first
image is simple.
So I'm going to go to show thumbs I'm going to say this dot state DOT light box images dot map and I
get to do item.
And of course we will return some GSX.
So let me fix this.
Very good.
So what I'm going to be passing is a new item and iteration.
And then of course we will return more GSX.
So now again we need to return only if we if we are on the second position of the array.
Right on the on the second value which is the first the number 1.
So if the iteration is greater than zero then we want to return it.
If not we are not going to return anything.
So what we do we return a div just a div with some property inside.
So if the property is going to go right here it's going to be the key.
Of course we always need to pass the key.
Now we need to do the unclick just like with it right here.
I'm going to copy this just like this and say that whenever we do an and click on click I get a copy
of this because it's pretty much the same thing.
So whenever we do one and click on this I went to trigger this function that opens the box at a certain
decision.
Now I'm passing the zero and this is why we are bringing the index since we have the index on the array.
We have the order.
So I'm passing the dynamic value.
Now I'm going to attach a class name the class name for this one.
It's going to be thumb thumb.
And again to add some more style and the style it's the background image so background and right here
we don't need to do this logic with it did right here at the top you know showing the image the first
image or doing this because if we do have more elements on the array it's because we do have images.
So we're going to do your L opening close and pass the item because we are just looping an array of
images and then no repeat.
Right.
And that's it.
See what we get.
Maybe stick something.
Let me just double check.
I mean forget forgetting to do something.
Second are just the.
What is wrong because we should be getting something at least.
Let me just do the inspect the console.
We get nothing on the console.
And if I go right here the bottom left and then product image container and ride and then and the thumbs
we get we are actually getting the images we are.
But some of these we are I believe the classes.
Maybe it's wrong.
Let me just double check on the classes and yes Or for that it was a class error.
So maintenance because we were getting it on the HD male and we get images of course later we can click
it and begin to trigger that function that opens the box at the particular this particular position.
All right.
And again don't take this as a reference I'm just attaching an image and doing it because contain.
Right.
And just setting it at the middle or at the bottom and realize you need to do a little bit better with
the CSSA force.
So we pretty much have all we need to start with the Lightbox we have all the images and the listeners
with the unclick.
So we need to bring the light box and start passing Baillieu's to the light box.
So let's go to the next one and do the box.