All right so let's create the light box.
So first I'm going to go to you tell us and create a new file called light box.
Yes so a light box.
Yes.
All right.
So this one is going to be a re-act class based components.
So let me get the there you go.
So with a capital L..
All right.
So you're kind of get to go now.
This light box will be receiving some things from the parent which is the image.
And what we're going to be doing.
We're going to be attaching and detaching the light box right.
OK.
Now this handle Lovebox and we're going to do this functions right now so we can get them out of the
way they handle light box is the one we click right here to pass which position we want to open on the
light box and right here we have the image position so we can need to toggle the state between zero
and one or two or whatever is that you know we are opening and then we have the live box false whenever
we attach something.
We were doing unclick going to change the light box to troops so we can you know toggle the state and
show the light box.
So I'm going to go to handle light box and remember that we are going to get a position now of course
we need to trigger the handle light box that opens the light box only if we have more than image.
You know if we have more than just one image I don't want to show the light box.
So I'm going to go and say this that state that light box images that length.
And if I have more than one then I want to you know toggled state.
So there's not set state and are going to say that now the light box is equal to true which is going
to open the light box and then I'm going to be passing the image position of where we are clicking and
we have a pulse right.
Real simple.
Now later we need the ability to close the light box.
So this closing the light box the what it's going to do is going to toggle the light box to false.
All right.
So I'm going to go and say handle light box and then close.
I'm creating the function right now because now we are going to be including the light box at the bottom
as a component.
And we need to pass this as props so this that sets state and we say that the lead box.
It's now false.
Right.
OK.
So we pretty much have everything to include the light box right.
So we're going to go with one and we need to call it a light box right here at the bottom.
So we only want to show the lead box if the state of flood light box is true if it's false we are not
going to display anything.
So again we are attaching and detaching the box.
So this that state DOT and then light box if we do have it true we do something.
If not we do know.
Now of course we need to import this light box from you tells at the top.
So let's include it import analemma mixes space import image.
I've been called black box.
Oh I'm going to clog image just like this image like box and I believe the name is wrong.
That's putting an image light box there we go.
Sorry for that.
I just want to get the correct name too you know because maybe.
I'm not sure that the box will leave you with the light box.
We need to import something that calls a light box.
So if we do it we can you know interrupt we can do we use the same class name as a viable that are real
that we're going to be importing.
You know the compound we are importing at the top.
So we're going to get a problem.
So I'm going to called Image lightbox and it's from you tales from DOT forward slash you tails for Slash
and then lightbox.
Right.
So I'm going to go at the bottom and I'm going to include the light box right.
All right.
So of course we need to pass a lot of props
so I'm going to add props.
So first I'm going to add the ID we are going to need the ID So detail ID right.
So then I'm going to do this I'm going to pass the images that we need to be passing to the light box.
So you know we can show it and these images are the one we have inside box images that array of routers
you know are real sources.
So there's that state that light box images.
All right one thing less than we need to tell the Lightbox if it should be open.
So I'm going to say open and this that state that open.
What else we need that persistence so pass open and close this that state that position.
What else.
We need the unclose.
Remember we made a a function to close it.
So I'm going to say on close calls whatever function we created to close the the light box so it was
can handle handle live box close.
And of course this is a function so.
We pass the array of images and we know that here we have an array just with the with the Uriel's then
the open which start just falls.
The position with the Starts is zero and it's going to change if we click on one of the images on the
thumb or the other one.
And then of course we tripled the clocks which is going to target the state of open to false.
So we are good Let's go to the lovebox.
So the light box is pretty much simple.
First we need to include it.
So import and this is what I was talking about.
The light box just like this.
It's pretty much the same name.
So if we use the same name as class and the import you know the application will fail.
So it's from re-act images.
Maybe they react lightbox was already taken so that's why they are using re-act images.
That's good.
So we need more state right here and there's state it's strictly related to the Lightbox right here.
So we need to use the same names and everything is on the documentation.
So the first one is going to be light box it's open.
This is the name of the O is open.
OK.
So this one is going to be true.
Why is it true.
Because right here we are attaching and detaching.
So whenever we attach the Lightbox is hopen.
All right.
So I'm going to go and say current image and this is again everything comes from the documentation of
this component's writing just doing this the props that the state I'm setting the state like they tell
us we should do it.
So we're going to do this.
The problem the past whenever we get we attached this class you know to the actual window we say that
the current image is whatever we are getting from the parent component which is Depass.
Ryan starts at zero and then we need to pass the images and right here we have a problem we can discuss
right now the images what we get on the images is just an array with you or else.
And what this component needs is an array with objects and then source inside.
And I I did this just like this.
So we can reuse that component later maybe you have a different section where we have an array of images.
Maybe here with a different structure.
So by processing the images from the parent we are making sure that we only pass the sources you know
they your else and this light box will always receive chess to you or else nothing else.
So but before we can you know pass the images to the actual light box we need to process this.
We need to change it to this structure.
So the books can you know understand this.
So for this we're going to do something simple.
I'm going to use the steps from props open and close and then I'm going to say OK props and state.
So if we do get props that images props DOD images just like this from props.
We're going to do something.
I'm going to do all of this if not of course we return false.
So what we do here we just change the structure and we return to a new state of images just with the
with the object the array of objects and the source keys on each Eurail.
OK.
So Konst images equals an empty array.
So then I'm going to enter props.
I'm going to enter images.
Remember we are passing this one right here going to enter images and I'm going to do a for each for
each now for each element we have right there.
We're going to do something.
I'm going to enter images are going to do push and this image is not the Sims.
It's the Bible you're creating right here.
I'm going to push to that array an object that contains a source of whatever we get back from you know
that loop.
So which is going to be the Eurail.
Right.
And then at the end of all of this we just need to return the new state of things which is going to
be images and the images will be equal to whatever we get from prompts and images.
The only difference is that we have this structure right now we just find the structure of the data.
So I'm going to go right here but I'm going to include the Lightbox so I'm going to copy the name right
here.
Light box paste it and then close it.
Everything is on the recommendation.
All right.
So first we need to tell the Lightbox What does the current image if we just open it from the from here.
The light box of course it will be zero.
This one will be one two three four whatever.
So we need to tell the light box the current image.
So current image and this one is going to be equal to this that state that current image.
Right.
Remember we store this at the top.
The current image of the next Propp the images that we want to render inside light box and this one
is this state that images because we are catching them with good derived state from props and modifying
this.
All right.
Next week to pass that is open so that it's open.
It's going to toggle between open and close.
So there's that state DOT and remember that we have that light box is open right next.
And this one I can you whenever we let me just show you the final whenever we click something.
Of course the lead box with open.
Now if I click on the arrow we are going to go to the next pick right.
So this one will be handled by a function.
So we need to do on Kleek previews.
And this is actually their property.
We are not just making this up whenever we this listener gets fired.
What we want to do is to trigger a function.
So this doesn't go to previews and all this.
Again it's on the documentation.
I'm not making this up previous.
Are right that we have a different scenario which is going to be the on click but the next.
So we're going to say on click next and then it's going to be go to next right and then we have the
on close.
So I'm going to say on close just like this equals to open and close and we again we use a function
this close.
Light box.
All right.
Let's do the closed locked box because it's the easy easy one.
So what do we do on the closed box.
We already have a prop that is attaching or attached detaching or attaching that which is the prop on
close.
So what do we do.
We just trigger on close.
So close close like box and this one it's going to be just a function that it's going to trigger does
that problem that on close this one.
And remember the on close it's with a single C you know no capital and this is a function.
All right.
So if we go to here our component can reload it just in case.
If I click the first one.
Ok we get the first one.
Now if I go to the next one of course nothing is going to really happen.
Begin to get an error right.
Because we don't have that function.
Let me reload it again.
Now if I open the back of the guitar we should be getting the back and no we get the front because there
is of course an error.
So let me just check.
I'm pretty sure that this is the car.
So this state that plus we didn't have this state to pass.
We have an image pass as well.
You're not getting the position.
It's always a zero.
OK.
So again the first one works.
The second one works right.
And again of course this one doesn't work.
So OK let's do the next and the preview so we can finish the lightbox.
Going to go here.
And first one I'm going to go.
Go to previous opening close and right here.
And again this is on the documentation.
This is going to be very simple.
We just need to get the current image that we are getting from state and we need to rest one.
That's it.
It was simple.
So there's that said state open and close and I'm going to say that the current image now it's equal
to whatever we have inside this that state that current image minus one.
And they go to next.
It's the same.
Same thing.
But plus one you know the opposite.
So we do plus one.
All right.
Let's try it again.
Going to open.
I'm going to go to next.
And of course go to next with me.
Copy go to next.
There you go again.
Opened next we get it.
And three.
And of course we are not getting the next one.
This is getting handled by lightbox.
So if I go to previous go to previews and if I close we close it and if I open it again it works.
All right I'm in.
So one thing.
One less thing to do.
So I'm done.
We are done with the light box and the product detail right here.
So the next thing the next thing we're going to do is doing all the logic for adding to cart right.
Whenever we click Add to Cart and remember that we have it at home on the carts.
We are going to trigger a function where we get to you know add this item to the user cart and it's
going to be it's going to be pretty long because we need to do a few few things and not just on the
on the client the client is going to be very simple it's just a function that dispatches an action to
redux.
Right but on the server we need to create a route that calls at item to cart that will be getting you
know the actual card and it needs to get the ID go to the history.
I'm sorry go to the cart on the models for example to the user schema.
Right here we get the cart and attached the you know all the information we can a need and we can if
need to merge some part of the user information with the part of the of the actual cart.
So we need to do a few things.
It's going to be very very fun because everything it's on the server.
So it's something I kind of want to say new but you know something we were not doing in the past.
I don't know six hours maybe 10 hours.
All right let's go to the next section.
Going to sip the current state of this project so you can get it.
And we're going to start with add to cart.