All right before we move on to the next section I wanted to add a quick fix.
If I go to buy a product and of course right now we get the correct ID and this idea accessed if I change
something on the ID.
This ID doesn't exist anymore.
So if we go we are get we are going to get stuck inside of loading because never get a response back
or a valid response.
So we get products.
All right.
So what we can do.
You can handle this here.
So if when then you get a response.
We are not going to really use a response.
What you can do is just evaluate if you're not getting something inside products.
So if prop's best actually does that prompts this that for up prop's dot product that detail exists.
We can do something but if it doesn't exist you know if it's empty then of course you want to do something
here.
So cancell lock you know no article found and you can show this on the on the actual component.
You can choose what to do here.
So for us I'm going to reload and no article found.
If you go to a valid one you're going to go to View product.
We are not getting this twice.
Of course I reload and we don't get it twice right.
So again what you can do here.
You can read direct back to home.
You can completely do that.
So since we are inside of a main route what you can do is it's direct from re-act right you can direct
or send the user back to not found.
The problem is that we don't have a not found out right now.
Right.
So we can to this the props that history that push and begin going to send the user back to home.
So back to home
of course right now works.
If I do something else not really happening and we go back to home in real life you should or show a
message right here instead of this component saying do this web page.
This article is not on the database anymore.
Maybe you want to you know tried to get related products that maybe not related but some other products
whenever.
Is that you want to show or you can kick the user back to not found or go to home.
Depends on your application of course.
I just wanted to add this is pretty obvious but I just wanted to add it.
All right.
So now let's go to the Add to Cart.