OK so let's add products to the cart of the user.
So if we you know think where are we going to be adding products to cards.
We have two different places.
We have the button this button right here on each card.
Remember we have a component for this.
And of course when we enter our new product we have the button to Carto we have two places.
Right now we're going to do the first we're going to do the the the one on the cards and then we're
going to go and do you know the one of the product.
It's pretty much just our dispatch dispatch all of an action.
Right.
OK.
I'm going to close everything.
I don't need it.
Just going to close it right now because it gets a little bit over whelming.
I'm going to go to court.
All right.
That's the first place.
So inside cart I need to bring redux because I need to dispatch an action so I'm going to go at the
top and say import I'm going to do connect just like this.
And from react Rita.
All right.
That's the first thing.
Now we need to import an action called at to cart.
We don't have it.
I'm going to create it right now import at two and then cart from and then that forward slash that that
that forward slash.
And this one will be inside actions and I'm not getting the hour to complete the Riego actions for Slash
and user actions.
Can you store this inside user actions because you know even though it's related to product we are adding
this to the user database.
All right now we are bringing redux.
We need to do the logic right here with CONNECT at the bottom of the hour of here.
So I'm going to go and say connect opening close and then open and close.
Now another thing I'm going to do I'm going to bring map state to prompts.
Maybe you're wondering why bring him upstate props.
Well the problem is that we want to add this to the user only if the user is logged in.
What happens if the user has not indicated and you know this one it's a different component so what
we need to do is to check inside prompts if the user is authenticated.
If not of course we don't add anything so user and of course we need to put maps take to.
So whenever this component loads we have the data of the user inside to state that user that user data.
All right.
OK.
That's good.
So instead of doing this I'm not going to do it right now because we should be getting an error message
if we go right here and do something.
But that's OK.
I'm going to go and bring the action card.
Right.
Are going to go to user actions.
And of course I'm going to add the type now the type.
Again real simple to card user or something like that.
Add to card and then user.
All right let's add two other types.
So export Konst.
And of course add underscore to card user.
OK.
Very good.
Now I get the type so I'm going to go back to user actions and I'm going to go right at the bottom.
They're going to do of course to function.
Now for now we are not going to do anything and the function.
It's so simple it's really really simple.
We just need to request the complicated part and this section is going to be on the server side so function
our two cards are going to call it add to cart just like this.
Open and close and we will be getting an ID which is the ID of the product.
Right.
And then of course we can return open close type with add to cart user and a payload that for now it's
not going to do anything.
We're going to do this in a couple of minutes.
OK.
Let's do the reducer so we can again get that out of the way.
So user we have the coma ATM card user and Ronnie.
Right now the only thing we're going to do is just return the state whenever we get the route done then
we're going to finish this.
So return that that that state.
OK.
Very good.
So now I'm going to go to court.
I'm going to go back to court.
We have this ATM card function right here.
Calls at the.
And what we will need to do whenever is that when we do an enclave right here we want to dispatch an
action right.
And we have it right here in my inside of my button of the card Add to Cart.
We are not going to do a console log anymore.
Now we will dispatch an action that you know.
Right now it's not going to do anything.
Now we need to know if the user wants to add to the card and the user is antiquated.
So first I'm going to check to prop's dot user dot user data remember that we get everything inside
user data and then is ours.
So if the user is out we will do it.
If not we are not going to do anything or are we just going to say you know you need to log in.
So I'm going to do it right here.
You need to log in and right here we will do this.
But Probst that dispatch and we do that at to cart remember that we are getting everything inside probs
and we need to pass the ID so we pass the ID of the product.
Of course if I'm not locked then I'm not going to get anything.
Let me go right here to the console.
If I add the cart nothing happens and if I go to state nothing happens right.
Products to Shaab brands and everything else.
So nothing really happens.
OK.
So of course if I log out and try to add from the cart we get.
You need to log in.
So right here you could show me a pop up or something like that.
I'm not going to really do it because we overdid pop ups but it's very simple.
It just render a different component could be a reusable component that says you need to log in go to
log in and then maybe you can give a link.
You know the usual stuff.
Now the hard part it's going to be on the server.
So let's go let's go to the server and do it.
OK so now we get to do the user you know the card logic on the server.
I can go to my car and I'm going to show you what I get from the final product.
You know the final project because we have a we have a tiny problem that I need to explain with an example.
If not you're not going to get it.
So let's say that I'm a new user and I'm adding an item to the cart.
Now I'm going to go to this.
It's not offenders and Ivan is going to click at court and we get the number one.
OK.
So I'm adding to cart and we get the quantity of one ride and the prize and the total amount and everything
else.
So now I'm going to go and do this fender.
So I'm going to add it.
And now we have two items.
They are two different items ride quantity of one quantity of one.
What happens if I go back to guitars and I want to buy two of these guitars are going to look.
And what we're going to show a different element with the same guitar.
Well not really.
So when I'm going to do.
I'm going to cook it right here.
And we get nothing right here at the top.
But now we get the quantity of two.
So from the server we need to of course enter to the user information on the database check if what
they are trying to add.
It's already on the database and go to this product they have on the cart and change the quantity of
to if of course the product.
It's not duplicate it.
Then we will add a new element to that array.
And if you remember on the user data right here we get the cart.
Let me see if I can find it.
Maybe Of course we didn't have it because it's not you know we didn't have any cards.
So let me go to user model so we have a card and it's a default of an empty array.
All right.
So let's begin with all of this inside of the server and to use this closes and go to the server.
You go to the user part of the file.
And why not here at the bottom.
OK.
So let's begin all of this logic.
So first we need a prompt.
Right.
So app that post open and close because we're going to be passing at least the idea.
All right.
So API for Slash users for Slash add to cart.
This is the route that Acoma.
And again they need to be authenticated.
So this is the second check.
The first one it's this one.
But if they are still not authenticated the you know nothing is going to move forward.
So open and close and we say request and response right now.
Remember that whenever we are passing through the middle we're out with the returns the user.
Right.
All the data of that user.
OK.
That the user that contains this token.
So by default inside the server you know where we are passing out of.
And we go to the Colback right here we can enter the user information right.
Like the user id and everything else and everything else is going air with all the information is going
to be inside.
Request that user just like this.
All right.
So first I want to use.
I went to enter the user data on Mongo the user is trying to do something on their account.
So I'm going to find the user right here I'm going to enter the data of the user.
OK.
So I'm going to say user because we have the model they're going to use find one.
Right.
So what are we going to be fine.
We're going to be finding you know we need to find by ID because we are have the user ID.
So I want to enter to that user id so request that user dot underscore ID.
Right.
I'm going to do koma open and close and then of course run the function error and duck.
OK.
Now the first thing we need to decide if this is the the what the user is trying to add.
It is a duplicated entry inside of that array or not.
All right.
So first I'm going to set Barville of duplicate to false by default.
We don't have a duplicated entry inside of the user card array.
All right.
So now since we get the information of Inside Out of the user information.
Right.
And even though we get it right here from dog whenever we find it one can access both.
I can do Doc Dot card dot for each and I'm going to do for each open and close.
So what we want to do we want to loop all the information that the user has inside the card.
Right.
Could be nothing or could be you know 20 articles.
And if we find one that it's repeated with the one that they are trying to add then we change this duplicated
it to true.
So that field it's duplicated.
And then of course that will decide what we are going to be doing here.
So OK so I'm going to say item and then run a function.
So if opening close and we're going to do something now what you can do as well.
You can check all of this out.
But I'm just making kind of adult check.
I'm entering the user from this find one with the ID.
All right.
So I'm going to enter item and the ID right.
OK.
So then I can say equal equal equal equal equal and then request that query that product ID.
Let me just.
Product ID.
So whenever we get the list of you know the thing that we want to add it's inside the query of product
ID.
This is going to come from the client.
So now we have the idea of the product that they are trying to add and this item id we don't have it
of course and that's why it's a little bit confusing.
Whenever we are adding or we finish adding products inside of the array of the user.
Right here let me just give you an example.
We're going to have many products in our array of products and with the product we will have an ID.
So what we are doing we are entering whatever information they have if they have information they do
have information and we are checking if one of the all the elements they have in the cart contains the
ID of whatever they are trying to update right now.
So if we do find something on that array we're going to send that we can change it to placated to true.
All.
And let me go back on this one.
So after this we know it would be useful to know the application knows that if they are trying to use
to add a duplicate entry or not.
So if we do have a duplicate it going to run some code right.
If of course we have something new.
Maybe they want to add something new.
We're going to do.
Else.
And they're very different operations.
If there is if it's duplicated we need to enter to that ID you know to the same ID enter and modify
the quantity.
If not we're going to push something new to that.
Right.
So when are we going to do the new one then begin to do the duplicated first since we have the user
going to enter user and I'm going to say find one an update.
We've already you know have the user we are already inside the user.
But but we need to do is to update whatever inside the user to open and close.
Can to go here and say underscore ID equals request coma user coma and then underscore ID.
So we are pretty much entering the user data information in a coma and we need to tell what we want
to do and now we need to push something to the right.
So I'm going to say push common.
We need to push an object.
So we're going to push an object.
What are we need to do.
We need to push something inside cart.
It's all in the mix space right here.
And then what are we going to be pushing.
All right.
We're going to be pushing the following that that's the logic pretty much.
Now whenever we push something we need you know several things we need the I.D. We need the mongoose
sorry the ID sorry you let me go here and we need the quantity.
So I'm going to say quantity just like this.
And we prefix it to one because you know we are just adding one to the to the right.
You know that item it's unique so far.
Of course if it's duplicated begin to do the code right here.
OK.
And then I get to do coma and I'm going to put the date so date right and the date and right here you
can choose whatever you want are going to do something simple to just put the date with javascript.
Now whenever we push a new item to the cart right whenever we push an item to the cart we want to give
an ID because later we're going to be searching by id and the ID has to be an object ID.
You know the mongoose type object ID.
So I'm going to go right here and say mongoose dot types.
Remember if we overdid this i'm said that this is an object ID.
And of course I'm going to be passing that request that Querrey dot product ID.
So that's going to be the ID.
All right.
And that is that is it for now.
Of course right here I'm going to do coma.
And I want to get the document back you know whatever the day whatever.
After we push this to the database I want to get that document back.
So for it to get it back we need to do new equals true.
All right.
Then I get to do coma and the last part of the code.
It's going to be the callback function.
And what we get when we get it we'll be getting is the error doc.
And then something else we're going to do something else.
So if we do get an hour I'm going to return a response with a Jaison open close saying success falls
falls and then are back and don't worry after we do it no we can see how it works we're going to go
over this again.
Just a quick recap.
Now I'm going to go and say OK if everything goes ok.
I want to send the status of 200 right and I'm going to send Jason back Where'd the dark dot and whatever
we are adding to the cart.
I'm not sending the whole user document.
I'm just saying sending back whatever we get inside court.
And right now we are just storing this the id the quantity and the date.
Right.
That's the only thing we are doing.
All right.
Let me make this a little bit nicer.
So in theory this route should be ready it's actually ready to be used if we want to add one.
Of course we don't.
We don't get the duplicate.
So I'm going to copy the you're.
Going to go to use her actions and right here I'm going to of course you know dispatch do you actually
create an actual request.
All right.
So Konst request equals ASIO's that post open it close and we need to pass the user server just like
this user or server.
And we closed it and we need to do the add to cart.
Let me go to the server and copy the your mail again.
So again it's Add to Cart.
OK.
So back to user actions and to court.
And remember we are passing the Querrey right.
We are passing the query.
OK.
So I'm going to do.
Open it close.
And then Product ID right.
We are not sending this adjacent just us as a query string and we pass the ID that the user is trying
to enter.
And then of course we have then open it close the response and we do response response that data data
right.
So now this whenever we go to the producer we will you know get the information back to the reducers.
Now the reducer needs to grab that information and instead of returning the card we need to go to the
user.
Let's see if I can get it right here.
Now let's look at.
So we need to go to the user data we have on the state of redux enter the user data attach just grab
whatever is inside leave it but modify just the cart ride.
So we're going to use the A-6 going to say user data entering user data.
And remember that we have it right here.
Right.
So we are entering that field and I'm going to do OK.
I want to start inside just leaving aside whatever we have inside state and use our data.
Right.
But I want to enter that card and modify it with whatever we get from the action that payload.
Remember that the server when it returns it returns the all the information that we have inside.
Not just this element that we are pushing right.
It returns all the contents of the card.
So whenever we get to the we do sir we will just modify whatever it's inside the cart.
All right.
So in theory we should be getting something at least or an error or something like that.
So let's go right here.
Going to logout from here going to make this a little bit smaller.
Logan Franz's password 1 2 3 are going to log in.
All right going to go to guitarist and I'm going to add one and notice that we get the number one right
here.
So if we go to the user to the store we can say user data card and it gets updated.
So user data of course user data we go to the card.
And now we have one.
And now what do we get on the card.
It's some small information just the ID of whatever we are adding the quantity and date.
So why we are just adding just three fields and not the whole information of the product.
You know this this model you know the product details could get really long.
Right now it's not that long.
So if we always tried to push a lot of information right here inside of the user data each time we need
to get something from the server is going to get bigger and bigger and bigger.
So the only thing we do is just we add the id the quantity and date.
So later when we go to the user cart right here we don't have the route instead of just getting it from
the user data.
We're going to go to the server and search all the IDs that they have there and fetch it from mongoose.
Right.
Fritsche from the server only when we do this request and not every time remember that we have the AUF
on the top.
So again if we this this needs to be small as we can actually do it it needs to be small.
So what happens if I tried to add a new one.
That's what happens.
I'm going to do this and we get my card.
So now we get to an open user user data card and we get to.
All right.
So everything works.
So let's go to the next one and we're going to do a tiny recap of what we just did here.
And then we can it go to create duplicated.