OK so let's do a tiny recap of the cart.
So from the cart component which is this one right here we are clicking that button and we are dispatching
an action to the cart.
Right.
So that action goes to the server and the server of course listens for this.
Now we have a now with middleware that is retrieving all the data checking of the user south and Decatur
not checking tokens and everything else.
And at the end it will turn all the data we have inside of the user.
Then what do we do.
We find the user.
Now if we stop for one second and think about this the we are using the Find one right we are finding
all the data instead of the user.
And we've already have an inside out.
We already get it.
But the thing is that in your application maybe in your application you are not going to be returning
the user because there is kind of a pointless returning all the information.
I did this of course because I'm teaching but maybe you want to just return the ID because that's the
only relevant thing.
Just returning the ID of the user if the user self-educate it.
So.
Right.
So again of course if this is the case if you're just returning the ID on the server of course you need
to do find one.
In this case we could have skipped define one and just do that duplicated.
But in this case we are just entering a user.
We are finding that user by the user id we get from the south and we are entering all the data of the
user.
Right.
So if we take this as an end and is an example I go to two users when we go to users and this one this
one and we go to card and we have two elements.
So we get all this information.
What we do we do a loop and check if we have a duplicate it Id remember that from user actions we are
passing the ID of the product.
We want to add to the cart if we do have a duplicated inside of the this instance of the user you know
inside cart we will just change the Bible to duplicated or false.
So if the if it's duplicated we do some code that we actually we don't get.
We don't have right now.
But if it's not duplicated we add a new documents.
So I'm going to go to that user or I'm going to enter to that user.
And again we could have used user find a use it again and again to push everything to the cart write
whatever data we get on the card.
So we are entry card.
You're adding an ID and we are making the ID of the element that we want to add as a mongoose types.
Right.
An object ID because later we need to loop all these cards and get the object at this as an object id
and this object d equals to the object id we have inside products.
Right.
All right.
Then we add the quantity of 1 because this is a new element.
And then we do that now right to Abda date just in case you can do whatever you want right here if we
want to get the document back.
The one we just enter.
We just do new and true.
I'm sorry now we enter the whole document.
So what we do we of course then we run a function if we get an error we return an error.
And at the very end we send a status of 200 and we send the Jason back.
Now instead of sending the whole document of the user because this is what we get back.
The whole user we just send what the user gets inside the card.
After we push it.
Of course that's why we used to.
If we don't use this and we use something else it's going to return to the previous.
So OK.
Now we inside Jason we have the new state of the card.
So the reducer is going to get that.
And instead of updating all the user data because we don't have it from the response we just get the
card information we are grabbing the previous state of the user data ride.
And we are merging it with the response we get from the server.
So we are just updating the cart inside the previous user data and we updated with the new values.
So that's what what happens in a nutshell.
Remember that you could have used the user we get from our right that user.
And maybe instead of doing find one use the same user.
All right let's get another do the duplicated.
This is fun.
This is going to be fun.
Going to go here and start this is we have a duplicated again we are going to do the same thing.
I'm going to go and find one an update.
So what do we need to find.
All right I'm going to go here and I need to find the user right and I need to find the ID of the element
that it's duplicated.
Maybe this one is duplicated.
All right.
So going to find the user.
And I'm going to go to the card and find the ID that it's duplicated and that's the one that we are
going to be changing or modifying.
All right.
So find user.
Let me do it like this.
That's a little bit better.
So first I do find the ID.
I'm going to go and find the ID of the user right.
OK.
So request that user dot underscore ID.
Now we are inside the user but I also need to find the record.
And if you remember whenever we add something new elements on the array we are doing this as an ID.
And it's inside of cart.
So I'm going to be passing this and a cart that ID and I need to find and we need to use the same thing.
This is an object ID.
So I need to find whatever object id that it's equal to the request query query and product ID that
they are trying to add.
So this is going to go and find let me do it like this are going to close this or go.
This is going to go and find the product we want to update inside of the card of the user.
Right.
It's not just entering the user so we're going to do.
Coma.
All right.
Going to go right here.
Now the next one is going to be what are we going to be doing.
So we don't really need to update anything.
We think about it we know it's going in kind of an update but what we want to do is just change the
number and quantity.
And this is an integer.
So if we have one it's too if you have three it's going to be four.
And so on.
Of course.
So what we need to do it's increment and for this with magos we have an increment so open and close.
Right.
So what we increment is whatever we have inside the card going to say cart and the way we increment
we need to do dot dollar sign dot and then the name of whatever we want to no change.
In this case is going to be quantity and how much are we going to increment this.
So by 1 that is that this is going to go to that record and increment the value by 1.
Okay.
So then of course coma and we when to go to the next thing.
Again we need to return to you.
True.
And this one will return all the card elements inside the user.
And that's one of the reasons of where we are doing this.
If not of course on the client or maybe right here at the end we will need to do something else.
But for now we are sending everything that is inside of the card of the user.
And then of course we just sent a response back.
Now what we can do is pretty much the same thing because it's pretty much the same function.
All right.
So this will of course increment by one that same article.
Okay.
So I'm going to save it and let's you know let's try it in a reload the application and I know that
I have an R G to 5 5 right click here and I'm going to go to robo 3 go to users and check this.
So the card now we have to.
Even though we just dispatched that action.
And if we go to the first one which is the R.G. 2 5 5 we get to if I just do it again.
Let me just do it again.
Now we're going to have three.
So if I go users open that card go.
Now we have three.
So the quality is very good.
So this works OK so now we need to do this.
So so far we can just add guitars from the actual card but not from the product so we can add this.
And of course this could be a lot more dynamic ride.
Again I'm teaching I need to be as clear as I can I can I can be.
So if you want to make it a little bit more dynamic you know maybe create an actual function right here
and pass arguments.
Yeah trust just try to do it to do it a little bit smaller.
Let's get.
So first we need to do this.
This is the last thing we're going to do for this section and then we're going to go to the actual user
account.
OK.
So whenever we need to add to cart we click and with dispatch and action.
So I'm going to go to that component which is the index of products.
And right now we have the card handler and this one goes to the product info.
So I'm going to go to product info just to make sure we are passing this.
So on the go here product info it's inside Pernik actions and whenever we go to product actions actually
we are not doing anything.
We are just saying at cart a consulate.
So of course we need to go back to the parent and trigger this function at the card function.
You know the property we are passing it's going to go to product info and I'm going to of course at
this.
So instead of the console lock it's props you know the problem we are getting from the parent and triggering
the function after cart.
Right.
So this function it's expecting the idea of the you know element that all the product we want to attach.
So this one is inside detail an idea all right now going to go back to the index.
We need to add this function to create it because we don't have it.
So anti-car car $10 you could do it like this or you could do it like this.
All right.
So now inside of here we'll be getting the ID right.
So far so good.
I'm going to cancel the ID just to make sure we are getting an ID.
I'm going to reload the application of course it's going to fail because the server needs to we start
at the cart and we get the idea.
Fine.
OK.
So now of course we need to dispatch an action right.
We need to bring readouts and everything else.
We've already have redux.
So what we need to do is we need to bring the user right the ATA card from user.
So import add to card and we call this this way from.
And then re-act redux just let me make sure the name of the function is correct.
Yeah that is correct.
Right.
So when you just need to dispatch the action we've already have redirects right here.
So again to go to the handler and of course this that's prob the props props that dispatch dispatch
and we say at cart.
And of course we need to pass the ID and that is it
react redux at cart we didn't have a next board.
Yes we do to cart.
Of course it's not.
This is not done for Slash dad for Slash one more.
Let me get the out to complete.
Maybe it's a little bit slow.
There we go.
Actions.
And then user actions sorry for this again
OK.
So we've already have this one and we have three of this one.
So I'm going to go to a different one.
I'm going to do the the rocket went out.
It's a rocket cart.
And now we have three.
All right.
So we're going to go and we have to.
If I open it again we have three.
And the third one it's the one.
Let's do it again.
Users won card three.
We have two.
So everything works.
So now what we need to do we need to go to the My Account that closes my account and whenever we go
to my cart we're going to fetch all the documents all the products right here show the quantity and
everything else.
Do the sum and later do the Pay-Pal.