OK science now we can add products to the user cart.
Now we of course will create the end point where we can see the cart remove items get the total amount.
And of course to check out if you want to buy this.
OK.
So first we need to do a lot of things we didn't have a component for this and we need to add it to
the routes as well.
So going to go to the user component and creating a new file called cart.
Yes.
All right.
So of course this one will be a react Cosbys component just like this and I'm going to call it user
cart.
OK then I'm going to bring the user layout so import import user lay out from that force last one more
time and then chose C for Slash and the user.
All right.
Now I'm going to bring connect.
We're going to use later so import connect from re-act redux react and then redux.
Right.
And we're going to use fonts.
Awesome.
So I'm going to import some brain now so we can get an out of the way and then later of course we're
going to use it and we don't need to do the boring you know import.
Awesome awesome.
And then icon and it's going to be from and it's at the fort.
Awesome react for it.
Awesome right.
So the two icons we need to use is the FAA import FAA and then frown just like this from ad and it's
forward awesome again.
But this one it's the free solid and we need to pass.
Of course the name of the icon right here.
And the other one will be the opposite of this which is F A and then smile.
All right.
I'm going to grab the connect.
I'm going to do the connect and then wrap the components and right here I'm going to go and say cart.
So OK.
We can use this right now.
And of course we are going to get something at least before I can do that.
I cannot wrap everything inside of the user or lay out so we can get the beautiful land.
And then of course we need to create the route we need to tell the router that we want to use this.
So I'm going to go here and say import user cart and notice that I'm doing this on the opening section.
So I'm going to call it again use cart real simple and it's from from DOD force components for Slash.
Then user for Slash and then cart right in it copy the user dashboard because pretty much the same configuration
and it's going to be inside user and then cart and we will use the component just like this we're going
to log out right here and get to log in.
All right.
So franaise.
And then password one two three.
OK.
So if I go to use our card we get a card that is good.
So what do we need to do first before we can do anything.
We need to fetch the list of items we have in the cart and we need more information than the one we
have and the redux store whenever we go to the user state.
So if I go to user user data we go to the cart and we get three items.
But this is just the idea of the product the quantity and the date.
So of course we need a lot more than this right.
So what we will do will creating you create a new route on the server of course.
And right here we're going to go to redux go to that server and past the list of the ID you know this
ID is that right.
And of course the server will get the ID and return the the all the up you know the detailed information
about this product.
Of course we didn't have this route.
We're going to create in a couple of minutes.
So first of course I'm going to do some things right here.
I'm going to add first to state.
We're going to use the state and this one is going to be equal to loading.
So we're going to have this loading then a coma at the end.
Of course we need to calculate the total So the total always starts at zero.
Now if the transaction goes success I'm going to do a show and then success just like that of course
at the beginning it's going to be false.
Now of course if we don't have any items or will you know after we created a section I need to lead
the application know that we want to show the total.
So at the beginning is going to start.
It's false.
And after we get all the information from the server and you know to everything else you can of course
change it to true.
If we do have items on the card because could happen that we don't.
OK.
So what we need to do we need to dispatch an action right.
All right.
We don't have this.
We're going to create in a couple of minutes.
So when we do it we're going to do it on the component at Mt..
Right.
Okay.
Now I'm going to create two different virals and I can explain why in a second I'm going to create a
cart.
Let part item equals That's right.
OK.
So they're going to say lead user they're going to just make reference to create an alias for this.
I mean to say that this that prompts the user.
So basically I'm just entering prompts and getting everything that it's inside of the user including
the user data.
And of course all the card that it's inside the user data now to access prompts.
Of course we need to do the map state to prop's So we're going to go and do map state to prop's map
state to prop's going to dilute the own props.
And what we what we'll be going to using is the user Ryan.
So user user it just maps state prompts nothing new so far.
So let me tell you what the problem is of me.
Go right here to our application and of course if I check the state I have a card.
Ryan and his ID card.
We have three elements.
So the only only information that we get inside of here is just the idea of the product and the quantity.
Right.
OK.
Now where do we go to the server.
The server will return this ID.
Right.
It's going to return pretty much the same array.
But with all the detailed information.
Right.
OK.
Now the problem is that we to get it from the server from the model of products and we didn't have the
quantity right there.
So we need to make a mix between both.
We're going to can begin to get.
Of course this card from the user.
And we're going to bring the one from the server that belongs to this ID.
And inside of that result we're going to inject the quantity that we get for that for that product.
All right.
So let's go to the component about let's start this.
Now first we need to do something if we do have information inside the user card data.
So first I'm going to say if user because we made a name I where I hear that and then user data you're
entering prompts.
And then the user data.
Right.
These are data dots and begin to use carped begin entering the card.
If we do have information inside the card if we do have a card then of course we're going to move forward
because we do have a card.
Now the problem again is that the card might be empty.
So I'm going to do one more check.
I'm going to say if user that cart data Dot card again that and then length you know very simple solution
length it's there go it's greater than zero.
Then of course we assume that we know actually that we get some we have some information inside the
cart.
So we want to go to the server and get it right.
OK.
Now again we can not pass this to the to the server.
We could you know and do all the logic on the server.
But on the server we just need to pass the ID remember that we can get around to just like this that
where we can pass many IDs and we're going to get the information about this.
Well this is pretty much the same idea.
We cannot pass this of objects to the server because we just need the I.D. We don't need the quantity
or nor the date.
So we're going to go here and say OK I want to enter the user again user data.
We could create an alias for user data and card you know so card data and then going to do a For Each
cell for each.
Let me do it right for each.
OK.
So open it close.
Now we're going to get one item and then we're going to do something.
So we're not going to do.
We're going to make reference to this card item and they're going to do push open it close and it get
it past the item that I.D..
So at the end we just get a single barbel with an array which has IDs you know we have three products
you can have the idea of this product and the of course coma.
The idea of the second one and so on.
So we can check send this to the server and the server will know that oh ok I need to fetch all the
products.
So this is pretty much what we are doing right now.
We could handle this directly on the server.
But again I prefer to do it right here on the client Ogam of course then when you did this pageant action
we don't have an action let's create it right now.
So let's go to user actions here.
User actions and of course when two types.
So instead of user actions I'm going to create a new one we could call it whatever we want to call it
a get carte items.
So export function get cart items now on this one we will be getting two different arguments right.
So cart items which is the array of items.
And then I get to pass a second thing which is user and then cart.
Let me go use our cart of course at the end you're going to return a type and a payload.
So gonna return the type which is going to be let's call it get carte items.
User.
OK.
So of course then a payload.
And for now the payload is going to be empty payload empty.
And of course we need to do more work right here at the right time at the top going to save it to go
to types and export Konst.
And then of course we do it again get it dry get carte item and the user.
You could call it whatever you want doesn't matter.
So now you get the user action and we need to add it to the reducers.
So I still are going to bring the time at the top so coma type and then are going to go right here at
the bottom.
So case we get the get item card use or whatever I want to return open and close that state and that's
it for now.
Of course we're going to test Rob first.
It's OK.
We have the actual function which so we can dispatch it right.
OK.
Get the card items going to go to court and I'm going to import it at the top so import just like this.
And of course let me just double check.
Yeah we need to go right here and save from and we need to directory's up to the DOT DOT DOT for Slash
and then actions for Slash and it's user actions.
OK.
So everything looks nice.
Of course.
Now we need to dispatch it.
So let's let's created this patch.
Of course after we're done we're going to say this that prompts that dispatch.
All right.
Open and close now get carte items and I'm going to be passing this card item we get right here and
then I'm going to be passing coma.
And it has the user that user data dot cart Oh sorry cart.
So I think it's again the card of the user.
So if you go here I'm passing this information.
The one that contains the the ID the quantity and the date.
You can see why in a second.
And of course then we can catch to then of course we just run a function was simple and begin to of
course do something.
All right.
So what is going to happen of course begin to make the request and begin to inspect it from here because
it's going to be a little bit weird.
There's kind of a funny scenario.
So we're going to go do we have a route to do this.
Well if we go to the server just here if you go to the server and start you know we try to find a route
where we can make this we do have it right.
We have the articles by id remember the articles by ID might be getting an ID quite type 1 ID and many
ID at the same time.
And right here we have that we have just that you know just an array with items so we can use this.
Articles by id route.
OK.
I going to go back to user actions and remember that these articles by ID is a product route and at
the top we are not importing the user that the products server we are using the user server.
So I'm going to go copy the product server going to go back to user actions and import it at the top.
So now we can use it.
OK.
I'm going to go back and bomb.
And I'm going to say Konst re quest equals then we get X-post that get opening close and remember that
we are we're using quite strings.
We're going to use quite strings so we make reference to that products and that server or at done so
if you remember the route its products Oh it's articles right.
Forgot the name of the route.
Articles by ID.
So then I had to pause for a second.
Are Building.
They're making a new building just you know.
And they're driving me crazy.
So I had to stop it for a minute.
So of course we need to pass strings and we need to pass the ID equals the card items.
Right.
And if you remember we need to give the type of this says we're passing an array.
We need to say array.
OK.
Of course then we will get a new response.
I'm going to do this at the bottom.
Then of course we get you response and then that response begin to getcha.
Catch the data and we're going to have a lot of problems a few problems with this first going to the
console log and then check what we get from response that data.
And I at return the response that data this is going to change a little bit in a minute.
And of course right now I'm going to send back whatever we get from the request and I'm going to go
to the user and do the user right here.
Now I'm just going to do the project so we can of course get it later.
So we going to return the state and a cart detail so all of the information about the cart is going
to be inside this key card detail we're going to of course see it working later.
So OK so we can skip the error message if we don't return anything from the promise.
So at the end we get this you know and we are actually getting something from the server.
So we get all the information about the product right.
The first one it's the first item which we have three.
We have three we purchased three of this item.
So the title the rocket whatever whatever whatever that is good.
So we get all the information now.
The problem is that it's out of here we didn't have the quantity.
How many items we purchase of this one are we added to the card of this one actually we added to the
carby getting to the purchased just yet.
So what we need to do we need to inject how many items of this ID we have inside the user.
And then the card detail remember that we got that information and the card detail.
Let's go to the right here now.
Now this one I'm sorry the is the user data and the cart right here we have three.
So we're going to loop this.
The response we get back from the server begin to match the IDs and if there is a match We're going
to insert a new key telling us the quantity.
So in the future we can of course just use this to get the all the data of the product and how many
items they are you know purchasing.
All right let's.
Of course one way to do it.
So back to the user action.
I'm going to delete this action.
I'm going to delete this because we are not going to need it.
So we're going to get a response with three items right now.
And of course we get the user Karch which is the detail information that says the ID and the quantity.
So we going to make a mix out of both marvels.
So use are going to enter use cart and are going to do for each each and this one of course we will
pass the item and then we will run a function where we do something.
Now this one is going to be the parent ride.
So for each child inside of the response are going to love the child.
And I'm going to try to match the idea of the parent if there is a match.
We're going to add the quantity to the child of the parent.
So responds that data that for each.
Right.
So opening close and I'm going to say right here.
OK.
And I you could call this whatever you want.
Now of course we're going to answer the first one which is the first element of the parent.
And then we're going to enter and loop all the responses all the array we get in response to data.
So if the let me do an if if the item which is the item parent that ID matches one of the child IDs
we get then we get to enter the child inside responds that data are going to enter with the iteration
and are going to say OK I want to add one that says quantity just like this and the value of this is
going to be equal to whatever we had we get on the parent for the same ID.
So item that quantity.
And at the end we'll have pretty much the same response data but with the real quantity inside.
OK I'm going to go back and say return response that data.
All right so.
OK.
So now we're going to be getting the information to see want together get right.
Let's inspect.
So it reloads and of course we go to state.
Now go to user and I get to go to car detail and right here at the bottom we get the quantities for
this when we get to ride.
We didn't have that.
Now we get it now and the other ones we just have one.
So you want to do one and the other one.
It's one but we have three.
OK.
A lot.
So of course now we're going to loop all of this information we can create a new component that renders
all the blocks right here and we're going to be passing this information right.
And they will show the title the image the quantity and everything else.
And then we will create a function that can loop.
This is going to grab the prize.
And of course multiply the prize because we needed to calculate the total.
Now the only thing that we're not going to do.
And of course if you want to do it no problem that's you know it's going to be fun.
It's of course to reduce the quantity maybe have a button to add more or reduce more.
And for this of course you will need a special route or special logic because you need to grab the idea
of whatever the user or they are they are trying to do.
Go to the server modify the quantity from the server and when it comes back you need to re fetch or
recalculate all of this through the store run.
All right.
So let's go to the next section.
We're going to grab the list of products and create the blocks right here.