OK so now we're going to create the carts Ryan.
OK.
Now again if you're asking yourself dude can we do this on the server.
Well yes you totally can.
That is the one of the benefits of you know creating your own server.
You can go to the routes and do whatever logic you want to do.
Sometimes that it's not possible sometimes someone will hire you to create the application or the web
page or whatever it is that you want you're you're getting hired to do and they will tell you.
OK.
So I have a server guy.
So you need to work with him.
All right.
So that is a problem because if you get a crazy idea or you have a crazy idea or you know maybe an idea
of doing something you can not just really go to the server and touch it yourself.
You need to send the mail to the guy and say Dude I need this and maybe a is going to pass maybe a week
maybe a month or maybe more until they give you just this line of code instead of a route.
So yeah this is one of the benefits of what we're creating yourself.
Creating server yourself.
Most of the times you're going to work the other way you're going to do the front end and someone else
is going to do the backend.
That's the way it works.
So this would be the best the best approach because you have pretty much the whole control.
This one is just returning something very simple.
So you do all the logic right here.
Right.
OK.
So let's create the cart.
So right then so far we don't have anything.
And later are we going to use this then.
Right now we're going to leave it empty but begin to do something else much much later.
First we need at least some cartes.
So I'm going to create a really usable component because we might be using it later.
So I'm going to create a new folder inside tells that cause user just like this user and right here
are going to create a new component called I don't know product.
BLOCK Yeah.
Why not.
Product block.
So it's a re-act react stimulus component.
All right.
So user product and then block.
Right.
So this one just going to say block.
So of course we need to do some something here.
We need to import at least this.
So it's going to be use our product.
Block from that that forward slash you tels for Slash user for Slash and then product block.
All right.
Now before we can include the component we need to do some more lay out right here.
First we need to title Ryan pretty simple.
So where we get card going to say H1 and then my cart cart just like this.
And then of course I'm going to rub everything inside of a depth.
So class name of user underscore carked and I'm going to include all the cards right here top so open
and close.
Now we need to pass some props right here.
First is the products so I'm going to say products and what you can do.
You can just pass the card detail with all the products or you can pass the user pass a user because
we might be using more things later.
So I'm going to pass whatever I get inside that this that prompts that user and instead of here we get
the card details.
Well again if we might we might be using this later.
So I'm going to name this component that all the blocks right here are from the cart.
Maybe we're going to use it later.
So of course whenever we click an item we need the ability to remove the item so I'm going to say remove
item and of course we're going to catch the I.D..
So going to see I.D. and then we will run a function.
So does that remove from cart that we didn't have this function right here on our component.
And we don't have it on the server.
We don't have a router for deleting card items.
Of course we can it created much later.
Right.
So let's go to user product block.
Now we're going to get it.
We're going to get the products type and remove item.
So instead of doing prompts right here I could use some destructuring and say that I just want to get
the products I just want to get the removed item and I'm going to keep the time because we are not going
to use it from here just now later if we do use it.
We know that we have a type.
So we can include it maybe later.
All right.
So the first thing is catching whatever we get inside products card detail and show it on screen.
So I'm going to go here and say render items it's a function.
So I'm going to create a function.
So it's Konst name of the function.
Then of course we run something and we want to return some GSX.
Right.
OK.
So instead of here we need to make sure that we have about detail so I'm going to answer that products
and I got to say if we do cart cart with T and then Details.
Details then we want to do something if not again which is return NULL.
Pretty basic.
Now if we do have card details when it enter and I want to loop it because we might have many or maybe
just one.
So it's going to be we're going to catch the products just like this and then we will return GSX again
now I'm going to get just a div with your class name and this the class to me is going to be user underscore
product underscore and then Block.
And then of course we need to add a key as a key.
I'm going to use the product actually it's Singler product just like this and then dot underscore ID.
So we should be getting at least three when they're reloader again.
Three maybe we are not getting it.
Just let me double check why products products card detail leave its detail.
I'm just flipping a coin right here.
OK I was right.
So now we get three card because you know three items because we have three card.
And now let me just double check something right here.
It's on this one I forgot to change his card instead of card items item is card items.
So I'm going to make it right because we might have many
everything still works.
So I'm going to go back to punt block.
Now on this block you'll have several items like the image the name the quantity the price and then
the button to remove.
So on the on each item I'm going to create a container for this.
So class name and item.
Now the first thing it's the image.
So Dave opening close and I'm going to add a class name opening close and then this one it's going to
be image.
Now image of course has a style of background.
So let me close this so we can see the whole route style opening close background just seems always.
You are l.
We open it close and we could say no repeat.
Why not.
No.
Repeat.
All right.
So just like before this image you know the array of images might be empty.
So we need a function or something that decides if we're going to see the first image on the array or
an image not available so render card can be card or maybe cart image makes more sense.
Card image and of course is a function AAPS a munged function or ago.
Now if you're maybe you're asking yourself dude we could use this in the past shouldn't we use as a
reusable component.
Yeah you should just get to do it this way just here again.
But I'm using a reusable component would be a good idea.
So Alce and of course if we get the images that length and you can go if you wish to the component and
copy the same logic.
It's pretty much the same snippet so return images.
We return the first position then the u r l and of course if we if we don't have it return dot for Slash
images for Slash and then we get the image just not available.
There we go.
I'm going to copy the name because remember I made a mistake with the name.
So I'm going to copy all that close it and return images not a baseball.
All right.
Looks good.
So that's what happens.
OK.
We get an error.
So length of undefined.
So let me just double check why should be ok.
Images of course you're not passing the images.
So it's product dot images.
Let's see if we get images at least.
Got we get something we are not getting the image.
Let me see why declasse image.
All right.
So it was very very dumb.
I forgot to close.
Right here I'm making the call to a function.
And of course I need to close it.
And what I need to do I need to close this.
So this was my mistake.
It was kinda weird Of course not attaching the style property and reload again so we can wait for the
server.
We can get it.
We get that sorry.
It's not available and everything else.
Of course we're going to attach more things to the right.
So this one is going to be pushed to the left.
All right.
Let's get to let's go back over this.
So we need to create more items.
This one is are going to be a little bit easy for us right now.
We need to act as the product name so ate it for then product the name and what we will be attaching
is the product name.
So I'm going to say product that name I'm sorry the brand product brand name and then of course the
product name.
So opening close and product that name lets you forget.
All right.
So we get it.
Next it's going to be the quantity I don't want to retype all of this.
I'm going to copy and paste and say quantity.
All right.
So again we remember that we attached this property quantity.
So we just get it right.
So on the
or it's going to delete does.
Let's see if we get it.
Quantity 2 rocket mental math.
OK.
It's reloading without my change.
That is good.
So.
All right.
So we are done with the quantity.
What else.
We have the price.
So I'm going to delete this one more and this one is going to be the prize.
I know this is boring.
We are almost done.
So I'm going to say price and I'm going to do.
I'm going to do the next one which is actually the Bunin.
So this one will be a little bit special.
I'm going to attached a class of BDM and I'm going to remove this one I'm going to say price right here
horse and I'm going to put the dollar sign right here or whatever currency.
So Def open it close.
And this is going to be the Remove button.
So class name and then cart underscore remove underscore.
And now we need to attach a non-collector to this because whenever we click that we want to trigger
the function that we are passing this prompts this one remember remove item.
All right.
So whenever we click it and I'm going to do it here we are going to trigger a function called remove
item and remember that we are doing the structuring so we don't need to do props.
Remove item we are already kind of doing this now we need to tell this function which is DJT that we
want to delete if we go here we are passing an ID.
So we need to pass it.
So it's product dot underscore ID and right here we're going to say remove or something like that.
All right.
OK let's see what we get.
Now it's not that nice could be much much better.
Like it's old for the styles we get.
We are not going to do a lot of styles.
It's a pretty simple layout.
So now there are a couple things we need to do.
First we need to create a kind of a function or something that loops all the items we get right here
and we get a total amount you know one half five times three of course than 400 And then one hundred
times two.
And then we sum everything and we show the total amount of what the user needs to pay.
And of course later we're going to add the ability to remove and then we're going to go to Pay-Pal right.
OK.
So let's go let's go to the next one and start doing the same.
And then we move.