All right so let's do the calculate total block.
It's actually very simple.
We just need to catch all the elements we have when we get it from the server.
Ryan can have a list of things so we can go and multiply the amount of items they get for each product
and multiply the price.
So I'm going to go to the dispatch of get cart items going to do.
I'm going to put it here and I'm going to do some logic.
I'm going to open it close and say OK if this dot prompts dot user then card detail can enter the card
details because after we dispatched this we will have a card detail but I'm going to check if we do
have items inside of the card detail.
So if we do begin a trigger function that you know does all the math for this.
So I'm going to call it this calculate total calculate then maybe total or total items or you know total
price or whatever.
And I'm going to pass that this prompts that user that card details so we can you know get it from there.
So there's a problem user card detail.
All right.
We don't have this function again to add it right now and then we get it passed to of course the year
from cult removed from cart.
But first we're going to do this.
So whenever we calculate the total we're going to get the card detail.
So just like this card detail.
All right.
So first of course everything starts at zero so I'm going to say let total equals zero.
Then of course we need to look this card details I'm going to do card detail for each just like this
and on each iteration we're going to pass the item and we can run a function.
So what I do.
I just enter the total and I'm going to do plus equal and what I need to grab from the item it's the
price and then multiply the same price by the quantity right.
Makes sense.
Now sometimes the price or you know maybe the price could be an integer.
So just to be sure are going to do parse and parse and there we go and are going to say that I want
to grab the item that price then we need to pass the prefix.
If not you're going to get a warning.
And then of course we do times and the item that quantity
the item that Fontane that's good.
So that is it.
This is the only thing we need to do which is grab the value we some and then we just multiply.
And of course at the top you're using the state for this.
So we can host the total right here and we want to change the show total to false.
True because let me just give you the example.
Whenever the application loads we don't have a total of nothing until we go to the server and we get
back.
So until that point we shouldn't be just playing a show total right here because you don't really have
items at that point and maybe if you go to the server and you come back maybe you don't have anything
in your cart.
So again we can skip that show total by using true or false.
So I'm going to go and say this.
That said state and begin to change the state of total total to you know the same key value and then
show total to true.
So the dysfunction the only thing it does it grabs the database or whatever we pass it to the from to
the arch as an argument.
We some.
And then of course we multiply and then we just set the state again and we're going to use this cockily
total several times on this obligation from different places.
This one works whenever we are ready to play something right.
Of course we need to go below the use of product.
And you know decide when to show this.
So I'm going to go here and say open it close.
So if this that state that show total it's equal to true then I want to show something.
Right.
If not I'm not going to return anything.
So I'm going to say no.
And we're going to change the interval for something else later.
Going to tell you why.
So I got to say Dave and I'm going to add a new wrapper.
This one will get a class name of user card.
Some could be total or whatever.
And then of course inside I'm going to put a new dev and say total just total and then amount dollar
sign.
Open and close and then we get it from this state a total time.
So in theory we should be getting something at least.
So we get total amount for and if you want to do the math it's of course correct.
All right.
So it's got now the problem is that what happens if you don't have items in your cart instead of just
showing nothing maybe an empty space.
You could show right here the opposite of that which is you know you don't have items.
So I'm going to delete the No.
Going to go at the bottom and say that I want to display a function that says show no item message or
something like that and I'm going to host it.
Could the code inside of a function because you know you get it up.
We get to add more code in a minute.
That's OK.
So just do it do it function.
So I'm going to return.
We could just return some GSX right here.
So I'm going to do it the other way.
Just return some GSX.
So open it close and we return just a div with a class name of card no items.
And this is the class and we will add that font.
Awesome icon.
We've included at the top the frown saying you have no items with a sad face.
So sad icon than the icon it's equal to FAA and then frown.
Going close the font.
Awesome.
And then a dev saying no know you just you have no items.
Now of course I want to see if this works.
But we cannot be actually Google can be because we didn't have the ability to complete the purchase
or remove items.
So the only way we can check this is by going to the server and trying to the user and deleting whatever
we get inside of the card.
So I'm going to try to delete it.
And I believe I just made a mistake and deleted the whole user.
Of course I knew to edited guys and sorry and they create the account again I'm going to put a pause.
And created the user again.
Ok I'm logged in again as Frances same user same same as always.
I'm going to go to my card.
And of course since I've create a new account an account I don't have any card elements.
So we get.
You have no items.
You know that works.
Is it real simple code.
OK.
Now I'm going to give you a different scenario.
What happens whenever you click can complete the purchase you make the pay and everything else.
And you know we complete that circuit.
You are not going to get any items because we can delete them from the database because you've already
made the purchase.
So you don't have those card items anymore.
But again we shouldn't be displaying You have no items again because this is going to go to what you
need to do is to show thank you maybe your order is complete or something like that.
So I'm going to go right here to the No.
I'm going to do one more check.
Remember that we get show success so whenever we complete a purchase a shit change does show success
to true.
So I'm going to do one more check this dot state that shows success opening close.
And of course if this is true or false.
True we're going to show something if not we're going to show this one.
So what are we going to do.
I mean at a diff just here and this one class name of card success and it's you know pretty much the
same thing with it right here.
So I'm going to copy this.
I'm going to paste it and this one it's a smile.
You know the opposite.
And this one should be saying no thank you.
Some like that maybe.
Thank you capitals.
Thank.
There you go.
Thank you.
And I know you are there it is complete now.
Here you go to your account profile and get the order number or you know someone will contact you soon
or you know whatever that you want to do.
Your order is now complete.
Of course we cannot really see this until we finished the Pay-Pal section.
So when we finished a paypal section you're going to see this kick in.
All right for now we're going to leave it at that.
Now what else of course we need the PayPal the Paypal logic so I can to go here at the bottom I'm going
at it right now.
I'm going to do this.
And why am I doing this.
Because we are not done to do the people going to do the remove it's because we can we should only show
the paypal button whenever the total or and whenever we have some carte items.
So I'm going to say this that state DOT show total.
It's true.
Then we can show the Bunin.
If not are not going to do anything.
They're going to put the button inside of a container.
So class name opening close.
Pay Pal pay pal underscore button and then container.
And this one you know pay Paypal whatever
all right let's see if it renders and you have no items.
I'm going to go to guitars.
I'm going to add one at two in at two.
You know one and two of the r.g.
And if I go to my cart we get the amount of the Pay-Pal and everything else.
So now we're going to do the remove of course if you click and nothing happens.
Now the problem is that we don't have a route on the server where we can listen for you know remove
items from a cart.
We have a get cart items you know at the cart and get cart items that me see if I can find it.
Of course cart items is the ID of products.
That's OK.
So just like add to cart you're going to do the move from cart.
It's not just like this is a lot smaller.
So we're going to do it right now.