OK so now we get it create the route so we can remove.
So whenever we click we are going to remove it.
Of course we need a route to do this.
So first I'm going to create the route.
So it's going to be a get route open and close that for Slash API for Slash users and remove from cart
or else we're going to use that Southmead aware and then we will run a function.
And of course it's going to be request and response.
Right.
So what do we need to do.
Of course you could just get the user from here.
But again sometimes you don't get the users maybe you're just returning the idea of the user.
So we need to find the user and do some updates inside of that user.
So we entered the user model.
Then we find one an update open and close if you remember we need to pass a few things.
First is which user are we going to be updating.
So I'm going to say ID can.
And we past whenever we get back from the mouth malware which is a request that user underscore ID.
All right.
That's the first thing.
Then the action that you can take in this case we already to push what we need to do is to remove something.
So for this we use pull.
Now then of course can and what pool needs is an object.
So we're going to say this what are we going to be pulling.
So we're going to pull the full something from the cart so we say cart and then we pass an object.
What are we going to be deleting from the cart.
Well whenever whatever document or piece of code you know entry that has an ID of something.
So again we are using mongoose type IDs inside the carts remember I'm going to copy mongoose types right
here sign or have to type it again and begin to search for whatever type we get from the from the route
you know from the client.
And remember that this route is going to be something like underscore ID equals to and you know the
idea of whatever they want to delete inside of the card of the user.
So we can have a get an inside request that query query that underscore ID in this case I'm going to
use underscore instead of ID.
OK.
So that is that after we make the changes I want the new state of the card off the user as a response
I don't want the old the old state of this.
So if you want know do we need to do new and then true.
So we can get it and then come right at the end of this.
Of course we just run a callback function.
And I remember we told you before that you could do some logic on the server.
Well the thing is that whenever we get the doc back this is the card of the user and on the card of
the user We just have some information we have pieces of information and we go to the cart.
We have the we get the ID the quantity and the date.
So this is a problem because we cannot just return this if we return just this whenever we get it.
We need to dispatch a different action to get the articles date again.
You know we need to trigger again get carte items with the new state of the user.
And you know we are already on the server.
Why not doing all of this logic from here whenever we remove the cart because the only place where we
can remove a card it's from here.
So whenever we go to this cart and we get the dog bag we're going to do some logic if we're going to
get the new state of all of these elements so what are we going to do.
We're going to grab the cart if we can go to Mungo's again and fetch all the data all the data from
here.
And then of course we will merge it.
OK.
So just like we did here just like this this code we're going to do the same thing.
Not this code this code we are going to still do it right here on the actions.
But this one we can of course do it right here.
OK.
So first I'm going to create a virals called cart and I'm going to enter the document that we get back
from this usurp which is the card of the user and you enter the card.
Right.
So now I have a volatile card called card.
With that then I'm going to create in an array led array equals I can loop the card.
I'm going to say map opening close and for each one I'm going to get an item open and close.
So what I want back the same thing we did here we need the IDs ride just an RE with the IDs.
So I'm going to return and of course we need mongoose types.
So we're going to return whatever we get back when we get back from item that you know the card and
this I.D. It is going to be converted to object types.
So now what we can do we can grab this new array and pass it to mongoose so we can get all the data
we can need.
So product going to enter product that they're going to go right here at the bottom.
I mean just do it here.
I'm going to say find OK what do we want to find.
We want to find all the elements which underscore the inside products that matches the all the elements
we have inside the array.
So this is going to go to the server and kind of get it.
All right then remember that the rants and the woods are when we get on a deal with this elements so
we're going to do the same thing we did before.
Just get it.
Go and show you the coach that can really to this to populate and the brand.
So we're going to copy.
We're going to go and say I want to populate the brand and they would on this results as well.
And then of course we execute something.
So exec.
Right.
So whenever we get a response of course of course we run a callback now error and then Card we're going
to get a card detail detail.
All right.
And now like I told before inside of the card right here we're going to get all the card details right.
All the products for the elements we have in the card for user and we still have access to cart inside
of here.
So if you wish you could do all this logic all this logic inside of here and then just return and you
Jason with all the data ready to go you could do that.
So we are not going to do this.
I'm not going to do it.
So I'm going to say return response to the status of two hundred and then we just send this Jaison response
right.
So the Jason response will contain the card detail which is all the data you know all the products detailed
product and I'm going to pass the cart as well.
So now that the action will receive all the card details and the new state of the cart that's why I'm
not going to do the same thing here.
I'm not going to pass.
Do you use a card from the client you're going to get it from the server.
Because at this point the idea that they deleted it's not here or I'm.
So we're going to loop this match this with the card detail and you know return whatever we want to
return.
All right that's good.
So for now the sort of a route it's done.
We don't need to do anything else.
Looks good.
Hopefully everything is OK.
So let's create an action for this.
It's going to go to the card component where we dispatched the action.
So of course we need to include it.
We don't have the function but it created right now.
So remove card item same as usual.
I'm going to copy the name and I'm going to go to user actions.
Going to create a type which is going to I'm going to call it how we should call it remove card item
user name remove the card item and then user.
I'm using user because I'm using user and all the types.
So whenever it comes to user I attached user.
This is something I do if you wish.
Just doing remove card item.
That's OK.
So we have a new type.
We need to add it to the types so export Export Konst equals to remove card item user right.
OK that's good.
So now let me go to the user actions again.
So now we get this type we are going to copy the name of the function so we can create it at the bottom.
So export function export function.
Yep.
Card Room of card.
I'm opening clubs now from this one.
What we will be getting we will be passing is the idea of whatever we want to delete.
The server expects that information you know the id of whatever we want to delete.
So we need to pass the ID right.
So we say Id OK.
Now the request.
It's very simple to Konst request it calls X-post that get open and close and we are still going to
use the same user server we use either on the product server.
Then for Slash and the name of the route which is going to be removed from cart.
All right.
Oh sorry on this one it's user server because we are making a request to the user.
So it's user server or user route.
And then of course remove from cart.
OK.
So on this one we need to pass the ID and we are making a reference to this with underscore ID.
So we just pass the ID and that is it of course then we will get a new response so I'm going to do then
open and close and we get a response back from the server.
And when we do we just do something.
Now what we need to do looks pretty much just like that like this I'm going to still you know type it
all remember that from the server we get back the card detail and use date of card instead of the user.
Right.
OK.
So we need to do the same thing.
Rapid response that data entered the card and do a for each just like this and open and close on each
iteration.
We will be passing that item.
And then of course we run a function.
Now we're going to enter the child of card detail.
It's a response that data data then card detail just like this detail.
Open and close and Azari card detail.
And we do another for each so for each then open close and we just make sure I'm using card detail you
know same key word card it should be carte
cards.
The tail is going to fail.
And this one as well card detail.
All right.
So I'm going to go back and we're going to loop that card detail and for each and just like before we
need to catch the item and to iteration.
And I'm going to delete this one.
All right.
And then of course we run something where we need to check if the item of ID of the child equals the
item id of the parent or actually backwards if the item id of the parent matches the item id of the
child.
And if it does we want to attach the quantity so responds that data Dadds card detail and then we pass
the iteration.
Let me close this so we can see the whole code.
So it's quantity.
Just like with it at the top.
So I'm going to copy this and paste it right here.
So the quantity of the card detail instead of the response we can attach quantity.
And then at the value and at the end.
Of course we return the response that data right.
Right.
So then we're going to do a return and we returned a new type and a payload.
So the payload is equal it's equal to whenever we get back from the request and the type it's removed
card item user almost done with the whole circuit.
All right.
OK.
So now we need to go to the reducer right.
I'm going to copy the type again just in case.
Go to the reducer and then just the type.
So what we need to do here.
It's pretty much the same then.
You know get cart item user.
The thing is that from the server we are getting the card detail and a new cart.
Right.
OK.
And we need to from this card we need to go to the users store to the state and turn the user data and
turn that card and update this cart.
That's why we are also passing the cart.
We are updating several things with the same dispatch.
So use a reduced or remove card item and do coma.
And if the case.
Oh sorry not coma if the case is removed card item.
We're going to do something so we return just it's always dot dot dot.
And then the state and then coma and I'm going to do this just like this.
So it's a little bit easier to read.
So we're going to enter the cart and detail and begin going to say that the card didn't tell now it's
equal to action that payload that card detail.
All right looks good hopefully no mistakes that begin to use the Enter the user data.
Remember that we use the user data right here.
And let me make sure I'm using cart cart detail Yeah it's card detail.
Maybe I made a mistake in using card with a D.
That's OK.
It should be OK.
So I'm going to enter inside the user data.
I'm going to put inside of the user data whenever we get inside user data.
Rhydwen have all the information we get from user data but I want to modify the card.
So I do a coma and a change to cart.
So action that payload that cart that is that we're going to update the card details whenever we remove
one item with a new state of this and then we do the same thing with the user data and the card of the
user data should be OK.
Let's try out.
So we need to go to that function.
Remember when we click it right here and we go to this function.
So what we do is a device that prompts that dispatch to open it close.
And then of course the name of the function the action.
So remove card item remember that we need to pass the ID.
So we are going to be passing the ID so Id And then of course we get a response back.
I'm going to go right here and say then oops then open and close.
We're going to run a function.
Open it close and then we do something.
Now we have two scenarios.
The first one is what happens if the user id sort of the user just they have maybe just one item right
here.
If we remove that single item the card data is going to be empty.
Right.
So we changed the show Teutul back to false.
So we can you know remove the show total right here.
It's going to be total amount zero anyways but we need to remove this item so we can end it the way
we need a way to check if the user has zero card elements zero card products inside the card detail.
Or maybe one or more.
So if open it close.
So if this prompts that user that card detail that length is less or equal than zero then we're going
to do see said state this.
That said state and we changed the state to show total to false.
Now of course if they are deleting an item and they have more items.
Of course we will maybe just delete this item but they still have one.
So we need to recalculate the total amount.
Told you we are going to use this Kancheli total function.
So what we do we just do the same thing does that calculate total.
And we need to pass the card detail that we get in this that prompts a user.
This version of course.
So I'm going to go and since everything is updated again it passed a new state of card detail and it
should be working.
So let's check it out.
OK.
So I'm going to remove the first one and then we can have.
We are removing everything.
Let me just reload the application.
And we are actually not removing from the server.
So I'm going to go here and just make sure let me open it I'm going to go to council and see what we
get and we get local hosts removed from court not found.
And this is because of a mistake with the route.
I'm pretty sure if this remove from card for four.
So let's go back.
API user remove from card.
So user actions get removed from a cart user's server.
Or by this I'm pretty sure that this is just a silly mistake.
So remove.
And we can get it.
So let me just think for a minute and find a problem.
Of course it's users have made this mistake before.
All right.
You know a lot of code man.
So again talking and doing and watching not so easy it's like going to reload the application and try
again this time should work because the only thing that was wrong was the request.
So we get it we remove it and we get it.
If we load the application and notice that it's recalculating.
If I reload the application everything is good.
Now we have the new state of this.
So if I remove it we should be getting the face of.
You have no items.
You know the sad face.
So remove.
You have no items going to go back to guitars.
I'm going to add it again two at three at four.
Go to my car and we get it and we are recalculating.
Let me delete this one.
There we go.
I'm going to do this one and we just get one and do it again.
All right.
So everything works.
So far everything works.
So I'm going to add more of this.
So what do we need to do now.
What we need to do now is going to be the people you know the Pay-Pal connector.
So let's go to the next next one and start doing the paypal.