All right so now we are going to be working with the paypal button and.
OK.
So what is the first thing we need.
We need a Paypal account.
This is going to be an account that I don't use.
It's just empty.
So I'm going to log in first of course you need to register and everything else and then trying to log
in of course I'm going to log into mine as well as a dummy account.
So once you log in of course you're going to get all the information right here.
Now to use a connector because we can use a connector to pay.
We need a business account.
It's not going to work with a personal account and it's because whenever we're going to go to a different
place inside Paypal inside Paypal developer we get a dashboard to of course work with the codes and
you use an API and everything else and the tokens will not work if you don't have a business account.
So you of course need to upgrade to business and it's free of course it's free.
The only thing with Paypal is that they charge you after you of course you create a transaction or something
like that.
So you will need to upgrade to business.
And of course if you go right here to the to the settings you're going to get all the information inside
settings.
And then if you go here you'd say upgrade to a business account.
And of course they're going to ask you a lot of questions.
What is the business.
And then continue.
And of course you will need to complete all of this until you get your you know your fake business account
is going to be a real business account.
But right now we're going to be using to use this to practice Of course.
All right.
So I'm going to I'm going to close this.
I'm going to go to you go back to pay pal.
Well I'm going to close it and of course I already have a real paypal account so let me log in first
and I'm going to show you.
So once you read your business account you can get a bunch of extra options you know add to your website
in line in Bogey's invoicing and everything else.
And of course if you go right here to settings you're going to get the business set up and profile settings
and everything else even you get the business name if you get.
Again this is because the business account it's ready now now this is actually where we don't want to
be.
We need to go to a different place to go and say Pay Pal developer just like that.
And he said pay velt developer once again since we are already logged in a dry here you're going to
get right here the connector if not of course you will need to log in with the same account.
And of course then you go to dashboard and this is where we care right now instead of dashboard you
get a bunch of things including a sandbox account.
You get this with the sandbox.
It's just like Mongo on mongoose on the on the server.
We get a sunburst we get a place where we can you know do some testing.
Right.
So if I go to sandbox and it go to accounts of course we get a lot of information of what's happening
and you get this whenever you get a sample of a sandbox account you get to fake users.
One is the facilitator which is going to be you know the register business.
Right.
Is going to be us.
And then you get the.
Of course the same name and the buyer so buyer it's declined right.
Is the the people that the person that is going to go in and make the purchase.
So whenever we make a purchase with pay pal with fake pay.
Of course if we're going to use this personal buyer account and this account by default we get like
I don't know.
Thirty thousand dollars.
So we can make purchases and do some testing and of course we get a lot of things.
Now if we go to profile
it's a little slow.
If you go to a profile we get all the settings you know funding right here.
Vallence 4900 a lot of money man then Baeza And you know a number and everything else you know everything
is fake.
Of course if you go to profile of course we get the address and everything else.
So right here you'll need to change your password or select a different password.
I'm going to do our password one two three password one two three.
I'm going to save it.
Of course.
So we can do it.
OK what am I going to do.
All right.
Let me just think I'm going to do testing one two three.
So now the passwords.
Testing one two three.
We should be changing the other one as well.
Profile and of course use the same passport.
Testing one two three going to save it.
OK so we get an error message.
Let me see if I can save it again.
Going to cancel close profile
and testing one two three right.
OK.
Well let's go.
I'm going to try later and see why we are getting this error message.
But don't worry for now we are not going to really use the facilitator.
The one we care right now is the buyer one that we're going to check the other one.
OK.
So once you get this you're pretty much ready to go.
There's one more thing we need to do.
If you go to my apps and credentials you get a lot of options right here different tokens you know and
we're going to use this one.
You notice the drink here I'm already using it from before I.
Our final project my final project and what we will need to do is create an app and with this one you
will get a token we can use right here with the sandbox so we can make the purchase.
So I'm going to do it right now I'm going to create the app and I'm going to give it the name of waves
and notice that the sandbox developer account is still facilitator.
So OK so going to create the application.
And of course you get you get some information of course what you can do.
People here along it would pay pal and everything else.
So right.
So people out here we actually don't need this one and this one we will need it and that's it.
And out at the top we're going to save it of course.
And at the top what we will need to do is to get this information this is what we need.
They give you a token and whenever we make the purchase from here we go to the connector and connect
to pay pal.
We need the actual token.
Right.
So I'm going to copy this right here and I'm going to go to our cart going to make a comment right here
at the top and I'm going to leave it there because we're going to use it later.
And then of course you get a secret and this is no.
A little bit more important because whenever you go to production it doesn't matter for now.
OK.
So I'm going to I'm going to leave this open after a couple minutes is going to lock me out for of course
security reasons.
But again we are using a sandbox.
So nothing is going to really happen.
It doesn't matter if someone copies this token.
Right.
OK.
So OK so I'm going to go to our application to go back to our application and first before we can use
the connector we need to do a lot of things we need to create a reusable component for the button.
And you know just prepare our component to get the prompts from this one.
Right so let's create reusable components.
I'm going to go to you tell us and I'm going to create a new file called Pay-Pal.
Yes.
All right.
So this one will be a re-act class based component.
And of course Paypal let me just change it.
Pay-Pal with a capital P.
OK.
So right now we are not going to really use this first we're going to include the Paypal but and so
right now I'm going to say just Pay-Pal right.
And if you're asking yourself Why am I using Paypal and it's because people can be used pretty much
through out the globe.
We have tons of connectors you could use PayPal in your business where your client may be using paypal
you have a lot of other options.
A lot of options.
They all Tarsh something after you use it.
So it's pretty much the same thing.
And but you always use a service to of course process payments into your into your of course application.
Right.
So let's go back to the cart.
I'm going to go right here and import of course the pay public and begin to use it.
So import than PayPal from dot dot for Slash utils for Slash and then pay pal.
Right.
So going to copy I'm going to go at the bottom and I'm going to put it where are people but an S.
So I'm going to say Pay-Pal open and close.
So of course we need to pass a lot of props.
So what are going to be the props.
All right.
So first we need to tell this paper people how much the user needs to pay.
And if you remember we have it on the total right here.
All right on the state.
So I'm going to say to pay equals to this that state that total.
Right.
OK I'm going to go at the bottom and I'm going to say OK what can happen.
Whenever you know the user makes intersection and we get an error.
OK.
So I'm going to pass a prompt that says trans section trans section and then error equals.
And of course from the connector from the people we're going to get a lot of data so I'm going to be
grabbing that data and then pass it to a function.
We will create right here to this transaction error and I'm going to pass this data.
Now of course we don't have this function going to create it right here at the top and just you know
live it empty.
You're going to use it much much later.
All right then we have a different scenario what happens if the transaction gets canceled.
Maybe the user reaches the final stage and they just you know cancel everything they're going to do
the same thing.
So Trinh S..
Let me just copy and paste.
I'm going to copy paste Antrix S.S. canceled
right and same thing for this transduction counsel and copy and paste and we will create the function
at the top and then of course we going to catch it open and close.
And that is it.
And the final state is going to be on success.
So I'm going to say on success what's going to happen if the user completes the you know the purchase.
So we're going to get data and then of course we will run a new function called this and then transduction
success something like that.
And then of course we are going to be receiving data.
And we do the same thing at the top.
So transduction success equals to a function.
Right okay.
So pretty much we have everything we need the amount to be paid.
And of course what happens when you get when we get an error when we get when it get canceled or when
everything goes OK.
Right.
So let's go to the Pay-Pal connector on to the Paypal component and right here we're going to use a
connector we're going to use a third party library.
So if you go right here and you are just trying to find re-act people express out.
I'm on the NPM could go you know to get help that we have here.
As a matter let's go to get help.
When not.
OK.
So first of course you need to install it.
But if we remember we make a little memory right here.
We've already have it re-act people express checkout.
So we don't need to install it.
All right.
So this is very simple very very simple.
You just use the component they are going to give you and you will need to pass all the prompts just
right from the beginning.
We need this you know we need the the the tokens so for of course they give you a box and they give
you a production of course you can get the production much much later.
Whenever you go to production.
So OK so the sandbox and we need to put creative are all called sandbox and put the token right there.
Right.
And then of course we going to be passing this to the button now and this is the important part whenever
you of course you complete they complete the purchase and everything else we're going to get on unsuccess
scenario an on console and an error.
You know the same elements we were using from the parent component right from this one.
Right.
So and then of course we need to pass the environment with is sandbox the currency of what we are using.
And you know the total amount.
Right.
OK.
So it's kind of a it's really really simple.
So let's go back.
We're going to go to the table and of course we need to do a few things.
So I'm to make a little bit of space right here.
And actually we don't need it because we need it inside of the render.
This is what they give you on the example.
I'm going to do it on same way.
All right.
So inside the render what we need to do to create these deep virals in this case Konst on success.
And notice just like before.
I'm trying to do this example the same way they did.
So you later of course you can read the documentation and you know no difference right here.
So of course unsuccess you get it you're going to get some data back.
So I'm going to say payment.
Right.
And of course you do something much later than we have uncancel so Konst on council.
And if you want to of course save some time you can copy the current code from get help.
Just to do it now whenever you get canceled.
You're going to get some data back and then the next one is the cons on error.
All right.
Open close.
And of course you get some errors back right now of course we need to set some other marbles.
So let's Envy's So we know that EMV it's environment.
So in this case we use the sandbox.
So we're going to use the sandbox which is the testing.
Right.
OK.
Then we need the currency equals and then you as d capital you as D you can use whatever currency you
wish.
All right.
And then the total so I'm going to say let's let equals.
Total right equals.
And remember that we are passing this as props.
Right.
So it's going to be this that perhaps.
And then to pay.
Right.
That is it.
So of course at least we should be getting something at least right here.
At least he would pay pal.
Right.
That that means that we get no errors.
Of course we need to import the Express button.
So import and then pay pal just like this express and then DTN right.
Okay.
Yeah everything's good.
And then of course from and re-act pay pal express check out now inside Pay-Pal you get different types
of connectors.
Now in this case we just get a button and that button will open a new window so we can make the transaction.
But you have different ways of creating a Pay-Pal know environment to create the purchase.
And of course everything is on the documentation of people.
It's pretty well documented.
All right.
But they are all the same thing.
After you set it up right here the connector and everything else they will give you just three different
you know final things.
And this is what we care because when we get the data back from PayPal we will have a lot of information
and then we will need to go to our server side and we will need to store that transaction in a different
place and we need to update the user account saying that the transaction was done.
Or maybe adding the items to the history of purchases and we can begin to do that after we connect to
Paypal.
But that's OK.
First we need to do this.
So after that total remember that we need that token.
So I'm going to say Konst client equals an array.
I'm sorry an object.
So we get a sandbox account sand box account and then of course we get the production of course we're
not going to use production.
We're not going to go to production on this one.
All right.
So the token if you remember it's right here the top.
So I'm going to copy the token I'm going to go to pay Paul Sand Box and paste it down there and of course
I did this in the past and the production there are pretty much the same.
And you just if you're working maybe in a different environment than react this would be really simple
it just passed the data to the HD mail they're going to provide you.
You can check this on the documentation you just pass the token.
And that's it it's going to it's going work.
It's just like including on a script at the top and that is it.
You know that's the normal way with just simple H.T. mail not with a single page application that you
put the script to of paper at the top.
You put the h d m l and inside you pass the token and that is it and it's going to go in works really
really good.
OK.
So what do we do now.
We need to create the button.
OK.
So going to go here and say OK I want to bring that Pay-Pal express button just like this opening close.
Now of course we need to pass a lot of information.
So if I ever load the application you know we get this PayPal button.
So at least we are getting it really actually and we can change it of course.
So we need to pass a lot of props to this people.
So first is the environment whether we're using production or some box.
Well we're going to use sandbox right.
The client the client is going to be equal to the client.
Same thing here.
All right.
Then koma.
Sorry going to ave Propp and we need to pass the currency so currency is going to be equal to currency.
Remember we are using it right here right.
What else.
We need the total So total it's equal to total and all this.
Of course this prompts are the ones that people express buy and will accept to make the transaction
a go at the bottom.
We get an on error.
So whenever we get an error we're going to run a function and that function of course has a callback
in some data.
So we pass the on error we did right here at the top.
So I got to say on error then we have the on success.
So unsuccess equals to the same unsuccess we have right here.
So on success.
All right then we get the uncancel so uncancel open and the council.
Okay.
And then of course this Bunin it's really really ugly.
So they give us different layouts.
And again you can check in on the documentation of PayPal.
So we're going to go to style and whenever you go to style we can pass up you know CSSA styling.
We can do that.
What they give you give us is different properties.
They give us a size and we can choose between large medium and small.
So we're going to use large that coma we can select the color.
And again they give you three or four options.
So I'm going to choose blue because I like color.
Then they give you a shape and again you have two or three options.
So I got to use recked coma and you know the label and the label is going to say check out something
like that.
Whenever I'm going to save it and if it reloads you know we get a much Pay-Pal check out you're going
to get a much better button right.
Much much nicer.
OK.
So if we actually do the purchase nothing is going to happen.
So we're going to go at the top so we can we can actually see it.
So I'm going to go right here and say console log open it close.
And if we do the payment of course if we cancel the payment it's going to come out on a can of a all
to it.
So we don't want to do is want to convert to a string.
So we can read it a little bit better.
So I'm going to do.
Jason stringin FY just like this opening closed.
And I'm going to just inspect the payment.
Same thing on the other ones.
I'm going to get the data and I'm going to get the error actually our That error.
So at least we can see it on the console and see what is going on after we do something right here.
So I'm going to save it and let's test it.