OK so let's test if this is working.
I'm going to go to people.
I'm going to click it and it's going to open this.
Now I'm going to go and open inspect it we're going to get a couple of hours.
Let me do this because of course we are not an HDTV P.S. And you know we get kind of that error but
that's OK.
Now if you click it to continue we need to log in and remember that is the buyer so buyer.
All right.
And we need to pay three four.
Sorry.
And I'm going to do the following.
Look at this.
I'm going to cancel it.
It's going to close and we get you know the to get the Konst lock.
And this one comes from an canceled.
So whenever we add they cancel the information or really close the connector we didn't get this.
Of course we can catch it.
And you know they give us the payment token the payment I.D..
And in the intent it was a sale and you know a bunch of information you know too that it might be relevant
if you want to store it someplace.
Now when I want to do and I want to cancel this I want to remove the one with you know the really pricey
guitar because I don't want to make large purchases.
I just want to go and do 400.
You know that's nice.
I'm going to go to Paypal again.
You're going to select a buyer.
Of course a buyer and stay logged in for faster purchases.
And then of course the password I believe it was testing 1 two three are going to log in.
It might take a while of course.
It's a little bit slow but that's OK.
You know it's just a testing varment.
And finally you get this of course you get the ship to.
You're not really using this.
And then of course paid with paypal Vernons or you can of course apply for a credit card or they can
give you the option to pay with credit cards.
They actually simulate that.
So I'm going to click campaign now.
OK.
At the end we get this.
The payment was succeeded and of course everything went OK.
And we get the address which is data we get at the top.
And if it was canceled it was false.
The e-mail of the person that it's buying this they paid true they pay your I.D. payment I.D. If you're
going to use it and the payment token and of course we get a return you are L..
We are not really using this.
But of course we can set this up from the accounts right here from the when we go to accounts inside
sandbox see if I can find it.
Oh no no.
It's back into my career and credential.
Sorry for that.
So inside of Wavves
at the bottom we get an option to return your l.
Maybe after the purchase you want to send the user back to a different route so you can put it here.
And it's of course going to work.
It's going to send you back to a different journal.
You're not going to use this because what we want to do is we want to catch from a function.
This of course this return.
And whenever of course everything goes OK we're going to do something to our component.
So OK so if we get the payment was exceeded everything it's OK.
We're going to go to this scenario.
Of course we don't have an hour.
We are not going to get an hour but it's OK if there is an error.
You're going to get it right here.
OK.
So now what we need to do is we need to of course on each scenario at least on success and then cancel
grab this data.
Run.
Run a function that goes to props right here.
Remember we added some props to do some things and we're going to go right here in our application of
course if we're going to do something if everything goes ok or something goes really bad.
Right.
OK.
So I'm going to copy this and I'm going to paste it somewhere and then we're going to go in there and
put it inside of the paypal and I'm going to put it put everything as a comment so you can have a reference
of what's going on.
Whenever they you know they pay the make the purchase because they're going to use this data.
Ok so I place the success scenario right here.
Let me put it right here.
Maybe you know just copy this and put it on the success and I'm doing this so you can have a future
reference of what's going on.
Whenever we get the response back because in a few minutes in the next few lectures we're going to grab
some of this information you know buy the key graph the values and we're going to store it on different
places in our inside of our database or application.
Right.
So I need to have a reference to this.
And of course I'm putting this so you can have a future reference whenever you download this project
from get.
All right.
Now there's one more thing.
Whenever we succeed with a payment if you go to the Sundogs account you go to accounts and you go to
the facilitator right here facilitator you're going to get.
You know what is going on inside of here.
So today is July 17th right.
So and this is the time.
So you're going to get an education for all the transactions that are processed within of course your
application.
And if you click it is going to give you the of course right here transaction ID and everything else
is going to give you the receipt for this invoice.
Right.
And of course by default whenever you make a purchase on Paypal the buyer will receive an email with
all the notifications and all the you know whenever they make a purchase with their receipt receipt
for your payment to test facilitator.
So of course this is not really happening.
It's what's going to happen on the reallife the user will get an email with the with the receipt right.
Of course this is not happening because this e-mail it's not real not real at all.
Right.
OK.
But we know that no the transaction is going is going and everything goes OK.
All right.
So let's go back to our obligation.
So whenever we complete the purchase we want to do a few stuff.
We want to clear everything right here.
Right.
We want to clear it.
And then of course clear this and say thank you for purchasing whatever whatever whatever.
So we need to still do a few few things right.
So on the card we have the transaction error the council and the access.
So whenever the transaction or success goes on I'm going to do that.
I'm going to comment this going to go at the bottom and say this this this prompts just like this.
And then on success.
Right.
And then we pass.
Whenever we get from the payment.
All right.
Right so now we need to go to this transduction success and at the end whenever we complete the transaction
we want to do this.
The state that said state and we want to change it.
Do we want to hide the total because we don't have a total anymore.
And of course first we need to go out and dispatch an action so we can clear the card of the user or
store the information off a at on a different place and every store located that you know that card
instead of the payment history of the user.
You need to do a lot of things first.
But at the end whenever everything is ready we want to show the total and begin to hide the total force
because we don't have a total anymore.
And then we're going to do the show success going to show that success message.
Before I went to do this I'm going to make going to make some changes.
I made a mistake right here.
Is unsuccess dull s and same thing at the top on success and right here.
Same same thing other props.
It's on success.
Just fix this on success and this one one more as transduction on success.
Sorry for this.
All right.
That's why we are not getting the stirringly Phi of the payment.
And we were getting an object.
OK.
So let's try again clear.
Everything is going to go to guitars.
I'm going to add a cheap guitar and then go to my cart.
We're going to do the Pay-Pal checkout let's do it again.
All right that's fine.
We need to log in again.
So testing one two three.
A state law then going to log in again.
Of course you're not get the Paypal connector takes a while to connect.
To of course trying to pass and you know Skip Skip the loading time.
But if you're getting kind of a long loading time.
Whenever you log in that is normal.
So I'm going to go Mbaye now and when we come back to our component.
Right.
We think your order is complete.
So we are getting the message.
Now why this one.
It's not good.
You know it's not disappearing and it's because whenever we go back to our component we're going to
do some logic some this patch and begin to return the story of the user.
You know the cart and that card at this point is going to be empty.
So when it returns empty of course this one will not show.
Right.
This has been managed by a different part on the application not the connector.
You know not this transaction success.
All right.
But everything looks good.
We can we make the purchase.
We come back and then we get the thank you or there is complete.
I'm not going to do the air because again this is Abdeen our placation maybe you want to show a dialog
or maybe a text.
I don't know whatever is that you want to do.
And in this case if there is an error I'm going to say console log opening close.
Remember we get some data right here on this ones as well.
We get some data.
So I'm just going to do a log.
You know.
So Pay-Pal error.
And on the other one on the council I'm going to say transduction canceled transect Sion Council.
It was like before you can do whatever you want right here maybe show dialog just like we did with the
log in or they were just our same idea.
Really simple.
Of course this is still in our cart.
The user on the user and in our server inside Mongo or Mongul T or whatever is going to be there.
So whenever we come back we're going to dispatch an action to you know update the state of the cart
of the user.
So lets go to the next one and start creating all this logic.
Its going to take us a while because we need to do two actions and we need to add a new plays on the
server a new route that is going to be handling this and later of course scenes begin to get payments
IDs coped Pay-Pal are going to get this we need a place for the administrators know to check the payments
so much later we can create a new model so we can store you know the new payments.