OK so now what are we going to be doing is creating the route to process all of this.
And then of course you get to go to the producers and do everything else.
But for now which is going to you know do this.
OK.
So I get close some of the things because they have everything open and I really like it.
There you go.
So let's go to the server right here.
And of course we need to create a route and it's inside users.
So I'm going to go right here at the bottom and added to the users we're going to create a route.
It's going to be an app and it's going to be a post and a U R L for this is going to be API API for
Slash use words plural.
And then success and then by and of course we will use the Our Connector coma and then we just run a
function right.
Just like always.
All right.
So of course we will get our request our response.
Now before we go inside of here we need to do a lot of things first.
So let me tell you a little bit of what you're going to be doing.
First we're going to enter the user history right.
Remember that on each user We're going to show you right now and I'm going to show you the final one
because on the on this one we don't have anything.
So going to show you what's can happen at the end.
So going to go to the user and they're going to go to this one.
We have a history right.
We have a history place so we're going to grab what everything the user has on the card after they make
the purchase and we're going to store that inside history.
So whenever we complete the purchase the history will contain whatever they just bought.
Right.
OK.
So of course we have all happening right now inside of this.
We're going to get the date of the purchase and what they purchased and of course we are not going to
store the whole data of the product.
You can do it if you want.
That's completely up to you on this route.
A lot of things are you know depending on what you're building and what the customer your customer not
the one that makes the purchase declined that is higher you higher hiring you.
What they want in this case.
Just going to put the date of the purchase some date of the product and then the payment I.D..
So again we're going to grab from the cart begin to go to history and store everything in there.
So the first thing we need to do is to do the user history right.
So after we do that we get the store on a different place.
The payment information because the people that it's hiring you they will need may be a place we are
not going to do it right here maybe I will add it as a bonus.
They will need a place where they can log in on the admin and Che and check the purchases or something
like that.
You know an end point where they see what's going on with the purchase on their Web site and they will
access that model and that model will have some information.
Let me just show you on the fine one we will Krita are here a model called payments.
And of course if we go to payments we will have three things again and this place at this point you
can add whatever you want or whatever your client asks you in this case.
I'm just going to add the user that made the purchase and this will be all the data of the user.
Right.
They're going to add the data which is the data that we get back from Pay-Pal.
And this could be whatever could be something from Paypal or maybe a different service and then you
know the product and the product is going to be whatever they you know they purchased.
And if we have many We'll have many a race of items right here.
Many are items inside the array.
So this is what we need to do.
So the second step is going to be the payments payments dash whatever.
All right.
So then we have a third step but that one is a little bit weird to explain right now.
So first we're going to do all of this we can just change the history and change the payment.
And then begin to talk.
I'm going to give you the inside of the that we are at you know scenario.
Okay.
So we are going to enter here right.
And from the from the from here whenever we make the request we go to you know make the request to the
server.
We will need to pass several things.
Right.
So we're going to be passing is the card detail whatever the user has on the card detail at this point
right inside the store and the payment data we get from paypal.
Right.
OK.
So I'm going to go to the server now from the payment card detail.
Let me just show you from the card detail we might have one item or several items and we don't need
all the information that we have on the card detail.
We just need some of this information so we can and need to grab this from the from the route right
from the request and kind of make our own array of data so we can store it on a different Olga.
So let's begin with this is going to be a little bit long but you know in fun.
So I'm going to create a viral called Let let.
And then history is to read.
And this one starts as an empty array.
OK.
Then I'm going to create a new Orval Coltrane's section Trinh section and then data and this data it's
the data we get you know from the Pay-Pal that's good.
So first is this user history we need a way to enter the card detail of the user.
They may have one item or many many items and grabbed that information change it a little bit and stored
on history again in the end.
And our inside history we might have one article or maybe many articles if they are purchasing many
things.
All right.
So if you remember we are Pat we're going to be passing the card detail from from the cart from redux
from the client to the server.
Now what you can do and it's completely up to you.
You can get the card detail directly from the off.
Remember that the returns
right here the returns the user all the user information so you could get it from there.
In this case I'm not going to do this.
I'm just going to grab it from the actual you know request.
OK.
So since we are going to be passing Jason with the Paypal information and the user card detail I'm going
to say I want to enter the request.
I want to enter the body because we use Jason and that I'm going to grab the cart the cart cart and
the detail.
All right Dot Net going to do a for each now for each element on the card detail of course we get an
item and then we will loop something going to do something.
So what we want to do we want to grab each element inside the card detail and push that to the history
of the user.
Right.
OK.
So history dot push open and close.
Are going to be passing an object you're going to have the and an array of objects if we have many card
details.
All right.
I don't want to push all the information that we get inside card detail because that's a little bit
long.
No and it's not relevant why we would want the sold or maybe the images.
You know we will need the ID and the name but why would I pushed it description.
I don't want to store that.
We don't need it so we can create our own object you know the data we need.
So going to eight going at a date off and then purchase.
So the date of purchase is going to be date now.
And of course you can choose whatever you know method to add a date you want right here.
It's completely up to you.
There are going to a coma.
Of course we need the name of the item.
So going to enter the item and get the name from the card detail are going to enter the brand and it's
item dot brand.
And remember that then get the name we're going to get the item ID.
So item that underscore ID are going to do coma.
And then the prize open item that price then we need the quantity.
So quantity item that quantity and we need one more thing we need the payment ID from Paypal remember.
All right.
So I'm going to say payment Id just like this payment ID Kong and this one we don't get it inside the
item of the card detail right.
We don't get it from there.
We get from the other thing that we're going to be passing which is the Paypal data this one so that
one it's inside request request that body that payment payment data are going to call it just like that
dot and then payment I.D. And it's you know just like this because inside PayPal we get it just like
this payment Id really be accessing this object.
Right.
So it requires body payment data and then payment I.D. everything looks nice.
Now I'll just give you an example.
After we process this and we store it inside of the history of the user it is going to look something
like this and we give you a real example going to go to users.
And here in the history we get two elements right this user but two things.
So the first one it's the date of purchase the name the brand the I.D. the price and then the payment
from you know quantity and payment from PayPal.
So at the end we should be getting something like this and much later we going to fetch this history
from the user and show it on the under my account.
The history of purchases.
All right.
Well let's go back.
So this is the first thing we have an array right now with all the history that we're going to be pushing
to the user.
So next one is going to be the payment dashboard.
We need to pretty much grab part of this information and the payment and everything else that we get
from from Paypal and it's stored inside a new model.
Now for this of course we need a new model so we need the two models going to create a new file.
And this one will be payment.
Let me do it like this payment that.
So I'm going to open payments.
And of course we need to import so Konst mongoose equals require opening close and then mongoose.
All right now we need to create a scheme out.
So it's going to be payment and then schema right equals mongoose dot capital S schema.
Open it close and we pass an object and I'm going to do the rest.
So we can have a Konst called payment capital P payment just like this equals two.
And when then we create a model.
If you remember that the model needs an I.D. payment just like this.
Capital P.
And then we pass the payment schema to create this.
And then of course we need to module that module that exports right and that equals and we just export
disparate payments right here.
Now just like a show you inside of the robo 3 2 payments we get three things.
We get the user data of the data of the user that's making the purchase the data which is the data that
comes from Pay-Pal.
And then you know information about the products that they purchased.
All right.
So when you go to server sorry to payments and are going to go and first one it's the user.
Now this one could be an object it could be whatever you want.
In this case I'm just going to create an array and store everything inside of an array.
You can go in a different way right here.
So that default and the default is an empty array than coma.
I'm going to say data open and close.
And again this one is going to be an array.
I'm going to copy and paste right.
And then we have the product information about the product.
So the product again is going to be on a rate and default.
I'm going real simple right here you could add maybe different keys or different types.
And you know in the process whatever it is that you want to process in this case I'm just going very
simple user or user data with an object data with an object and the product with an array of objects.
OK.
Get well it's fine.
So now we have this.
So we need to require payment from the server.
So we need to go at the top and just like here I'm going to say Konst and then payment with a capital
P payment and it's equal.
Require opening close that forward slash and that models and then payments.
All right so now we have access to payments.
Right.
So let's called the bottom.
Now of course right now we are not going to do this because to do something else because we have the
all the information in pieces we didn't have just one object that says Okay here's the user data the
data and the product all in one.
We don't have it.
So we need to kind of create a new object and you know grab it from different places from the history
we get the user data.
I'm sorry for the out.
We get to use our data from history.
We get the history of the transaction which is the products.
And then of course from Pay-Pal we get the data of the paper of the payments.
All right.
So I'm going to go right here.
I'm going to create I'm going to use distressed intersection data I'm going to say transaction data.
Dodd and are going to add the information of the user just add keys to this.
So this one is an object and we need to put the ID of the user which is inside request then user dot
underscore ID.
Remember we get it we are using the app so that's where where are going to be getting this.
So then we have a name same thing it's request that user doesn't and the name what else we have the
last name then.
QUEST user.
And then last name coma and then e-mail.
So we are attaching very basic information about the user.
All right user dot email and like I told before you could get the card detail you know from the US directly
because we have all the information above the user.
Now if you're thinking maybe someone could inject the information well that could happen.
Of course there's always a chance that someone is going to try to break your application.
But the thing is that of course just like always someone at the end will need to check that the payments
inside payment PAME Pay-Pal the payment went through and everything is OK.
And they of course they will contact the guy that it's buying there's check the shipping address.
And then of course make the shipping so there's always someone controlling that.
Everything is OK and there is no you know funky business going on there.
OK.
So now we have the user inside transaction data protection user section data user.
Sorry.
Then of course we need the data of people here are going to go very simple are going to grab whatever
we get back from Pay-Pal say because body and then payment data.
Right.
This is where we have all the information about PayPal and we're going to stored inside data.
This one could be you know payment data and then we need it we need a place where we can store the products.
So I'm going to say transaction data dot product could be products because you know it might be part
plural but that's OK.
And right here you can do whatever you want.
You can have the card detail and push everything to you know the product.
But the thing is again you have a sold key you have a lot of things that you don't really need.
Right right right there.
So I'm going to use the history graph whatever we get inside history when we do it right here and store
the history that contains you know the date of the transaction the name brand and you know a couple
of things.
And of course the transaction of PayPal the key but that's it.
It's the first limb.
All right.
And that's it.
So now we have the user history right here and then we have the payments information right.
So we can store first inside of the user the history.
And after we are done doing this we're going to go to payments and store a new payment.
All right.
So we're going to go right here at the bottom.
Let me see if maybe this section went too long.
OK.
It's already too long.
So on the next one we will start you know going to the database and making all the changes it's going
to be really fun.
So let's go to the next one and finish this.