OK so let's complete this.
So now what we need to do is to go to the user and update the user history.
Right so we can enter the user and begin to find it and update it.
So find one an update.
Open and close.
The first thing we need to pass is you know which user.
So underscore ID and we passed the request that user that underscore ID you know we get it from the
OF.
Remember always we get out of the coma and we make this nice.
Then we can tell the find one and update.
What is that we want to update.
So in this case we want to do perform two different actions.
Two things we want to go to the user.
We give you an example.
Go to the cart and delete whatever they have on the card because the purchase is done.
So the card is going to be empty.
Right OK.
And then of course we need to push what whatever we have on the history array and put that push it inside
history.
Now remember that we need to push We don't need to just set because if we push and they have maybe previous
data right there we need to push it and added at the end you know.
All right.
So first we want to push so I'm going to say push call and what is that we want to push.
So we going to go to history and push whatever we get inside the history array.
Right.
That is that then what we want to do we want to grab the card and delete everything on the card.
We want to change it to an empty array.
So in this case what we use is not push is going to be set.
So we are changing the value of the card to an empty array.
Right.
Of course then going to do go under and go to the next one.
And remember that whenever we use update if you want to get the we want to get the of the the updated
document of this user we want to use new equals true.
If not you can get the old one or nothing.
Obviously the old one and I remember now after this happens we run a callback.
So our and then user of course the user it's the updated users state right now after we do this.
Right.
So now what are we going to do.
I'm going to say if if there is an error.
You know the usual stuff.
Let me go right here if there is an error so error.
I want to return a Jaison response response with Jaison we could add the four or four some like that
not for four.
So I'm going to say success and then falls.
And then of course PAHs your usual stuff OK.
Now once we are done updating the user what we need to do is do pretty much the same thing but inside
of the payments document right.
We go to payments grab whatever we have to inside trisection data and you know add a new a new document
to payments.
All right.
So since we have it right here the top called payment we're going to grab it and we're going to go and
say OK.
So I want to create a new payment.
So first we create a new payment Condes payment it calls new payment.
Open and close and then are going to be passing these new payments they're going to be passing what
are we going to be using to make this new payment.
Well the transaction data.
So I'm going to pass that transaction data.
All right.
Now we can enter this new payment.
We're going to do that and I'm going to save it open and close.
So after we save it of course we have that error and that documents.
All right.
Of course if we get an error I'm going to copy this one right here so I can skip the typing.
Return success falls and the are.
All right.
And now we have a problem because of course this information will be getting.
Will will be stored inside of payment's right here inside of payments just like a new a new key with
all the data.
A new document with all the data and that is good.
You know it's going to work.
It's going to work really great.
But we have a tiny problem.
Whenever they make a purchase of a product remember that inside products inside of each product we have
something we have about a key insider database say in how many products of this one we've sold.
And of course they make a purchase we need to add one to that list.
Let me just show you here and go to products and I'm going to say I'm going to grab the last one.
I don't know if we have the sold property.
So whenever they complete a purchase we need to grab all the all the data and you know grab all the
products they are purchasing go.
We need to go to that product specific product.
And you know increment the sold because you know we sold one of this.
Now we have an additional problem.
What happens if the user is buying multiple of the same product.
So instead of adding one you know some of this by one increment by one we need to increment by the quantity
of they are what they are buying.
Right.
Okay.
So again we have a kind of a new problem because what happens if they have more products.
Maybe they are you know make you're buying 10.
So we can not really just do one update.
We cannot do product just like this product that update.
And then you know pass whatever we want because right here we will pass the ID of the product.
But the problem is that we have many ideas and we have many types.
We have but we could have different quantities.
So what are we going to do begin a trigger if we can at this moment have you know triggered this several
times.
So if they have maybe 10 items on the on the cart we're going to run this command with the ID of you
know 10 times.
So again we're just doing a loop.
So let me give you an example so simple we're going to do a for each or something like this.
We're going to grab the every of products we're going to run for each and for each element of course
then we can go to product just like this product dot and then update and then we will pass the ID.
So underscore ID and whatever we have on the element that ID.
All right.
So okay.
So of course if we do this this action takes some time.
Right.
It needs some time to go to mongoose update the element and then comes back.
So whenever we trigger the callback right here you know the callback function at the end when we are
going to get multiple callbacks.
So how can we know whenever we are finished updating all of this.
So we really can't we can't because we have many many options right here.
And then of course we get many callbacks.
So we kind of need a way to of course do all the actions maybe 10 maybe one that doesn't matter.
And then we need to know when all of this actions are done and then run one single callback now for
this what we can do we can use a sink.
So I'm going to go at the top right at the top and I'm going to require something actually it's from
Noad and it's called Eysenck.
So Konst a sink I'm doing this so I can show you in sync we could do something else as well.
But you know this is always ok is going to work very Burguet.
So with async we can trigger we can you know about Dimba create many many requests this case to the
mongoose.
And then we can know when all the transactions are done.
You know when all the requests requests are done right and when they are all done we're going to say
okay then run one single callback Burguet.
So I'm going to call and grab that.
They think they're going to go right here at the bottom.
So how can we use the async.
It's really really simple.
It's not that weird.
So first we need to do is go to a sink and then we use something that calls each of piece.
Now this each of series needs three arguments the product.
This is a loop pretty much does.
This is a for each loop.
So we need we need what we're going to be looping and we don't have it.
So this is going to be I don't know the array the second one it's what we're going to do on this one
which is the second argument in this case we're going to do the update right.
We're going to do something like that going to do the update and then we have a third callback.
So the third callback is going to be what are we going to do after all of this updates are done now.
The first problem is this we don't have an array to loop.
So I'm going to go right here and say OK we're going to create a lead called products right.
Product equals an empty array and are going to enter dock products.
Now why am I entering dock products.
So right here whenever we find an update and we do the you know the payment of say and everything else
we have the key off products on beaches go to payments.
There we go.
So we have product right so we can enter product and begin to search all the elements we have on that
product.
On this particular payment.
Right.
And we can get the data.
And of course we get the idea of that element.
So if we can grab an ID stored on that array and we can get the quantity.
All right.
So we can enter actually product dot product that we're going to run for each open and close now for
each we can grab an item and then we're going to run something.
So what we need from the two for the update to work is the idea of the product are going to be updating
and we are going to be updating the quantities sold by what so product are going to push it I'm going
to push something up let me do it correctly.
You go.
So I'm going to push.
I'm going to push you object so if you have 10 different products we will get inside the Lilly products
array 10 different objects.
Right.
So the first thing we need is the ID so we can know where are going to go to do the update.
So item that ID then we do coma and we need the quantity.
So I'm going to say quantity equals item that quantity right.
So now we get an array of products could be one single object or many different objects with different
products but we have an array we can loop.
So now I'm going to be passing products.
All right.
Now the second callback.
This is the second function.
The second argument is what are we going to be doing with this.
So we're going to get an item and then this one that calls callback can explain this one in a minute.
So we're never we are done doing whatever is that we want to do.
We need to kind of a trigger this.
So this is kind of like we solve reject pretty much the same idea.
So we're going to go here and say OK.
So on each iteration of each product we need to go to the actual product do that and do an update.
So what are we going to be updating.
Well we're going to be updating the ID of whatever we get on the.
This item on this situation.
Right.
Get the item and we grabbed the ID they're going to do coma.
And what are we going to be doing.
Well we need to increment the sold right.
OK.
So are going to do increment open and what are we going to be incrementing the salt.
Right.
So what are we going to do.
We're going to added just one to.
Well no we have the quantity right here.
So we need to grab the item quantity.
We're going to increment by whatever they are buying if they're buying three we're going to increment
by three right.
Make sense then of course we do coma and I'm going to say new falls because I don't need the I don't
need this.
Actually we don't need the new document back.
And then of course we have the Colback right.
OK.
So this Colback is this callback.
So this is the way we get this to tell the async of C-rist saying that you know this action this Colback
right here this one it's done go to the next one.
All right.
And then at the end after all of this are done and all the code callbacks are done each of Sirius is
going to say Okay.
So all my oh my oh my commands are done.
They are all done.
So now I'm going to run this callback that this is the way we get to run different things and trigger
a single callback after they are all done.
So I'm sorry it took this long but I needed to have this environment to play it.
Explain this.
Once you get it it's not you know it's really easy.
It's just like creating a new promise.
That's pretty much it.
So return then if everything goes so it goes bad.
We return a J-Zone response of of course success falls.
And then of course the error OK.
Now if everything goes OK what are we going to do.
We're going to rescind send a response with a status of 200 and then we send a J sign.
OK.
Now what are we going to be sending back to the client.
So I'm going to send success.
True right then I want to carked.
Now whenever we go back to the client we need to go to redux and update the card of the user.
Remember that the cart after we make the purchase we need to delete the card because they don't have
elements on the card anymore.
So I'm going to say card and what you could do you could do user that cart.
Remember that the tab that we are making the update to the user and we are deleting whatever they have
on the card before sending the card to zero.
So we get the user back.
So what we can do we can access user in say a card or we can do this.
You know it's just an empty array.
But you can do it for example if I do it on the card detail remember that we also have a card detail
going to go to state user.
We have a card detail with one because we have one item of the card.
So we need to clear the card detail.
So I'm going to say cart cart detail equals to an empty array and it's going to work as well as user
dog cart.
But in this case of course card detail it's not really inside the user.
So again we are just setting the card detail to nothing.
And this of course will update the state on redux.
And it's going to finally at the end it's going to delete whatever we have here and begin to get it
inside the day my account of the history.
We are not there yet.
So hopefully there are no mistakes again.
You know go to the next section you get to maybe check this a little bit more but not so much if you
get an error.
I would like to tell you the error because you know this is part of what we do.
We get errors the whole time.
So what does the next step in all of this logic.
It's done.
We need to make a request to dispatch an action to.
And then go make a request to this route.
And then of course update the state of the application.
So let's go to the next one and begin with that.
And that is the only thing the last thing we're going to do for my card.
We are pretty much done.