All right so now we are going to be creating the actions and the reducers rhyme.
OK.
So are going to go to actions and this one is going to be a user action.
I'm going to call the type.
It's going to be on success.
Bye bye.
And then user.
All right.
So I'm going to copy.
Of course we need to add this to types just the same as always.
And I'm going to say export export then Konst unsuccess by user and same thing on success by user.
All right.
We're going to go back to user actions and you know create the request for this.
So at the bottom we're going to export a function called whatever you want on success by whatever.
So this one will be we will be getting some data back.
We're going to talk about this in a minute.
So after we get the data of course you're going to do the request and at the end you're going to return
something.
So what we return is that unsuccess by user.
And then we return a payload pay load with whatever we get back from the request and begin to create.
Right now we don't have the request going to add it.
It's a very simple request.
So going to a concert request equals and it's going to be a post.
So CEOs then post opening close.
Now the hell were we going to be sending this to the user or server.
All right.
So we can say use our server then forced laugh and the route its success by.
So we do success fine.
Right.
OK.
Now we're going to be passing this data for now which is going to I'm going to pass it and then we're
going to create this.
The way then of course we're going to get a response.
So then open and close we get a response and we put this.
Of course we return something so return so we don't need to return.
We can do.
Response that data and that will be returned.
All right.
Burguet So let's get good.
So now what do we need to do is to include this success by.
But before I'm going to go to read reducers go to use the reducer.
We need to copy the type added to the reducer and I'm going to do coma and on success by user Breguet
now the douceur will be receiving several things from the payload.
So first are going to created we have a case a case of unsuccess by user.
Right.
OK.
Then we want to return an object with dot dot dot.
And the state right the pre-state.
Now we will get we will create a success by key with whatever we get back from the server.
And remember the server returns and we find it at the end returns the success so we can store that here
on success by.
We say that the action that payload that success and success Burguet will make sure I use success IMMERGUT
right.
So what else what do we need to do after we have everything you know.
Correct.
So we need to go to the user data try here just the user data and we need to update the card because
now it's going to be empty.
So I'm going to go to user data.
I'm going to open it close and I going to say that we're going to put in a graph and stay put here whatever
we have inside user data.
But the card is going to be updated with whatever we get back from the server.
So payload in that cart.
Right.
And remember we are passing a cart with nothing.
Of course this is going to be an empty array.
All right.
But that's OK.
They're going to do.
I'm going to go right here at the bottom and remember that we also have a card DTL property right right
here.
So we need to comment and say that now the car detail it's equal to whatever we get from the action
that payload that cart detail and the car detail is just an empty array.
So it is going to set the car detail back to default.
All right.
Now pretty simple.
Now of course one dispatched reaction so we have the action and everything else.
We called it unsuccess by.
So going to go to cart and included here at the top.
All right.
So of course then we need to dispatch action.
So whenever the transaction.
It's success we're going to go here.
All right.
So what we need to do when you dispatch it with this that props that dispatch open opening close and
we put success by.
So what are we going to be passing to you know the success by right here we say that we are passing
data.
But what do we get inside that data.
Well we need to pass two things to X-server expects two things.
It's going to be a we're waiting for the cart detail.
That's one thing we need to pass.
And the payment data from from Pay-Pal right now.
So we're going to be passing the card detail and the.
And everything else.
But we are pals we are going to be passing just one single no value.
So we're going to be passing an object opening close.
So we have the cart detail which is inside is probs the user that card detail at this point of course
that coma and we need the payment data.
So just to avoid any mistakes I'm going to copy the payment key payment data and this one it's equal
to whatever data we get back from the Pay-Pal connector.
And of course then we run something.
So what are we going to do if everything goes OK.
Well we're going to do the said State.
Now I need to make sure that everything is you know correct.
So if this that prompts that user that success by Remember that we get a success by.
Right.
Let me go here.
Paste this.
First we get a success by on the use of reducer.
We get to access my if we get this equal to true.
It means that everything went OK.
So if we do have this inside user and success vi then begin to reset the component.
Back to you know to show the success message and clear everything else.
So looks good.
Hopefully again there are no mistakes but okay.
It was a lot of code.
So I'm kind of expecting a mistake.
So right.
So let's do the let's do the circuit let's try to buy something.
We're going to reload the application.
I have one right here I'm going to remove it.
Going to go to guitars.
Again an to add maybe a different one.
They're all very expensive.
Well.
Well the rocket one.
Yeah whatever.
And I'm going to add the wrote casters so you'll have two products.
So the amount it's one on one I'm going to go to people of course are going to pass so you can see this
are going to log in.
So it is a testing.
You three say log in log in.
All right so I'm going to complete the purchase pay now
and there is some mistake of course.
All right let's see if we get something on the server.
Nothing.
Let me see if I can get something right here.
Would be open.
Let's see Hermanus.
No that is OK.
OK so let me try to find a mistake and I will tell you what my error was OK.
I did find the mistake but I want to show you something else first.
If I go to the database to rubble 3D everything went OK.
At least with the server.
But it's not updating it's day component but everything else it's fine.
So if you go to waves and go to payments.
So now we have one record and we have the user with the user information.
We have the data you know with the Paypal information and then we get the product.
So if we go to hear date of purchase and everything else everything it's ok.
At least with the payments.
So let's check the user.
If I go to user the card it's zero so it's zero elements and the history it's OK.
Now we have the two elements we just purchased with the pay and everything else.
So the problem must be on the update of products.
We're going to check that right now or the actual components right here.
Notice that everything you know re-offender and now I'm getting this.
But that is OK.
So let me just keep checking.
What is the error.
The next thing going to check is the products that we update it.
You know we are updating the value of the salt that might be the mistake and I'll be right back.
All right.
I know what the problem is versus a mistake.
So right here.
I've deleted of course right now to try again.
The history is that they did everything the payments just deleted everything back to zero so we can
start again and try again.
I did a few cons. locks you know very common way of testing.
The problem is it's not each of serious.
Of course it's serious.
That is this is why everything was working.
But when we enter here we are not reaching this because of course this will not work.
It's each serious story for that or so.
Well you know a lot of code could happen.
OK so I'm going to reload the application I'm going to go to be Tarz.
I'm going to go to Roadmaster again back to my cart.
Pay-Pal check out.
Try again.
I'm going to pay now pay now and there we go we get thank you.
Or there is now complete.
And of course if you go to Mungo or rowboat sweetie and go to payments we have a new payment with all
the data user data and product.
If we go to users we're going to get the cart with zero net with nothing.
And then the history with these fields.
And if we try to find the road caster let me try to find it first.
We get 16.
Well maybe of course I will need to try again just to make sure of this but I'm pretty sure it's working.
Maybe you had 15 from you know from the previous state.
So this one should be go to 17.
Going to do the same thing again to go to guitarists at the broadcaster go to my cart do the Paypal
check out I can pay and remember that we have 16.
So I'm going to pay all of this is correct.
So now if I reopen it's the entry number 10 if I reopen and go to 10 we get 17.
So OK.
So everything works sorry for the solemn stake.
But you know that could happen.
Right.
OK.
So everything is good.
Now what are we going to be doing next.
We're going to be going to my account and we go when we go to my account and of course if I go to my
card we have new items we clear that.
So there's no need to trigger a dispatch with a clear success or anything because the success we get
right here on the card the success by it's only after we do a transaction.
So there's no need to do that.
So if we go to my account we get the history of purchases.
So if I go to my user which is the Francis one we we have now a history.
So we need to capture history and display all the elements right there.
Right.
Very very simple stuff.
So what we need to do next of course is going to be this end user information will create an endpoint
where we can modify some of the information of the user like the name of the passport.
Again very very simple.
And then we can manage this site info which is going to be adding an endpoint to handle the address
the phone and everything else.