All right so now we're going to get the user history and display history right here.
Very very simple.
I'm going to go to the index which is the user dashboard.
And if you remember we've already have access to user and user data so we can grab that user data history
from the user.
And you know do a loop right here.
So first I'm going to go I'm going to go here and I'm going to wrap this I'm going to make a conditional
and are going to say OK if we do have a user and we do have user data and we do have a history history
of course we're going to do something if not we're going to do no.
Ryan same as always.
So no.
All right.
And I'm going to put this inside of here.
Now we need a place where we can render this.
I'm not going to do it right here so I'm going to go to you tills inside user and create a history underscore
blog.
Right.
This is going to be a re-act stateless components and I'm going to call it user just user.
And then history and then block.
Right.
And for now just history block history that's OK.
It's going to go back to index and require this at the top import and we call this user history block
from dot dot for Slash utils for Slash and user for Slash.
And then history block.
Now of course this history block in order to render something it needs to receive the list of products
no history.
So I'm going to call it products you could call history you in it if you wish.
So products equal and the same user user data and history OK.
So now history blogs is going to receive some props and we're going to do something very simple we're
just going to render a table right here a very slim and easy table.
All right.
We're going to let this going to rub everything into a class name and history underscore blocks.
Right.
So we have a table and we have a T head.
All right.
So inside city had we have a T.
Rowe.
And then that's the hetter.
All right.
So the first thing we're going to do is the date of purchase right here then we're going to copy this
out or have to type it again and we're going to have three more.
The next one is going to be the actual product you know the name and the brand and then the price paid
prize paid and then the quantity.
So.
All right.
So right here you could provide the user if you wish.
The idea of the transaction.
Now the idea of our transaction is Mango.
Mango mongoose ID or the payment ID.
Now if you wish to create a different ID you could totally do it.
If you go to the to the server and go to the package that Jason we are using crypt.
So you can create your own encryption and use it as a you know transaction ID to store on the on the
on the payment model.
You can you can go there and use the generated hash and use it as that.
And then of course keep that to the user.
All right.
I'm not going to do it.
We're going to do something very simple.
So we have a t body of course we have the T body open and close and again to create a function called
render and then blocks something like that.
And this is just going to be a function that's going to loop the products.
Right.
So Konst render blocks is just a function that returns some GSX.
So we're going to go here and say OK if we do have props and we do have products you know this product
key comes from prop's we are passing right here.
All right then I'm going to do no where we don't have we don't get anything now since if we do have
something we're going to do prompts that products that map open and close they're going to be passing
the actual item.
Or it could be product and then the iteration.
And of course we return more GSX remember to do that do this and not the curly braces so t are open
and close.
I do key and I going to pass the iteration.
So we have four different things to do.
Just like that.
And we have four different things.
The first one is going to be the date.
The problem is that the date looks a little bit weird.
So this is the data purchase it's non readable for humans.
So we've already installed momen so import moment from moment.
So with moment of course if you don't know moments it's a library it's a third party library where we
can we can use it to parse dates different formats of dates.
Is the you know the best library for that.
I'm there so we use moment open and close.
We need to pass to moment.
What is that we want to parse.
So in this case is product and the date of purchase.
Let me just copy right here.
Date of purchase just to avoid typos.
Then of course we need to pass the format so the format.
It's very simple.
We do month month date date and then Year Ear and one more time.
That is it.
We should be at least getting something and we do.
All right.
Very simple.
Of course right here we need to pass the brand.
So it's product not brand brand.
And then the name of the product so product that name the next one is going to be the price.
So product that price and the last one its product that quantity.
All right let's see what we get.
And there you go.
Of course the price paid and the quantities just one that is OK.
All right so this component it's pretty much done.
We don't need to do anything else is something very very simple.
Right.
So on the next one we're going to do of course we're going to keep completing this because we need to
do three more things.
They use user information to update some of the user information.
And then the site info and we can agree of course a new model on that one to store the page or the site
information so we're going to do that.
And later after the user information.
And then at the end of course we will create the 4 0 4 and then we are ready to deploy.