Right.
So now we're going to be adding the user information which is going to it's going to be where we're
going to be updating the user profile and begin to update the named last name and email then as a bonus
again at a different component to you know reset the passport inside of here of course.
OK.
So let's create a component and we need to create.
Do we need to get two things.
The components we need to render.
And then we need to route on the server where we can handle the request.
But of course let's go first with the actual component.
So we don't have a route I'm going to close everything and open just routes and I'm going to go to a
user and inside of user of course we need to create a component called update profile.
Yes.
Now this update profile that Jay is going to be real simple it's just going to go to a different component
which is going to render the information about the user.
I'm not going to do it here because maybe as a bonus again I'm going to be adding things.
So I went to you know create a clear place for this.
So re-act stateless components just like that.
And there's one update profile could be just user profile.
All right.
We need the user layout right here so import user and then lay out from and then dot forward slash.
And I believe it's going to be oh sorry that that force one more time that that force slash a Josee
and then user cut.
So we need to wrap everything with the user layout right here going to add in each one which says profile.
And then of course we're going to make a reference to our new component.
I'm going to call it up update personal info.
So import update personnel info or info and info and personal with a capital P..
All right.
We don't have this component.
I'm going to go again to user not admin inside user and create a new directory file called update underscore
and do it again update underscore personnel and then info dodginess.
All right so if we can get imported from DOD forward slash and then update personnel and info.
So we're going to make a reference to this component.
Copy and paste and does it now on this one.
This one of course we need to make this.
We need to do handle state so it's a re-act class based component and are going to call it the same
as this update.
Personal info.
OK and this one I'm going to say info.
Whatever.
Now of course we don't have a route for this so I'm going to go to our routes and import and I believe
we can call it a personal info update profile update profile.
Right.
So update profile from date for Slash components for Slash user and then update profile.
Now the route of this.
First I'm going to copy this one and paste it at the bottom and it's going to be inside user this time
not open and then user underscore profile profile and the free go to the route it's user oh so user
profile that took it so can it copy the component and pass it here.
It still update profile and just one true.
All right.
And since it's a user I'm going to chop it and put it with all the rest of the users right.
So now of course we get the get the app and restart server.
All right.
So I go to a user information.
We get it.
Sometimes you get that loading it's because the server is not running again is not giving you any response
back so that's why we get the loading but that's ok.
Sometimes it's a little bit slow.
All right so now we have the profile.
So what do we need to do inside the profile.
Well we need to create a state right here state where we can handle all the forms and everything else.
So right from the start we need to import the form fields because we need to use it and instead of doing
this I want to save some time are going to go to register log in to register and are going to copy this
because it's pretty much the same.
Same same idea.
So going to copy and paste the form fields from you till we are going to use connect.
So I'm going to copy the connect and put it right here at the bottom.
What else do we need.
We need the form actions.
Remember form actions.
So I'm going to copy and paste it at the bottom right and that is it for now.
That is it.
Of course after we create them we need to create this patch for the actions for this and everything
else and we will create a new form action a new function because whenever we we are going to be rendering
just some inputs.
So whenever we enter here we need to fetch information from the user and populate the inputs.
We can do this on other sections.
Not in this project.
So we're going to do it right now so what do we need first.
First what we need is a state.
Again we are using forms.
So I'm going to say state equals open and close.
And again I'm going to go to register and we still have the form are and the force form success.
Then we have some form data.
So I'm going to copy the form data and open and close Dargo.
Now on the form data we have three different elements the name the last name and the email and if we
go to register they are the same here.
So again going to save some time or going to copy this and paste it right here.
And that is it.
We still need some functions from the from here just like the update form.
Remember that function.
So then it copy the update form I'm going to paste it right here and this one is going to be update.
Underscore user.
All right.
Then on the what else do we have the submit form.
So I'm going to copy the submit form and of course we're going to make it very simple can it copy paste
the submit form instead of register right here is going to be update user.
So update user update user.
And there's one for now.
We are not going to dispatch anything.
So I'm just going to say console log data to submit so we can of course make some changes right here.
All right let's get.
So I'm going to go to the actual component right here.
They will return.
And we are going to return a div with the form again on the register.
The form contains an answer made with the Submit submit form handler.
So on safe bet we do the submit form.
All right.
So I can divide the the left and the right so we will use the same thing then register the form block
2.
And you know the blocks inside.
So I'm going to copy this one the form block leaks the first one and I'm going to paste it right here.
Very simple.
Let me select this and make this a little bit nice.
Nicer.
There we go.
So I will of course add a title.
So it's going to be page 2 and then personal information could be personal account information.
All right.
So now we get the name same key and same key for the last name and the last one is going to be you know
the e-mail.
So for this one just going to be adding a dev.
And what we need to do is same thing here.
Just add the form field e-mail.
So it's pretty much like the register.
Same same idea.
So of format selection.
There we go.
What's going happen with it but I'm again saying we will have a success as a form success in our error
if we get an error.
So we're going to copy this just same thing pretty much going to paste it and make it a little bit nicer.
All right.
So we do have one form error if we get an error and it's plit please check your data.
That's OK.
Now I'm going to add the success we didn't have it on the on the register because we were showing a
dialog box but in this one we will show the success.
So it's not state we make reference to that form success.
And if we do have something we're going to do something if not no.
Right.
So the dev.
It's the same no voice are going to attach class name of form success.
Right.
And you know this one is going to say success whatever.
Now instead of create an account you know update abjured personal info whatever.
Very good.
So if you go to our component real simple.
It took us nine minutes to create everything.
Now the only thing we need to do is to of course dispatch an action with all this information but first
I need to prefetching it Prete populate the information about the user inside of here.
Let's do that right now.
All right so if we think about this we don't need to dispatch an action to get the information about
the user.
We've have all everything inside the redux right store.
So we can get it from here.
Now the thing is that we might be using this function just like we did with update or data and is form
valid.
We could use it later.
So on the component that bound are going to say component that Mt..
Open and close and again to create a new virus called new form form data some like that and it's going
to be equal to something and we can create a function inside of utils and forms and form actions that
you know where we can grab the personal information and update state of this form.
Right.
Just like with that before.
So I'm going to call it populate and then fields and not option fields.
Make me the suggestion for this one because we have a populate option fields but this one is for the
selects.
So I don't want the option I just want fields right now again if we think about this what do we need
instead of this function.
We need the state of form data so we can loop that and replace the values and everything else.
And we need the user data so we can you know grab the values and put it right here.
OK.
So I'm going to go and say the first argument there's that state that form data right.
The second one is the user data.
So there's that Propst that user and then that user data all right of course after we get the news the
new state for new form.
You know we get the new form the I'm sorry the OMI this that form the new state of form data.
We want to set the state with whatever we get back from that function.
So this that said state open and close and then we say that form data it's equal to new form data.
I'm going a little bit fast because we kind of did this like five times already throughout the you know
the whole course.
So we did it a lot of times so there's no need to go really slow right here.
So we're going to copy the name of the function.
Going to go at the top.
We need to include it and right here are going to do this and put populate fields and we're going to
go to form actions and create the function.
So we need to export the Konst so export Konst populate fields.
This is just a function that returns something right.
So on this function again we will be receiving the form data form and then data.
I believe it did it just like this.
I'm going to leave it like this doesn't matter right now and then fields right of course coma fields.
Right so now what we need to do.
The only thing we need to do we need to loop this form data right.
And inside of this grab the same key we have in fields and you know replace the values.
So just to show you that before I was doing this and this is actually correct.
But you can do you can just grab the form data loop head without storing it inside of a new marble.
You can totally do this.
It's going to work.
I'm just doing this just to be safe.
So form.
Oh sorry for opening close and then I'm going to say let let key in form data right.
So for every keenly informed data we can grab the key and whatever is that we need to do in this case
that bother you the valid and the touch and we can also grab the message validation message and replace
it with whatever whatever we have in fields and then true or false.
Right.
So.
So we have the form data open and close we pass the key and we enter the first one which is the value.
And this one it's equal to fields and the same key right there we go updated the value are going to
cover this one just here and they form data.
Whoops let me copy the correct way.
So ok then we have the valid and we need to set it to true because now we do have a value.
So true.
What else we need to form data.
Again the key and we need to change the touched at the top.
It's going to be true.
And then of course we need to validate some validation measures message.
So I'm going to copy and paste that.
And we set it to nothing.
And at the end of course we will return form data all right that is it.
If we go back to our application and see if we get it we get an error C-y can out every property user
data of undefined.
This prompts that user and the user data.
Let me just see why
of course it's because I forgot to inject the props.
That's why we are not getting it there.
We have no props.
All right.
So over this.
So I'm going to do maps data prompts and this happens when you go a little bit faster forget things.
So we will enter the user will access the user and then user again.
And we need to pass the connect open and close map state to props and then we pass it to the component.
All right.
So all the time now and we've got to get Francis and we get Jones and then Francis GM and that comes
everything.
It's correct now.
Sorry for this mistake.
So again when you go fast and talking at the same time you of course make mistakes.
That's OK.
So what do we need to do now.
If I make a change I need to dispatch an action that action is going to go to the server and we will
be updating the information.
And when we return we will update the store with the new dig new information inside probs.
All right.
OK.
So of course this went a little bit long.
Let's go to the next one and create the route and the dispatch.