Right so whenever we submit the form we need to dispatch an X right.
OK.
First we need this route on the server to handle the request.
So I'm going to go to server and going to create that function.
You know that route right now is going to be very very simple.
After doing this this one is piece of cake.
So I'm going to add an apple up the Rigaud app that post and we will be getting the data.
As Jason saw AP forward slash users for Slash and update update person or add up the profile events
we're going to use the oath because they need to be authenticated.
And then of course we run a function.
So request and response.
So we need to go to the user.
So we say user user.
Now again since we are using the ALF we can just find one an update now what we need to find.
It's the user ID so we search by id and we have it inside.
Request that user that comes from the AUF and then underscore ID.
So what are we going to be updating.
So we need to update and for this prematch we need to update everything that is inside the body.
So we do set.
Let me do it like this.
We do a dollar sign and then set and then we say that we want to update whatever key we have inside
the request.
That body which is named last name and forgot the one name last name and email right.
Email your email or get a copy.
So of course we want to get the new data back.
The new state of this all the updates the of the user.
And then of course we say new true.
And then we just run a function the callback function reader is simple error and document.
Now of course if you get an error so error we return response with a J sign saying success then falls
and the actual error you can catch this whatever you want.
And then of course we return a response with a status of 200 and we just send something.
So what are we going to be sending for now.
Nothing just success.
And then true.
Just send success true if everything goes OK.
We should be you know getting the new information.
All right.
So I'm going to go here.
So everything looks good.
No mistakes hopefully no mistakes.
So now we have a we have a server.
So what we need to do now.
Inside of update personal information we need to create that dispatch you know the action.
So I'm going to call it update user data.
Let's go first to the user reducer the user actions and I'm going to create a type just like always
and this one update data user right.
I'm going to add to the types.
So export Export Konst update data user and then update data and then user.
All right.
I going to go back to user actions and I'm going to do this at the bottom.
Why not.
So we need to export a function called an update user data or update data user whatever we're going
to get a data to.
So mad.
And then we just run a function.
So Konst request equals and then we do X zero's post and we need to pass whatever we get back from the
user server.
I'm sorry whatever we get back in this marvel from user server.
And then the route.
It's update profile and again and going a little bit fast because we kind of did this previously many
many times.
So we do a post to that route and we pass the data to submit.
Right.
All right.
Then of course we get a promise.
So whenever the promise resolves we're going to send the response with.
And in this case you can do this return response that data if you want to safes and code you can delete
this and just return.
This doesn't matter.
It's not completely up to you.
So OK.
So at the end we will return a type and a payload right.
The type it's going to be equal to update data user.
Right.
So update data user and whatever we get back from the request.
All right.
So very good.
Now we do have this.
And of course in this case after we update you can a changed state that everything was a success.
So after a couple of seconds I went to remove that.
So for this one I need to clear whatever is going to set on update daily user.
So we kind of need an export function func shone clear.
Update user.
So we need that in this case so clear update user.
We just get a return type and I'm going to create it right now I'm going to call it clear.
Update user data and the payload payload.
It's nothing.
All right.
We don't have a type I need to add it so clear update user data.
I'm going to go to types.
Export Konst equals to.
I remember that a maybe when we started this project I show you the state of this file which is what
was real slim.
Look at it now read it back and it does good in real life is going to get much much bigger.
So update user data.
All right.
I believe.
Clear.
Update user data.
Very good.
All right.
So we're good to go.
Now we need to go to the.
Of course to use a reducer and do both.
So get a copy of the data user and clear and go to the reducer.
So user readers are going to bring to type.
All right.
So now at the bottom when we copy the first one update data user.
So if the case is that we get an update data user but we're going to be doing is return something.
Right.
All right.
So we will return dot dot dot and the state.
And now again we need to create a key to catch that success so update user and equals to action that
payload.
Right.
So now we need the clear update user.
So in the case that we get clear of the user data we return that adad stayed coma and we set the update
user to whenever we get on the action that payload.
Very good man.
So if you think about it you know just use one that's ok for now.
All right so let's dispatch in action and see what happens.
So I'm going to go to update personal information.
And of course we need to bring the right here.
We need to bring from the user actions these functions so import and then update.
I'm just going to go to the user actions and copy again.
I don't want any typos right here.
So we bring that one and we need to clear one.
So we call that clear update user right.
So it's from the that for Slashdot that force slash we go to actions and we go to user actions right.
All right.
Looks good.
So and I made a mistake right here.
Update.
Why is that.
So update update user data.
Right.
So now whenever we submit the form we want to go to submit form and on the date that's made whenever
the form is valid we want to of course dispatch an action.
So I'm going to delete this.
I'm not going to test it.
We're going to go because of course you know we did this many many times so there's no need for me to
show the console.
So we are going to do it this patch and we do the update user data.
Right.
We need to pass that data to submit so data to submit.
And of course then we're going to do something.
So then opening close and we run the callback function right.
So what are we going to be doing now is an update going to check if we have an update user inside of
the store when or where the application comes smack from relax and begin to check if we have an update
user of true.
Right here the update user.
So if it's success true of course you're going to say say change to form success to true.
And after maybe two or three to three seconds we can at dispatch to clear up the user and we're going
to set this back to false again because of this.
Precisely.
So first if open close if this not props that user dot and we enter the update user remember we called
this on the user register.
Just going a copy update user and we get a success.
So success will double as then we're going to do something if this happens we can at this not set state
and the state we're going to change to form success to true.
All right then we're going to attach this is a Colback and we're going to do a said time out.
So after two seconds we're going to run a different function that you know clears everything out and
dispatched it clear.
So this that prompts that dispatch and we are going to use the clear update user.
All right.
So clear update user and we don't need a callback right here.
So and again we're going to do that does that said state and begin to change the form success back to
false.
So we can get rid of that you know success message America this should be working.
Hopefully no mistakes I've reloaded just in case I get to do friends.
Jonas's and then update personal information.
We get success.
Now if I overload the information and there was a problem with the server or something like that this
is going to be Jones again.
So I reload and we get Jonas's Francis Xavier just like the no x.
You didn't know.
Can I reload.
And everything is good.
Maybe you don't want to change email but that's OK.
I'm going to change it.
So it's going to be Francis X..
Of course not let me do it here.
Francis X. update are going to reload and everything is cool.
So let me go back on this one and update it back and update the Jones right.
Farver load Jones Xavier and Frances.
Everything was OK.
The State of the file right now because you're done.
Later as a bonus I'm I can add a new component to know reset the passport.
And of course they need to know the current passport because they are they are Lagann so they should
know the password.
It's going to be very very simple.
So let's go to the next one and the next one is going to be site info.
Going to create a new plays on the models where we can store information about the site.
Could be you know a u r l maybe an address or well of course all of this and maybe some other things.
And remember that at home and we are not going to do it right now going to do this as a bonus.
We are rendering this images but we didn't have a place where we control the image and where we control
the you know the title right here title and the button and everything else.
So on that place and that model we can host this kind of information you know the misc information just
like the page inside info.
And maybe the promotions right here.
So let's go to the next one and start with the site Imphal.