All right so now we are going to do the site info.
So inside of the site info it's going to be pretty much different components.
For now we're going to get only one later I'm going to do as a bonus one more component but pretty much
in this place we can we can update the site information just like the footer with the address and the
phone and everything else and maybe you are thinking why doing this.
Well imagine that you're the owner of the other shop needs to change the phone and you can have a common
place to do that.
So they will need to contact you and you will need to go make the changes you know deploying the application
again.
So you know not a good idea.
OK.
So first we need to come place to it so we can render this site info.
So I'm going to go to user are going to go to admin because he's an admin route and I'm going to create
a new file called manage and then site that jackass.
Now this managed site is going to be kind of like the index because remember I told you I'm going to
do a bonus section with a feature.
So this one is just going to render a component that contains a form.
So we can you know make the request to make the update.
Right.
So Match site is going to be a re-act stateless component and I'm going to call it manage and then site
right to that and then manage site.
It's going to create insight Atman a new file called Update site and then info whenever you know something
like a good name.
So this one is going to be react class-B component because we need to dispatch actions.
Use forms and everything else so update a model within the company will you update then site and then
info and then side info.
Or could be formed you know form that's get a copy of course from within mench side.
We need to import it so Update site info from that forward slash and then update site info.
And of course I'm going to make a reference to this component inside of your second open.
Make the reference and that's it.
That is the only thing that this component is going to do.
Now of course we need to create the route.
Oh and of course we need to include the user layout.
So import then user and then lay out from that for Slashdot for Slash that one more time then I believe
it's a chose C..
And then for Slash and.
Oh no sorry it's one more up three.
So H.O. C and then use lay out right.
And we need to wrap pretty much the whole component inside of here.
Of course we need to we need to add this as a route.
No.
So let's go to routes.
First I'm going to import it so import and we call this managed site.
From dobbed forward slash components for Slash user or slash.
And then the update.
Now been of course then for Slash and then manage site.
So since this is anatman I'm going to copy and paste it at the bottom and this one.
The route for this site info could be you know something else but that's OK.
So going to paste it and of course every year load the application.
We get the nav and then the form which is the component inside this one.
All right.
So we need to do a lot of things first.
First let's start to get something out of this.
Maybe the form or a title or something.
You know the start to create the form up.
Going to close this one close and pretty much everything.
And just like with that before because we are going to be working with forms are going to go to the
ER just to log in and bring the register components because we need to import things at the top and
you know this ones are pretty much the same thing.
So update site info.
I'm going to paste it right here so we have a form fill up update generated data is form valid and if
you remember with that function you know to populate fields.
So this one is the same.
Same thing.
So I'm going to go to update personal info where we actually it.
I did this and copied it populate field right comma and paste it.
Now the rowdiest is going to be a little bit different so that forward slash.
One more one directory up and the same thing for you tells all right going to save it and see if we
can get the error.
Now let's get it works.
Now we need to connect.
So import then connect and then from Riak redux.
All right.
And of course then later we can import the action.
For now everything is get so going to bring connect and then update site info.
All right.
Now of course a pre-populated we need to bring props and we can't import the prompts from a new reducer
in a new auction.
Right because now we have the site and they are now decide it's not products and it's not user.
So we will need to create a news pod for this so I'm going to do it right now and of course later we
can to use it.
So going to match state to prompts just like this going to lead the own prompts and the keyboard for
this is going to be site.
Then state that site.
All right so we don't have a file for this actions and we don't have them pretty much.
We don't have anything so let's created right now.
I'm going to go to auctions and inside actions.
And you filed called side actions right.
Or go when you file side actions that Jap's what's good.
So now just like the other ones going to bring the all the ones we need to import ASIO's just like this.
We need to import types.
For now I'm just going to import it and do this and later of course we're going to use it now.
Of course for now it's going to be empty so I'm going to comment.
And now we need to import the route where the site requests are going to go.
So if you remember we have this one inside components and then Minsk.
I'm going to go here to create a new Marvel called site server so we are pretty much doing the same
work we did with the other ones.
That's the only thing we are doing so we need to go to Eutelsat and misc.
So tells me go ask.
And of course I'm going to create a new place for this one.
So export export then it Konst and then side server equals and we are going to go to.
Same thing than before.
API for Slash and for Slash and that site.
So we don't have this route and server.
We will need to create it.
But there are going to be the route it's really really simple.
All right so now we have the we have a site server so site server and that is going to work.
All right.
Now of course in a minute we're going to create the action.
But first we need to bring the we douceur to this.
So we're going to go to reducers when it opened the index of reducers and create a new file called side
reducer.
Yes.
So on this one on this section we're doing all the boring boring stuff.
But we need to do it.
There is no way around this.
So just like with the index I'm sorry with the actions we need to import types.
So I'm going to copy paste and from now empty.
Then of course we need to export a function.
It's going to go to a reducer I can accomplish pretty much everything.
And then of course delete it and maybe if you're on if you're saying Dude why are you not typing what
you can do.
You type everything that you build your application.
No not really OK.
So it looks looks OK.
Correct.
Now of course before we can begin we need at least maybe something that looks like a form right here
and we pretty much have everything we need inside register because we kind of already did this.
So we need the form state and the form data inside the state.
So I'm going to go right here and say state equals and then we get the form data with the form error
and everything else.
And of course we will need to do a lot more right here.
So OK so what are we going to be using.
We're going to create a pod right here inside of our our server that it's going to be it's going to
be site.
And in this case is going to be sites and the site sites begin to have a different piece of information
just like the address the working hours the phone and the info always.
Right.
OK.
So what we're going to be pretty much using is again address hours phone and e-mail.
So we need to create a valid you know a valid form data that we can use.
So I'm going to go to the register and I'm going to copy this one.
And of course we're going to change it.
So this one is going to be address.
So address it is still an input.
It's not named Iput is going to be address input address.
And please enter the site address.
That's OK.
And again this is going to be valid false touched false.
And we can add that show label property show Leavell.
And this one is going to be true.
I'm not sure if we are really using the show label.
We're going to check it later.
That's OK.
OK.
I'm going to add a label right here.
We're going to use it and this one is going to be address.
All right.
Next one is the working hours.
So get a copy of this one pasted at the bottom and then I'm going to say.
Hours.
OK.
So input address you know working hours and right here hours you know that this is boring but we need
to do it.
And inside hours or maybe working hours.
All right.
Next one is going to be the phone.
So phone copy paste is when it's going to be phone than working actually phone number.
And this one with the phone and enter the phone number
all right.
So we have one more to go which is the email of the website and everything is going to be true right
here with show Leavell going to show all.
So I'm going to cubbing phone are going to go here and say e-mail.
And now think about this instead of the register.
We do have an e-mail Sanch is going to copy that one.
Go to update site info.
Replace this one.
And the only thing we need to add right here is the show Leavell of true.
And then we just passed a label that says label open close and then shop e-mail or something like that.
Doesn't matter right now.
OK.
Get Burguet.
So now we have all the form data we need more thanks right here including the update form function.
So update form update form.
One thing less to do than we need to submit forms so submit form just get a copy go right here submit
form right inside if you're going to say console log and then data to submit.
Right.
You know we did this many many times.
So this one is going to be site info.
Same thing with the old ones.
We are going to need that populate but we're going to do it later.
Because first we need a server or maybe a place where we can you know fetch the information about the
site.
Right.
All right.
OK.
That is good.
So let's create a form for this.
So we were going to use a div of course just like they were just for.
We need to copy the form and create a form.
Right.
So form.
So we will need four different form fields.
I'm going to copy the first one.
I'm going to copy the e-mail so I don't do it again.
And we can have four.
So the first one the second one the third one and the fourth one and I'm going to rearrange this so
you can look a little bit nicer for my selection.
Right.
So the first one it's the address.
So address just like this and address right here just like we have at the top address Burguet.
And I'm going to maybe close this ones.
Yeah that's it.
OK.
So the next one is going to be the hours so hours and same thing right here.
Now the phone and then phone what else we need e-mail we've already have it.
All right.
Get some going to go back to register.
And now we need the Budenz you know the Confirm error and form success and everything else.
So I'm going to go to this def and it copy the div and go back right here and I'm going to paste it
right.
And it's a dead format.
And then arrow label.
OK forget it.
You can show it in this instead of this one.
Create an account.
Well not really.
No it's going to be modify or update update it's a good word update.
And then we need the does that state that success.
So we don't have it on the register so that state that form success may find success if we do have something
that we do something if not we don't do anything.
And what we're going to do we just render a div just like this one and this one is going to be form
success form success and we're going to say chess success.
We are almost done the pain.
It's almost over.
All right.
OK.
We are done with you know the boring stuff.
Let me add a title because it looks weird to me without a title.
So let me go here and say one side info.
Right.
OK.
Looks a little bit better.
So we pretty much have everything we need right at least to show something right here.
Now when I enter to this modified site info I want to go to the server fetch whatever we have on the
on the database for site info.
Right.
And pre-populated right here.
Now the problem is that we don't have anything on our database.
We don't have anything.
And if we go to the models we don't have anything that says that talking about site info.
So this is what we need to do.
We need to create a model for the site.
Right.
So we can update modify values.
We need a route on the server where we can make the request to update or to you know get the site information
and we will need to add some dummy information at the least the first information on our application
that talks about about site.
So whenever we load the screen we're going to get the values and populate right here.
So let's go to the next section and we can go to the server and do all of this.
It's going to be very very simple.
Right.
Not that complicated.