All right so let's do all the server on the server side part of the you know the site info.
So first we need to model.
So I'm going to go to models right here and create a model called site and remember it's going to be
called and I can tell you something right now if we go to models for example and maybe you didn't notice
you know maybe if you go to models we see brand we see payment product user and what everything is singler.
If I go to brand it's brand everything it's singler.
But if I go to mongoose whenever I go to it goes to Mongul Mungo creates the plural of this so brands
payments products users.
And what's it going to do something and this is of course relevant.
So I'm going to create a model and this one is going to be site not sites or something like that just
site.
All right.
So on the side we just need to bring all the logic right here.
Konst mongoose recalls require and then mongoose or ago.
Then we need to create this schema so Konst site schema right equals mongoose.
Then schema schema open and close and we pass an object that of course Konst Konst then side with a
capital S equals mongoose.
We passed that model just like we did before.
And we say that this one is capital S side coma and then we pass this side schema right.
Just like that before.
Piece of cake.
Then module that exports equals and we export.
Cite this site for forget.
So how are we going to do this.
So later like I told you again we're going to hold up the contact information and maybe some relevant
information about the website.
But we also are going to do the home this one so we can have several pieces of information inside the
site info or the site.
So again is again is saving going to store everything in a single a single document and inside of that
document of course we're going to get all the information we need.
So going to create two places one called featured.
So inside feature we're going to host everything that got to do with the you know this one.
And of course we're going to do it later.
So this one is going to be required.
True.
And that coma type of array type and then array coma.
And each side of the array which is going to be the default as in re begin to store all the information
about the feature.
Later we're going to do the promotion or home promotion and we can have a different key called home
promotion or something like that.
But the thing is that when we do when we do an update we enter the key that we need to do the update.
For example if you want to update the site we will not enter to this one.
We will enter to the next one which is site info something like this.
Right.
So we're using a single document to host many many things.
So this one again just like this one it's pretty much the same thing required true and blah blah blah
blah blah Vergon.
So now we have the model of course we need to import the site from to the server.
So I'm going to close the model I'm going to go to the server right here top and we need to Konst site
equals require open and close for Slash.
We go to models of models.
Well models.
And then it's going to be of course site.
Right.
So now we have the model right here.
So are going to go at the very very end of the application we're going to do and get a copy and see
if I can find it I can copy this.
I'm going to go right at the end.
So you know where to find it on the final code.
And this one is going to be sacked.
So right here we're going to get all the side routes.
So now we have a model year including the model on the server on the server file so we can create the
routes and we need two routes one to get the data and the other one to update the data.
Right.
So going to go to app are going to create the route.
Right now at least they want to get it.
So app and this one is going to be get.
So the route is going to be API for Slash the site for Slash and side underscore data.
No we don't need an entity middle middleware right here because we're going to get it from the home
or actually for the footer.
So request and response.
So the only thing we're going to do right here is enter a signed site and bring everything.
So I'm going to go to a site I'm going to find open open like this and I'm going to say OK I want to
bring everything that you get inside the site part of the database and then we just run the callback.
So we get an error and a.
And the site actually the site information.
So of course if we get an error and I'm just going to copy this we if we get an error I'm going to send
a status of 400 and then send error just like that.
Very simple.
Now of course if everything goes OK which it will I'm going to say send status 200.
And now what I want to send is going to be let me do the scent first.
It's going to be whatever we get inside the site right here.
But we need you know kind of a different piece of information maybe later we can change it.
But right now the only thing I want to get is that these the things we have right here the site info.
I don't care about the featured images.
I just want to get this one.
So since here you are pretty much bringing all the doc everything all the document right here.
You know we are bringing feature inside info.
I'm going to say OK.
Give me the site but I want just the information that it's inside the site info.
So it calcite info right site info.
Yeah.
So in the media on the front and what we will be getting is just inside info and then we will send this
information to the footer.
And you know bubbletop everything else.
All right for now we are get we need to we need to update.
But can it do we can to do it later.
Now the thing is that we have a route making a request for this information but we don't have this information.
We don't have it at all right.
So what do we need to do.
We can end it.
We going to need to manually create a collection.
So I going to go create a collection.
And remember that everything is plural.
So this one is going to be sites I can create.
And now we have sites right.
Going to show you how the structure is going to go have the finished one right here.
Notice that I get to sites and it's going to be just one document just one with all the information
we need inside.
You know the id the name which is going to be site info or whatever.
You know you could actually not get this one but you can pretty much what you can get is featured and
the site info actually an array just like this so I'm going to do this I'm going to edit and this is
what we need to get.
So I'm going to copy this one and you will need to of course pretty much do it by hand.
But don't worry I can give you time.
I'm going to cancel and I'm going to go to our waves.
I'm going to go to sites and I'm going to inject I'm going to create a new document insert documents
can I select all and paste it.
Now since you're going to be entering this manually you don't need the object I.D. So you don't really
need it.
We don't need the name.
We just need the feature and the site info.
It's a feature.
It's an empty right site info.
And mine is mine XP.
And the site info.
It's an array with an object inside.
Now this object key contains key value pairs right.
You get the address.
And if we go to update site info it's pretty much the same thing we get.
We get right here.
So make sure that the key names the keys are you know pretty much the same address address.
We get ours.
We get ours get phone we get phone and e-mail e-mail right.
So I'm going to save this and I a mistake someplace.
There we go.
I'm going to save it and advocate sites we get one result with the idea of course.
And the featured but we do have some site information right.
So in theory if I go to this route we should be getting it right.
OK.
So I'm going to go to postman and you don't need to do this.
I'm just going to test it right here with you.
So I'm going to open I believe we were using the U r l u r l.
I'm on the waifs environment.
So it's a u r l than we do for Slash and it's API site data.
So if you make a request here we should be getting the site information.
So let's see what happens.
I consent and we get you know an irate with an object inside that says address our phones and e-mail.
So we are getting the information.
So now we are ready of course to go to update site info and dispatch an action to get you know all the
data and pre-populated everything inside our form right here.
So let's do that right now.
OK so let's go to the producer and create a valid use for this.
So when did you go to site action.
Right.
OK.
So we need to import types.
Right now we don't have a type for this.
So we need to create it I'm going to call it get site data or something like that.
You can again choose whatever you want.
Zeid data.
So we need to add it to types.
So I'm going to go to types and I'm going to split this and export it will do the same thing.
Export Konst get side data and then get site data right.
So now we have the action and we have a type.
Now we need a function or something right here.
So I'm going to create an export function called Get site data open and close.
So this one it's really simple we just need to make a request that you are l and that's it.
So Konst request equals ASIO's that get for Slash.
And we have the site server right here so we going to use template strengths are going to pass the site
server then for Slash.
And I believe we called this site data right.
Data going to go and say Okay.
So then we can at open catch the response you know usual stuff and returned response that data then
we need to return a type and a payload.
So we turn open and then type of gets data and then payload bay load off of request.
Sometimes I make weird noises.
Sorry.
So request Burguet.
Now we have to get side data.
What do we need to do next.
At a reduced or ryme.
So I'm going to go to every company gets data go to the producer and it's going to be site reducer and
we need to import from types.
So import types and then get site data right.
So this one really simple.
If the case is that we get side data we can return whatever we get inside the DOD state state coma and
then side data call an action that payload write looks nice now everything's ready.
Everything's ready to go.
This has dispatched the action.
So I'm going to go to update site info and since we need the information from here so we can pre-populated
everything we need to do a component that mount right just like it before it.
I'm going to copy the name of the function get side data and I'm going to import it right here at the
top you know below the connect.
So import open and close get side data from the action so that that force last one more one more and
and actions and then side actions.
Right.
Nothing so far.
I'm going to go right here to the component that mount are going to do a component that mounts so we
can fetch that information component that mount.
Then we open it and we do this that probs dot this patch and then we do get site data.
And whenever we get that data back then we do it then and we do a function and we run the callback.
So again we need to Prete populate this form fields with the data we get from Get side data.
So just be sure to get a console log it because maybe you get an error.
So I want to inspect this stuff Propst that site.
Right.
We are doing map state prompts for a site.
And there's one more thing we didn't I didn't do.
Maybe you know side data.
So remember that from the data the response is an array.
So I'm going to answer that site data and bring the array.
So while I'm creating this as an array right why am I using an array.
The thing is that later outside we might have many many things inside and maybe I would like to add
different things inside site info not just decide if you want to add a different object inside the array
that contains something else.
So I know that the first position on the array is going to be the site info and the next one is going
to be whatever something else.
So I can add multiple things right here.
That's why I'm not just using what single object.
But again you can do it whatever your own style just can use an object within a key and then you have
a key which has that info.
And then inside you have a different object you can completely do that no problem.
Totally do that.
All right.
But let's get on the cold side.
I don't eat it.
OK.
So now I'm going to cause luck and I'm going to of course get the information the way we want.
But the thing is that what I didn't do is to add the side reducer right here.
So we were not going to get anything so import.
I can call a sight from that for Slash and then side reduce or and then say coma site right enough.
So from here the only thing we need to do is to create a barbell called again whatever you want.
In this case form data because it makes sense in its new form data you and then form data.
And this one is going to be equal to the populate fields we created at the top.
So going to copy are going to bring the populate fields so we can pre populate all the fields we need
to pass that this state that form data.
That's what this function needs.
And then let me close this.
You're going to need pretty much the response from the server.
Right.
Whenever we get injected inside side data through prompts.
That's the first thing.
And then we do this that set stayed open and close and we saved form data and it's equal to new form
data.
All right.
There you go.
So let's see if this works.
Hopefully no arse so when our side reducer cannot resolve types in reducers OK so I possibly can save
some time.
So I've got two mistakes.
The first one is dot dot for Slash actions and then types.
That's the first thing.
And then each side of the update info I'm not passing the maps data prompts to reload it.
We get the information and we are populating everything correctly so everything is get the own thing
we need to do now is to create a route inside the server so we can update you know we can send the post
create a post route so we can send the request and update the information here and we're going to be
adding you know the dynamic information.
That's why we are doing all of this instead of the future footer.
We're going to be connecting to the side getting the information about the side.
And of course passing the props right here.
So let's get to the next one and do that.