All right so let's create the route for this.
So it's going to be app post opening close and we need to pass pretty much same thing than this one.
So OK.
We do need the south more aware and we need the admin middleware.
And then of course we run a function with request and response right copy request and response.
Now if you think about this inside of the sites we only get one document so we can find it by what by
ID.
What happens if you don't really have the ID or what copy of the ID.
I don't know.
So you could yeah totally could.
What are you going to do.
I'm going to create I'm going to edit the document and I'm going to add a name to this.
Remember we had a name I just deleted this.
So you know I going to go below the I.D. and I'm going to say OK so the name for this whole section
it's site just like this and then coma.
And I'm going to save it.
So now instead of this document we have a name so we have a reference to you know to find it by what
we want.
All right.
So I'm going to go and say I want to enter the side.
I want to find an update the one that calls cite as a name right.
So there is one way to do it.
Name Of course you could do something else if you wish.
Completely up to you.
So now we're going to find this name and the thing is that we don't want to update all the information
we get inside of here.
We just want to update site info on this case.
OK.
So we're going to go and pass this.
So when I'm going to do I'm going to set it we're going to set the whole orbed you know.
So the whole information we have inside the site info.
So I'm going to say I want to enter the site site and that info and this key it's equal to this key
and the site info.
I'm going to say.
OK.
So now the new state of this new values are going to be whatever we get from the body.
So you always need to pass pretty much all the information.
So I'm going to do Khoa I'm going to say new equals true and then coma and then we run a function with
error.
And the documents are.
And Doc now again just like before if we get an error I'm going to send the 400 or we can said we sell
a Jason we can do that Jason.
And we sense success falls and then the air.
And if everything goes OK I want to return our response with a status of 200 just like this.
Then we do send and we sent them Jason.
So I'm going to send the same success.
So success.
True coma.
And I'm going to send.
I want to return just to site info.
So I'm going to do site info and this one.
It's inside the doc that we get back whenever we update and whenever we update of course we get the
whole document back everything.
So I want to return just to Doc and whatever I get inside site info.
And that's it for me.
That's nice.
All right.
So now we have a right of course we need to create.
Go to the site actions and at the you know the update logic.
So first like for going to do the type so Update site data.
Right.
Going to create a function.
Real quick export function and update update site data.
Open and Close.
Now of course this one is going to be getting the data at this med so data to to see met.
And then of course we need to make the request very simple.
Pretty much the same that this one can copy and paste and this one is going to be a post request and
as an argument we need to pass data to submit so data to submit.
That of course we return same thing response that data are going to copy this one pasted at the bottom
and make it a little bit nicer.
All right.
And we return to type update site data and whatever we get back from the request.
Now let's go to the site reducer.
I'm going to bring to type and I'm going to say OK if the case is that we get site data we're going
to return something.
Right.
OK.
So what we're going to be returning is they of course dot dot dot dot state coma and are going to change
this data.
So whenever we make some changes right here since we are displaying all the site type data of course
we don't get it through prop's everything is going to get updated.
All right.
I'm going to go and say action that payload and this time I just want to bring the site info.
Remember from the server we are returning key with site info.
So that's the one I want to get inside of here.
That looks nice.
So we're going to close it.
I don't need it.
I'm going to leave this one open and I'm going to go back to update site info.
So on this one of course we need the update site data which is the name of the dispatch know the action
and I'm going to bring it right here at the top.
So now we need to dispatch whenever we of course submit the form.
So go here and say instead of cancel log data to submit.
You're going to say this that probs that dispatch opening close and then update site data and we passed
the data to submit then we do something else which is going to be just a function and we do something.
So when I wanted to do I want to change the state to form success to true.
So that set stayed open and close and then we say form success equals to true.
So this one will just play at the bottom the you know success in a green day.
And after a couple seconds I went to you know remove that state.
So opening close we do a set time out because of this.
Nothing new so far.
We run a function.
All right.
And we do this that said state and we just change it back to false.
So him success do false.
And of course the set timeout meets the time of two seconds.
All right let's give it a try.
Let's see what happens.
All right of course update site data.
Oh we didn't added to types so types the name of the type.
It's update site data.
So.
Right.
And this is pretty much the last thing we're going to do with related to this.
And inside of this round of course.
So update site data right.
Let's see what we get.
OK.
At least we get no you know error message.
So Kramer four five six seven 20 whatever.
I can update success.
All right.
So if I reload the application we get you know the correct values.
And if I do one two three four five six seven eight maybe eight or maybe the area code.
I know.
Sixteen sixty eight.
I don't know what kind of area code is that so Update are going to reload it and everything gets updated.
You know it was updated.
So good.
So again we did all of this.
And the sole purpose of doing all of this is to fetch the information dynamically at least on the router.
So we're going to take five minutes I'm going to pause for a minute and we're going to do this can go
to the footer to the section.
You know does sexually the layout and going to fetch the site data.
So let's add the dynamic information right here and now if we thought we think for five seconds I could
close all of this.
I don't need it to close it.
So we can inject the information right here in a dynamic way.
Now you could do it you could go to the footer just for and create make this you know a different component
and bring Greta right here and do the connect.
The thing is what happens if we need this.
We need something from the data inside of the header.
So I believe it's a better idea to put it on the seat on the high or the components on we find it.
There you go inside lay out.
So right here we're going to bring redux and we're going to you know pass the props to the footer and
later of course if we need we can do it to Hetter right OK.
That dog.
OK.
So we're going to bring redux.
So import connect and it's going to be from that forward slash.
OK.
Sorry re-act redux react redux.
There we go.
So one thing let's do then we need to import to get side data.
We created a couple of minutes to go get site data and it's going to be from that that forward slash
actions for Slash site actions.
So now we can make the request of course.
Now we are using Kinect so we need to bring Kinect open and close.
We need to wrap up play out Rigaud and I'm going to do the math teacher props now so I don't forget.
So map state props.
We bring the buildings and we need the site.
So there's that state that site.
So now all the information is going to get injected inside Propst and we pass the maps stage props right
here real simple.
Now I'm going to go right here and on the component that Mount component did mount I'm going to do the
request I'm going to you know dispatched the action.
Now the thing is that I want to check if I don't have information because this component this layout.
This one right here the top the header and footer.
They're going to be rendered IMAO and they're going to be mounted every time we go to a route.
So if we just do the dispatch instead of here every time we get you know we mount this the header and
footer which is the HAMC we can do that dispatch a thousand times.
I don't want to do this.
So first I want to do I want to check if we already have information.
Now the thing is that the inside of this that props that side what we get it's pretty much in a.
So I guess I'm going to do this.
I'm going to do object when you do it right.
OK.
Object just like this dot checked keys opening close.
And this that props that side.
And I'm going to check the length and if it's equal to zero then we're going to go and fetch it.
And it's because we didn't have it.
So this that props that dispatch around this patch.
And of course we can get the site data right open and close and then close it.
For now we don't need to do anything else.
Reload reloaded.
All right.
I'm going to go to home and I get to go to the store and reloaded again.
So we're going to go to the store and we get the site and we get the data so good.
So now we need to pass to the footer all the props.
So I'm going to say data equals this that props that site.
All right now the footer and I'm going to go to the footer now.
It's going to be receiving this is props of course.
So we need to catch catch the props are going to say open and close and get the data prompts that we
are passing and I'm going to go here and say OK.
If inside data we have something that calls site data then of course we can render all the information
of the footer.
You know a good read there actually the footer.
All right.
Of course if nothing happens I'm going to go here and say that we want no we want to return no.
Pretty basic stuff so far.
So now up on the address instead of just saying Kramer we do data dot site data we access remember this
is an array and we access the address
and in theory we should be getting at least a dynamic address.
So yeah.
Kramer four five six seven eight whatever.
OK.
So same thing with the other ones going into the phone one.
So opening close.
And of course site are going to copy this one data and then phone the next one is going to be the business
hours.
So they copy paste.
They call this ours now.
Now and the next one it's the e-mail.
All right.
So e-mail.
So the application reloads and if we go to the footer all the data is right there.
Now if I go to my account and go to site info I get 20.
And right here 20 I going to modify it to update and the data comes comes back and gets updated.
Forget it because we are of course rendering everything through prompts and we are updating the state
of site data in site store.
All right very good.
So we are done with the whole project.
We are not going to do.
I'm not going to do anything else to this project.
The only thing left to do is to of course make some changes to send this to production.
And this time we're going to use Heroku because of course we get a testing your L and we get support
from Mongo and everything else.
So we're going to do that on the next few sections.
And of course much much much later after the current course it's published and everything else are going
to take maybe not much later after he finished uploading the course and it's public.
I'm going to start recording the bonus sections and it's going to be quite good luck.
We're going to do a few a few things on the bonus sections and of course you can watch it if you're
only interested in what we're going to be doing.
All right.
So let's go to the next one which is going to be preparing for production.