All right.
So this is what we're going to be doing the theme route.
So if I load this of course we have a transition effect around with all the players.
Nice effect.
And of course we have categories right here in midfield defense keepers.
So right from the start the first thing we need to do is create a route and then fetch the list of players
from the server.
Right.
OK.
So let's go back to our application and I'm going to go back here.
All right.
So I'm going to delete edit players I'm going to close it actually for uploader firebase we don't need
it.
So what we need to do we need to create a route.
So I'm going to go inside components and again to create a new directory called the team the team right
and the team we will use just one file because it's not a lot of code.
It's going to be a little bit weird a little bit weird but not a lot of code.
So this one of course will be a re-act class based component just like this.
I'm going to save it and of course this is going to be called the team.
Ryan the team or could be meet the team or something like that.
Again you can call this whatever you want.
Doesn't matter.
So right here the team Burguet.
So now we need to include this inside routes.
So this is a public route going to go here import the team from that forward slash component's forward
slash.
Then the team.
All right we're going to add this this public crowd.
Just like to sign in but I can copy the one from home.
Put it right here at the top let me close this and we will use boobie.
We will be using the team and then the team.
Oh sorry.
On this one.
And this is going to happen whenever we go to the route called the team.
Right.
OK.
So the team.
All right.
So if in theory we go to the team at least we get no errors.
So if I inspect this we get a div below is called the team.
Very good.
So now the first thing is going to be importing all the things we're going to need right.
So with the team we need a few things.
If you remember we've already did this play or cart we have it inside you I right here play your cart
so we will need to import that.
So import play your player and then card from than a dot dot for Slash you I forward slash and then
player cart right done.
Then we use We'll use a fading effect.
So import then fade from.
And this one is going to be re-act reveal forward slash and then of course fade brigade.
What is next.
Now if you notice we have this background and we've already used this inside home right here and this
section is a little bit different but pretty much the same the same as pride.
So I'm going to import import.
There we go.
And it's called Strypes just like this.
Strypes from Dot dot dot dot for Slash resources for Slash images for Slash.
And then I believe I called this tripes that PMG.
Very good.
All right.
Next again we need to make a request to firebase.
So we need to import some things from firebase first firebase and then the players and next since we
are going to be checking the storage for the images firebase from firebase.
Let me make it right.
All right.
Next one oh of course I need to set the from the dot for Slash forward slash and then firebase Burguet.
Next we need the firebase Luper.
So import open and close firebase and then Luper remember that the data comes in a weird way.
So we are going to change it with this and this one it's inside dot dot dot dot for Slash you eye and
then Miscellanies.
And last but not least I'm going to import promise just like this with a capital P promise Fromme then
core dodginess very good core jazz.
So OK let's get.
And you going to see why we are using this begin to of course check this in context because the problem
is it's kind of hard to explain.
So first the our component it will start with the state of loading and then falls.
I'm sorry.
True because whenever the application loads up we need to load the list of players first and then of
course when we have the players we can to store them inside the state.
Now first let's try to fetch the list of players.
So I'm going to do it on the component at Mount opening close and on the component that Mount we need
to of course enter firebase players.
OK I just lost the connection.
Maybe you see this.
And there we go.
I don't know what happened.
So.
So component in Mt..
I'm going to save fire base then players dot and once just like we did before.
So an axis in the value.
And then I'm going to say then of course we will get our promise with a snapshot.
All right.
Opening close.
So when whenever we get this we need to get the list of players in a way we want so Konst players.
This one it's going to be equal to firebase Luper opening close and we passed a snapshot right.
So now what I'm going to do I'm going to do console log.
And then players the application will reload of course and in a minute we get this.
So this is what we get.
Of course we get a list of players from the server and inside of this we have the image right.
And this is a problem for us right now.
We have 20 elements with an image that we cannot really use because we don't have to download your app
which we just have the name of the image and storing the your L inside the image directly.
Not a good idea.
OK.
So what do we need to do now.
We need to go to the storage and for each entry on each player and for each player we need to grab the
name of the image go to firebase storage and bring the download out.
That's what we need to do.
And this is why we are using promise now it is kind of a problem because whenever we get this you know
we get the players we can set the State of the new players store the oldest of players here.
But all of this requests you know the storage getting the image they're going to take awhile.
They're going to take like two seconds or maybe more or maybe less.
I don't know.
Depending on the server.
So if we set the stage before we have the images ready the application will break because we didn't
have an actual image.
You know we have this fake name.
So again we will use a promise.
What are we going to do.
It's something pretty standard.
Maybe you're not so kind of cool.
So I'm going to create a viral called Promises and it will be a lot of promises is going to start as
an empty array.
So what I'm going to do I'm going to loop through all the players so I'm going to say for open and close
and for each key so that key players begin to do something right.
OK.
And what I want to do I want to create a new promise and push it inside promises just like this.
So I'm going to say promise says Dad push push open it close.
Now inside of each push what we will push is a new promise and has to be with a capital P.
So what we going to be doing is for each player we're going to create in New Promise we're going to
make a request to the server bring the download your L for that player for each player and we're going
to push up promise we reject and we solve to the promises.
Right.
So at the end whenever this is done we can have an array with promises with 20 different promises.
And if you don't know how promises works after we get the download you are l.
We can call we can call to something right here.
We're going to be using it called we solved or reject.
So whenever we called we solved that promise inside the array will be resolved.
So be.
And when we get all the images from the server we begin to get an array with promises with 20 promises
with resolved promises and only and only after all promises are resolved then we can update the state.
That's why we are doing this but we are not there yet.
So whenever we called we create a new promise.
Of course we have a resolve a state in a reject.
So of course the reject is when something goes wrong.
We call reject and the promise fails.
All right.
So what do we need to do now is to make a request to firebase.
So firebase Dodd we access the storage DOD we and the players just like with it before.
And then of course we grab that child and inside of the child we need to pass the you know the actual
image.
So we can access players.
The key of you know each iteration and and we're going to bring that image name.
And then of course we can get download your L and after this has happened and this happens the promise
is going to get resolved.
This promise the firebase not this promise.
So when does it get resolved.
We're going to get a U R L back.
So what we do we grab the L and we place the you are the image property we have inside players you know
the one with the static name and we replace that with the u r l.
So we say players opening close we get the key we access Oh I'm sorry we're going to do something else.
We're going to add a new property called your L because we might need the image name.
So instead of changing the image we will add a new property.
So for that I was sick thinking about something else.
And then of course this promise since we do have that we get the information and everything goes OK.
We need to tell this promise this one we have right here that everything went ok and then we want to
resolve it.
So at the very end we're going to say we solved.
And we need to put this out.
And of course resaw So this command for example this will resolve this promise.
So inside of the promises this promise will get resolved.
And of course this is going to happen 20 times until we get all the images and we insert all that you
are all the new keys.
Right.
OK.
Now of course nothing happened so far because the only thing we are doing is just resolving promises
in the inside of the promises.
All right.
So we know what we need to do we need to update the state until all the 20 promises that we will get
out of here are resolved.
So what we do are going to go right here at the bottom and I'm going to use the key word promise.
This is a research keyword and I'm going to say until all promises are done we don't do NOT want to
move forward.
And of course we passed as an argument of promises.
And whenever all the promises gets resolved then we're going to do something.
So open it close and what we do with this we do this.
That said state opening close and we say that loading now it's false because low ducking no loading.
Sorry.
Loading.
Because now the promise it's resolved all promises are resolved.
We get all the time nails the thumbnails the images that you or else.
And of course we changed the loading and you know the players we have the list of the players so we
set it on strict.
So now we're going to do just to you know make sure we're going to go to the render console.
The blog does not state that players just don't check.
We get the correct URL or we are getting the URL at least and I know after a while the app the component
renders and we get the list of players.
And now we have a u r l with the you know the location for this and this is why we are not storing this
inside of the you know the the actual database document because it's a pretty long while.
All right.
So now we are ready to create the the right here the components the actual the HD mail which looks asexually
GSX to show all the different players of course we need to do a lot before we go there.
But now at least we have a list of players.
So first I'm going to go to the main div class name open and close and I get to say the team container.
This is a class I created for this one and I'm going to add some stylings.
Remember that we have that striae background.
So I'm going to say style opening close.
And going to change the background to Dodd you are an L opening close and I'm going to be passing the
stripes we have on the top stripe.
No stripes.
And of course we need the repeat and this goes after repeat.
All right very good.
So of course we get it.
You know I've added to that container a min height.
So that's why we get it.
Burguet we are on the good track now of course we want to show the contents right here only if loading.
It's false.
OK so close and we say we want to own the show whenever it's inside of here.
After the loading.
All right.
If not of course we could show something else maybe a progress or whatever.
In this case we're going to keep it simple and do.
No.
All right.
Now it's out of here.
I will return a div and he's out of here.
Something else.
Now if you notice whenever we get the data from the database we get a pretty large list right.
OK.
And we don't know.
We don't have maybe four different lists.
We have just one.
For all the players.
And if you check it right here we need to render a piece for the keepers a piece for two different deal.
The difference then midfielder's and then attack.
So we kind of had we have four different modules and but we have one list.
So we need something or we need a function or something that it's going to split and show Cester keepers
on this block and maybe show the defense on the other block.
All right.
And that's what we're going to do right now.
So first I'm going to create a div div opening close and distinct will contain a class name of team
underscore team underscore category.
Underscore wrapper.
I hope the name of the classmate makes sense to you.
They do make sense to me.
So class name I get at this.
And now I'm going to add the title now for each title for each block.
We have a title keeper's defense midfield and strikers.
So the first one will be keepers.
Right.
And inside of there we need to push to carts we need to put all the cards.
So I'm going to create a div with the class name of team cards right now instead of here.
We could have one card or we can have many cards.
So we need to grab we need to create a function that is going to be grabbing the cards.
There are lots of players and you know showing the cards.
So I'm going to call this that show players could be just like this.
Players and then by category because this is what this function is going to do it's going to show the
players only by category.
And as an only argument going to be passing which category in this case I'm going to show the keepers
and I'm using this keyword because on the database we have this Keyworth and it has to be the same key
word for keepers.
We are using keeper.
So if you make a mistake here will not recognize the category inside the list of players and nothing
is going to work.
So we don't have the function you can to create the function just like this.
Now what we need to return is GSX.
So instead of curly braces parenthesis and then on each iteration.
I'm sorry whenever we call this function it's category going to get a category Breguet.
So now we need to make sure that we do have a list of players.
So this state that players just like this opening close if we don't have it we're going to return.
No.
So now what we want to do we want to we want to map the list of players and return only the ones inside
that category.
So there's that state that players that map opening close on each iteration we will pass a player iteration
which is the index.
And then of course we will run a function.
And what we will do we will return something.
Notice that right here I'm not using parenthesis just a new basis.
That's why we need to return.
And I'm doing this because we need to perform a check right here.
We only want to return if the player that position it's equal to whatever category we have from the
arguments.
And of course if there's a match we will return something.
If not we're going to return NULL.
So what are you going to do right here.
I get a return of fate.
Remember we are using fade from Briac reveal and I want to fade it from the left.
Of course we need a key and the key is going to be.
I you know I'm using the iteration right here instead of here.
When you get to do are going to use div and are going to add a class name and a class name it's item
and he out of here we need to return the card.
You know the player card.
And at the top we are using the player card we are importing.
So I'm just going to use that we use this at home.
So it was kind of a while ago.
So this card of course needs some props.
It's the number of the player just like this needs the name of the player needs the last name of the
player.
And of course the background image of the player.
And we got we got all the information inside players so player that number than player doesn't name
the player.
Dodd last name and Dukes it sounds sounded like a song and played that and you are Al.
OK.
So OK.
So we pretty much have everything.
So if we go to our application we get a man.
All right.
So you know the transition it's a little bit weird.
Everything slides up.
Kevin the same you know I kind of don't like it.
And before I go to the final one you know the last one the recision is a little bit different.
Notice this we have you on the keepers.
We cannot tell the difference but on the on the rest notice that the transition is a little bit different.
So when I did I added a delay delay opening close and it added a delay of 20.
Now why 20.
And it's because I did and I grabbed the iteration number and it did a multiplication so on each fade
the delay is going to be a little bit different going to be a different number.
That's why we get a difference on the transitions.
So of course if I save this and we go back oops let's go back.
We get you know a the decision is a little bit different.
Of course we can exaggerate as much much more everything is going to be the same results going to take
more time.
We know that it is a little bit different.
So like 20 so I'm going to leave it at 20.
So we are pretty much done.
The only thing we need to do right now to finish this component is to create the defense the midfield
and then of course the attack.
So this case is going to be defense and the name but the contemporary defense the fans I'll write the
next one.
It's the mid field.
So we're going to go right here meet field and right here mid field and the next one our district is
so dry Kerr's
strikers and this is Singler striker.
All right.
Now make sure that the different categories are the same.
Same you have inside here.
So of course if you go get difference we get midfield right.
Everything works and we get strikers and notice that I'm getting the up the images of the players because
I of course took the liberty of going to the our database the ones for this project not the one I had
ready and enter all the names and you know all the all the actual images I have replaced all the images
with real images and they are stored inside our storage is so very good.
The team is ready.
We're going to give you a zip code of this and now we're going to do the matches.
The mattress is going to be a little bit different.
It's going to take us a little bit more time because even though we fetch lots of teams and we showed
this we have this at the top so we need to create some functions to do some filtering.
All right.
So let's go to the next section and do the matches.