OK so let's create the matchups and point.
So at the end we're going to get this.
So on this we have three different parts.
We have the part of the top which are the filters we're going to do to fit two to two filters and they
will be really simple because on the next project we will be creating a Web site and we have a big filter's
section.
So we're going to go hardcore on that one.
And then in the left you have a league table which is actually fake and in the real left of course right
here on the bottom this is what we're going to be doing you know getting getting the matches and doing
all the logic of this and the league table I'm going to tell you what to do in a minute.
So first of course to create this we have a route we need to create a route and a component to work
with this.
So I'm going to go to components and inside of components what we can do is create a new directory called
the matches.
The other one was the team so this one is the matchups.
So instead of the matches we have three parts first the index that G-S them we're going to get a different
part which is the Imagist list.
So matches and then list that James and then we have the table and I'm going to tell you what to do
on the table later.
Now on this one the index will be getting a re-act classic ways component just like this.
And of course this one will be called the matches.
The matches.
Now I'm going to paste this.
I'm going to say the matches.
So let's inport this is to create a round for this element for the matches.
So I'm going to go two routes and this would be a public route so import the mattress.
Let me do it right from.
And of course for Slash components for Slash the matches.
All right.
Since we have an index we don't need to put in x.
Now of course this will be a public route.
So just like the team I'm going to copy this route.
Copy and paste it right here the top when it closes and I'm going to bring the matches from the mattress
and right here the route.
It's a little bit different.
I believe we're going to be using the team I'm sorry the matches you know the same thing.
The matches right now in theory the application reloads.
If I bring the console we should be getting at least a div saying matches right.
Just like with it before.
So we get the matches get.
OK.
So let's go to the mattress.
I'm going to close the team and I'm going to use it and pass it to Jason goodbye and look up the side
of the index.
We need to start requiring to importing a few things.
We're going to use a progress.
So import circular circular and then progress and we need to import it from act mature and UI core and
then Tsukuba our progress whatever.
Now we will need to do some medical requests to the database to firebase.
So import opening close and five days just like this and then matches we're going to use them and then
from that force slash that that force slash then one more and firebase get one last thing to do import
we need to firebase Luper.
You always need to firebase Looper.
So labor and are going to bring the reverse array reverse reverse array every time I say rebirths I
just remember the BDO from the guy from a guy saying rebirths Antti you know the woman that was driving
and trying to park the car.
Very funny to look on that on YouTube.
Rebirths aunty just like this just just looked at reverse reverse of course Antti and you can see a
very funny video.
So now of course we have the matches list.
I'm not getting imported right now.
We're going to do it in a couple minutes.
So of course this one will need to use the state because we need to do all the network requests and
we will need to store them inside of here.
First I'm going to do a loading could be loading or loading.
Doesn't matter it's completely up to you after we get the mattress are going to store them inside of
an array.
All right.
Now later we're going to be filtering the matches.
So this is actually you can choose how to do it.
You can manage the whole match just inside the magic list.
But I'm going to do it on the pound component so whenever I load the matches from firebase I going to
store the unmodified list inside matches.
And then when we start filtering we will use the filter matches to store the filtered matches because
we may be.
And we might get just two matches and by storing them here we are not modifying the one on the top.
That's why we do it.
And again you could do it whatever you want right here.
Player filter and this one right now makes no sense.
I'm just going to add it and then we're going to go back to this and then resold.
And this one actually something for the.
So resoled filter.
And again I'm going to say all we're going to go back to this.
Don't worry.
OK.
So now before I do anything I would like to fetch.
Fetch the list of matches from the server.
So firebase Oh sorry component that Mount opening close and firebase matches.
We do the ones we do the value and then of course we get our our promise.
So we're going to get a snapshot.
And after we do that which is run and then Konst and they're going to store the matches and remember
that we need to use the foreign based Luper with whatever snapshot we get back from the server.
All right.
So close.
OK.
So now since we have the matches I want to store the matches inside filter matches so I'm going to say
this that state this that sets stayed open and close and bloating.
Since we have all the information now it's going to be false then the matches are going to store with
the reversal rate and going to reverse everything.
So I go and grab matches and pass the reverse array and the same thing with the filtered matches right
here.
They're going to store the pretty much the same thing.
Then of course it changes whenever we select a filter or we start filtering that list it's going to
change a little bit.
OK.
So we promote much have anything I'm going to do comes along and just make sure that we have this state
and you know the matches make sure we get everything and we don't get any surprises later.
So if filter matches and matches Breguet same result.
All right.
So now of course we need to show something maybe a loader if it's loading and remove it.
Of course when it's done loading.
So first we need to create and close you know to create the basic layout for this.
So class name is going to be the underscore match's underscore container.
We're going to do one more thing first we're going to say Konst state equals to this state.
We're going to be referring to this that state many many times inside of here and in a few and a few
minutes.
So by doing this I'm just storing this in a state in state of state.
So now instead of referring to this that state I just can say state right makes sense.
We do this all the whole time.
So Dave open it close and I'm going to wrap everything inside of a wrapper so the mattress matches underscore
wrapper.
All right.
Very good.
Now if we take a look at the original you know the final one we have a left side and right side.
So I'm going to rob we're going to create a div with the left.
So class name and this one is going to be left and the other one would be left as left of course.
Now Sorry it's going to be right.
So I am just joking.
OK.
So we have a left and we have a right side.
So in the left and I'm starting the ride we're going to get the league table.
Now I don't want to show you how to create the table because it's just fake information.
If we go to the database and I go to positions we just you know have all the teams with the how many
draws how many wands.
And you know the points and everything else.
Now why are we are we not doing this.
And it is because I've worked in a company called Starts with an F O and ends with an X and then sports.
And I've worked with E S and then and when the P and Anantapur.
So I work for both companies so I know a little bit about you know web pages or you know apps or whatever
that they got to do with sports.
Now what companies do they they don't enter the information manually.
They don't have people doing this.
What they do they hire a service and this service of course they have people or maybe people are maybe
not trained monkeys or something like that.
Entering information about the magic maybe Manchester City is playing the game right now.
So there's a guy entering the information live.
And of course they use these companies they hire this service and they consume an API.
So what we're doing right here with the games actually in real life doesn't happen.
I just really we are doing it because of course we are practicing.
But in real life they hire a service and they consume their API.
And the same thing with the league table.
If we had to create a part of the application just to create a table and all the logic of positioning
the teams with the goals in favor and goals against and local the wins and way wins it would be very
very very long and not very useful because you can only apply it to a league table or something.
And the rules might change with each sport in soccer or football.
They are one way maybe on the NBA they are different.
So again no no makes no sense to just create a section to do a league table.
So what Im going to do as a resource.
I've added the file I have inside of here.
Right.
The final file calls table that J.S. just download the resource just download the file and put it inside
of the matches.
Right.
And of course make sure that all the imports and everything is correct.
If you did it this way maybe you changed some names and something's not going to work.
So check the console and and make sure what it's wrong.
So I'm going to do that are going to puzzle BDO you bring the file right here and then I'm going to
connect to it and show it.
OK I've imported the file and it's you know really simple as just a table.
It's consuming it's bringing from the database to positions and then of course we just loop the table
rows inside of a table.
So so simple and we kind of already did this.
So I'm going to go to index going to go at the top.
And of course we need to import league table.
So import league table.
Right.
And it's going to be from dot dot for Slash and then table.
So link table are going to go right here at the bottom and the only thing we need to do is just import
it.
Now of course I didn't try this time right now.
So ok we get the league table.
That is good.
So you should be getting the same thing.
All right.
So let's go back to our project.
So in the left in the left side is where are we going to be working on the left what we got.
First are some match filters which are the ones at the top.
And we're going to do that last.
You're going to do that last but I'm going to create the container for this right now.
So we add a class name and the class name is match just like this match.
And then filter's right now inside of the filters we pretty much have two boxes.
So we will create the boxes later.
So I'm going to say boxes sorry of course it's not javascript.
OK.
So it's after the filter is what we need to do we need to bring the matches.
So this file.
All right.
So of course we don't have anything right here.
Let me create at least a class inside the matches list because we will need a class.
So re-act classmates component just like this and this one will be called match's list right here.
And of course a list.
OK.
So he's out of here.
We need to import it.
So import then matches list matches and then list from that for Slash and matches list and a copy.
And I'm going to go right here at the bottom.
So this match list pretty much needs and actually needs the information about the matches the information
we are fetching right here from the server.
So when we make our way when we import we actually make a reference to this component to say matches
list and begin to pass the prop and the probably matches something like that can open in clubs.
Can I say this.
Actually there's no need we can say state DOT and then filter matches.
Now one of my passing I'm passing the information about filter matches this one not the original.
Right.
OK.
So inside the matches list we will do all the logic right here.
So let me just those.
Don't check on our project that we are getting list and we do OK.
We are getting a list.
So now what we are going to be doing we are going to be looping this list and we can be using node group
now no group comes from re-act move from IMR we installed re-act move going to bring We asked move.
And with this this property what you can do you can you can actually do something else and the animate
that weve been doing this not group me trying to find the live examples and code.
All right.
Going to give you a little bit tiny overview to this.
And then of course you get into it.
So okay so more examples documentation no break here.
If I go to note group what we do is something like this.
Notice that of course this is a list just a list.
And when we animate it is going to change the position and the positions on that list.
So maybe a is going to go to a different place and you know its pretty much changing the order on the
list.
Now for this and this is actually what were beginning to be needing later when whenever we filter the
information right here this list is going to change instead of maybe having 10 we can have a 5.
So react move by using this node group.
What it does is going to is going to store the old list.
Its going to be getting a new list and its kind of merge both.
And when it's doing that is going to generate an animation on that and that particular list.
So this is what we're going to be using right.
We're going to be doing whenever we alter the list node group we'll check which ones has to go have
to go and which ones are going in.
As we ran out at all.
And then if I check it we can just maybe four or maybe two.
Now the list of course now has two elements.
We don't have all the 20 matches we just have two but no group removes the ones that are not in that
list and entering the one that we have a Belva right now.
So that's why we need to use note group by doing this just just with animations with the animation we've
been using with re-act move.
Could be a little bit a little bit challenging.
All right.
So on the mattress list we're going to leave the live this at least ready to go.
I'm going to say state opening close and I'm going to store the mattress list inside of here.
Now the thing is that if I do do a console console log with this that prompts the first time that this
loads
we don't have anything.
So if we trigger something with an empty array or empty an empty list and something with an empty animation
it could fail.
So what we can do we can use that get the right state from props to do something simple.
You know you shouldn't use get the right state from prompts to do a lot of things you can use it the
whole time.
It's just for tiny things.
So when you begin to be doing is we can be catching the promp the props the coma the state and we will
we will be returning return.
We always need to return something the state with the actual Just list with whatever we have inside
the probs.
If we of course we get it we get some information Propp that matches.
And this of course will grab whatever we get from matches and it will tacet inside matches list.
So later what we can do we can check if we do have matches list.
And of course run whatever we want to run.
All right.
Now let's go to the next one because what we're going to be doing.
It's a lot of you know with a node group with the animation so we do all we need to do quite some coding.
So let's go to the next one and start this one.