All right so let's enter the It's create the animation.
So first on the container is just a div but I'm going to make reference to a function so open it close
this that show matches something like this matches open and close.
Of course we don't have this function going to create it right now.
So we're going to go right here and we're going to say that the show matches show matches it's equal
to a function.
And of course when we return something we return some GSX.
Now first I'm going to make sure that this state that matches list.
It's actually able to use.
If not I'm going to return no.
Now the usual stuff if we have something we do something if not we don't do anything.
Now what we will be returning is this note group from re-act move.
We need to import it.
So first I'm going to import the transmission remember the ease.
So ease ease then Polie and then out.
This is what we use so far from D-3 than ease.
All right.
So import and now we import node and then group just like this note group for our arm and it's re-act
move forward slash and then the same name build up.
All right.
So now we can use this note.
So what do we do.
We return this you know this component this node group open and close.
Of course we wanted to do a lot of things inside of here.
Just like with it with the animation of re-act move.
So the first property we need to add right here.
And of course we get all offers but can it clear them in second no grouped.
What it needs it needs.
The group that you're going to be animating in this case we need to animate the list and this list at
least we have at least I don't know 10 matches.
All right.
So the way you can pass the list on the data property.
So we say this that state that matches list.
So this is the list going to be using.
Now this one it needs a key accessor.
Now for example if on data.
Let me just do the console log console log and let's see if we get we can get it before getting to matches
list.
Maybe not.
We just double check and no we are not getting it's failing before that.
So I'm going to try to come and that's going to remove it and I'm going at it.
I want to show you what we get on the list.
So on the list we have this list.
And then of course we kind of have an idea and this idea is actually come from comes from firebase.
So now whenever we loop something this note group actually is going to be looping this data right this
list and it's nice to know what is the key of that of this of each entry.
In this case the the entry in each key of each entry sorry is the ID.
We know that this is the I.D. We could use whatever we want doesn't matter.
But the key one it's this one is the I.D. We are not going to really use it on this.
On this example but maybe you need to refer to an idea of something and I it.
We're going to talk about this in a minute.
So we need to pass a key if not this no group is going to fail.
So let me go back to the Prius code.
All right.
So the property that takes the key its key just like this key accessor All right now Diski accessor
of course we do brackets what we do.
We pass a function.
This function takes the D which is pretty much kind of a state and then D and the ID.
So this list could be it's kind of the list.
This data this does for data.
So we are passing the data and we are saying that the data and we're going to be using the data ID whenever
we have inside of here in each iteration.
The key ID if we were using I don't know the ID of course.
You know our property called cars we all say cars doesn't matter in this case is the idea.
We are not going to really use it but we need to tell no group what we could use as an ID.
Now if you remember when we do any missions we have a starting point an entering point an update and
leave.
We didn't do the leave because we didn't need to.
Now we're going to do it.
So we have a start.
Equals.
And what we need to do in this case we didn't pass an object.
We need to pass a function so we do open it close and we return kind of a some some GSX and inside of
here we return an object.
So this is the you know what we need to use right here.
So inside of the object we need to specify what is the starting point of each element inside the node
group.
So we're going to use Chesed opacity just like this and it's going to start at zero and the X is going
to be minus 200.
We are not going to do something very very complex.
OK.
So the starting point is going to be opacity 0 0 and they're going to be hitting you know after outside
the the the viewport.
All right.
So then we we have an Enter property whenever the element enters what are we going to do.
So what do we do.
Again we just need to pass a function to open it close and then we return with the object.
Same thing with it right here.
Now on this one is what we can do.
We can say the D and remember that the key word d is the data right here.
And then the iteration and this is something we're going to use the iteration.
Remember that this group actually creates a loop right.
So on each iteration we can grab the index.
So it's just a loop inside of here.
We can define the opacity.
Same thing we did right here.
And this works like we did previously.
We need to pass the array with what is the final Balou.
In this case it's going to be one.
And what is the ending point is going to be zero ride show right on the screen.
Now we need to add a timing just like we did before.
Now the timing timing is again just like the other examples with that timing.
There you go.
And we need to pass an object on the object.
We can set the duration the delay if we wanted a delay.
And the ease so for duration I'm going to say 500 koma are going to say delay and on the delay we're
going to do the same thing with it which we can move the iteration and I'm going to multiply it.
And if we do that we're going to get that escalating animation because they have different values and
that's why we get this.
All right.
So on delay going to grab the iteration and they're going to multiply by 50.
Then we have an ease and ease is going to be the one we are using at the top.
All right.
And let's go back to our project and now we're getting there's the problem children and it's because
we don't have anything inside.
All right.
So let me talk a little bit more about this.
If you go to react move documentation this D and if you take the first the first example this one going
to see what is that.
So let me give you an example right now.
Let's say that you have a list of matches you have maybe I don't know objects not objects maybe elements
something like that and you have an array of objects.
And what you want to do maybe you want to animate this objects right here and you want to pass the properties
of what you're going to be any meeting.
Let's say that this one has an A pass city of 5 and then and opacity of I don't know actually you know
it's going to start at 0 and 1.
Let's say that all these properties they come from this you know this object is array of follies.
So since you're looping something you're looking this list inside node groups just like here with the
data you do have access to data on each iteration.
So if you need to pass the opacity instead of hard coding it's doing it like this hard coding the value
where you can do.
You can specify the dot and then of course it's going to be and opacity and this value is going to be
equal to each element on each iteration.
So that way you can pass dynamic values.
For example right here we get letter and frequency.
And for example if we go when we find the actual code we find it slide right here.
There we go.
So we have the enter D and notice that X is used in scale and then accessing the D and the property
letter and the letter we have it right here.
All right.
So OK.
So you can use the D as a reference to each element on that list that you're using.
All right.
Right now we are not really using this we are just putting fixed values.
Ok so we have a start.
We have an enter and we have an update.
What happens when everything updates so update and it's going to be equal to the same exact thing.
So I'm going to copy this and just do passing everything up and then update for now when we don't worry
about much about the update.
So this is going to do the same thing when it updates.
But again we are not running an animation.
What we get but we're going to be doing is running an animation when we leave when the element leaves
the screen.
Then we want to animate it back.
And what we're going to do we get to go back to defaults opacity is zero and minus 200 Ryan.
OK.
So going to copy this.
So I don't need to type everything again.
And for the timing since you're repeating code you can host this on a variable later.
Can it do this.
And you know feed it from there.
Now there there's no need to do this.
We are practicing in real life would be you know a good idea not to repeat this code.
OK.
So on leave pretty much we do the same thing but we go back to defaults minus 200.
All right.
So all of this is just right.
Ready to ready to use.
Now the thing is that the problem and why the application is going to fail is that we don't have anything
inside.
No drop.
And it works in a weird way.
Now whenever we let me show you the example they give us inside node group what we need to return first
is a function with the notes and inside of the function.
We need to return a map which each element.
Yeah a little bit we're going to do it right here and it will make sense.
So first we need to return inside of this child.
This note function.
So we do notes we need to pass notes and then open it close and we return some GSX.
Now whenever we return this function well when it returns something it always needs to return a single
element.
So if we pood we create a map right here.
And for each element we have on the list we return to Dev.
This is going to be something like this.
And and this will not work because this is GSX.
So we need to return only one div..
In this case you're going to use a diff.
And if you check the example they are returning a tag.
Gee I don't know what it is.
G doesn't matter.
It's just attack.
We return one element now instead of here what we will be returning is the map of whatever notes we
have.
So this notes is a list that contains all the temptations of all the lists all the elements in our list.
So we're going to go out of here open and I get to enter.
No it's going to dot.
I'm going to do map open and close.
Now instead of map of course we need to do something and then run something and what we do we turn is
some GSX.
Now of course instead of the GSX we will we will be returning a deaf with a lot of things.
Now on each iteration we need to tell this element what it needs to do.
Whereas going to go where when we have the Pasotti and where it's going to go when we have the x.
So we we pass this right here open and close what we do have by default from notes is the key.
Remember that when we map something we need to specify the key.
So we open curly braces and we say key then we get the data.
This is something that we might not really use but we can use it there by default and then we have the
state.
So inside of the state and it's not the application state.
Now this one is the state of this node group and inside of the state we have the information of what
we are doing with it you know with the actual transition just like we did with four with animate you
know with the same re-act move.
So what we going to be bringing it's X and capacity.
This is what we're using.
If you have transform or something like that you need to bring it here.
If not of course not going to really work.
So we are growing notes.
We are mapping and we are bringing to the three things we can to use.
And inside we return some GSX so diff needs a key because we are mapping something we need to pass the
key.
And then of course this has a class name.
This is my class name our class name match box and then back.
And of course we need to tell the application how that transition is going to go.
So what we do we pass the style and so right now we can do pretty much the same thing with it with all
other animations on our you know at home and everything else.
I noticed that at least right now the application is not breaking.
So what we do inside of style we just pass whatever is going to happen with the passerby.
So we grab the value we have from there.
And then the transform transform.
And what we do.
I'm going to use translate translate opening close just like this and are going to be passing the template
string with a value X and then of course pixels.
All right.
That is it.
So of course instead of here we don't have anything to have nothing at all.
So I'm going to type something.
Doesn't matter.
And at least we get it.
You know it's a transition and it works.
And that is it.
All right.
So now the problem is that we are looping our list within the note group and all the information we
need to put right here.
It's inside our this that state that matches list.
So how can we access the values from our list inside of this.
You know this note map we don't have the information inside notes.
Well in theory we do whenever we make here we bring data.
Data is a quick reference inside of notes to our data right here.
So what we can do we can say data that local or data that rissoles and we will be accessing the values
of each element on each iteration record.
You know it works really really really great.
This one and one of this is a little bit hard to understand at first but once you get it it's piece
of cake.
So on the right here if we check the final one we pretty much have two different things.
You have the left side and the right side and we have the team and teams that have left block a block
at the top and a block at the bottom.
Let me check maybe this.
We were 16 minutes too long.
So we're going to go to the next one.
And at all the you know the actual layout right here.
So let's go to the next one and do that going to be pretty simple.