All right let's do the lay out right here.
It's going to be really simple.
So instead of here are going to create a div with a class name just like this and I'm going to add the
class name of Bach's wrapper like that.
BLOCK wrappers sorry.
BLOCK wrapper.
All right.
So instead of here we get two different blocks.
And this block wrapper would be the one that is going to be rubbing the two teams on both teams very
good.
So inside block opening close and the first block are going to call going to call it block.
So this one will host the first team.
They're going to close this so we can clearly see this.
So the first thing it's the icon the icon of the team.
So class name icon.
And this one will of course we need to add the style to this.
So it's going to be style equals opening close.
Now of course we need to add chess to background.
Just a background.
So it's going to be background just like this.
And who me bring it at the bottom.
Not to look a little bit weird.
So background we use template strengths we use.
You are opening close and if you remember the logos the team logos are inside the public directory inside
images and team icons.
So we need to make a reference to that.
So it's for Slash images.
Just like this images for Slash theme icons for Slash then opening close.
And now we use that data key we have right here.
So it's data DOD and the one on the top is the local So local.
Capital T H M B.
That is the name of that.
And then of course we attach that P.A. and that is it.
You could put no repeat that it's OK for you.
So OK the next thing it's going to be the name of the team.
So leave class name open and close with a class of team and inside of here we make reference to data
that local.
And that's it.
The next thing they're going to copy office is going to be salt.
So result data that result.
And then again local ME FIX IT resold and then local are added.
Ok sorry.
Result local.
OK.
Sorry for that.
So OK so if the application reloads Let's see what happens if you don't get anything.
Well let's get we get what we are not getting is the actual icon.
So let me see thing icons made a mistake right there.
So this is kind of late already and I've been being actually recording this the whole day.
So I'm a little bit tired but we're almost done and I want to quit right now.
OK.
So we have the first block.
We need the second block.
So I'm going to copy this one going to go at the bottom just paste it.
And now we need to make reference to a way data local data way and data results local data results away.
All right let's see how it goes.
All right.
There's it very simple.
OK.
So now we are going to add the info.
Real simple stuff.
OK.
So we have the block wrapper which is the first one.
And then again to add a new block wrapper just here below.
And then Dave but this one has an additional class of fault for info.
Right.
All right.
So this one def and inside will have a strong and the strong is going to be you know the actual key
just date.
And then of course we put the date.
So data data that date.
All right.
The next one is the stadium's up get a copy of this one.
And then of course stadium and stadium and the next one is the referee.
So rare for a read.
And of course again referee.
All right.
We'll see if this works the application reloads.
And OK.
It is getting weird.
Of course something is broken.
So we have the blog robber what you see with him.
But my mistake is block block wrapper.
Let me see one second.
Find a mistake I'm pretty sure it's really silly.
Oh of gays.
So I know I know I know what the promise this rapper Eminem was take on the class I did.
I went with one P..
Same thing right here.
This is a mistake on the CSX.
So we were loaded.
There we go.
OK.
That is get if you want you can go to the CSSA and change the name for this you know fix it that you
know there's no need to do that.
All right.
So what are we going to be doing right now.
It's this filtering thing.
This boxes and they are really really simple pretty straightforward.
I just add them to the project to show you how no group can work with they you know some changes on
the actual actual object you know the Jayson object.
All right so let's add the filter boxes something we can add the template first real simple and then
we will add the functions to filter.
Now we are not.
Again we are not going to do something very complex.
Notice that if I make a change in this filter it and I change this one this one resets.
So we are doing one filter all the time.
You're not mixing both.
All right.
Real simple.
OK.
So inside match filters we can have two boxes you know two different filters.
So I'm going to go right here I'm going to say Dave and I are going to wrap that box inside of a you
know a class.
So inside match filters this one each box is going to be called is going to have a class name.
Class name of match underscore filter's underscore and then box.
Now each box has a title.
So Dave open it close.
Class name and I call that night called the.
So the first one is going to be for the show match so the show match will toggle between the played
match and the not played matches right.
OK.
So after the attack I can at you know the actual buttons.
So this container calls can't just you know not right container.
So each option.
We need a device which is pretty much debone.
The first one in this case the on the show match is going to be all.
And again to do the other things I'm going to add a class name.
So the class name for this one and it's going to be option.
Now later we need to change the classes of which one is selected and which ones.
Which one is not going to do that at the end.
But since we're going to be swapping classes I'm going to use template strings and in this one I'm going
to put this option later.
We're going to going to change it right.
Don't worry.
Now later of course we need to add an unclick.
But for now I'm going to finish this so all and we have three options the first one is all.
The second one it's played.
And the third one.
It's not played.
At all right.
We should at least get something
until we get it.
Of course they're not clickable.
You can add that functionality right now.
OK.
So what we need to do whenever we click and all and it showed all the results if I click and played
again across this database that we have the state actually the filter matches.
I'm going to call and only show the ones that say play and the keyboard.
Yes.
And this actually comes from the database.
If I go to the database we have the right here the property here.
Here we go.
So we have a final so final it's going to be yes or no.
So if I check the other ones.
No.
Of course the final.
Yes it's going to be the one that was already played and the No.
The one that is not played.
All right.
So we can use the keyboard yes or no.
Real simple not a boolean.
It did with yes no.
So it could be a little bit easier to understand.
All right.
OK.
So now whenever we click I need to tell the application to filter that and for this of course you're
going to create a function.
So I'm going to go right here and whenever I do an unclick just like this I want to run a function open
and close and I going to run a function called this that show and then play it makes sense.
And is this option.
It's all I going to say.
All I need to do the same thing pretty much for all the other options.
So this one instead of all is going to be yes.
And the next one is going to be on click Show play.
Yes actually no.
Burguet of course we didn't have this function created right here so show played is just a function
and it will be receiving that played as an argument so we can use just filter from javascript.
And a creator Konst concert.
There we go.
And I'm going to call it list and it's going to be equal to the filtered the final filtered you know
army of objects.
So this state that matches I'm entering the list where we have all the matches all of the matches.
Now the filter matches and are going to say OK what I want to do I want to filter open and close and
on each iteration I'm going to use matches could be match actually match just like this.
And of course we will return something.
So what we return is going to be all the match which final it's equal to whatever argument we are passing.
So this will be returning all the.
For example if we select all is going to is going to return pretty much all in a check in a minute.
To fix it.
But if they played it's equal to.
Yes.
It will filter and bring all the elements right here where we have yes.
And it will skip all the notes.
Right.
OK.
Makes sense.
It's very simple just a filter function.
It's.
This is not react.
So then what are we going to do.
And this part it's important.
We're going to set the state.
And now I'm going to use filter matches if you remember the filter matches is the property that the
No.
Group these matches list is going to be using.
So whenever I do filter matches I need to check if they're resolved it is keyword displayed.
It's going to be all because if it's old I just return the whole damn thing.
The whole matches no all the list of matches if not are going to be returning whenever we get back from
the list.
So in this case I'm going to say okay I'm going to go back and I'm going to say if I played.
It's equal to triple equal to all.
What we want to do we just want to return to this that state that matches matches.
All right.
If not we're going to be returning whatever whatever we have inside the list and we need to do a few
more things.
Now if you remember at the top you were using the player filter and the resoled filter.
And this is the default state.
Right now we just have the show match which is going to be all but later we're going to have the result
game which is.
Oh.
All right.
So this is the default state of this despondence since we can filter only one thing.
What are you going to do if we click on this one.
We're going to reset this one back to zero and then backwards.
If we select something this one goes back to zero.
So what do we do.
Right here we just change the state of that are going to say Play play or filter is going to be equal
to whatever we get from played which could be all yes or no and then coma and the result FELTER is going
to be equal to all.
So we result we said the other one back to the beginning.
All right.
So I got to reload the application and let's see if it works.
So if I go to all that get we get all if I go to played and nothing.
And if I go not play nothing I'm pretty sure there is something wrong.
This looks OK and this is a problem.
It's no instead of no way.
All right I'm going to reload the application and let's see if it works.
So if I go play let's get most of them up or play.
If I go not played we get only one match.
So let me change this from the database because I'm pretty sure I made a mistake on this one.
One second.
Let's do the following.
We have a dashboard we can edit matches from our application.
So what is scenario scenario to you know change them.
They're all final.
That's why we are not getting this.
So I'm going to go maybe Tottenham and I'm going to change it to no.
And of course since he's not played the return the result is 0 0 0.
Whatever doesn't matter and result none available so EDID match.
And if we go to matches we get not played and now we get to see how that works played.
And there we go.
You know it works.
All right.
So now of course we need to add the other one the result game and then to toggle the classis inside
of here.
Well let's go to the next section and finish.
We're going to finish the matches after that we will add a not found page but that's going to be really
simple.
And then of course we will grab everything with DID and we're going to push it to production.
We're going to push it to find base hosting.
We have the ability to host our project right here so we can do that.