All right so let's finish this.
I'm going to add the classes and then add the other one which is pretty much the same code.
So we're going to do a little bit of copy pasting.
I want to fix something right here.
It's not play or filter is going to be played.
Filter sorry for that.
So we just made a reference right there too.
OK.
So that is good.
So OK.
I'm going to go right here and use a turn.
So opening close.
Going to say state DOT played filter then if this one is triple equal to all Barens simple I'm going
to show something.
If not I'm going to show nothing.
So what I want to show is the active or I want to show nothing.
All right.
And the same thing for the other one's going to copy.
This one's going to paste it and paste it.
And this one instead of all is going to be yes and this one will be.
No no.
There we go.
So if I reload the application OK we get all because the default scenario is 0.
And if I go to played we get played and not played.
We get not play very good.
Now that works.
Now we need to prove we are pretty much do the same thing for the results filter.
So I'm going to copy this instance of match filter's box and I'm going a pace that right here.
And of course we need to change that tack with resolved and then game OK.
So of course we need to make a new function called result called assault and result.
Now of course right here it's a little bit different.
We have all four to the fold case.
Then instead of yes we have double checked the database.
These are the wins.
So I'm going to say Davola you then we have to lose the losses so we can say well and they're going
to create a new one copy paste.
And this one is going to be the draw right.
Of course we are not going to make a reference to a plate filter.
We will make a reference to resolved filter result.
Filter get a copy and replace the other ones.
And if I if I check it at least we should be getting something here now going to work.
But we're going to get it.
OK.
That is good.
So I'm going to go back and now we're going to be passing to show we're sold.
Win lose draw or.
All right.
We didn't have this function.
I going to go right here at the top and this function calls show we solved it calls played open and
close again.
We will be receiving some arguments in this case is just a result and what we need to do is the same
thing than this.
So we could just create one function and you know do everything in one function.
But again we are almost almost there.
So we get a state matches going a filter and we're going to check the result so instead of final is
going to be really soft.
Right and whatever we're going to be checking all begin filtering all the the rissoles that matches
the argument right.
All right so the filter matches instead of played.
It's going to be result.
And again we get if we get all we just returned the normal array of matches the one that has all the
matches.
If not we returned the list and same thing with right here with the result filter.
So we're sulfurous or we do the opposite.
We return result.
If not we can reset all the one to all.
So we are doing the same thing here but backwards.
All right.
Real simple.
So if I go to when we get all the wins.
All right.
I go to lose.
We get all the lose and the draw Burguet.
And if I go to played.
All right let's get this one not working properly.
Maybe I made a mistake.
Just let me double check why I'm going to go right here.
And it's because we didn't change this.
This one of course uses different arguments.
So this one is going to be when this one is going to be loose and this draw now should be Morgan.
All right.
Win lose draw and all.
And if I go here and suck something it will reset everything Burguet.
So this is the final.
It works.
So now the next section will do something very very very simple.
I'm going to sip the code for this one so find it as a download as a resource and begin to do the not
found.
And then we will send everything to the hosting.