OK so let's add a not found screen because if I go to whatever you know it's kind of a to go but it's
not really going.
And the thing is that let me show you why whenever we go two routes it's Riak Browder it's entering
here it's reading OK it's going going and since it's not finding anything it's not it's not returning
anything.
So we will create a scenario for you know for no match for not not found.
So I'm going to host it inside you I because it's not a very super important route so I've not found
you could create inside components and not found file or not found directories.
It's completely up to you now not found.
This case is going to be really simple.
So going to react statelets component.
So this one not found not found.
And I'm going to add a class and not found container not found container.
All right.
So inside of the not found.
But I'm going to do something so simple.
Sorry maybe sorry.
And a sad face or I'm sorry sad face sad face.
There we go.
And at the bottom I'm going to create a new dev saying Page Not Found.
All right super simple.
Now of course we need to bring this to routes so I'm going to go to public route because it is a public
route import not found from that forward slash and this time we need to go to you.
So it's not inside it's inside components and you go.
So the component calls not found.
That is it.
So no.
And here's the thing.
This is like a totally a little before.
This is how we react router works starts reading routes from the top.
So if we put it at the top is going to match whatever we passing on the not found because they've not
found has no routes is going to display the route.
If it's not finding anything but if we put it first it would always display that that found because
they matched the route it's going to match it.
So we always always always we need to put it at the end.
Ride is the final route that will match.
So I'm going to copy the home I'm going to put it right here.
We still pass the props if you want to restrict it the path and the path.
We don't need a path.
So this is what happens with not found.
We don't need a path is going to match whatever route we are passing but has to be the last one.
So I'm going to go to not found in a pace not found.
And now if I type what ever we go to not found very good of course if I go home it goes home if I go
to matches of the team or the matches.
That works if I try again.
Not really happening.
Burguet What is it.
OK.
So right.
So at this point we did a lot of things on the application.
So the dashboard the outman we know how to upload how I have to upload files how to create forms and
we didn't you know we did a lot of things but the most important thing is the authentication is the
most usable thing I believe for it from firebase database.
Maybe not so much like I told you before and maybe if you come from a different course with me you know
I don't like that much.
The database of firebase.
Why.
Because it's a very simple database.
You don't get to do a lot of things if you want to do complex queries or something like that.
Firebase is not maybe the choice for you is to do simple things simple stuff.
You know it's a very slim database and Burslem API for this one you know works good could work.
So on the next section what we can do we can create a built of our our components our you know our project
and we're going to change some of the rules inside the database and the storage because so far if I
upload this to production or whatever anyone can read and anyone could write so we can change some of
the settings and we're going to use to see a live or firebase to push everything to hosting if we go
to hosting we can deploy it to their hosting and they will give us a fake u r l where we can see our
you know our project working with authentic cation and everything else so we can host it inside firebase.
All right.
So let's go to the next one and do this.