OK so we need to build our project to create a build of our project and host it inside of our base.
First we need to make some changes.
If I go to database right here inside our project it's going to take a little while.
So if we go to our project and I go to rules the rules say say that anyone can read and anyone can write.
So anyone can enter to you know our obligation get the keys and everything else.
And of course they will start writing so anyone can write.
But we don't want to do this.
We want only authenticated users to right to our application.
Makes sense.
So we need to change this a little bit instead of true.
Everyone can read that's cool but on right we're going to change this.
So I'm going to do this.
I'm going to open and see if I can make this bigger or go a little bigger.
And I got to say OK if our love is different than Nouel so only users which are authenticated which
different dental can right now we have one problem.
If you go to our application and I go to home I scroll down and we have one part where anyone can read
to our database because any user should be able any actually.
Any user should be able to enter the e-mail right here and right to our database.
So we need to write a special rule for e-mail.
OK.
So I'm going to go back here.
So the Partan database where are we going to be hosting this promotions.
You know these emails calls promotions that is the name of the document.
So I'm going to say OK I want to do this for pretty much everything but for promotions promotions I
want to do something else so I pass an object in promotions.
Anyone can read.
So I need to do dot read.
And then Con and true and then coma and anyone can write.
So dot right.
CONAN And then true.
All right.
And I'm going to publish this.
And there we go.
They are published and they're going to make this back to the fold.
So now not anyone can anyone can read but not anyone can write.
But inside promotion's anyone can read and anyone can write.
So if I overload the application I go to enter email and of course this email is already on the list
going to type whatever.
And then gmail dot com and I'm going to enroll and it's letting us do it.
And the same thing happens right now with storage.
If I go to storage
Let's wait for it.
We have the players benefit but if I go to rules anyone can read and anyone can write.
So a loud read a request out is different to No.
Oh no sorry.
It's by default.
You know and anyone can read.
Anyone can read but not anyone could write.
OK.
So this is good you know this is actually correct.
So we're good to go.
Now how where we can find information in how to host our project inside the inside firebase so I'm going
to click and get started and right here they say NPM install G tools.
I'm going to cancel for this.
I'm going to go to the QuickStart.
So this is the docs.
It's inside firebase docs hosting hosting and then QuickStart.
So this are all the instructions.
It's going to be really really simple.
So first we need to install the firebase tools I've already have this but I'm going to install it anyways
so it's going to go to the terminal.
I'm going to quit the process and I'm going to clear now before we can put anything inside firebase.
All right.
We need to create it we can not put this project inside firebase because our base is for you know putting
up simple apps right here right here.
So we cannot we cannot just put whatever we want.
We need to create the belt first.
All right.
So I'm going to go to M city and if we go to PAX to Jason here you have the commands to create a built.
So it's NPM run build or in this case.
I'm using John Ron built in a press center.
It's going to create a build going to take a few seconds and I'll be right back.
OK so everything was built.
If I go to my directory I have the build.
Right.
Right here.
Very good.
It comes in.
So now what do we need to do.
We to install the tools from firebase so we can push this to hosting.
We need to do NPM install global Firebrace tools.
I'm using yarned but I don't know if you know this will work with yarn so I'm just going to do and PM
NPM install says you have node by default you have and PM So it's going to work for sure.
Right.
It's going to take a second and I'll be right back.
OK so everything was installed going into to clear.
Now notice that we are doing minus g so this will install far base globally.
We are not installing this inside our project.
So we are installing this in our computer.
So whenever we want to do I want to use a command from firebase we can do it and we don't need to install
everything again.
All right.
Clear.
So now the first step would be to do firebase log in in order to you know create a fire base project
or hosting right here we need to loggin.
I'm already logged in but I'm going to do it anyways.
Firebase log in and it's going to ask you something.
In my case I'm already logged in.
But in your case if you're not Logan is going to say please log in.
Just enter your username from firebase and the password.
Now how can we initialize this.
So right here.
The third step.
It's initialized your side.
So we need to do firebase innit.
So I'm going to do firebase in net and now you need to be careful you're going to get this you're going
to get a bunch of functions and the one we need to use is the one that says hosts hosting now don't
press anything so far yet is going to say do you want to set up this folder or press space to select
features then enter to confirm.
So inside hosting what do we need to do.
I need to press space just like hostessing and then enter and the set up will begin.
So let's give it a minute.
It's going to give you some some options.
Select a default bar based project for this directory.
So right here it's going to give you the options of which project you want to use.
I'm using the m city.
I have three projects and we put four inside firebase.
So I'm going to select am City so am City.
So what do you want to use as your public direct directory.
So by default as public as this one.
But we don't want that.
We want to use the built.
So in this case I need to specify the building.
That's why we did it.
So I'm going to say Build Now it can say configure as a single page app.
Well yes we are using as a single page app.
So when you say yes.
So the next question is going to be file index HVM l already accessed.
So yeah inside built we already have an index that HVM L.
Now if you click yes it will pretty much override whatever it's inside the shemale and they will put
their code and we don't want that our HCM L comes from re-act from built.
So that's the one we need.
So we're going to say no.
All right.
And that is that is going to pretty much created a Jeff firebase the Jason File.
We are not pushing didn't push anything so far but is going to create a file where you know it's going
to put everything is going to take all these instructions and deploy it to hosting.
So now the next step is one.
It's not the one we already did this one.
We need to deploy your site so firebase deploy firebase and then deploy a presenter.
It's going to take a second and that is it when it's done it will give you the project console and hosting
you or else.
So if I copy the hosting your L and pasted right here are the top
you're going to get our project.
So everything works right.
And if we are even getting things from the database with the players and you know this works.
All right.
OK.
So what happens if I try to authenticate it.
I believe in our project the route was signed and so going to go to sign in and I believe and I don't
remember right now.
Oh right here of deployment history you get the of course the dash forward of all the deployments.
If I go to a indication I was using Francis at gmail.
Weird.
So Francis Jamail and then I believe password one two three.
So if I log in.
All right.
It's Ilet letting us log in matches players.
So there we go.
OK.
So this is the last thing we're going to do for this project.
We're going to move on.
We're going to move on to the next and the third and final project maybe it's going to be pretty long
but we can do a lot of things.
So so complete.
And for this one.
After the course it's done I am done publishing this course.
I get to you know stop 3:55 for a few days and think what I can add to this project and I will add a
few bonus sections to each project maybe the second one and the third one because the first one it's
so simple.
So maybe I will try to add something for fun functions or maybe something with e-mails or something
like that going to add some bonus sections.
Now if you want and if you want you know if you can think of something for me to actually do right here
to add to this project you can just comment there and I'm going to read the comments.
All right.
OK.
So if you got this far congratulations.
It's not a super long web site but we kind of did a lot of things so there's a lot of logic right here.
So let's move to the next and final project.