OK so let's do the pre-event route right here.
So I'm going to go right here.
And if you remember the previous component of the previous project we did.
We created a dedicated component instead of showing a route.
So now we're going to do something else we can agree to a high or the component begin to render that
high or other component and that high or the component is going to be in charge of taking whatever component
we want to render in that route.
And of course do some checking and check if the user should enter or not.
All right.
So let's go.
I'm going to go a little bit slow because it's a little bit weird.
So I'm going to create a file inside H O C called out and I'm going to leave this empty and I'm going
to go back to routes.
Of course we need to import it so import and I'm going to call it out from that forward slash h o c
forward slash and then it's going to be called out.
Right.
I mean a mistake right here.
There you go h o c.
And then out.
So now instead of rendering this component begin to be render rendering that out component instead.
And of course we need to do this on all the routes.
So we're going to do this.
I'm going to do this and I'm going to do this.
And then of course I'm going to close it.
All right.
OK.
So now whenever we render a route this route for example instead of rendering this component is going
ever or out.
Now of course we need to do more things because if we think about this this route it's public.
This ones are kind of in between.
They are not really public but if the users log then we shouldn't let the user end.
We should show the user the dashboard in of course if the user is logged in it's going to be a complete
private drought.
So I'm going to create a second argument for this.
So for complete private routes this one is going to be true.
And for kind of the in between.
This was going to be false just like this false coma and false.
And for the other ones the completely public it's going to be nil.
All right then we have one more scenario which is going to be of course is going to fail is going to
be the if the user is in a trader.
And for this one for that for those routes we will add a third argument.
But we don't have this route.
We will create the logic but we're going to do it later.
And I can explain why you're going to get.
Don't worry.
So right now we are rendering this out.
But of course we the application fails because this one does nothing.
All right.
So let's go to the other component and we need to create a re-act class based component.
So this one will be called authentication check of Fenty cation and check.
You could call this whenever you want.
Just going to call it this way.
Now we need to import quite a few things.
We're going to use connect from redux because we will dispatch an action to fetch from the server.
This whatever the outcome returns and if you look at this the hour will be returning all the information
about the user included if it's been or is out indicate it.
All right.
So we need to import connect.
That's the first thing.
So import connect connect there or go from react redux.
All right.
Then of course we need to import something from user actions.
We don't have it but we're going to read it right now.
So we get to port and then we import the South from that that forward slash.
We go inside actions and then user actions.
Now we will show a loader.
If we are you know fetching the information about the user or deciding if you want to let the user in
or out.
Sorry.
So I'm going to import circular circular and then progress.
Sorry for that.
I was.
I had a cold.
We could go maybe more not.
I'm not completely recovered but I'm you know can it get so much much better.
So I mean porting circular progress.
So if the user of course is not authenticated and we're still doing some checking instead of showing
whatever component we want to show I'm going to show it's circle or progress and after and only after
we do the authentication check begin to render the component and remove the progress bar progress.
Now what are we going to be returning calls a composed class I can post component kind of weird name
but that's the name.
It's a component components composed component.
So we are going to be returning a function that returns a class.
So it's a function that returns a function pretty much that that is the idea of all this.
So I'm going to go right here and create an export a default and a function of returning a function
just a normal function and this function will be returning some code.
Right.
So the code that we will be returning is the complete code of the class that we want to return.
Simple as that.
All right.
So I'm going to go right here to the export before at the top.
So this function will be receiving some arguments because we are passing arguments right here.
The first one is the component that we want to render at the end.
If everything goes OK.
So this one it's a composed class just like this.
Then it's coma and we have the second argument which is the true falls of the null.
So on this one I'm going to say I'm going to call it reload and then we have a third argument that we
are not passing right here that we can use it in the future.
So I'm going to call this main route because this one it's only for adding routes.
Now since we don't have on other routes this argument the third argument going to set by default to
null so we can do this.
And with ESX.
All right let's get so now of course we enter this function and this function returns this class since
we're going to be using Kinect instead of exporting default.
The indication check.
Let me just change the name here instead of returning this.
We need to return connect.
So we say return just like this connect and notice that we are not doing the export default because
this is the export default we can only have one export default per file.
So if we do it the connect.
And of course open it close.
And what we return is the indication check.
Right now we need to use a redux and we will use map state to props and the props that we will be accessing.
Accessing is the user process.
So I'm going to go over here create a function function then I'm going to say map state to props and
this is of course from redux.
So in this function what we will get we will get.
Of course we'll pass the state and then what we will be returning is the user.
So return open and close and we say that we want to return the user and inside of the user whatever
we get onstage that user and we will use this later.
So whenever we use connect and we are using maps data props from redux we need to pass it as a first
argument.
You have a second one which is map this patched props that goes on the second one.
But if you don't put it it doesn't matter.
Right.
But always map state prompts is the first argument.
The second one this patch we are not really going to use at this point right here.
We will dispatch something but on a different way just like with it before.
It's OK.
So I'm going to go right here inside of the to the render and I'm going to say OK.
So if I do have to have a result right I'm going to show the compost class.
You know the class we want to return.
If not I want to return the loader.
All right.
So first I'm going to need to state and I'm going to say state equals to opening close and I'm going
to say loading equals to true.
Right.
By default we are loading something we are doing some checking.
So at the bottom instead of returning the component that we want to return at the end are going to do
some checking first.
I going to say if open it close and it's outside of the return if that does not state that loading it's
true instead of returning this we're going to return something else.
So we need to use the keyword return and I'm going to return a div with a call a last name of main loader
at inside and then to use this circular progress.
So opening close circle or progress if you remember we can pass some props.
So I'm going to change the style a little bit.
So open it close open it close and the color can be 2 1 9 6 EF 3 and I'm going to change that thickness.
So thickness equals two pretty large.
Pretty big.
Seven.
Now of course if everything goes OK at the end you know we return the components.
So we're going to get back.
So let's go to our application and at least it's not failing but we have the loader and this means that
of course says we are not changing the state.
It goes right here to this scenario.
So before we go to any any any any route and to go to a different one we're always going to lower.
So this in this way First we can do something right here maybe in the component amount.
And until we don't get an answer from the server telling telling us if this user gets authenticated
nothing is going to get this plate.
So are we always first do the checking and then we show the component.
Right.
So of course if everything goes OK we want to return the component.
Now which components are we going to be returning the composed class.
So this first argument.
It's equal to whatever component we want to render whatever we specify right here since we kind of pass
the first argument we are kind of rename in the name of the argument.
We can do something like this instead of returning there.
I just can return that compost class.
So now if I changed this to false
you're going to be returning the compost class and this case is home.
Right.
OK.
So let me go to the user dashboard because it's one we need right now.
So you really was user dashboard.
So we get that dashboard.
We're getting the actual component.
Of course we are not doing any checking or going to change this to true back to true now.
And of course the router and everything else they pass prompts.
So we're going to do open and close.
Dot dot dot this dot props.
So we're going to include all the props from the router now.
Then at the end at the very very end when we do the we do that request to the user.
We will get some data back that will be stored inside redux with the map state two props.
So inside of this component we will have access to whatever is inside the user in redux.
And we could need this in the future so I'm going to say user and much later we're going to check it
so I can include whatever we get back from the server whatever we get back from redux that we have inside
this that props that user.
All right.
So for now of course nothing is going to happen.
We just have the same result.
All right.
So what do we need to do next.
We need to make a request to the server and get this hour's going on.
So we're going to do this on the component demand component.
Did MT open in close.
So what we need to do we need to dispatch an action to oath.
Now we don't have anything inside out.
So I'm going to go to user actions and we can have a you know need to add it.
So at the top I'm going to call this user our core user.
So this our user will be just a function so we'll go at the bottom and say export export function call
out the user how we're going to call it.
There we go.
So this one just creates a request to add that to the server so Konst request equals ASIO's that get.
And remember it's a get request to user data server just like this and close that.
And then for Slash if you remember the route it's out.
All right.
Then of course we get a response.
So we say then we get a response from the server that it's equal to response that data the data and
at the end we will be returning opening close and a type of and a payload is what we get back from the
server.
Now the time just like we get right here it's going to be out user and the payload whatever we get back
from the request.
Right OK.
Now we need to add the type of our user types.
So export Konst out user equals our user user right.
So now we have the actions we have the types we need to create the user reducer.
So on the user user again we will be getting this alpha type so our user.
And he said here you're going to do it at the bottom it's going to be a case of our user.
And whenever we get a return we will re re payload we will be getting the state returning the state
and I'm going to call it user data because if you remember from the server whenever we get a response
it's with all pretty much all the user data.
All right.
So there's one action that payload.
You're get.
So let's go to back to south and now we can you know dispatch in action and see what we get.
So I'm going to go to our I'm going to say OK.
I want to add this that props props Dodd this.
Opening close you're going to be doing an hour and then of course we will get a response.
So I'm going to say response opening close and I'm not going to do this now I'm going to host the response
inside.
Let the user and again say this equals to this that props.
And now notice I'm not using this that this a response that this patch I'm using this that props because
when we read when we reach here that this patch already injected the props with the map state the props.
So now I can make a bigger check to this that props that user because after we get a response from the
promise everything is should be there from redux.
So I'm going to access user data and I'm going to console log user and see what we get are.
So I'm going to go right here and of course nothing happens.
I can open the console and I'm going to go to console and we get an object with error.
True and it's all false.
And remember that when we go to the server.
This one right here and we go to that middleware which is south we get is out false and error true.
If the user is not authenticated and this is because we are going to the application right here at our
server it's checking for the cookies and it's checking this user it's really authenticated and maybe
the health and education is failing.
So OK so let's try to go to do the following.
I'm going to go back to out again and change this to loading falls
and it pretty much doesn't matter where we go because we are still getting that authentication fails
so we're going to go to council lock.
Let me show it again reload again.
So we get is outfalls and are true.
All right.
So let's go to the log in.
I'm going to go to sign in.
I really will sign in.
I'm not really sure how but it's at the top.
I'm going along here.
So we're just along.
All right.
Sorry for that.
So we're just log in and I'm going to log in again.
Francis LGM of that come and passport.
One two three.
I'm going to log in.
And now we get something something else we get log success.
True.
And it's outman true.
And we have all the information about the user.
So in theory if I reload the application this hour.
And of course we are logging in and we are getting it getting a correct token right here we D-W out
if I reload the application is going to answer to this scenario is going to go and check if we do have
a valid valid token.
And since we do we are going to get this instead of is our pulse.
So I reload the application and we're getting OK.
This dude has to correct token.
So we should be letting the user pass.
So this is it.
Now of course we need to do some more checking.
It's going to go right here.
And of course at the end of this that sets date open and close and I'm going to say loading false and
right here going to say loading true.
Now of course now we do have user information.
So what we need to do we need to check if the user is antiquated.
Right.
Let me do it again the consul law
because I want to show you something of course relevant.
So the application loads that we go to a route and we get this in return.
Right.
So now what do we need to do.
We need to check if the user is authenticated.
We need to check if we do have a prop inside user and user data that it's our equal to true because
if we don't we want to kick the user out and we will never reach this place the loading falls.
All right.
So I'm going to go I'm going to leave that one and I can say OK if opening close.
So if the user remember we have a user right here Dot is off then we're going to do something.
If not we're going to do something else.
Now I'm going to go right here and I'm going to say if I open it close and then reload.
We want to do something.
Now remember that this reload is going to be true false or no.
So if this element here if we are not a decade it and this route that we are trying to enter it is a
complete private route instead of going to the dashboard because the user is not authenticated at all.
We want to say this that prompts that history that push and I want to get the user back to register
or log in register log in.
All right so since we are authenticated Of course it's letting us pass.
What happens if I remove the token going to go right here.
Remove the token I'm going to remove all tokens whatever I can to reload the application.
And since we are not authenticated we get to go back to just to log in.
So you know it's working.
All right.
I got to log in again you are going to looking at why not then password one two three.
And of course we go we go to dashboard reload everything is good.
All right.
Now we have a different scenario because if the user is it is authenticated it's actually authenticated.
What are we going to be doing.
We're going to let the user pass or not.
Well if opening close if we do have a reload remember that we do have a reload if they reload.
It's equal to false.
Right.
Which is right here.
And the user it is often dictated instead of showing the register and log in because we shouldn't show
this route to the user if it's logged then we should go to the dashboard.
So OK.
So if the reload which is the opposite of here it's equal to false just like this.
I'm going to say OK this probs.
Am I'm going to copy from here.
There's that probs that history push and instead of you know letting the user pass to their routes they
register a log in since they are already logged in.
Again it push the user to the dashboard.
Right.
So user for Slash dash board.
All right.
Well let's try again.
Let me make this a little bit smaller.
Now of course the users Longden and I'm going to calls it says that your users are actually logged in
right here.
So if I go to read just so Lagann shouldn't be able to enter.
So nothing happens.
I go to her just to log in and nothing happening.
Register log in.
Enter now happening because we are already logged in.
So it's taking this back to use your user dashboard.
Now later we can begin to get this admin route logic with a third parent with a third argument.
So we need to catch it right here and I'm going to say if I open and close and then we get we going
to get an else and the else will get on the.
That's all right.
Now if the user is out antiquated because at this point we are authenticated and the user is not anatman
right.
It's not an administrator.
Instead of showing the route I'm going to send the user back to the dashboard.
So I'm going to say if this is an app en route and remember we have it right here.
So this property this argument should be true in order to access here.
So if it's an app on route and the user user and say user dot is and I've been Strader is apin begin
to do something else.
Remember that we have right here the property whenever it comes back from the server console.
We have as admin in this case this user is an out Binny's trader.
All right.
So I'm going to say this that prompts that user that dashboard begin to kick these again to dashboard.
So if the user it's an administrator I'm sorry it's not an administrator and it's trying to enter an
have been route.
We are not going to let the user pass which is going to kick the user back to dashboard because you
know they are they are allowed right there.
And that is it works.
So let's try the possible scenarios.
I'm trying to I'm locked in.
I'm actually locked in.
Let me just remove the token and logout.
It's going to go to application.
Clear everything is clear and I'm going to close this if I reload the page of course we are not antiquated.
So again if I tried to go to dashboard it's actually a user dashboard not happening if I want to go
home.
It's actually happening because it's a public route.
So go back to logon are going to log in France's passport 2:59 log in.
We are able to go to the dashboard.
We are logged in we shouldn't be able to enter to.
Just a slogan.
And it's not happening.
So again this really works.
And now we have an additional piece of information.
If I go to the state.
Of course we have inside the user data we have pretty much all the information about the user.
So now whenever we load this user dashboard we have access to the prop's right here at the top.
And if you remember we are also passing the Propst to this component.
So we have something inside that this component where we can access this prompts the user and get the
user information right.
All right.
So that is get you know we are we are pretty much done with this.
So on the next section are going to be complaining this is going to be finishing this using information
we're going to call it that prompts and everything else.
And then of course we going to move on to a different thing so we can change it and do something something
different than you know forms and everything else.
All right.
So let's go to the next one and keep going.