All right so now we are going to create the links on the header and this is going to be a challenge
because they are a little bit weird.
Why.
OK.
Let me show you the final one.
Let me go to home now right here.
We have some links and this ones are kind of public.
So whether you're love then or not you should be getting this option and then you have a different part
to the letter which is the user options.
And and this one if you are locked out you mean.
I mean you're not locked in.
You should be getting log in.
Now if you logon just like I'm going to do right now.
Passport.
One two three.
I'm going to log in.
You sure can.
You'd be getting some other options.
And the public option.
Well now some of these options are links.
Most of them are links but the log out for example.
It's not a link.
We are not going to create a route just to log out.
So this one is it's a device that triggers a function.
So we need again to remove this.
All right.
So let's you know let's begin with this.
So first before we go right here I want to output the name last name and e-mail right here.
Now remember that if we go to a user an index we are just displaying some information now right here.
When after we did we did the out of all the components all the children of that you know then that composed
component are receiving new props.
In this case we could say prompts that user.
But I'm going to just bring the user.
So now instead of here what I can do I can make corrections to that user that user data just like this
user data is a data and bring just a name.
So if I reload the application of course when you log in.
So Francis and then password 1 2 3 get to log in we get Frances.
So instantly we easily get all the information above the user that it's luck and once we are inside
this route and this is happening right here and it's happening at home for example if the users log
then we should be getting the user information and we should be able to perform some of the actions
like we will in a future like adding things to the user account.
All right.
So let me complete this.
We need the username we need to use a last name and then the e-mail.
So last name and then e-mail.
And if you remember again inside of this user user data we have again the prompts for the history so
we can begin to catch a history of the user.
OK so now let's go to the head.
I'm going to go to the letter like it's all before this is going to be a little bit weird.
So right so right here we have the logo at the top.
We have some blanks which is the user links and at the bottom we have the public links.
Now we don't have any any of this links to see yet.
So like with that before you're going to create.
Right here on the tablet we go right here you're going to read some kind of a bbls or maybe a state
or whatever where we can host the links and they're going to do it through state not state opening close.
Now we have the links at the bottom and the links at the top.
So I'm going to host them on a different place.
So Page is going to be the Public Links and then we can have the user links.
So I'm going to say user and we can have more links.
All right.
So inside of here it's a link.
We'll it will have some properties.
First the name of what is the name of the link in this case home.
Where are we going to be going to.
So link to and this one will be home.
And then we have a different option which is going to be is this a public link or a private link that
users should be getting this should be getting this link.
Even they are locked out.
Well there's going to be adding in the public.
And if it's a public link it's going to be true.
That of course we're going to do all we're going to do all this logic in a coma.
All right the next one after home we have guitars which is the sharp guitar section.
All right.
And that one of course is public.
So.
I'm going to say guitars and then shop are going to name this shop.
Of course we need to remember this when we created the real route.
Then we have the user.
All right.
So going to copy and paste now on the user it will get an option that calls my cart.
So I'm going to say my card with a capital C and this one will go to user.
If you remember for Slash and then cart.
And again this Natas this route.
It's not public.
If the user is logged out we should be able to get this right what else we have my account.
So my count.
So we're going to get this my account and whenever we click it we're going to go to the user dashboard.
So dashboard and this one is false.
It's not public.
All right.
Get a copy again and paste into the next one.
And now right here at the top we get the log in.
But if the user is locked out begin to open.
Oh sorry we are going to get the log in.
And if by log in Francis at gmail dot com password 2:59 that log in goes out and we get the log out.
Right.
All right.
So this one it's going to be log in log an I'm sorry.
And whenever we do the log in we're going to go to register underscore log in.
And now this one should be true because we can get the log in option whenever the user it's not locked.
And but this one is on the user options.
So this one will be pulled the chair and the next one which just log out.
It's pretty much the same thing.
Logout and then user for Slash log out.
And this one will be public false.
All right.
So now we have all the options.
So of course we need to catch.
We need to do something right here maybe create a function or do something else so we can go.
And of course render whatever we want.
So now I'm going to read a couple of functions.
But before we do that the thing is before we do that we need to check we need to access some place in
our application so we can check if the user is locked and or the user is locked out.
You know if it's out indicated and the problem is right now that we get that information inside the
route but we are doing better on the layout so we can not access that prompts that we are doing with
the mouth.
So what we will need to do is we will need to check with redux need to access this that prompts the
user.
So we need to bring redux to the equation.
Right.
So I'm going to go at the top and first begin to import link because we don't need links so import link
from Rio re-act router Tom Raigad.
Now I'm going to go right here and say import and we need to import connect from UPS connect from and
re-act redux.
All right.
Now of course we need to go at the bottom and you know connect to redux.
So export default then connect open and close and then open the header and close it just like this.
Now we need to bring map state to prop's because we need to inject the user prompts know the prompt
we get from back from redux.
So we can use it right here inside of the render.
So just like with that before function map state two props open and close we get a state and we say
return open enclosed user and we get back whatever we have inside the state that user.
All right.
Very good.
So now of course we pass the maps state to Propst so we can inject the props right here right.
Now now we have two different types of links the page and the user.
So right here first I got to say this dot show links.
We don't have this function we can agree to right now.
Capitol show links.
And whenever we want to show the links at the bottom I'm just going to pass that does that state that
page which are the blanks at the bottom.
And whenever we want to render this section the links at the top we're going to say I want to render
the users.
So now this function will be receiving the items we want to display on each part of the you know the
right section of the header.
Right.
So I'm going to go at the top.
Let me just make this.
OK.
So I'm going to go right here and create this function that we didn't have so far.
And that's why we get an error on the page which it says show links and I get a call.
I'm going to pass it as time because it's type of page or type user.
This one should be user.
All right user right.
Very good.
So now we're going to get this time.
Now the thing is again on this section right here at the top we need some of some of them are public.
Some of them are you know links some of them are something else.
So we need to do some checking and do something else.
Now the first problem that we get is that some of the links are only going to show if we are authenticated.
So we kind of need to do some checking.
And what I'm going to do instead of just rendering whatever we have inside of here I'm going to make
a new list right here a new array.
I'm going to make some checking.
Of course we're going to look them we're going to do some checking.
And if the elements should be on the list I'm going to put it on you list.
And at the end will render this list that we can't get right here instead of this one.
All right.
So first we're going to create a new viral called List equals to an empty array.
Then of course what we need to do we need to check if the user it's logged in.
Since we are using redux we have already injecting the props we use or so this prompts the user and
I get to make sure that we have that user data property.
Now remember that if we go to a route and if we are not authenticated let's assume that we are not authenticated
and we go to home that our file our file that elth logic is still going on.
So we will always get some something with user data whether user data or maybe saying that the user
is not indicated or something like that.
So we will always get it even though we are authenticated or not.
OK.
So if we do have this this we're going to do something now.
What we're going to do I'm going to enter the type which is where we have all this links and I'm going
to do a for each for each just like this.
OK.
Now for each We're going to do something.
And what I want to do I went to pass an item on each iteration.
Now first we want to check if the user or south indicated or not.
So I'm going to say if open and close and if not we're going to do something else.
So if the user is not open to it begin to do something.
So if this that prompts that user that user data and remember that we have that is off property.
So if the user it's not o'th indicated we're going to do something in this case we want to check if
the item is public because we have some of the options are public and some other are not really public.
So when you get to do or are going to check if they are public because they need to be public so public
equals true we could get this because we've already have billions but that's OK.
I'm going to enter to that list and I going push this item item.
OK so what we are doing we are entering this list and since the user is not out indicated we are creating
a new list with only of the items with the public.
True only.
So for example if you're locked out this one is false.
This one would not be on the list.
This one will not be on the list.
This is the one.
Yes.
Because we are not logged in so we should be getting the option to log in.
And this one will not be on the list.
So that is the meaning of doing this.
OK.
What happens if the users log in.
OK so I'm going to go right here I'm going to say f and create one more check.
Now for example if the user is not blocked then we shouldn't show this option to the user because they
are already logged then.
But we need to use it to show the log out.
All right.
So I'm going to say if item that name it's different then log in and we need to use the same keywords
and copy just to be safe.
Log in we're going to push that item.
So list that push and then item.
So now all the items that we have right here that are public falls we're going to push that to the list
unless we have the log in.
This one will not be on the list.
So if these are lost is logged then we're going to get my card my account and log out.
That is the idea.
All right.
So then at the end of course the end of doing all this nonsense.
We need to return something.
Right.
We are just doing the checking right here.
But at the end we are not returning anything.
So nothing gets displayed on the screen.
So I'm going to return and what we will be returning.
It's a loop.
I'm going to answer to that list.
I'm going to map over it.
I'm going to return an item and iteration.
All right.
And then of course we return something so what will you be returning.
In this case I'm going to tell you why in a minute we're going to return a new function return.
And I'm going to say this dot and default like opening close item that I later we're going to have other
options like the cart like Deckard takes a different layout.
So for this one we need to have a render a different components or we need to pass more arguments and
make the changes on this function.
But the default link is just a link with with it you know just a link from Briac rotor to property and
the text that's set.
That's why I'm creating this.
Just a default link.
So of course we're going to return this default link and this one will be returning to link.
All right.
So let's create a default link option.
Going to go right here.
Default link equals to item II and at the end this one will be returning some GSX.
So for now I'm just going to say look we can extend this in a minute.
But for now I'm going to say Lenk.
So the link if you remember we get it to an inside of the item of this function.
We have the item that link to.
All right.
Then we have a key because we are looping something so key opening close and I can get past the iteration
iteration.
And then of course we have the contents of the link which is going to be item that name.
All right.
And that is that.
Let's see what happens.
Items it's not defined.
Let me find the mistake.
Item the item its list pushed item.
There we go.
Sorry for that.
Let's try again to get it right.
You know we can get it because we are not Blug.
So we get the non public true options home guitars and log in.
Now if I log in we're going to go to Francis Jamail then password 2:59 are going to log in.
Are we going to get it get my card my account log out home and guitars and just like it's all before
we need to extend this because the my card it's going to be different.
This is a link but with something else on top and the logout.
It's not really a link.
It's going to be just a function.
So we kind of need to create something else maybe a div with an unclick or something like that because
by default the linked property of re-act router needs to.
All right.
So this one went too long already.
Let's go to the next one and finish this.
It's going to be to resemble.