OK so let's try to finish this.
So now we're going to do it in my cart and noticed that this one is kind of a different link.
So I'm going to create a different function to just render this one.
What you can do for example in real life is just I don't know of a third argument.
Same type of the item of whatever and then handle everything on the same link.
You can just check the third argument.
Render does if it's a default or random the other one.
If it's a different one.
So in this case I want to be a little bit more clear here because in the future of course this project
this whole whole project it's going to go to you.
So you're going to see default link and then card link and you can notice that there is a difference
right there.
So I'm going to go right here.
We're going to create an opening close and then else else open it close.
Now of course if you have a default link We're going to go to the default link.
So I'm going to say if item dot name it's different than my cart the one happening here.
Then of course we want to render the full one.
If not we can go to my link.
Now instead of this one and then it copy this I'm going to return and this one cart like right.
We didn't have the function going to create.
Right now agoo right here at the top card link.
It calls something else something else.
And at the end of course we will return some GSX.
Now the Codling link it's a little bit more complicated.
Instead of doing just a render of GSX going to render a function that at the end will be returning some
GSX.
Now on this Karch link we can it every time let me show you on the real one.
Every time I add something to the let me do the log in again Francis and then Francis and then pass
Ward 1 to 3.
Every time I go to guitars for example and I add a new guitar just like this we get this from the user
data.
Remember that we are going to redux and storing everything on the user data.
So every time it comes back we get injected into props.
We're going to be changing the number we have right here of course at the beginning it's going to be
zero.
But then we can get it.
So we kind of need to get how many items this user has on the user data.
Right.
So first I'm going to return to Divx.
So that will have a class name just like this of cart link.
Then of course I'm going to add a key and a key of I just like with it.
For now the number you know the red number is going to be just a span.
And I'm going to open it close.
Now this card item the card link is going to get an item and iteration and tore inside barbel called
user that does not probs that user that user data.
So I had you know the next time I make a reference to this I'm going to say this user.
So right here I'm going to say OK if user that cart has something you know and it's defined you're going
to get the user that cart Dodd and we get the length.
So langue.
There we go.
If not we turn zero.
So if we do have a user card we have something in user card.
We're going to return how many items we have on that list if not by default zero.
And then of course we return a link and this link is going to go to you know the user profile user card
inside the dashboard.
So the two will be item that link too.
All right.
And then of course just like the day before we get the item name so item that oops item that name.
Right.
OK let's see what we get.
I'm going to go.
I'm going to log in Francis and then pass Ward 1 to 3 and we get my card and nothing else inside.
Now this one it's kind of interactive this one because you know I need to make some changes but for
now it's going to work.
So my cart and we get to zero.
So that is working.
The next thing is going to be the logout.
Whenever we go to logout we click the logout.
It's not going to be a link just like it is right now.
If I click it we go to use or log out but instead of doing that if fire a function that is going to
do the logout.
All right.
So how do we do this.
So again we need to make some changes right here we are saying OK item name equals different log and
we are just pushing the items.
And then of course we return a default link.
So the default link instead of creating a new F conditional.
If we have a log out button on the default link I'm going to do just that and then enter right here.
I'm going to say OK.
If the item that name that we are getting triple equals out on the copy the name logout will equals
log out.
We're going to do something if not we're going to do whatever we do with the default links.
Now on this one instead of returning a link or going to return a dip and a definite date for this one
it's going to be class name.
Log out link because this is not a natural legs.
I need to keep it a class to give it all the link style.
I'm going to go right here and add more props.
Remember we need to add a key and a key it's why am I going to do click on click just like this and
whenever we click this what I want to do I went to a fire function that calls this dad lock out.
Handler could be just logout handler.
All right.
This one is a function that you know we don't help right now.
And then of course instead of here we just rendered the item that name so item that name.
All right.
See what we get.
Of course we are inside logout.
We don't have this.
So you know we have to log out.
If I look at.
Of course it's going to fail because we don't have this function so that's created right now.
And now on this one.
What we need to do we need to go to redux again because this love that we have on the server a route
that is going to be up for force listening to this log out and after we of course we log of the user
on the server we destroy that token we can kick the user back to hope.
Now we don't have dysfunction that's created right now.
Right.
So I'm going to go at the top and I'm going to import opening close and going to create a function called
log out user and it's going to be from that that force slash that that slash.
One more time.
And then we go to actions or slash and user actions.
Very good.
Now we don't have this we need to create it.
So let's go to user actions right here.
And of course we need to export that function.
Ok I'm going to go and say export function logo user open and close.
So I'm going to do Konst request X-ers that get just like this.
And I forgot to put that equal actually those that get and we do open and close.
We use the same user server and that we close it.
And this one the route for this if you remember it's lock out right.
And that is it.
Then of course we will get it.
We will get the promise will get resolved and then we will do response and we will send responds that
data.
All right.
Now we need to type so return I'm going to say type and I'm going to call this logout underscore user
coma and then we will add a payload and the payload it's whatever we get back from their request.
Now let's add to the type and after a while this gets you know really repetitive.
So it's at the time it's going to be called export Condes logout user.
And then you log out user.
OK so now we have the type we have the function of inside user actions.
What else we need to go to the producer.
So import the type and then use a reducer of course pretty much the same thing.
Case log on user.
We return open and close that state of coma.
And in this case we actually don't need anything because if the user logs out we just destroyed the
token from the server.
And that said.
So you could do something like log out something like that and the server will be returning so successful.
So you can attach it.
Now in this case there's no need.
We don't need any verification of this.
So I'm going to log out of this just to state and say just returned stated.
All right.
So of course now we need to go back to the header to see if I can find it or go and I'm going to go
to the logout handler.
Now on the handler we just need to dispatch the action and afterwards do something.
So this that probs that this patch just like this opening close we do the lock out user and then just
then we get a response back open and close and just like this.
Now remember that the server will be returning log out just like this.
We believe it's going to be returning the log out success true or log out success false.
So we can directly catch it directly from here.
Instead the props.
So if open it close responds response that payload just like this.
Success.
What we need to do.
We're going to do this this that props that history
that push open and close and we go to forward slash you hope response payload success.
I believe it called success.
Yeah.
OK.
OK so let's see if this works.
I'm going to click and log out and nothing happens.
Pre-shared that this is an error.
So I'm going to go to cons log.
We get some errors and says Fate's low resource the server responded with 4 0 4 and this is because
it's not finding the route.
So on user actions we are saying that we want to go to log out and we do have a log out and oh look
at its users.
Rowdiest users not user.
All right.
So let's try again.
Going to reload the application and we're going to get a prompt.
If you get what we did wrong right here what we are actually we are not doing are going to give you
a tip.
What we are not doing on the head header right here and the push just you know trying to fix the need
to fix the problem then log out and.
OK we get an error.
It's different error.
Can we properly push of undefined right.
Of course this component it's not really related to react router.
Sorry.
So of course we are pushing something from the prop's we are finding trying to find something other
Propst that it's related to history but you know we don't have anything like that.
So just like we did before we need to inject inject with the router right here.
So we're going to go right at the top and import with router and then from and it's from Bre-X router
Dom and now that I think about it I have to write here so I don't need to bring it again so I can import
it from broken down.
So we need to wrap the component right here and since we are using connect I'm going to go just like
this and close it and let's try again.
Of course we need to log in again.
So I mean it closes Francis at GM and dot com and then password 2:59 log in.
And if I log out back to home.
So everything works.
And if I tried to go to restrict the route just like user or dashboard not happening.
So now we are able to log in again log out and we get all the options at the top.
So very good.
So now at this point do you have a you have a website you have a server you're fetching you could if
you could fetch some information you know from the server like the products and everything else and
you have a logic for logging in and logging out.
This is the most difficult part of the application.
The other part if I go to the final one is going to be the filtering but everything else just gets really
really really simple.
Right.
We just need to do coding of course we need to code a lot.
But there is there is no complex logic right now.
All them the most complex thing we can ever over to did it right here.
OK.
So let's go to the next section and move to maybe a different thing.