OK so now what are we going to do on this section.
It's going to be the slider at home and then of course we're going to do this which is the promotions
section inside home.
So I'm going to do this and I'm not going to teach you anything new of this.
We can already did it.
And at the first in the first part of this project the first version of this project this one the you
know the title and everything else.
It's not going to be really linked with the server.
What we get from the server I'm going to add later much later I could add a bonus section so we can
of course create a part on the dashboard so we can enter you know all the promotional stuff in home
and you know do a lot more set up.
And of course again it's not going to be anything new.
That's why I'm leaving this in a bonus section you know relating this to the server.
So there's two choices you can.
We can build it right now with me.
Right now we're going to do it or you can you know at the end of the session get the code and just put
it on your on your project and that's it because again I'm not going to teach you anything new right
here.
All right.
So we're going to start building this first.
I'm going to start with this lighter.
So of course if we go home nothing happens.
We need to include this.
So OK so I'm going to go right here.
And the clothes are going to close everything.
And we've already have a route for this for this because this home we have the index.
So I'm going to just inside of home are going to build two different files.
I'm going to say that I want a home underscore slider digests and then I want the other one which is
the promotion's So it's home underscore promotion that.
OK first I'm going to start with the slider because there's a little bit more complex than the other
one.
So first we need to react component right here so we could create a stateless component so we act stateless
components.
And there's one of course it's going to be called home.
And then slider a little bit nicer homes lighter.
All right well we'll be receiving Propst.
You're not going to maybe really use it.
We could use it much much later on the application but not for now.
But I'm going to leave it ready right here.
So I'm going to open right here.
And first we need to create slides.
So I need the information that we're going to be rendering.
So we have an image.
Let's let's go alone.
We have an image.
We have the first line which is the beast dog.
We have a second line that we can set up.
And then of course the button which is the link to.
OK.
So I'm going to go Raheel the top and say Konst sleights equal to an array.
Now you might have many slides.
So that's why we need an array of objects.
So image and now I'm going to leave it empty.
Then we have line one just like this line 1.
And by default of course we can add only two lines one title and a you know a second line so Line 1
are going to leave it for now enty coma.
We have a line.
So Line 2 are going to leave it empty.
And what else.
We have a link title which is what.
What is the button going to say bew offers or no shop now or whatever.
So we have the link.
Title equals right now to nothing.
And then we have the link to.
So where that link is going to go.
OK now I'm going to copy this one at the top.
We're going to put a coma at the bottom and chest you know.
Paste it.
OK.
So this one right now like it's all before we will not fetch this from the server.
We're going to just prefix everything right here.
Just you know hard code everything.
So again if you go to images to the images directory inside public images you can get the feature and
right here you get the images.
So I give you three.
You can add just two slides right here.
So go for flash images for Slash featured for Slash and I believe the first one it's featured just like
this featured underscore home that JP.
All right.
So this line for the first line is going to say Fender which is a brand of a guitar than custom shop
which is the first line.
And then of course the linked of the title which is going to be sharp now.
Right.
Then we're going to go to shop which is the shop section you know shop right here.
And of course we're going to do something more intelligent because we're going to do this on the bonus
at the end of the you know the course because maybe you want to shop custom shop guitars.
So we going to need to quit whenever we add to guitars and guitar.
Say that this one is a Fender and maybe this one it's a custom shop so we're going to be able to check
by category or something like that so we can pass something like.
I don't know.
But category Khattak equals custom shop and this will that we will detect this on the shop section on
the guitar section and bring from the server.
Only the ones with categories custom shop.
All right.
But of course we're going to do that much much later.
I'm going to copy this one right here and again paste paste it and the name for this one is going to
be underscored.
And this one will be saying be stock.
If you don't know what a beast archetype is it's the guitars that they have maybe scratch or defect
or something like that.
So they have to charge you a little bit less this counts.
All right then the button is going to say bew offers.
And it's going to go to shop.
Same place for now.
OK.
Now we need to use a slider and we've installed the re-act slick we use previously.
So import that slider from re-act slick.
All right.
Well as we're going to use but in ABBERTON so I'm going to import my button and we're going to bring
this from the Tilse So does that force slash tails buttons.
So for now this is the only thing we need.
All right.
OK.
So let's go with the button.
And if you remember the slider needs some settings so I'm going to say Konst settings settings.
There you go settings.
That's good.
So we all need to pass an object.
And first we just say if we want the dots you know the dots to handle the slides.
I don't want them.
So I'm going to say falls coma.
We need to decide if it's going to be infinite.
An infinite slider.
This is going to be true.
What else we need to speed we can set up the speed of the slider.
So speed 500 milliseconds and slide to show one all of this is the kind of the default configuration
of the slick.
So you can check this on the documentations of course of very slick.
So then to scroll begin to say one comma and arrows.
I don't really like the arrows on sliders.
I don't know why.
No I don't really like them.
All right.
So we have the settings.
It's going to go right here at the bottom and say OK do we want a class name off featured and then container.
This is the main wrapper.
And then of course we will create a slider.
Now the slider needs the settings so we can grab the Barville and say OK dot dot dot put whatever settings
we have inside of the slider.
Now of course we need to add the slides and we have kind of state.
So OK.
So I'm going to go right here and I'm going to create a function called generate slides open and close.
We didn't have this function.
We need to create it right now.
So I'm going to go to General slides opening close and then of course we just return a function.
Now this function will be returning GSX.
So we can roll back and do this all right.
We can know this.
So then if we do have slides and I'm adding that of course we have slides but I'm adding this because
later we will fetch a slice from the server.
So I'm going to kind of leave it Friday for now.
Of course this is going to change a little bit later.
Now I'm going to do sleights dot map opening close in on each iteration.
We will get an item again that data transfer item item and I can at Cookout and then do coma.
I hate that.
So why not for the duration.
And again we still return some GSX.
So opening close so are going to create a def and this Ziv needs a key and the key is going to be the
iteration.
All right.
So instead of here we have a couple of things.
We have the background image which is going to be the feature image.
And inside we have some actions like the title and then you know the button.
All right.
So the first line first Dev is going to be the container which contains the image.
So I'm going to say class name and then featured image.
All right.
Then of course we need to add the styles and inside of styles We'll have the actual image.
So style opening close and I'm going to say that the background of this bad boy is can it be you are
all opening close and we pass the image Eurail which is going to be inside EMG ride.
OK.
We do eat item that EMG we need set up height because we are not really using an EMG Tac.
And I'm going to set this height to the height of the window Sargen to say window window dart inner
height.
There we go.
And then of course we can attach pixels to this Breguet pretty much ready.
Now I'm going to go inside and say DIVX and make a table inside of the dip of the actual image that
contains the deck that contains the image.
I'm going to add a class name and call it featured action.
At this point we should be getting something at least of course we are not including the home slider
from home.
So OK.
Important Than Home slider from Scott for slashed home slider and again corrections.
Right this right here.
Open and close.
And again we should be getting something.
And General sleights it's not defined.
I know what my promise slides generate slides and it's because I didn't do Constantines lights.
All right.
Let's get really ugly.
But we can get it all right.
OK.
Let's get.
So let's go back to the home slider.
And this is actually mistake we're going to fix it in a couple minutes.
But for now it's cool.
So OK.
Featured action.
And I'm going to add the title.
It's going to be a div off and at the class name the class name off track and title.
Notice that there is no underscore right here.
And then of course we pass the item and the line 1 we do pretty much the same thing for the other one.
Do it right.
Same thing for the other one.
And this one is going to be low tile or it could be a lower title doesn't matter.
So lion too.
All right let's see what we get.
All right let's get.
So what else we need the button.
So we're going to create a div and I'm going to say OK I want to bring my butt in right here.
And again we just use the default link.
So we need to pass the type which is default then we pass the title just like this and it's equal to
item that link title.
Then we pass the link to and the link to it's equal to item DOD link to.
I believe we call it link to.
All right.
Yeah.
Then I'm going to add some default Starling's to remove the margins at Styles and we are always on right
that margin opening close 10 pixel's 000 and that is it.
All right.
If I go to shop now of course we are going to shop.
So let's fix this previous.
I'm pretty sure that this isn't my mistake on the settings.
So yeah it should be arrows.
It was my mistake.
All right.
So OK.
So the application loads we get the slider and it's the same hypothesis that we know and if we go to
the next one we can get it for good.
So later we get it fetched.
All of this data right here from the server directly from the server.
All right.
So let's move on.
Let's do the other one which is the right here.
They have promotions which is going to be real simple it's just a background image.
The text at the top and then the button it so let's go to our project and we go to home promotion.
So this one reacts stalest component.
And again home promotion of course we will get it done.
So we need to import my button from.
And it is going to be that for slashed hotels forward slash buttons or button.
Right.
We can receive some props.
What really happened Rob happening right now.
So I'm going to create a viable cold promotion equals opening close.
And we pretty much need the same thing with Dad and home slider.
So I'm going to go to Home slider copy all of this and I get it.
Paste it right here.
Now we need a different image.
And of course different values so for this in this one is going to be underscored and three.
Oh now I remember now.
Now I know how would we get a three because
yeah.
No.
OK.
That's fine.
I know what we got three.
It's two for the slider.
And then you know the other one is for the for the actually you know background.
OK.
I'm sorry for that.
So that's good.
We're going to use a image number three.
So right here I'm going to say up to 40 percent.
So this container right now it's you know these components are not really important for us to practice.
They are really really easy to do.
So in second I didn't put too much thought on this ones so guitars and then shop now and then we're
still going to shop.
So right here at the bottom I'm going to add a class name and it's going to say home promotion promotion.
And each side will create a function render promotion.
Or it could be show promotion or something like that.
So again Konst render promotion.
And we just returned some GSX.
So Ronayne right now we just need to say if we do have a promotion we're going to do something if not
begin to do null.
All right.
So what we're going to be returning to is just a div with the class name off home promotion underscore
EMG could be container.
You have used container.
That's OK.
So when he said the background style opening close and we say back round and the background it's equal
to you are opening close and we use promotion that EMG and promotion going to get rid of a lot of a
lot a lot of plugins.
So OK now I'm going to cheat because we have pretty much the same information on this one than we have
in the home slider.
So I will copy this ones from here.
The button the tag title and the low title.
And I can paste them right here.
So again you're kind of cheating but you know it's better than just typing the whole component again.
You know everything again.
So I need to format or get.
So we get still a default and this one instead of item is going to be promotion.
So we're going to change the items for promotion promotion and promotion and that is it is done you
know really really fast.
So let's include this from home.
So we are almost done.
I know that this was boring and it was it was boring for me and I'm pretty sure that it was boring for
you because again are not learning anything new promotion
and home promotion.
All right.
If I included a home promotion and then we close it.
We should be getting something at least.
Yeah.
So it's OK.
I'm not getting the right here.
The paddings like we do get here.
Well let me check why.
All right.
It's because I did Priem permission.
So promotion and that is it.
OK.
So I'm going to skip the project so you can get this two files and then you just need to include them.
If you didn't follow the instructions right here you know you didn't create the component right here
with me.
You just can get it you know from that from that zip file and just included was simply too simple.
So on the next sections you're not going to do something really simple.
You're going to go to something fun which is this.
So what we need to do we need to create first a component that is going to be rendering some carts and
then we need to create a component that is going to be ruling each cart.
And remember that each component.
Each card has a new to you but it's you know there's one to add something to items and the new product.
Right.
And then of course we need to do fetch from the server so we can get the best selling guitars and we
can we need to get going need to fetch from the server they get new arrivals.
So again the next one it's kind of important.
Right.
OK.
So let's go to the next section and start with this.