All right so now we're going to do this because it fetched the new arrivals.
And again we're going to go and get the best selling guitars we've already have.
Have a route that can handle this kind of request so you know that is covered.
So the only thing we need to do is to go to the index which is home create connect redux right here.
We need to go to read x set up the products action created types and then they create the reduce or
so we need to do a lot of setup first before we can you know make the request.
So let's start with redux.
I'm going to go to actions and create a new new file called products actions that jackass.
So inside of a person's actions first we need to import axially.
And I don't want to type it.
I'm going to copy right here.
I'm going to paste it right here.
I copied it from user actions.
Of course these types are not really right.
Begin to use other types.
Now if you remember we are importing the route from the from Maersk so I'm going to copy that as well.
And I'm going to go back to Misc. because the Barville it's different.
We need things from the product server which is API and the product.
OK.
So product server.
All right.
That is good.
Now we will create two different functions begin to make two request.
We could create just one options one on one function right here and get all the things byte ID arguments.
But uncreate I'm going to create two.
So because this project again is going to go to you at the end maybe in a few months you will not remember
what this function is all about.
So by creating a function that says get product by a rival and then get products by sell.
It's kind of obvious.
So that's why I'm reading this like this.
All right.
So I'm going to export a function get called Get products by and then a rival.
This is the first one just a function.
Then we have export function and then get and I get a copy the one at the bottom get products buy sell.
All right.
Open and Close.
Of course this ones will be using two different types.
So I'm going to go here and change the type.
So get products buy sell and same thing with this one but this one is going to be arrival's So now we
have the import for the types of course we need to go to types and at them there.
So I'm going to pace them both.
I'm going to copy the export Konst and do them both.
All right of course on this one we need to type we can at present so get get them products buy and then
sell.
Right.
This is done.
Next one equals and then get products by a rival.
Right.
One last thing to do.
OK.
So now we need to create a reducer.
We don't have a we do so for products.
So I'm going to go to reducers.
I'm going to create a new file and say products could be product but you know and then reducer that
Japs are going to go to use a reducer copy everything pretty much and then I'm going to close it and
go to the product reduce or going to delete the types we need to import this types.
You know these are the product types.
And then of course I'm going to delete everything right here.
The first one that we're going to be creating is the get products buy sell.
So if the case is that we get products buy sell we can return.
And for now we can just return dot dot dot and the state and they're going to do the same thing for
the other one.
So pretty much we are leaving everything ready to perform the request you know from that action.
All right.
So now we have the products reducer.
We have the types and we have the products auction.
So now auction.
So now the only thing we need to do is to go to next right go to index and include redux right here.
So first I'm going to import then connect connect and all right connect from re-act redux react redux.
All right.
What's next.
Next thing we need to import the functions you know the functions where we're going to be dispatching
things.
So it's going to get products by cell coma and the other one gets products by a rival.
So our rival.
So in real life of course right now I'm creating the project with ubat in real life.
I just do this do multiple things before I need to use them and then I use it.
I believe you know most of us we we pretty much all up all we've got the developers they do the same
thing right.
So we need to go to connect connect open and close and then we wrap home.
All right.
So after we get the products we're going to do a component amount after we get the Prada products we're
going to inject the products inside of here with the props.
So we will make a reference to a new component and we will pass the product the Propst with all the
products.
All right.
So we need map state to.
Now on the previous lectures.
I was doing function substate to Propst.
You can still do Kunst.
You know let me do we have a complete map state of prop's you can do it like this cons upstate to prompts.
So it's pretty much same thing but just with iOS 6.
So now on the Propp we do have a user I'm sorry a product reducer right.
We have the file help fight right here.
The only thing that we don't have is import inside of the producer.
We are not combining that reducer.
So import products from that forward slash products reducer.
All right.
We're going to put a coma and I'm going to bring it and close it because we don't need it anymore.
So it's going to be products.
It will be called products.
Sorry I closed it.
They closed this and I actually needed it because they don't remember.
Sometimes they have bad memory.
So products.
I was right there and then we of course passed the state products and we need to make a reference to
the maps with the maps the props inside of that connect.
All right.
So far so good.
So let's let's try to make a request you know dispatch does get products by cell.
And of course we need to add the request right here.
But let's first try to dispatch this component at Mt..
Open opening close and we go to this that props that this patch opening close and we get the products
by cell.
All right.
So of course we are not doing anything inside of our components.
That's why we get an error because we are not returning anything right here.
OK.
If you remember.
We need to get this from the server and right here we do have all the information.
So first we're going to get the buy sell right buy sell so buy sell.
It's this it's sold by something or they're descending or ascending depending on what we want to do.
And then we go in and do this the limit I'm going to skip are going to copy this one from here.
And remember that the request to forward slash and then articles.
So going to go right here at the bottom and I'm going to paste this just to have a reference.
So products buy sell at cost request equals CEOs that get opening close.
And then when we need to make a reference to the server so template strings and we make a reference
to the server and it's inside articles.
So what we want to do we need to do this sort by.
So we do the question and let me close this so we can see pretty much all that's just going to paste
it.
Copy and paste it.
It's OK.
So on the buy sell we get to sort by everything sort everything by sold then the or there descending
just like we did before.
And we're going to limit 100.
Not really.
We just want to get four.
So I'm going to say four right.
So after this Zygons request we're going to get the proneness so open and close we will get a response.
And from the response we get the response that data.
All right.
And of course and this is why we're getting an error message.
It's because we are not returning anything from redux.
We need to return something.
So type at it's get products sell coma than payload and it's whatever we get back from the request and
then go to request.
All right.
I made a change to the server.
They are going to say so.
OK so now get products buy sell.
We are doing the request.
So now we need to go to the actual reducer.
So let's go to products we.
So in products reduce or we to get the elements so we can store them buy sell open opening close and
then action that payload not open and close is just Conn's com PELAYO.
There we go.
All right.
So then it's not defined.
All right this is my mistake.
Forgot to put that thought.
All right.
OK.
So at least of these is not you know breaking.
So if we go to the stake right here let's see what happens.
Right.
So we go to state and we get the users of course.
And then we get products and we get buy sell and I'm getting a 404.
All right let's see we see the actual message.
So product not found secret policy.
I'm pretty sure I made a mistake with the actual route.
So it's articles articles.
There we go.
Sorry all right state and to get it get it.
So pro-CPS buy sell and we get four different elements.
So Goodman your work is really good.
So let's do the VI arrival since it's so easy so easy going to go and set said the get parts my arrival.
Then inside actions we pretty much need to do the same exact thing.
So like a all before it makes a little bit more sense to create one one only one dispatches one where
we can pass all the options disruptions inside in inside of arguments.
You know we pass them by using arguments and right here we just make two different requests with different
arguments.
Right.
OK.
So I'm going to copy this.
I don't want to type it again.
I'm going to copy and I'm going to paste.
Of course we need to change some things that make us right.
All right.
So we're still going to articles now this sort by is going to be bye.
And let's go to the server and check it out.
My arrival is going to be created at the time stamp that Mongo it's creating for us.
Then the order is going to be still the sending and the limit for the only changes they created.
All right.
So we are getting the arrival so we need to go to the product for douceur and it will that we will really
have the type there.
OK.
So now of course instead of by cell we get by a rival by our rival and this one will be getting the
action that payload.
All right let's reload the application and see what we get.
So actions state we go to products and we have a buy sell and we don't have a bio rival.
That's kind of weird.
Products by cell I made a mistake with this.
No my arrival.
Fine.
Oh it's because I'm using the same type of course of course.
All right let's try again.
State opening close and we get buy sell and buy a rival get.
OK.
So now what we need to do and we're going to do it of course in the Knesset next section we have a buy
sell and buy a rival so we will need to create right here a component that will take the four elements
in device cell and another one right here the bottom that takes the four elements of the by arrival
and of course we need to create a different component that it's going to be rendering carts why a different
component.
And it's because right here we have a cart that we have to begin to get one component rendering the
four carts and then for each we have a cart.
If we go to guitars we pretty much have the same cart.
So this one should be reusable components right.
All right.
So let's go to the next section and create the carts.