Good.
OK.
So let's create a component that it's going to be receiving the props for the buy sell and the arrival
and it's going to loop them and show each card.
All right.
So I'm going to create this inside you tells so inside details.
I'm going to create a component called Card block.
You'll have two types of card blocks.
This one will just print or four or maybe a little bit more if you have you know a sing line but they
will be all all rendered in a single line single straight line.
The other one is going to do a different thing which you know right here we get this kind of a lay out.
So they are kind of two different things.
They look pretty much similar pretty similar but they're different.
So inside the card block right here we need to create just up a component right to react statelets components.
So there's one tool called Card block card block.
OK.
And this one will be receiving props because we get it from the server and we pass it to this component.
So on the return and I'm going to mix them spacebar here I can create a container class name of card
block.
Now each side of the card block we will have a container.
So Dave called class name of container just like this.
All right.
Everything is going to be center right in the in the middle.
Now I'm going to do this before hand on each card section.
Let me go to home.
We will get a title and then you know the elements.
Now what happens if I want to use this component but with a different title.
We are doing right here.
So right here we have new arrivals.
And the best on the guitar so I can not just do H-1 and hard code that.
So when I'm going to do.
We're going to be passing the props by title.
So I got to X props.
I'm going to check if we do have a title I'm doing this because we might not have a title.
Maybe we don't need a title.
So we have the ability of not passing the title so that props and then I'm going to add a class name
and there's one title and this one will be renderer rendering whatever we have inside props.
And then that title.
Now the actual container that contain that contains the going good style right here inline style an
opening close.
And this one will be a display that is play and that Sprague is going to be flex and are going to app
flex wrap just like this and then wrap.
All right.
There you go.
So now I'm going to create a function that it's going to be looping the cartes render cards.
And remember that we only can only render one card inside a component.
We just need to create a component with a single card.
So this one is the one in charge of looping of this.
So again it's a process that list and begin to be passing the list of cards inside the list property
we're going to do it in a minute now.
OK.
So this one will be called Konst and the function name it's rent or cartes equal to open and close.
So this one will need to check if we do have a list.
Now if we do have a list we do something.
If not we do we don't do anything.
Now I'm going to enter props.
I'm going to enter list and I get a map and whenever we map we need a card which is what we get a card.
And then each ration number Y card block.
No card.
Then of course we need to return some GSX.
So I'm going to do this and I made a mistake right here says we are going to return J sacks.
I need to do the parenthesis.
All right.
OK.
So now what do we need to do.
We just need to return something for now.
I'm just going to say card in a string.
Just going to render a string maybe a div with a string because at the end we will have a div or a div
with the word card.
Doesn't matter.
OK.
So in the end when we rendered this component we should be getting two cards to keywords cards right
here.
OK.
So let's go home.
So now let's import this component from this.
Let's pass the props and see what happens.
So import import.
And it's going to be called Card block from the dot for Slash utils for Slash.
And then a card block.
Now I'm going to go below the home slider and then make reference to the card block and we open and
close.
Now if you remember we need to pass a list and a title so list with equals.
And if you remember again we are using redux So we are injecting props and begin to be passing this
props Dodd products because we are storing everything inside products and then we have the buy sell
property.
All right then I'm going to say title title equals and the title and I believe best selling guitars.
All right so the application will reload.
And what we get we get the best selling guitars and we get four different card renders.
All right.
So that's good.
This is actually working.
And I've got to create a new one for the whole promotion and just do it right now.
So the only thing left will be creating the actual card that it's going to go inside card block.
And this one it's by the arrival OK and new arrivals you arrivals right.
OK.
Let's see what you get and.
Oh and of course I'm storing this.
And of course it's restarting this notion is restarting the server and we are trying to fetch something
before the server gets restart.
So if you get just like this frozen like this just reload the page because the server you know it's
already up and running.
OK so now we need to create the cart.
Right.
All right.
So let's go to you tell us one more time.
And inside your tears your tools are going to create a new file called cart.
All right.
So the card component it's going to be pretty pretty much simple.
But later we're going to extend this a little bit more.
And I'm going to use a class based component so create a react class based component.
All right I'm going to call this car with a capital C right.
OK.
So what do we need to do here.
First when we are going to get some props around here this card will only be rendering of course went
with props the props or be are passing from the card blog that we're going to make a reference right
here.
So we're going to be passing props.
OK.
So whenever we get the props we just need to show with the template the template with the props we have
inside.
Really simple.
So I'm going to import from the card block the card.
I believe the gold cart cart not carts from that for Slash and then just cart.
All right.
So OK.
Let's make a reference to this card.
Open and close.
So again we are looping something right here.
So I'm going to remove the div and just pass the card and I'm going to give the key a key to these actual
component.
So going to say key and you make it right.
Keep off.
And I pass the iteration and the other thing we need is whatever we get back from carts.
Now if I do a card like this and then pass whatever I have inside card inside of the card component
I will need to do this.
Probst up card the card and you know it's not right so I'm going to do something else.
I'm going to do that dad and then cart.
All right so now with all the promise that we all the kids devalues everything else we get from card.
We're going to inject this to the cart.
So now it's out of here.
We just need to make a reference to this doc Probst and the whatever name we have inside of their movie
The images or the name or the brand or whatever.
All right.
That's good.
So let's go right here inside and start creating the template first.
I don't want to make a reference to props to this that props every time I'm going to say this props
and now I'm going to make a reference just props.
So the class name for this is going to be class name and I'm going to do the following.
Now later much later and I'm going to show you this right now.
We're going to get this at the top.
We're going to show the elements by this type of cart or by this type of cart ride.
So we need to change classes the only thing I'm doing right here is change the name of a couple of classes.
So we will get whenever we pass a cart we will pass a property of you know style type of style.
You're not doing it right here at home because we don't need it but we can use it much later.
So instead of giving a class name with just quotes are going to use templates strings and then anything
to attach or detach classes.
So this one is going to be cart item and then wrapper then it's paste and we're going to get this from
props.
So if we do get something that says props that grew red we can you know display the other type of layout.
But right now we are not going to do it.
I'm just going to leave it ready for the future.
Whenever we create this of course whenever we go we create this component this behavior we can go back
to here.
OK.
So the first thing we need to render is the image.
So Def opening close.
I going to add a class name to dip a class name of image.
Very simple.
And then we need to pass the style because the background image.
So style open and close.
We need to pass the background.
So back ground.
All right.
So opening closer a template string parenthesis and then I'm going to make a reference to.
And what are we going to be using.
Let me comment this now.
What are we going to be using.
So if I go back to home and I check I state open and close by cell and we get 38 and a c we don't really
have images so we have an empty array of images.
What are we going to be displaying.
So in theory we should be getting at least one image.
If we end whenever we enter a product later we get do it.
We should be getting at least one image but right now we could happen that we get nothing.
Maybe the image of the product is not ready yet.
We don't even have the product maybe.
So you know again the attachment of image whenever we create products it's not required.
So we need to create a way to detect if we have empty images.
You know if we don't have an image and maybe show a different one.
All right.
So instead instead of background I will say this dot render card image which is I'm just going to call
to a function and I'm going to pass probs dot images.
So what going to happen of course is that we have an empty array.
Later much later we will attach images.
But for now we're going to do this function so we can catch that.
We have no images and maybe show a different image or none available image.
So we have no repeat and that is good.
So I'm going to create the render card image function we are using a class we can do this.
So right here we will be getting images.
We know that this is an empty array.
So I'm going to create a NF and an else.
So if images dot length it's greater than zero it means that we do have an image.
So I'm going to access that array with the same return.
I'm going to access the images and I'm going to pass the first image and then I remember that we have
a new or else I'm going to be passing the R L.
Now of course we didn't have that scenario right now but later when we enter images inside of the aerial
images we'll have of course objects and inside of object we have the title of the image or maybe the
you are an L or something like that.
So we can call it by you r l we need to remember this but we are not there yet.
OK return.
And since we don't have an image I want to return whatever is inside images and we have an image not
available image not available and then that PNB pinchy just like this.
If I go to images we have the image not available right here.
All right.
Very good.
So are we getting something so far.
Maybe not.
Not yet.
OK.
So OK.
So now I'm going to go right here at the bottom and say Dave and I are going to go to create a class
name off.
I'm going to call it action underscore container.
Me move it around.
All right.
Oh sorry it's not inside the actual image.
It's outside of the image container.
So let me move this
so.
So now what we need to do.
We need to feel this.
We have pretty much all the information about the product.
So you know the brands the type the name and you know that model name.
So inside the actual container and it created one more container.
And this one will be getting the class name of tax because they are pretty much tax.
So they're open and close we're going to make it on one line.
So the class name for this one it's brand.
I'm using different class name because maybe later we can do something special.
I'm not sure yet.
So this prompts the brand that and we get the name we remember that the brands are inside an object
then we have the name.
So I'm going to say name prop's that name.
What else.
We have the price so we get price.
And of course we can attach the dollar sign or currency sign or whatever.
OK.
So we get something we are not getting the images.
I don't know why.
We're going to check it in a minute.
So but for now it's get what else we have a description right.
We have a description of this one but we might not have a description on this one we didn't have it
but we could attach it.
Now if I go to the grid mode we do have a description and that of course comes from the server.
So I'm going to do it right now.
I'm going to go right here after the action conductor after the tax.
I'm going to open something and say OK if prop's dot grid opening close we're going to return something.
If not begin to return.
No.
Right.
So I'm going to create a class name.
I don't know Dave.
Yeah.
And the class name of the scription.
And this of course is going to be whatever we get into this later much much later then we need to do
more.
We have the actions right.
OK.
And this one is going to be a little bit longer because the actions the buttons that we get are really
different than the other ones we get.
You know this one has a different style.
We even get it.
Hoover.
Hoover effect.
And it was just when it's bigger so they have different DSS.
And on this one we just have a Nikon So again instead of using the default link we need to create two
different links because they are of course different.
So this one went a little long.
Yeah a bit long.
So let's go to the next one.
And keep doing this.
Meanwhile I'm going to check why we are not getting the image.