So let's do the buns.
And I know what we are not why we are not getting the image and it's because the name is strong and
by here the name it's wrong as well you know the name the real name of image.
I'm going to copy and I'm going to paste that real name.
All right.
So if we reload we get sorry image not available.
Maybe you're wondering why I make mistakes and it's because well it makes sense.
I'm talking I'm coding at the same time and I'm watching the final code right here so I could have a
performing three tasks at the same time.
And not only that when I when I watched the final code I need to decide what comes first.
So you can understand it.
And one what comes last.
So yeah again you can add up a human.
My wife it's actual neuroscientist.
So the brain cannot process three things at the same time could do only one.
That's that's how it is.
But what we do we multitask we change from here to here to here.
And that process of course wears you out.
And that's why I'm making mistakes so I have to apologize for that.
OK.
But again talking writing and watching all the things not that easy.
All right.
So OK.
Let's I'm going to save this.
Now we get the image so we need to create the buttons.
Now we have two types of buttons right here.
We have the new product and this one.
So what I want to do I want to create inside buttons because we need to go to button.
We need to create a new type of button.
Now for this one for this button the only thing that changes from default is just to class we changed
a class name so I'm going to make this a little bit better.
I'm going to back to I'm going to go back to cartes right.
Going to go back to cards and I am going to change.
I'm going to make a request.
I'm going to I'm sorry I'm going to include the acoustic component my button and it's distilled default
but I will add a new property called alternative class.
So if we do have this alternative class we will switch classes.
All right let's do it first.
I got to say my Birnam Let's first create the wrap for this because we need a wrapper right here.
So I'm going to add the class name off and it's going to be called actions.
And he said if you're going to rub the button inside something called class name and then.
And.
And then.
OK.
So you sort of here of course we will get the button right.
So I make a reference to my button opening close.
I know we are included at the top.
That's good.
So again this one needs props.
So the type again it's default.
So I'm going to say default.
I'm going to add this of turn out of class.
So class alternative class and it's Card link.
All right.
Next we have a title so title equals and this one will be bew with a capital B and product.
Next we have a link.
So it's link capital T and two equals two.
And we pass the location of this product.
Now if you remember from the database let me go here from the database.
Each card has has an ID and this is how are we going to be accessing this product later on it's own
section.
OK.
So I'm going to call the section product detail for Slash and then we attach this props that underscore
ID.
OK.
Then we go and we need to add some stylings and I'm going to do the same then before I can add styles
and styles equal to opening close.
And I will add this and margin the same thing we did before 10 pixels zero zero zero.
All right.
So right now if we go we get to fold one right.
So we need to make the logic right here for this alternative class.
So I'm going to go to button and right here we're going to say OK if we do have an alternate class we're
going to show it.
It's not going to show the default.
We just need to do a turnaround.
Very simple.
So I'm going to delete this.
I get all of this out.
I'm going to open and close.
So if props that alternative class is not defined then we want to return the class alternative.
Like I'm sorry.
Link default.
If not we're going to put whatever we get back from alternative class since it's going to be the other
one we get the product right now we get pretty much to 100 percent because this is flex and we need
to add the odds of the other.
But in we don't have a case for this it's going to be a new case.
That's OK let's create it first.
So on the other one the first burn rap going to go outside that and create a new element with the same
class name but in rap because they are flex.
So now this one is a little bit special because it's not a link it's a function.
Whenever I click on this I went to trigger a function and that function much much later is going to
go to the dispatch begin to dispatch an action so we can add the card I can add that element ID to the
card of the user right.
And of course if we don't have the user it's not really luck then we're going to do of course something
else we're going to show an alert or Right now we are going to do just to console.
OK.
So we're going to go here and say my button open and close.
Now this one we get a call this one type of.
And I called this back like open close and then I'm going to save run action.
So this run action is just a callback function.
Whenever we trigger we're going to trigger this callback function.
Right now we're going to say Konst log to cart something like that something simple or added to card.
That's good.
And now we need to go to button and add this back link case.
So inside of here we're going to go below here and say OK if we get back Lenk we want to do something
and never forget to do the break.
All right.
So tackling gets risible.
It's just a button with an unclick.
So we do Templi do the template.
It's equal to.
And I'm going to do going to do it here.
It's equal to just a div with a class name of back link and I'm going to attach right here the on.
I'm going to say unclick it's equal to a function.
And whenever we want to run this function we run the prop's Dot run action that we are passing right
here as a prop for that run action.
This of course this run action will be triggered by this and right here we then we going to do that
dispatch.
But for now we are called bigot.
Now this one has an icon.
This shopping bag and we are not including any icons at the top.
So I'm going to go over here on the top and in say import font then.
Awesome awesome.
And then icon then from.
And it's going to be at Fonte awesome.
And it was the last one yeah.
The free solid read that is get oh sorry.
No it's not the free it's fun it's awesome.
And then react.
Awesome.
The other one is to freeze solid.
Now of course we are bringing in front of on Thompson I come and then we need to import the icon and
that's that is the one that it's solid.
So this one calls it a shopping and then back from at 0 at Sorry we'll do it again at an font.
Awesome.
And I believe it was the last one found and this one is for.
No fun.
Awesome.
Let's do it go again.
And it was the last one for you saw it.
All right.
For slash F.A. shopping bag.
And that is it.
We have the icon right now so I'm going to copy the name of the icon.
I'm going to go here and we're going to make a reference to this font.
Awesome icon.
And paste it right.
So now we need to pass the name of the icon.
Pretty standard stuff this.
And it was called a shopping bag.
Hopefully they're not there are no mistakes.
So if can he get it.
All right.
There you go.
So let's see what we get.
Couldn't find font awesome reaction.
Awesome.
I'm pretty sure I made a mistake with this.
So let's go back.
It's a font.
Awesome.
Actually Well we are getting this a lot of this.
Oh I just realized this.
It's just very hard for.
Awesome.
Why awesome in that font.
And this is actually coming from the Noj modules and it's actually weird.
Never realized this.
So if I do four awesome
we get it.
Hurrah.
It's really weird.
OK.
Well maybe they are not the official font awesome kind of a get have dependency all over or whatever
you want to call it.
So maybe that's why they are using a different name or something like that.
It's weird.
I don't know why.
Maybe it's because they are the one to use a different keyboard so they don't use the same keywords
and all the ones.
So that's why they do this.
But that's the way it works.
Why now.
OK.
So we get the icon.
And if I click it and I go to the inspect we get the console lock out at two cards.
All right.
So that is good of course.
Now what we need to do.
We need to do some other stuff because whenever we click right here we didn't have an action to dispatch.
Right.
So we wanted to create an action to add this item to the to the user card and what it's more more important
is that we didn't have a request to handle this right.
We didn't have a request to do this on the server.
Whenever we make a request we need a place where we can catch the idea of the product.
The idea of the user and go to the server go to the actual model get the product and stored inside of
the you know the history of the user.
Actually it's not history.
It's the cart we need to grab the element.
The idea of the product get it go to the user and store it inside of it.
A theory of cart since of course we are using all of this will of course reload the props and it will
inject right here at the top and we'll see a number and everything else.
So we need to do all of that we can do it.
We're going to do it later.
We are not going to do it right now we can go back to this when we have a more complete website because
the whole card logic and then the log in and inside the user we can see the we can actually make the
purchase.
It's going to be pretty complicated.
We're going to get there.
But for now we are get we are really good.
Now on the next few sections we can be doing the guitars right here in the shop section.
So this is actually going to be really fun because we need to create of course the different layouts
just like this is actually going to be easy but this one is going to be the interesting one because
we need to filter.
We need to filter things right now we are getting all the fender ones so we need to have a complete
we need to create all this components to collapse from a mature UI.
We need to create all this logic and it's going to it's going to take a little bit of time but it's
going to be really really fun.
All right.
Let's go to the next section and start with the guitars section.