OK so let's continue with this.
So if we go to the stars and I'm going to go to the final one if you go to the TAR's we get the shop
section for last shop and right here in the left side of the top and have a bar.
And this is going to be reusable very simple reusable components because when we go to products we pretty
much have the name of the section.
So again we're going to create it and it's going to be very simple that at the bottom we have the right
side and the left side and on the left we'll have a lot of filters and all of the sections.
You know the brands and the woods just like with the with the server.
We need to fetch two categories from the server.
Now for the price and not for the frets.
And of course when we select them we need to do some magic with the state and something else and we
need to filter everything.
For example if I felt a fender and would filter frets of course we're going to do some filtering.
We're going to filter by both.
That is the main idea going to remove this and make it a little nicer.
And of course in the right we're going to get all the carts we can show them.
And of course we can change the grid.
And if we are pretty much doing all we can do a load more and load more products.
OK.
So again we will need to do a lot of things.
So let's start small.
I'm going to go to our component right here to components.
And of course we need a section where we're going to be putting all of this.
I'm going to call the section shop could be products or buy or you know whatever doesn't matter.
It's completely up to you.
It's going to create an index not just because it's the main thing we need.
And of course this one is going to be a re-act class based component because we need to do a lot of
things.
OK.
So I'm going to call that shop of course just like the name.
So it's going to be shop copy shop and then shop and then going to say just job whatever.
Now of course since we want to use the route we need to add it to routes.
So I'm going to go right here at the top and noticed that this ones are kind of a public and this one
is not so all the other main routes I'm using is paysan using just a different place where I can see
them.
So I'm going to say important and then jump from that forward slash components for Slash and then shop.
And that is it.
We don't need everything anything else.
OK.
So I'm going to copy the name again.
Right right here we have the admin and right here we have the public the public ones.
So and then copy home because this is just like home.
I'm going to put it right here.
So it's going to be shop the components going to be shop still out.
And still no.
And the location is going to be shut.
All right.
So we go to our project and I go to guitars.
We get to shop.
So that is good.
What is the first thing we're going to do.
We're going to do this the the peach top I called the page top.
So I'm going to store this inside tills because later whenever we go to a new product we have pretty
much the same section the same component.
So we're going to do that.
We're going to import it right here the top of course it doesn't exist begin to create right now.
So Page top from Dot dot dot dot dot dot dot for Slash.
It's going to be tails for Slash page underscore top.
Of course we need to create this so get a copy go to Eutelsat and create a new file Coale call the page
tab.
Yes.
So again whenever we change routes this is going to be displaying the name of the route and from within
the parent component.
We're going to be passing the name of the section to page top.
It's going to be a very simple component so react statelets component just like this.
And it's called page and then tab right.
And we're going to be we're seeing some prompts and then we will return something simple.
It's a class name off page tab.
And inside I'm going to put a container so we can put everything in the middle container and inside
of the container.
I get a pass the props.
That title maybe and just maybe on the bonus section are going to do something else right here because
maybe we are right here in a click fender.
So I would like to get this tax convert to something and maybe put a line right here and show the tax
you know do that kind of a breadcrumb or something like that.
But you know right now it's not really that important.
So we can do it much later.
Maybe we are going to do it much later.
As a bonus.
OK.
So let's move forward.
We have the page top so I'm going to go back to index and of course we need to do a lot more here before
we can do the pitch top begin to use redux because we need to fetch a list of brands and the list of
words from the server.
So import connect import that connect from and then react and then redux the Rigaud.
OK.
For now that is good.
We need to import a lot of things.
But right now Kinect is just that.
All right.
So of course let's go at the bottom export default connect to opening close and I'm going to close shop
now.
We will be using maps take the prompts.
So I'm going to say map state to Propst just like this and delete the prompts and we will be returning
products because we need to do the request to the server.
And this will return everything inside products so we need we need access to products.
So far so good.
So let's go to the Render I'm going to go to the render and start creating the main layout for this.
So we're going to make a lot of references to this problem.
So I'm going to say Konst products equals this that props the products.
So now we don't need to do this problem that this that prompts anymore we just make a reference to products
and that is it.
OK.
So on the main div I'm going to include the page top so I'm going to say opening close and self-closing
Takk page top.
I'm going to pass that title Propp title equals to browse products.
All right.
There we go.
So in theory we should be getting something Dhokha we can get it.
I'm not getting the title it's because a mistake title
we get Brion's products same thing than here Burguet.
OK so until now we need to divide the rest of the ad the the container right here into a container right.
We need to center pretty much everything and then kind of divided with the left and then divided with
the right side.
OK.
So we're going to go right here.
Open and close.
And this is going to be a container.
So class name of container and the layout for this is going to be very simple.
So lay of container are going to add one more wrapper just like this.
And this one is going to be class name of shampoo rubber OK.
And then of course we have the left side and we have the right side.
So div class name will be left.
And that class name of right.
So if I put left right here and I put right we should be getting something at least.
All right.
So let's go here and we get left and we get right.
So that is good.
So what are we going to do next.
We going to go in order and the first I would like to do everything that they got to do with the filter
because if we make a request after we filter everything we can actually do the console log and check
that we are getting the information or we can even go to redux.
So this is not really that important right now.
This is important part of the application right now.
Right.
So what do we need to do next before we create anything we need to do we need the data actually we need
to use right here we need to France and the woods and for this of course we need to make a network request
to our server so we can we can get it right.
All right.
So of course we're going to create two different functions so we can we can dispatch an action so important
and close and I'm going to call it get Brandt's because we need to get Brandt's and then get word because
we need to get what and what's pleural from that that force Slashdot that that force slash and then
actions for Slash and up products.
Right.
Of course we didn't have them.
We need to create them right now.
So I'm going to save this and they're going to go to the actions directory and product actions.
And of course we need to start cleaning them right now.
I'm going to play it I'm going to split this with categories because of course we are getting products
but we are getting the integrity of the product the product and are going to copy the name here and
I'm going to go over here and say export function.
I'm going to paste it and then I'm going to just create a function just like this.
We are using this you could read up on our function right here.
It's just pretty much the same thing.
So export function and it's going to call get votes.
Same thing of course at the end we're going to get an error because we are not returning anything from
here so that that we know that.
OK.
So we need to create the types so coma and then get what we could call this get worse or you know fecche
words are going to culturist get Brandt maybe get words what's going to copy the types and I'm going
to open types because we need to add them.
And since they are related to products I'm going to put them right here.
I'm going to paste copy the export Konst just to make a little bit faster and then equal.
Same thing right here.
Export Konst equal to something.
And of course we need to add this and we need to do this manually at Brandt's.
We closed it and then it got worse or it got worse.
So very good.
Now we have the product actions we are importing we have functions and types and everything else.
So in theory I'm going to open reducers.
I'm going to go to products reducer and we get a need to do the same thing for the types we need to
bring the types get brands and get Woods Komar get brands and get what's very good of course we need
to add the case right here.
So can be very simple really real simple case get Brandt's and make it right get Brandt's.
And of course if you get Brandt's we will return opening close data that we return to state coma.
And I don't know we could call Brant's action that payload Burguet are going to copy to get Brant's
because it's pretty much the same same thing.
So get Brant's this one will be get woods and then it's going to be what's an action that they look
really simple we were not doing anything new and actually you could cut to the chase if you ask me.
And since you want to get categories instead of creating a route where you can just get one category
and just well go to one database where you could do you can of course fetch different things from the
database.
And then internally from the server create an object with two categories Brandt's and woods and you
will be each year you know just getting the brands and the words on the same route from the same request.
So when you get back to just get back in contact with Brandt's and woods right now we are practicing
and at the same time I'm assuming that maybe you're learning right now all of the developers are really
experienced as experienced.
So I'm just trying to split things up so it gets a little bit easier to understand.
But of course if if we could make something better something a little bit smaller or smarter I can tell
you you know you could just read one route and do both things but it's completely up to you if you want
to try it.
Yeah.
Goodman go and try it.
OK.
So we have to get Brandt's we have the types we have the reducers.
We pretty much have everything.
So right now we're going to be it we're going to fetch the information.
So I will go inside of the class and of course we need to do this.
This is what prompted this patch from the component at Mount component that Mount open and close and
we do this that when we make it right there's that props that dispatch
patch opening close and we get to get Brent's right.
So after get Brant's I'm going to do get what's in it for us at the end.
We're going to get everything in injected inside props.
Right.
That is the whole idea.
And why we're using maps to props.
Oh and of course I need to pass it right here to the connect sorry for that.
All right.
So let's see what happens.
The application really renders.
And there's the props and maybe I made a mistake.
Of course of course.
Sorry I forgot to do something we forgot to do the reaction of request.
Sorry for that.
Sorry.
OK.
So again really really simple.
We do a concert and I'm going to do the first one to get France and then I'm going to copy and change
the change.
What we we actually need to print.
So constant ASIO's that get opening close and it's going to be from products we have it right here the
products sever and the get it's Brandt's.
All right.
After that we can again respond the issues of response equals to reads pongs DOD data.
All right
that I'm going to take one more thing.
And this is just sometimes I do it like this.
If the project is not really really complicated why do I create a different function that it's not been
exported anywhere.
Right.
It's a function of fear could be a functioning side misc or you know something like that.
And what I do is create different types of requests I just create again a function that handles get
requests right.
Is the only thing that is going to do.
And of course at the end it just returns something simple.
You know this is a very simple request.
There is no configuration there's no nothing.
So what you can do instead of writing little of everything just every time you do a request you just
can create a function that does this that receives maybe one or two arguments depending on what you
want to do.
And that is it.
And you just create the request it later uses says you can just create a function get my data just like
this.
And at the end you know this will get resolved and returned.
So you could do that.
You could do something like that.
I did that many many times depending on the project of course.
Sometimes that requires they get really really weird because you know you need to do a lot of things
first or something like that.
But you know this is a good example.
Just create a function that handle handles simple requests and that is it.
So again you could do that.
So I'm going to return opening close and I'm going to return to type and a payload.
All right.
So if you remember we helped get Brandt's so we passed the type get prints and then request.
So we have the type and the payload.
Now on this one it's going to be the same thing for the get go.
That's why I'm telling you you could create just a function to avoid repeating pretty much the same
code.
It's not the same because we have different kind of a different route to our arguments.
But it's pretty much the same.
So this one is instead of get Brant's is going to get worse.
All right that is get.
So now at least it works.
We're not getting an error message.
So of course we have dev tools.
So if we go to state we get products we get the Brandts and we get the word so we are ready to work
with this.
We can get the products and the words from within the store.
And you know generate all of this.
Now we can get used for example this one the checkbox you can use it three times.
So there's no point in copying pasting the same component three times with different properties.
So we can read a reusable component because again maybe we can use it later on other sections.
So we're going to create a reusable component for this.
This one went too long.
Let's go to the next one and start with the reusable components of the checkbox.