OK so let's start with the fun part which is going to be the checkboxes and the filters and everything
else.
So first we're going to get this and we need two types of components.
We need the check boxes boxes and we need the actual dropdown right.
We need that.
So let's go first to our component.
Let's go to indicate that J.S. and we will create reusable components right now are going to go to the
top.
And of course important we need to create it but first are going to imported import import and clinical
uncoiling call it.
I'm going to call it collapse because it's a collapsable and then check box and then from that that
you tills for Slash collapse.
Same pretty much the same name called object collapse checkbox just copy paste it and make a small c
could be a capital C up to you.
And then I'm going to close it.
Of course we need to create this component and it's going to go to you Tilse.
Now I'm going to put it outside of you tildes could be inside forms but you know that's OK.
So collapse a jackpot checkbox and make it a single.
Very good.
OK.
So this collapse checkbox we need to do a lot of things.
I think you might be thinking do it is just a collapsable and checkbox.
How hard can it be.
Well we need to do a lot of things because we need to use use it with with matyr you I'm sorry.
So OK so first one this is going to be a react class based component.
That's the first thing and I'm going to change that capital C to collapse checkbox.
OK.
So we are moving in react and we need to bring all although that got to do with material and we need
to input a lot of things.
So I don't really want to type this one by one.
So what I wanted to do is go to the web go to material do I and demos go to the demos section component
demos and go to lists.
Now whenever you go to lists you just scroll down right here until you find that one with the face of
the guy.
And I just find a list with a checkbox with the title you know and it checks pop a checkbox in the right
and open the source code on the source at the top.
You can have all imports.
So we do need to import lists.
We need to import item.
We need to import second secondary action just like this and then item text and we do need a check box.
So I get a copy of this just going to copy and paste it and that's it.
You know we have a list we have item we have text.
We have this.
The only thing that you're not getting is the collapse.
So I'm going to import this one manually import and then I believe it's collapse from at materials like
core for Slash and then collapse of course
and that is it from.
And that is it.
We pretty much have all we need now.
If you for example maybe you're watching this in the future and you don't really have this maybe you
have something else give you a different example.
You will need to possibly deal and manually copy.
That's that's what it says.
Sorry for that.
You know I can't I cannot help you there.
This is why when we need to do in real life.
OK.
So we pretty much have all of this.
We will use some font awesome icons and this one will need to manually.
So import fonde also awesome and then icon.
And it's going to be from Fort awesome.
You know that weird react for it.
Awesome.
A little bit.
You know it's can we are.
I don't know why but that's OK.
And then we need to import at the angle down and angle up this arrow and then when we close that we
have the down arrow.
So we need to import that.
So import and it's going to be called a angle down just like this from Fort awesome.
And I believe this is the last one yeah.
Awesome Fun font awesome free.
It.
So again we just copy the name go down and I'm gonna copy this one.
Paste it at the bottom and it's angle up.
The other one you know kind of makes sense.
And then going to calls it if you notice you don't need to do this is just what I do.
And the world is divided by the people who does them I call and the one that they do into it.
But you know again you could be one of those guys that they don't get into it.
That's OK.
You know it still works OK.
So we Whenever with the component loads we will bring the components right the filter and the checkbox
component and now this filter might be open or it might be closed.
So if I reload web page you'll notice right here in the final one that I have this one is open but the
other one.
This one is close close.
And this one is open so we can decide that whenever we include the component from here.
So I'm going to create a state right here called equal open force and then a checked and this check
this array is going to be the finalist.
Whenever we start you know checking boxes.
Now of course by default it's false.
But we can check.
We can change it whenever we include this on the other components.
We're going to do that now.
Going to go back to the index and since we do have a collapse checkbox right now we can start you know
including the check boxes.
So let's go right here.
Let's go to the left.
I'm going to make some space.
And what I need to do I want to bring this collapse checkbox component and of course we need to pass
a law.
We're going to do them right now.
So first the initial stage so in at the state and this state is going to be the open or close.
I was you know we were just talking.
So this one.
The first one which is going to be the Brandts is going to be true is going to be open whenever it looks
then we need to pass a title so the title is going to be the text of what is the collapse and this case
will be brand So title equals and then brands.
All right.
What is the next.
We need to pass the list of what is what we want to know to show when this component has a list of checkboxes.
So I'm going to say list equals 2.
And if you remember we are already using products right here and we've already added the components
amount to get the brands.
So everything is going to be inside products that brands of the redux store.
And then at the end when we make some changes on that list of checkboxes we need to trigger function
from within this component so we can trigger different action and go to that route from the on the server
and bring the Filcher.
Of course we are not there yet but I'm going to call it right now.
I'm going to create it.
So it's going to be handle filters this handle filters will be a function just like this and it will
be receiving the filters from the child child component and then we get to go to a different phone function
called called handle filters.
Pretty much same name right and they handle filters.
We will be passing whatever filters we get from this collapse checkbox OK.
Now one more thing on the handle filters we need to lead the function no with which checkbox is this
one because the all of the checkboxes are the same but the prize is a little bit different.
So we need kind of that function we need to know what are we filtering just checkboxes or our radio
buttons.
So I'm going to say coma I'm going to pass a second argument and this one will be brand you know just
passing the title of whatever we are doing right here.
Then of course we get to catch it and I'm going to do something else with prices.
Get we have the initial stage the title that we are passing a list and we have to handle filters for
it.
So I'm going to create this function so we can skip that message.
So handle filters is going to be equal to a function whatever whatever.
And then we just create a function.
OK.
So let's go back to the collapse checkbox and do this ok since now we are getting prompts inside collapsed
checkbox.
First I want to grab the initial state so I'm going to go to the component that mount.
You could do it in a different way from the from the static for example.
But I'm going to do it the classical way Actually this is the recommended way.
The other one you should not use for everything.
So initial state and this that said state opening close and I'm going to say OK so open is going to
be equal to this that probs that initial state.
So whenever we mount we're always going to get the default that we are passing right here.
And of course it's going to change this state and should change it right here.
All right.
So let's start creating the the checkboxes for the.
They believe that the collapsable.
So the container will be class name.
Open it close.
Collapse.
Underscore items underscore wrapper.
OK.
Now inside of here we need a list.
And this actually from material you let me go back a list.
So this is from material you are.
I'm not making this up of course.
So this list I will need to add a board there bottom note notice that list list it's collapsable has
a border.
So I'm going to add it manually so we can override a part of the initial stylings of Mattioli.
I'm so bored there just like this and bottom and one pixel's solid.
And it's a great color.
So dbd BTB.
All right.
So then of course we get two different things.
You can get the title which is which is where we're going to click to open and close.
And then at the bottom we have the list of checkboxes which is the actual probable.
So this ones are kind of a no not related.
This is kind of a div where we can bind on unclick and whenever we click it this second list the second
div you can open it close and drop or drop.
So they are kind of a related but not really so.
OK so since we have a list I need to add a list item.
Open and Close.
Now whenever we do an unclick on this like this item we're going to do something.
So I'm going to say unclick and I'm going to create a function that calls this handle and then click.
Of course we don't have this function.
I'm going to add it right now.
So handle click opening close and we just do a function.
Now this handle click.
It's really simple.
The only thing we do is we just toggle the staked so this that set stayed open and close and we say
that we want to grab that open that we have the top and we want to change it to true if it's false and
false.
If it's true so does that stayed open.
So if we if it's the open it's close it's Gates follows and we cook it.
We're going to change it to true.
If it's true and we cook it we're going to change it to False.
We just toggling the stick.
That is that that's the only thing we do right here.
All right.
Skip moving forward now this list item again I'm going to overwrite some of the stylings because I don't
really like them and I'm going to close this and this is going to be a pattern because the default panning
of this list item it's a little bit weird.
So 10 pixels 23 pixels 10 pixels 0.
So this one this actually looks nice looks a little bit better than the default one.
All right.
I'm going to save it now if you go right here we can see and maybe you notice that I'm making a lot
of reference to the final and I could be showing you the Photoshop with design but I don't really want
to do this.
You know this is a better example of what we want to do.
OK.
So in real life of course we will be watching the designs so well instead of here we have two pieces.
We have the left which is the title and the ride with the arrow.
And notice that every time we change this state this arrow could be up or it could be down.
So we need to change the names of the font or some icon.
All right.
Actually we need to change the font or some icon.
OK.
So we have two parts.
I'm going to create a list.
Let me do it correctly list.
An item and text just remember that we've imported this at the top I'm going to make it a self-closing
tech opening close.
Now this one takes a primary and the primary it's the title.
So the title is going to be this problem.
And remember we're passing the title from here title.
So I was going to get this.
That prompts a title.
Then we need to add a class name so I can override some of the default Starling's you know the font
and everything else.
So class name I call this collapse underscore title.
All right.
Then we have the the R.O. the up and down.
And I'm going to do this inside a function so handle and then angle if you can think of a better name.
You're welcome to use to use it.
So again I'm going to create and remember that we are using a class based component so you can do something
like this and it's still going to work completely up to you.
So on this one we'll just you know change the icon if it's the state it's open or it's not open right
if it's true or false.
So inside this handle toggle a handle Well I'm going to return some GSX.
So there's that state not open.
If it's true we will do something.
If not we will do something else.
So what are we going to be returning.
Is the font awesome icon opening close.
Now we need to pass the name of the icon.
So the first one.
I can't.
If it's true it's going to be that it's up.
Right.
And depending on the application this might change.
Some people like to do it you know the other way round.
So class name icon and I'm going to do pretty much the same thing.
We could just create a sink component and just change the name right here.
You could do that.
Now think about it.
All right.
So angled down
all right that is good.
So let's go back.
And of course I have it right here.
So if I click it remember that we are already changing the state we have right here to open and to false.
So if we click it we are able to change the art.
So everything's working right.
And I think about it this is actually something we could do with F.A. angle maybe with the ternary just
return one single piece of code and check if it's open and return this or return that we could do that
for now.
That's OK.
I'm just going to leave it like this.
All right.
So what do we need it now.
We need the actual collapsable.
So I'm going to go outside of collapse outside of the I'm sorry the list item and I'm going to say call
ups Oh getting close.
Now let's go on the collapse.
I'm going to say I don't know maybe item text is going to copy and paste it right here.
Of course we are not going to really use this.
So with the collapse we need to pass some properties and some of them are really required.
So the one that is required the most important thing is going to be what is the state of this.
It's it's collapsed or not collapsed and this one it's inside in whenever we do in we do we do.
True or we do false.
And if you remember we have this on the does that state that open.
So this state that open.
Right.
We are going to pass some more defaults so we have a timeout and I'm going to say no.
And we have one more property which is mount on exit.
And this ones are from material.
All right.
Right now it is open.
That's why we get the second brands.
If I click it we close it and their works are good.
So now our only job right now the only thing left is to add the list of checkboxes.
So this one will be rendering will would be rendering a list.
It is a list of checkboxes but it's just a list.
So I'm going to say what is the component that we want to render as a list of components and I'm going
to say dear.
And again this is a prop from material you I and lists.
Now I want to disable the padding but because by default on the lists they give you a weird padding.
So disable panning and this one this one is going to remove the paddings.
Now of course nothing is going to really happen right here.
So we need to create a list.
So I to create a function to render a list that is Dudd render render list and we are always there.
Not that there are but we are almost there.
OK.
So I'm going to copy the name of the function.
Go right here at bottom and create it render list open and close and we will be returning some GSX so
open and close.
Now what do we need to do.
We need to grab whatever we are getting as a list of products you know and create that text right here.
And the checkbox and right now that's fine.
OK.
Render list.
So very good.
This I believe I'm using the same name.
So OK.
That is good because because we are not returning anything.
So first I need to check that we have we do have something inside this that props list.
So if we do have something we're going to do something if not we will not return anything.
Now what we need to do we need to map the list so this that prompts that list and then we map over it.
I'm going to open it close and for each one we will be getting a value now opening close.
And there we go.
And for now I'm just going to return dip.
And with the with something inside of course we're going to get many brands.
And that is the server.
So we get it open and we have all the list of brands.
Now let's check.
What is the structure of this.
So we have brands and for each brand we have an ID and we have a name.
Now if we stop for one second and we think what what can happen with this when we make a request to
the server what are we going to be really using the name of the category or the ID.
And if you remember again inside products because it's what we're going to be filtering products we
store everything we store the brand with the I.D. not with the with the name so we should use the idea
instead.
Right.
So let's go back to render list and what we will be rendering since we have a list.
It's a list item.
So I'm going to do this.
I'm going to say list item.
Open and close and let me check if this went too long oh it's already went so long.
So we're going to continue this on the next section.
We get a created list item with the of course the text of the checkbox and then the actual checkbox.