All right so let's keep going with this.
We are creating a list item right here.
We're rendering a list of list item.
Of course we don't have nothing inside.
But instead of here we have at least eight list items.
So instead of a list item we need to put the name of the item and the checkbox the actual checkbox.
So inside list items we we're looking something I can add a key key because opening close and we get
it passing if you remember that whatever we have inside the value and the underscore ID which is the
ID that comes from the server.
Then I'm going to put a file modify some of the stylings are going to change depending padding.
Open and close some pixels and zero from the sides.
Now instead of here we have two things.
We have the text in the left and the checkbox in the right.
So for this one we will be using a list item because we are using a list item but it's going to be an
item text so open and close.
There we go.
So we need to pass the text that's going to go inside.
So this we do this but adding adding the primary so primary the primary is going to be whatever name
we get from the server.
You know the name of the brand.
So value that name.
All right.
Then we need to add the checkbox and we cannot just add the checkbox right here because it's going to
get a little bit weird.
We could add the checkbox but it's going to be here.
So to put it in the other side of the you know the list item we can use that list item.
Secondary action.
And it's going to go all the way to the right.
So I'm going to wrap this inside the list.
Secondary action.
Of course we need to open it close this.
So there you go.
So instead of here we need to put the checkbox so checkbox again self-closing tag.
And this one of course need some configuration.
First we're going to do the color and begin to set it to primary right.
The default color for a checkbox and then when two main things and everything that we're going to do
right now it's on the actual demo.
So it's on the documentation.
Of course you're going to do it one by one right here.
But if you have some doubts everything is on the demos.
All right.
So we hope we have two different properties.
The onchange which is going to be a function and then the checked which could be a function but begin
to do it right here.
So if this checked.
It's true.
And first I'm going to add something here let's say console log.
Hey we are not going to reinspected and just adding something to the change.
So if this checked is true it means that whenever the application whenever it renders that checkmark
is going to be true.
And of course if it's false it's not been show checked.
Right.
Makes sense.
But at least we get a list and the checkboxes.
So what we need to do is that whenever we do change we need to.
We need to grab whatever value we have from this checkbox and added to the list of checked right here
we just push it back to that list.
So we need to create a function to rule this and then whenever we checked something to render with this
component we're going to check that state we're going to see if the I.D. of whatever we want to rent
to right here it's on that list and if it is of course we are going to we're going to do something we're
going to of course.
So true or false.
That's what we can do.
And again everything is on the documentation.
So for now whenever we handle an and change what we will do is run a function or function.
So this handle Tuggle because we are toggling and we're going to use the IDs so I'm going to be passing
the you dot underscore ID.
All right.
So I'm going to copy the handle toggle I get to go right here on the bottom and says that handle toggle
equals whatever we get from value and then run something.
All right.
Brian a function and I'm doing this just just like the the documentation that we could use this on on
the on the usual way you know just a pad or a function.
OK.
So what are we going to do.
You're going to be doing.
So we are going to grab whenever we get back from this handle toggle we're going to create a copy of
the of the checked state.
Right.
And then we're going to store everything inside of course we need to do some modifications.
So this is just like we did with the with the forms to update the actual value of the input.
It's pretty much the same idea.
So first I'm going to create a viral called this.
And again I'm going to go with the exact same we have in the documentation because maybe in future you
will read the documentation.
If you don't get this you can always you know get this video.
I can explain what is happening with this and why we're doing it like this.
We could do this on a different way because this is pretty much what we did with forms previously creating
a copy checking the copy.
Then of course putting everything back to St..
So this is pretty much the same idea but on a different way.
So I'm going to do this this that state now if you're not familiar with this going explain you right
now maybe you are and you can just move forward just a little bit.
So by this what we are doing is we're creating right here a Barville that it's good it's going to be
called checked and this checked is going to be equal to this state.
So this is kind of a shorthand of doing this next thing too is something like this.
There's that state checked.
So this is pretty much the same thing.
What we are doing we are accessing we creating a Marvel comic called checked and we are saying that
this when it's equal to whatever we have inside this state that check.
But this is of course the short version it's a different way to do it.
But they are pretty much the same thing.
So by this we are just reading the Bible saying that instead of here we want to put everything everything
that we have inside this that state that checked which is just an empty array for now.
All right.
Then I'm going to create a variable called Konst current and then index.
And this current index is going to be equal to whatever we have inside check checked.
And let me do it like this.
Checked and then dot and this is of course just pure javascript index off and Balli.
So what we are doing right here since we are going to get a value from the handle toggle with an ID.
You're entering the array of checks that we have inside of the state and we're checking if you have
the index of that particular value.
So when the index off you're going to enter an array and you can search for this if you have an entry
with the same ID with the same value.
If we do have any deal with the same value this one is going to be a negative number.
If we don't have that value on the list this one is going to be a positive number and is going to give
us the position of that value on the right.
All right either way right now it's going to be very clear.
So then I'm going to create a viable that is going to be called New checked and you checked and it's
equal to.
And again we make us on the range.
Just an empty array and we put everything inside we have inside check.
So if we had previews values we're going to create a new viable and put a check.
So again this one is just like this one you're just creating a new place so we don't mutate this again.
So if open and close we're going to do a conditional.
So now we need to evaluate this because whenever we handle toggle we could be adding the value to the
array or removing it from the array.
So if the current index is equal to minus 1 It means that it's not on the list because you're getting
a negative number.
It's not on the list.
So what we do.
We access this new checked that at the beginning of course it's an empty array but later if we have
a more checkboxes checked we will have some values and we're going to push the value to that list.
All right.
And if not we need to remove it because if it's a positive number it means that we already have that
value on the list.
So what we do we enter new checked and we do as plys.
Now with this place what you want me to do is to pass the position of the value we want to of course
delete and would index off if it's a positive number is the position of that.
So we passed the current index and then we say we want to remove one entry.
Just one entry.
If you put two or more is going to start on that index and it's going to delete the next two.
That's why we always need to put one.
If you want to delete one.
All right.
And then what we do we do this not set state open and close and we pass the new state of things because
we have new values.
All right.
So of course this is going to work.
But behind the scenes but you're not really going to see this if I click it.
Of course we are clicking this but nothing happens.
And it's because we are adding things to state.
But right here the check it's always false.
So we need to enter to the you know to the state that checked and check that we have that value.
And if we do set it to true.
Right.
OK.
This that state that checked dot and we can find the index off.
So if we do have the value I.D. We are using right here remember that we always pass the value and we
get this from the map if we can find this value inside the array of this that checked it means that
the value is true.
We that check box it's checked.
So this one will be true of course if you're not finding it is going to be false.
So what we're going to be doing is going to be going to say if it's not equal to minus one.
So if the element of course is not on the array this one will be true.
Right.
I'm sorry it's on the rate it's going to be true.
If it's not on the array This one is going to be fault false.
So if I save this and go right here I'm going to do this and not really working.
Maybe I made a mistake.
That say that check in off the value I.D..
Let me just check what went wrong.
Maybe I did.
Oh of course.
This is not new.
You checked.
It's going to be checked.
They stayed right here the name it's checked it's not checked.
I'm just adding something to the state and I don't one that I want to say the check.
It's now equal to new checked.
All right.
Sorry for that.
So now if we check it it works and if I uncheck it it works one more time.
It's so like different values.
All right everything works or I mean.
So now we have a we have one more problem.
Whenever we are we are checking things right here.
We are of course again changing the state of this component.
The collapsable component the check box component but we are not really doing anything on the parent
component and that's why actually we need to go to make the net the network request and pass the filters
and everything else.
So if I do this console log device first inspect what we are getting.
So I'm going to say you checked me bring the inspect go to console.
If I click it we get one because his defender that is the offender.
If I do more we get an array with all the values that we are checking checking.
So what do we need do we need to grab this list and send it to read to the parent component.
And if you remember we have the handle filters for this right now.
Not doing anything.
But if we pass the filters we call the go to this problem.
We passed the filters as an argument.
This handle filters will be receiving the array of IDs and it knows that this is from a brand.
So we will need to do some logic right here to store it someplace.
All right let's do it right now.
I'm going to go right here.
I'm going to say that we need to go to this stock probs and you could do it right here.
Or you could do it on the callback of the state.
You have the ability to do that.
So this that prompts Dot and I believe we call it handle filters.
Let me copy to the mistakes and the filters and are going to be passing whatever I get from new checked.
Now instead of here we will get some arguments.
You know the filtered arguments so I'm going to say filter's coma category and I'm going to do some
cons. look for the filters just to make sure we are getting everything correctly.
So let's try again.
And if I click it we get the rights Breguet.
So let me check if this went long now that we get we've got to go.
So now of course we could just copy the same code right here and do something else because we have more
checkboxes if we go.
And these closes if you go to the final we have Fretz we have once and everything else.
So then we just need to kind of manually do this.
So I'm going to copy this one they're going to go right here at the bottom.
So the second one it's going to be for four frets.
Right.
And actually we do not have frets right.
We don't have frets because they don't come from the server.
This one is coming from the server but Fretz we don't have a place on the server where we're going to
be hosting this so we can host it on a viable.
Right.
But first I'm going to I'm going to change the balance right here.
This one is going to be Fretz this one instead of products that brand are going to call it Fretz cinnamon
y and this one it's going to be Fretz.
OK.
So the initial state for this one and change it to false.
So from where we can get the frets.
Again I'm not going to do.
And we are now going to host something on the server where we can have just for values where we can
do can add a viable inside misc or someplace where we set the amount of Fretz.
Right.
Really simple.
So I'm going to call it fixed categories.
So I'm going to go to you Eutelsat and are going to add it to form because most of the times we will
be using this insight forum.
So your file fixed underscore category as the Jazz suffix categories is just an array of real values.
So I'm going to say Konst frets opening close an array of objects.
Now again just like we did before.
We need an ID and we need a name.
So underscore ID and why am I doing this because we're not really getting it from Mongo.
The thing is that on the clock checkbox we always make reference to show the checkboxes to underscore
ID so I need to respect the same keys if not of course not going to work.
So 20 coma and I going to be adding a name and 20.
Now this ones are to the amount of Fretz.
Now maybe if you're not really related to guitars but of 20 frets it's not very it's not very common.
You could have 21 frets on very old guitars.
I have a guitar from the 70s real expensive guitar.
You know it's a classic guitar and it has 21 frets but it's not very common.
Most of the time you're going to get 22 frets on you know modern guitars and you're going to get 24
guitars.
Most of my guitars they have 24.
I like the extra uptake on this but that's OK.
You know it's completely up to you.
So now we have the frets.
So now of course we need to import it at the top so we can make a reference to that viral so important
and we can bring Fretz and it's going to be from DOT DOT forward slash you tels for Slash form for Slash
and then fixed categories.
OK.
That is good.
So now since we have Fretz and we are making a reference to Fred if we go right here.
Let me just reload it.
We should be getting it.
I don't know what we are not getting it and I'm pretty sure I know why.
Maybe you know I'm not going to tell you.
Just think for one second why is my mistake.
Got it.
No.
I created a viral and and I'm not exporting it.
So I'm going to go at the top export Fretz.
All right.
So now should be working.
It's going to reload.
And if we go to France we get the amount of France that is get.
And this of course also work if I go round here and check the 20 on the console we get the arrays of
the you know whatever we are checking.
And same thing with the ID.
All right.
That is get.
So what else do we have.
We have woods and the woods.
We do have this from the server.
We get it from prop's inside redux.
So I'm going to go to the index.
I'm going to go right here at the bottom.
Get a copy the one for brands and paste it right here.
OK.
So what's it's going to be called words.
Well and include what.
And then products and then what's something right here.
The filter called Get it called what.
All right.
If I save it
because as we get good and we get it from the server forget.
So now again we have a tiny it's not a problem.
It's actually how it works.
And I going to show you what we're going to be doing.
So if we check something we get you know the ID for an array for IDs from the from the brands that I
get if I go to Fretz we get a different.
We are not replacing replacing a rates.
This is a different rate.
The only difference is that this was this one is for Fretz.
If I go to once we get the ID for it the Basswood.
Now notice that on the brands I have to if I click one more we have three.
So you know there are different rates.
So when we make the request to the server we need a way to tell the server that we want to filter using
multiple things.
Right.
Because that's the idea.
We're going to go to the server and tell the server we want to do multiple What we want to return a
single operation a single array of objects but with multiple things OK.
So we need to pass to the server multiple instructions.
So I'm going to create a state and we're going to use more things right here in the state.
I'm going to do it right now.
I'm going to say grid.
I can do it like this.
That grid is going to be this we have at the top that initial state of this if it's empty.
Of course the default is this one.
But if we do have a value we're going to change it to that.
Are we're going to go back to that march much later then we're going to have a limit of six coma going
to have a skip of zero and we're going to go back to this later.
We are not going to do this right now.
Filter filters open.
And this is going to be an array of objects.
Now we have four different categories.
We have Rantz brand open and close an array of objects we have Fretz claw open an array of objects than
we have would open an array of objects and then we can have something called price.
Right.
And the prize again an array of objects.
So at the end when when we make when we go to that drought that we don't have we don't have that round.
We're going to be passing adjacent file.
You know Jason with the filters and from within the server on that route begin again.
Jason I'm going to say OK what do I get.
Do you have Brandt's for filtering.
Well yes you have two types of friends you have two IDs.
OK.
So when I go and go and find the data are going to search for only for this brands do we have Fretz
Yes.
OK.
So I'm going to search for Fretz as well.
Brandts and Fritz do we have would no is an empty array.
OK so I am not going to add what to the mix.
Do we have prices.
Yeah.
It's between zero and $1000.
OK so I'm going to search for all the brands with this values all the frets with this values and within
the range of price.
So that is it that which is going to be passing an array with an array of objects with instructions
that are on the server we going to filter and make the actual you know action.
But for now of course we need a way to send the values we get to the filters on the state and we are
going to do it on hantle filters now handle filters can do this.
We have a category that we're not going to really use right now because of all of the checkboxes are
the same.
The only one that is going to be a little bit weird it's the radio that we're going to do this on the
next section.
So on the handle on the Hendel filters we're going to do Konst new filters and it's going to be equal
to dot dot dot.
There's that state that filters.
So we're just making a copy of filters so we don't mutated.
So I'm going to enter new filters.
I'm going to open it going to be passing the category.
Right.
The category we get right here.
That's that's how we are able to go to the state and purchase values on a particular category then we're
going to use it for a different thing.
But for now it's good.
So I'm going to say OK so we're going to go inside that category and we're going to put inside whatever
we get back on filters.
You know that array of objects.
All right.
And then of course what are we going to be doing.
Is did this data set state opening close and then filter filters equals to whatever we have inside New
filters.
All right now I'm going to do console log.
There's that state and I'm going to go RIGHT HERE.
Now if I click on Fender now we have filters on brand we have LMB do this better.
Is this that state that filters just like this.
It's a little bit better of course when the application loads we have nothing any fight click.
We have brands and we have one.
Maybe then we're going to select I want to see all the Basswood guitars.
So we have two categories to search the brands and by what same thing would Fretz well.
Okay.
So this works of course we need to do a lot more a lot more after we said the state of filters begin
to run a different function to make the actual request to you know this Patchi action.
But we are not there yet.
First we need to do the price with the radio boxes the the radio and this is a new reusable component
just like checkboxes.
So we need to do a lot of things right here.
So let's go to the next section and do the radio.
We still need to do a lot of things but we are almost almost done on done.