All right so now we are going to be creating the radio component.
OK.
Just like with the collapse checkbox we need to do a lot of things but we're not going to spend a lot
of time on the collapse radio because a lot of the things we haven't collapsed checkbox begin to be
we're using them so we're going to do a lot of copy paste.
OK.
So we're going to go to you tell us your file collapse radio that.
Yes of course the radio itself is different and the collapse checkbox but you know the functions they
pretty much look the same everything else.
So the Columbus radio will be a re-act class based component so I'm going to create it right now collapse
radio whenever whatever.
There we go.
So import import collapse and I'm going to do it just like this collapse and then radio from DOT DOT
forward slash you tels for Slash.
And that collapse radio of course.
Right now we need to call it.
So I'm going to copy this one and paste it at the bottom and I'm just going to change the name tag.
So collapse radio the initial state will be the same but this one is going to change it to True and
I change this one to false.
That's correct.
So the title of course needs to be something else because now we are working working with prices.
So this one is going to be price list and this one is a little bit weird.
I'm going to say price now.
We didn't have this list.
We're going to create it from fixed categories.
So inside handle filters will be we will be handing price.
All right now let's go to fix ecoterrorists because we need to add them manually.
I'm sorry for this but we need to do it.
And in the meanwhile I'm going explain you because the array of objects it's a little bit weird.
So price equals an array of objects.
The first one just like the other ones will have an underscore ID right on and square ID when you know
right now zero.
And this is just the ID.
We have many values.
One two three four five six.
So will have ID 0 1 2 3 4 5 6.
Right.
Then we have a name and the name is what its going to be get.
Getting this played right here.
So we need a name.
All right name and the name in the on the first one is any because of course at any price then we have
a problem.
So if we think about this for one second whenever we select a category from the collapse checkbox we
pass the value we have in site name or the value we have inside ID as get actually the ID but we can
pass zero because when we go to the server what are we going to say we want to bring all the products
with a price zero or and then zero to 1 or 2 1 to 2.
Well thats not going to happen you know we have a problem there.
So what are you going to do going at an array.
So I'm going to say re open and close and the first one is going to be empty because we are not filtering
by any kind of price.
I would copy this one and Im going to paste it at the bottom and this one will be id of one and the
values are going to change because now its from 0 2 and I don't know 300 right 300 could be ninety nine
or something like that and we make it look so it can make a little bit more sense.
Zero to two ninety nine.
Now when we go to the server to search you know a value from where to where we going to be passing an
array with two values.
The first one is going to be the from and the second one is going to be the two.
So again instead of parenting and ID when it comes to prizes we will pass the rate we can to go to the
server and search all the products with the price between zero dollars and 2 8:51.
Thats why we do on a rate.
All right.
And the same thing with the other ones so I'm going to copy paste the ID of this one.
Going to be 2 and it's from 299 2 and 8 9 2.
I don't know if 5 Nine-Nine makes sense actually sorry it's 300.
Because tonight 9 the next one is 300.
And the next one.
599 Okay.
And of course the array it's again 300 to 5 9 9.
So for that 5 9 9.
So then I get a copy.
I'm going to go right here and I can say name again five by nine.
This one is 600 and the next one it's going to be $999.
So this is a very good price for a guitar.
You know a guitar for this price is a good guitar.
Six hundred and then nine a 9 0 2 2 9 9 and 300 2 9 5 9 9 to $600.
Not a good price.
No it's a shitty guitar.
So don't buy it.
All right.
So in that coma we have the ID of number four and we have instead of 600.
We have what nine or nine.
It's going to be a thousand dollars sorry.
And we get to go to $2000.
So a guitar of $2000 is a professional guitar.
So if you have the money and you want to play guitar professionally that's what you need to spend.
Sorry for that.
Get a copy
and the next one it's the last one because more than two more than $2000 is a boutique guitar custom
shop guitar.
So we're going to go right here and say more than $2000.
All right.
So I'm going to say 2000 and right here we need to pass a value.
So I'm going to put a ridiculous amount of money.
All right so whatever it's up to a thousand dollars we going to get it.
OK.
So this is why we have the ideas 1 2 3 4 5 0 1 2 3 4 5.
So we have six type values.
Let me just make sure I type everything correctly 6 2 9 9 1 2 2 and then 2 2.
Yeah I think it looks nice.
Okay.
Sorry for this but we kind of need to do it.
So now I need to include it and I forgot to export it.
Price and we bring price.
So now the collapse radio will be getting a list of prices.
All right.
So let's keep moving forward on the collapse of radio.
We will need a bunch of stuff just like have with the collapse checkbox.
I'm going to put it right here.
I'm going to go at the top.
We will need the font awesome icon same icons.
So I'm going to copy.
I'm going to paste now I'm going to go right here at the bottom and we need a lot of things from here.
And we need to delete some of them so we will still list.
We will list a list item we will need.
And I'm just going to arrange this.
We will need let a list item text we will need the collapse is going to put it right here.
We don't need the list item the list item second reaction and we don't need to check box.
Of course we need to import some other things so import are going to say radio from opening close ad
material you ice core for Slash radio what else we need.
One more thing I'm going to copy so I don't have to type everything again.
So we need something that calls radio group which is going to ingroup all of the radios.
So radio group we have one more one more which is form control label.
So I'm going to say form control and then label label them that is good.
Let me make it right.
OK.
Form control label is correct.
And then for control label and that is it.
That's all we need.
One two three four five six seven.
Let's look at that that's all we need.
Now again just like with the collapse checkbox we need a state with the initial state of the collapse
which is going to be open falls and then instead of the checked remember that on radios we can have
only one value.
So instead of checked is going to be value of zero.
OK.
So right here we need the components around from member to handle the State of the.
You know if it's open or closed.
So we will do the same thing just copy and paste right.
And if we think about this we could create a component to show a collapsable and then inside create
a different component just for the radio checkboxes.
You could do that as well.
We still have a handle click.
So I'm going to copy the handle.
I'm going to go right here and paste it.
What else we do have a handle angle so and copy and paste it like it's all before you could just create
a single component check for the collapsable and inside maybe create a different component here here.
And you know maybe in the list and show a different list with checkboxes and the radio we could totally
do that.
So we have the handle angle and see what else we get and that's it.
That's it for now.
Everything else like the rental list and handle Tuggle.
This is going to be a little bit different from now on.
So I'm going to go again to collapse checkbox and I'm going to copy the complete list from the list
the way up for this and I'm going to paste it down here.
Of course we need to change some few things.
So we still have a list with the board there bottom right.
Remind me tomorrow man.
So we have a list item.
Again we triggered on the handle click and again we have a list text which is the title and the handle
angle that stays the same.
The class is still a collapse time at outgo an amount on it.
Same same idea.
We still have a list inside.
But what's going to change is what we get inside the list.
Right.
So if now I just put whatever doesn't matter when I put an and we go to our component and we make this
a little bit smaller.
I go to Price I toggle and works and notice that on the render we get it open because that was what
we passed.
That's a property right here.
Initial State.
Get.
So now we need to create the radio.
And for this one.
Remember that the radio we can get only one value so all the radios are pretty much you know into one
right they are all related.
That's why radios work.
So first we need to use that radio group.
We've imported the top so radio group and opening close.
Now we need to pass some properties here some default properties.
We need the area label and this one is going to be prices this is just from material.
Then we need to pass a name so the name is going to be priceless right.
And then we need to pass a value whenever we check something inside of here different radios.
They bailed Baalu is going to be the same.
So value bound you equals to whatever we have inside this that state that value.
And then of course we need to handle the change just like what they did with the arm with the checkbox.
So we need to pass the on change and the change is going to be this not handle angle no handle change.
We don't have this function of course we will add it going at it right now and then of course we cannot
complete this will change just a function open to close.
OK.
So inside of here will have a list.
This is what we can do right now.
I'm going to say this render and then list opening close.
Now let's go to this function right here.
I'm going to put it on the top of handle change.
So this render list is going to be a function that at the end is going to be returning something.
And what we will we will be returning is some GSX so parenthesis.
So first we need to enter to this that props up list and make sure we have a list to render if we don't
we don't do anything.
Then of course we need to loop.
This prompts the list and then we do a map just like we did with check boxes and on each iteration we
will get a value.
And remember if you have one there's no need to do this.
It just can do it like this.
And of course again we still want to render some GSX so parenthesis.
Now what are we going to be using to render the radios.
Is the form control level.
That's why we brought it up top.
So inside of this we will return this form control label.
Right.
Can open and close.
Now of course this form control label needs a lot of properties so I'm going to go right here.
The first thing is is the key.
So we going to be passing the value underscore ID as a key then we need a value.
The value is going to be equal to whatever we get.
And again I'm going to be passing strings on a string if not going to get an error.
So I'm going to be pozna again banlieue underscore ID.
All right.
That we need the actual control and the actual control.
It's what it's going to be rendered at the end.
So control equals to what and it's going to be the radio.
That's why you're bringing this at the top.
And it's the only one that it's not used.
So radio control is going to be past this.
Of course is a component because it is a component and then of course we need to use the label label
open in close value that name that is ZID.
So let's see what we get.
If you go to our Ok we are rendering everything that is good.
But we are getting a failed pop typing ballot prop numbers supplied to where you're OK.
So if I go to read your group or here I'm sitting at this that state that values so we need to pass
trng right here.
We cannot use a number.
This is how this works.
So they're passing a value of a number.
So what I do I just changed it to a string.
As a matter right now so the application will reload.
No error anywhere.
That is good.
So we have any zero and everything else of course.
Everything works OK.
Now what we need to do we need to do next is we need to do the handle change because if we go right
here we are saying that every time we do something we do they handle change.
We have this function but it's not doing anything.
So what do we do.
And the thing that we need to do is to grab the value right here.
We got the value from the radio group and we said at this stage that value and that is it.
So I'm going to go to the handle change and say this that said state opening close and now the value
is equal to what whenever we do the unchanged.
This one will be passing an event and the event contains the idea of whatever we are selecting.
So we going to catch that event right here and you could do it like this.
You know we have a single argument and the value is equal to event that target that value that is at.
Let's right again or I.
So if I select 300 we get it we get it and everything is good.
All right.
So now inside of the state of course we're getting the value of whatever we are selecting right.
And that is good but of course this is happening inside this component.
And I want to delete this I forgot to let this sorry goodbye.
So we need to go to the grab the value of whatever we are doing and go to the parent component to the
handle filters and pass the value.
All right.
So I'm going to go here and say this that props that handle and I believe it called handle filters handle
filters handle filters.
Open and close and we pass whatever we get inside the valley so event the target value target.
All right so this component it's pretty much done.
There's nothing else we need to do right now.
Now what we need to do we need to go to the parent component and check what is happening inside this
filters because now inside the handle filters whenever we go to this function with the price we are
saying OK we want to put something inside the filters with just one boom value.
And if you remember the value it's not the actual array the value is the number it's 1 0 or the idea
of whatever we are looking right here.
So it's 5 1 0 and you know and that.
So we can i need to fix that.
OK.
So let's go to back to index and we're going to go to handle filter's.
So what we need to do now is go to this fixed prices find the ID of I don't know maybe zero we have
zero value.
We go to zero and we know that is nothing.
So the array will be empty.
If you have three we go and the array with this one.
So what we need to do is you know go to that bring it and then merge it with what we have right here
on the filters.
So I going to say I'm going to make space I'm going to say if opening close category category yes equal
triple equals price.
Remember we are passing the category right here.
What are we going to do.
We cannot let price values in and say create a barbell and say this dad handle price you're going to
do this in a minute.
Of course we don't have this function and handle price is going to be equals to the filters which is
going to be the value of the ID.
No one two three four five and once we get this from this function we're going to create it.
Right now we're going to enter new filters and we're going to say again pretty much the same with it
before new filters.
Category equals then prize values.
All right.
Now of course we don't have this handle price could be handle prices no matter how the price is going
to go right here and say handle price.
So like I told before we need to go to the array of the initial prices array of objects find Yadi and
bring the value which is the rate so going to say concert data equal price that we have a top price
target.
So once we do that I'm going to create an empty array so array it equal to nothing.
Then of course I'm going to do a good old for a loop so let key in data.
So once we do this what we need to do.
OK.
If we can find the same key or inside data which is the prizes of Ray I want to bring it and stored
inside a rate so data we grab the key and we access the idea.
All right.
And that is equal to 1 2 3 and are going to convert everything to number because we are actually using
numbers and whenever we come from filters we are getting a string.
So I need to do Par's and open it close and we do value coma and we need to use the 10 because if not
begin to get an error message.
All right.
That is get some insight if you're going to enter the array.
I'm going to say whatever.
If we find this of course whatever we have inside of here are going to make it equal to that array.
So we say data and key and we're just going to copy this dot and I'm going to bring the array value
remember that here we have the array.
So whenever we find a match we grab whatever we have inside the array and we set it equal to a rate.
And at the very very end I'm going to say return rate.
So the result of this the values is going to be that a rate that matches the ID right.
That of course we added to the categories of prices.
In theory this could should be working.
I'm getting an error with banlieue.
Maybe I made a mistake right here.
I'm not passing of course the value.
Right.
The value we get from this handle the price.
All right.
So let's check it out.
If I click it we get something else.
And now notice that we have a price with an array of the 300 to 5 9:9.
If I change it we get 0 2 2 9 9.
If I select all four brands we are still getting it right.
So now we have pretty much all the logic we need right here to make a request to the server and send
this this on as a Jason.
Right.
So we can catch it on the server of course on the next section we're going to do the request.
We can use redox forced to do the request and we need to go to server and create I'm proud because we
don't have it.
So let's go to the next one and start with that.