OK so the next thing we're going to do and it's kind of the complicated thing of this little one is
complicated but we need to do a few things we need to put this patch in action and this action is going
to get all the filters all the things that we need right here.
For example in the end of the top we have the limited escape and everything else we need to put all
together.
We need to go to a new route that the going to be creating inside server.
And of course whenever we get a response we will go to that reducers and then we will feed the list
right here.
So we need to do quite a few things.
So I'm going to promote close everything are going to close everything.
Right.
And I'm going to go back to shop I'm going to open shop because we need it I'm going to go to actions.
I'm going to bring product actions are going to go to the reducer because we can meet product producer
and I'm going to go to the server and need needed.
All right.
So first let's go to the index.
Now what we need to do is to create a couple of actions we need to create actually one action is going
to be called get products to shop.
So I'm going to call it get products to and then shop.
And what happened.
Product products too.
And then shop to get products to shop.
Of course we don't have this inside action so this will fail of course.
I'm going to save it and I'm going to go right here and I'm going to go to products and export function
called get products to shop which is you know going to be just a function.
And for now we are not going to do anything.
Of course we need to create the time for this.
So I'm going to go right here at the top and say Get over it.
It's two.
And then shop.
All right.
We didn't have the.
We need to add it.
So we're going to copy copy that type go to the products section and export Konst get products to shop
and get products to shop.
Very good.
This is done now out of the way.
OK.
Now we need to go to the reducer import the type and for now you're just going to do something simple
case.
We get products to shop.
I want to return opening closed door.
That is going to return to state.
For now she's going to return the same thing.
All right.
So now of course now we have an action right.
It's not doing anything but we do have an action so I'm going to copy this.
And again explain what we can do.
We're going to dispatch in action and this action will contain pretty much everything we are doing right
here because whenever we make a request to the server we need to tell the server OK how many elements
how many results in the database we want to get back from the server.
So we need six for an on each load.
We're going to get 6 so we can add one to three and one two three just like we are getting right here.
And we do it like this one two three and one two three.
And then we just load more than we need to set the skip why we are using a skip because later are we
going to use a load more.
So if we want to get six more we're going to say OK go to the database get the next six starting from
where.
Right.
Just get me all of this but skip the first six.
Bring me everything from the beginning.
Skip the first six because you already have it and bring the next six.
That's why when you're using the skip and then we just need the filters because whenever we filter something
we need to do some logic on the server telling.
We need to get the next six but use this filters.
All right.
So we need to pass off a sense now whenever the application loads the sexual loads we need to bring
some products by default so we can do it on the component amount.
So I'm going to go here and say this that probs that this patch just goes like this and I'm going to
say get products to shop.
Now of course we need to pass all these arguments.
So I'm going to go right here and I'm going to say OK I want to pass that this state.
That's Kip Coleman.
I went to pass the limit.
So does that state that limit coma.
I went to pass the filters.
Does that state that filters.
So now this function does get perks to shop will be getting all the arguments.
Of course we need to go to get products to shop.
And you know that's going to go to the products action actions that are going to go over here.
Now this one of course will be getting arguments.
First one is the skip.
Second one is the limit.
The third one is the filters.
Now make sure that sometimes we are not going to get get any filters.
So by default I get to make it to nothing.
And later much later and beginning come back to this later we're going to have a previous state just
like this going to get back to this.
For now you just put it right there.
We're not going to really use it right now but put it.
All right.
So I'm going to go right here and say Konst data opening close.
I'm going to say OK I'm going to a fixed object with all of this properties inside and this data is
getting is the one that it's going to be submitted to the server.
Just like a data to submit so we pass the limit.
We pass this TKIP and we pass the filters just like this filters out let me fix it right here.
It's pleural filters.
All right.
Then of course we need to do our request.
So Konst request equals to X Yeo's that post open and close and we make a request to products and server.
Right.
And the route for this is going to be shop.
We don't have this route.
We're going to create it in a minute.
And what we passed is whatever we have inside data with the filters to limit and this cap this could
get much much longer.
But for now it's good.
An now after we get the date of course we will get a promise so we're going to say then open and close
and we will get a response from the server.
So whenever we get a response what we want to do we want to return something now from the server you're
going to get two things we're going to get an object with two things inside a size of how many articles
were received.
And again just like previous state we're going to discuss that later.
And you know the articles the articles that we need some of the articles are going to be inside responds
that data that articles are going to said that on the server and the size is going to be inside responds
that data that size.
OK.
So instead of doing this I'm going to return open and close and I'm going to return to size and the
articles now the size again responds that data dot size and they make a little space and then we get
a response that data dot articles we could set this directly from the from the server.
But again we're going to do several stuff.
This is going to change in the next couple weeks or maybe in the next few minutes.
So.
OK.
So from the server we get something with the size of the articles and something with the actual articles.
So this is what we return from the request of course with redox we need to return something.
So we're going to return pretty close type with the get products to shop around get products to shop
coma and a payload and the payload it's equal to size and articles.
Right.
Whatever we get from the server so request now the server will be getting.
I'm sorry.
The reducer will be getting this.
So we're going to go to that reduce or so inside of the products to shop.
We're going to get now two things.
So I going to say coma and I'm going to make a little bit of space right here so it's a little bit better.
So of course we returned to pretty we just whatever we have in the state and I'm going to create two
keys to shop and to shop cise.
Now the shop size is going to get it's going to be really important later.
So on the shop we will just put whatever we get back from the server inside payload DOD articles.
You know this are the complete articles and to size is going to be size so action that payload data
size and again we will back to that little bit get back to this.
All right.
So now we are pretty much ready for the actions we are making a request to shop to this and we are trying
to get something.
Of course we are not going to get anything.
That's why we get at four or four because the route doesn't exist.
So we are going to go to the server.
All right.
And I'm going to go right here at the top.
So we need to create a new route so app that post because we are listening for a post request and it's
inside API for Slash product for Slash and then shop then a coma request and response.
And this is not a private route right just the public route so request coma and response.
And I'm using a post because we are listening for something for Jason data.
That's OK.
Doesn't matter.
So what are we going to do.
First we need to get all the filters.
You know the data that we're getting from this right here.
The limit the skip and the filters.
So we need to create a set of Barville so we can catch them.
And in the future we might be getting some other things maybe the order it's descending or ascending
maybe we can add it later.
You know we're not going to really do it right now but maybe you want it later you want to filter by
something and you want to or there and it's sending or sending way right.
And the same thing with the ID maybe you want to fetch something and instead of ordering everything
by ID.
You went to or there or by I don't know the price.
Yeah whatever.
So we're going to set that marble right here.
I say let.
Other.
And this is going to look pretty much familiar.
It pretty much the same right here.
Right here we are using queries but now we are using Jason data.
So request that body because we are have to get Jason and then we get the order and if we do have an
order we're going to set this value to whatever we get inside inside the inside the order if not by
default is going to be descending.
Same thing with the sort.
BI So let sort by and sort by it's equal to an exact copy of this request that body dot sort by right
and I make it it made it a capital should be capital.
And of course if you get a sort by the value of this is equal to sort by.
If not we always search by ID and get changed to this.
All right so now we have to sort by then of course we need the real you know the what the arguments
you're getting.
You're really passing.
And there's one we can meet them.
So let me set the limit.
How many articles the server will return.
So if we do have a request we do have a body of limit we are going to return whatever we get from the
limit.
If not we can by default return 100 articles.
Maybe it's too much depends.
And this depends on your application how much articles you want to return.
By default then we have the skip.
So let let skip it calls to and right here on this cap we could do Richard Quest dot body dot skip.
All right.
Now we're going to have a prom.
Remember that for the limit and the skip inside Mungo or Magoo's we need this to be a number just like
this.
So we need to wrap everything in parse and open and close and then we close it.
And the same thing with the skip.
It needs to be a number.
So parse it and we make it a number.
All right.
What do we have next.
We have the filters we have the skill limits we have to skip So now we need the filters.
And this is going to be it's going to be a little bit weird because the filters they come in a kind
of an array with an object with keys and values that are erased.
So we can really pass this to Mungo right.
What we need to do is we need to modify a little bit so find Arkes and this one is going to be equal
to an empty object.
So Mongo is going to accept as an argument to do the filtering.
An object with the keys and the values inside.
So what we need to do first we need to check if from the actual client from the request that we can
be getting if we actually do have some values to filter because maybe brand is going to be an empty
array.
So we're going to check right here.
If it's empty and if it's not empty of course if it's empty we will not add it to the fine arguments.
Kind of makes sense.
So I'm going to say for opening close now I'm going to enter.
Going to say Leti and enter the request a body that filters so request that body that filters.
Now if you don't want to do request a body every time you can create an alias and stored on a marble
you can do that.
This is of course Javascript.
So remember that the key is filters not filter.
Right.
So once we are inside we are looping all the filters we get you know for filters.
All right.
So on each iteration we want to enter the filter and check if they are empty if they are not empty we
are going to do something else.
Of course now I'm going to go right here and say request dot body dot filters and I can enter the key
and how do we check if the Keets empty or not.
You know the array of fetcher.
It's empty.
Empty or not.
We do dot and we do length.
It's just an array.
So we do it lenge backwards.
There we go.
And if it's greater than zero then we move forward and we start adding things to the fine arts.
Now if you remember the filters and let me show you right here the price is a little bit weird because
for the other ones we just get an array with values and we can pass that to a.
You know just get me all the Brant's with you know this array of values but the price is a little bit
different.
We cannot just pass this to Mongo.
We need to say this is the lowest.
And this is the highest number.
So we need to actually set that.
So instead of here are going to say if opening close and else.
So if the key of this one that we're checking right now it's equal to price we're going to do something
if not we're going to go to the default case and the default case would be entering find arcs adding
the key of this loop and saying OK the key of this it's equal to whatever we get from request that body
that filters.
And they know that the key the key of this loop of course which in this case is going to be Brandts.
If it's not empty threats and would if of course they are not empty we are actually filtering right
here.
And of course if we get price we will do pretty much the same thing.
But with something inside it we will enter find arcs at the key with this case price and it's going
to be equal to an object.
So for this one we need to pass an object.
OK.
So how can we tell Mongo inside of an object to look for the greater and the lower then.
So we use a dollar sign and we do GTY.
Now if we do G.T. which is greater it will start checking.
Starting from this number let's say 300 but it's not really 300 it's going to start from the next number.
Three hundred and one and there is a problem because maybe we are we have guitars with the price of
three hundred and Mungo it's not going to be looking for 300.
It's going to start from the next number which 3 0 which is 3 0 0 1.
So how we can fix this.
We use the this the e is greater greater than an E or something like that.
And then we do a.
And right here we need to pass the Greater Than what.
So we have it inside request the body that filters open it close and we pass the first position of the
array which is the starting point.
So we enter the key and we pass the first element on the array.
There are going to do coma and same thing for the lower then.
So it's LTE and we have it.
So request that body that filters we add the key and then I'm going to say OK I won the first position.
All right.
So now I'm going to go right here at bottom and I mean you can really do anything.
I'm just going to send the response of a status of 200.
Of course everything is going to fail but it doesn't matter right now.
I'm going to do console log and begin going to see what we get on the terminal.
So console log find ARX.
All right.
So let me see.
Maybe you are going to get me going to get a nerf from from redux but that's OK.
So right now we are getting something and if we go to the server OK we get nothing.
And that is ok because all the filters are not really applied.
We when we make a check nothing really happens.
And if I go over here nothing really happens because on the our application we are not triggering anything.
After we make a change on the filters but that is OK.
We are getting the actual values on the server.
Are getting this.
And we are filtering the data on server correctly right.
We don't have any value so we will return an empty object.
So there is that we have no filters.
All right.
So now let's let's let's make the actual request this is in part going to go right here.
And since we want to sorry we want to find products are going to say products product.
And remember this product it's a reference to this to the model.
Right.
OK.
So I needed to do this.
So once we enter products we need to find something.
So I'm going to say find opening close.
And what do we need to find.
We need to find to find Ark's passing this object mongoose.
It's going to actually take it that are going to go right here at the bottom.
Remember that we need to populate whenever we get the results we need to change the ID of France and
the idea of would just like with it right here.
So I'm going to copy and paste.
All right.
Next it's going to be the sort we need to decide.
So by and the other side the sort by and the other is going to be descending ascending and begin to
show it by what.
So we're going to go right here at the bottom and we use the sort.
If you asked me Mangu Mongo Indigos I really love them.
They are really really good and easy to use.
So we passed first to sort by as an array and then it takes an array of the order and it's going to
take it remember that we need to use the skip right now.
We are not really skipping because we are pretty much fetching everything all the results from the zero
right from the first article.
So we use skip opening close and we pass skip which is right now is going to be zero later.
We're going to change it of course and we go to the next line of code.
We have a limit how many articles we want to bring in this case default.
We said it's six.
Now the default here the default on the products action right here filters and right here we are saying
that we want to bring sex.
So it's going to preexists.
All right than Dot.
And now we are ready to you know get the information get the data.
So we use that exec open it close and then we run a function.
Let me check if this section went ok with one to luck.
So I need to cut it.
He advised us to record because no less than no greater than 20 minutes.
So again it's slug.
So the only thing we need to do on the next lecture is to you know create the execution of this.
And we turn something back to the client real simple.
All right.
So let's go to the next one and continue this.