OK so let's continue this.
Whenever we get this we pass a set of instructions we're going to get an error and we're going to get
the actual articles right.
OK.
If we do get an error we're going to return return a response of status opening close of 400 because
we get an error and going to send error.
Of course if everything goes OK we're going to rent We're going to rest.
And the response of status opening close of 200 which means that everything goes OK.
And the response is going to be a Jason and instead of the Jason if you remember the reducer it's expecting
an article and a size.
So I'm going to go right here I'm going to say OK.
So the size of this it's equal to articles Dot and I going to get that length of this.
And again we will get back to this later.
We will need it.
The only thing we do is to tell the send the response and tell how many articles are actually returning.
If it's a 6 or it's less.
And right now it could you a tip.
So articles are going to say articles articles is going to be equal to articles.
Right.
We are just sending the articles.
So now the producer will be getting this response.
So we should be getting something at least from the server on an unload.
So I'm going to go right here to the state and we go to products and we have to shop with the first
six articles.
Right.
And then we have the two shop size which is equal to sex Burgman.
So we are kind of getting this right.
Of course we just get the first six on the database.
All right.
And it's by default again it's descending.
So it's bringing the first the new ones.
All right.
So now what happens if we apply a filter.
I'm going to go to this and we don't have that logic so far.
So when this is going to happen and I'm going to delete the console log right here because it's bothering.
OK.
So of course we need to trigger this whenever we make change on the filters.
So they handle filters will be a place to you know trigger this idea.
All right.
So whenever we make a change to filters and of course we set the filters are going to do does not show
filter red or something like that results and are going to be passing the new set of filters because
at this point whenever we make a change we have new filters inside of the state.
Right.
So when it copy the name of the function and I'm going to go right here at the bottom and I'm going
to say that this one is just a function opening close.
And of course.
All right.
So the only thing we need to do here is to dispatch the same action we have right here but with different
data ride with different state because now the state of philtres is going to be different.
So pretty much we just need to trigger the same action.
So I'm going to copy this because I want to type it again and I'm going to go right here now.
We need to change a few things because whenever we filter something it means that are starting again
from scratch maybe the user clicked the offender.
Right.
And so the server goes and Frank brings all the articles with Fender and maybe they have I don't know
200 articles with Fender.
Right.
And then OK when they say I want to get fender and I have a..
So the server needs to start from scratch.
It cannot skip any values because we need to bring again from the zero the first six from the zero of
the pen there.
And Ivan its results.
So we need to reset the skip back to zero.
It's going to start from the scratch.
The limit is going to be the same and the filters are going to be whatever filters we are passing right
here.
So we're going to pass this as an argument filters and that this that state that filters not anymore
is going to be filters.
All right.
We'll be sorry.
And then of course since we are resetting skip maybe maybe later again maybe the user had its cause
has to skip off.
I don't know.
Twenty.
So after we dispatched this we are kind of resetting that state.
So we're going to do.
Then and only then after we of course we get the new articles we are going to graph this state this
that said state opening close and we're going to set that cap back to zero.
All right.
So in theory sorry we should be getting something are going to save it.
I'm going to reload it.
And of course we are getting inside of the state the articles right.
Usually the default articles.
Now I'm going to click on fender and we're going to check the state again.
So right here we have something else.
It says that the shape size now it's two.
So the server is just ringing.
It's just bringing two different results.
Right.
So I go to shop and we removed all of this and now the state it's something else.
It's something different.
It's difficult to state.
We have to shop and we get two articles.
And this one's our funder of course we don't see that.
We see the the the idea of the brand.
Right here we have a DVD out there we got we get fender and the next one of course is going to be fender
as well so brand fender.
All right.
What happens if we select buy wood.
I know that this would for example it's Basswood.
Let me check the other one.
The other one the other wood it's mass whatso.
Yeah.
Well it's not going to work.
This one has 22 frets this went 22.
OK just let me try to find something unique on this one.
This one is the price of 600.
And the other one is the price of let me find it.
The price of one.
All right.
So what we can do we can go to Price and try to filter that.
So if I do tune only to zero from zero to 99 we're going to get one result right.
That's the logic.
So we get one we solved on the difference and if I go here we get only one result.
So from the server we're getting that correct response a price point we get only one result.
So from the server again we are getting the correct response.
So the filters are really working.
Now the next thing is going to be catching this results.
We get from redux and this playing the cards right here.
And later we're going to go back of course to all this logic on the reducers and everything else to
create the load more because of the load more we're going to need to use that cap and that limit so
we need to modify some bad news and do some a little bit of logic.
It's not going to be really hard to get.
Let's go to the next section and start with the carts right here.