All right so let's try to render something here you know render the carts first.
So OK so I'm going to do the following.
I'm not going to I've just rendered the cards.
I'm going to close and close everything inside of a different component called load more carts because
maybe in the future this is of course I haven't decided yet this yet.
Maybe instead of doing the load more I will show you a different component.
But with pagination and of course we need to change them.
Some other things to do pagination instead of a lot more but I could add it as MOTOS as a bonus or not.
So I'm going to enclose everything into a new component.
I'm going to go to shop creating new filed code load more and then cartes.
Yeah why not.
Cartes capital C cartes dodginess the load more cards is going to be ever yakked stateless component
for now.
Could be could be a class based component re-act stateless component.
There you go could be a class based component but yeah that's OK.
Load more cards.
Right.
Of course we need to include it at the top.
So I'm going to go over here the top and import load more cards from that forward slash load more carts.
All right.
Burguet so I'm going to go here and make a reference to this to this.
And of course I need to add more more things right here because in the right side we will have this
grid and this thing.
So I'm going to create the layout for this and we're going to do this at the end because it's you know
not really that important and it is just something we add.
So I'm going to add a class name inside of right with shop options and instead of here are going to
add a new div with a class name.
Class of shop Gritz space.
I'm going to add it clear because I use floats for this one right now at the top.
Nothing is going to happen.
I'm going to say just Gritz.
Now after the Shub options I going add a new depth.
So I'm going to go right here and this is where we're going to be putting all the carts.
So I'm going to make a reference to load more carts.
Now of course we need to pass a lot of props.
We need that grid that we're using at the top right here that we are not really using right now but
to use it in a couple of minutes.
So I'm going to say grid opening close this that state that grid than going past the limit.
Remember that we need the limit so this that state that limit are going to be passing the size size.
And remember that we have this inside redux so prop products we are bringing in here products we are
going to bring products and then I believe we called it to shop size.
In short yes to shop size.
Right.
So we have the sites that we need the actual products of course products equals two products and we
call it to shop.
Right so its products to shop.
And then again to create a function which is going to be a lot more with a capital M load more equals
opening closed.
And this will be a function.
We don't have this function.
So for now I'm going to do console log load more.
We're going to do the load more at the end.
Okay.
So now we have this component that it's not of course it's not really doing anything.
Now of course you're catching the props and inside of the red the return of course we need to return
something.
So I can go inside the div.
And again to create one div at the top so to open it close.
Right here we're going to be rendering the carts.
Now if you remember we've kind of already use a container to render the carts at home.
Maybe you remember this one right here.
So we can not really use this one.
It's a little bit different than the one we need to use right here.
So we need to create again a reusable component that it's almost sink.
But of course we have a lot of changes.
So instead of going to go to your tills and creating a new file and this one will be Karl called Card
underscore blague pretty much the same thing.
BLOCK And then underscore and then shop that is the difference is a different file.
All right let's look at imported at the top.
So import card block and then shop with a capital S..
There we go shop from and dot dot for Slash.
You'll tell us your tails.
Sorry for slashing sales.
Forward slash and cart lock shop.
All right.
Burguet now going to make a reference to this and this component what it's going to be expecting it
is the grid which is the lay out we're going to be using on the cards and that this that props up sorry
its props not this it's props.
And we will be passing the grade we get from props.
And then of course we need the list.
So list equals props that props that list.
All right.
This is the only thing we need later right here.
We're going to be adding the load more button right here.
But we can do it later.
Not right now.
All right.
So this component is very very simple.
So of course now we need to do the card lock shop.
So let's go to card block shop.
So this component is going to be re-act stateless component.
Right.
Going to call it card block and then shop this one again will be receiving prompts.
And again it's just a simple a simple component that we need to pass the class name of the container
and card block and then shop OK.
Now inside of here I going to create a div container and we could receive a title.
I'm going to add it right now but maybe we want to add a title just like we did with the other component.
So you can actually pass this prop but I'm not going to really do the title right now.
I'm just going to create a new container and it's out of here.
Will we be getting the props that list.
So I got to say props that list.
So if we do are getting props that list from the from the props.
We're going to do something if not we're going to do something.
We're going to do something else.
All right.
Now if we do have props list could happen that maybe the user choose something where we don't really
have products.
So we need to tell the user.
Sorry.
Nothing was found or something like that.
So once we are into two propolis we are making sure that we do have that property.
So I'm going to enter to prompts that list.
And again to check the length so length and if it's equal to zero then we want to show a message right.
And if not we're going to say nothing.
And what I'm going to say it's something very simple Dave.
Opening close can attach a class name and no result and it's going to say no sorry no results.
Get if we of course if we do have something we're going to run a different function after this.
So I'm going to go right here and say render cards open and closed.
And I'm going to be passing the props that list.
Remember that inside promp we have the list and the grid.
OK.
So now instead of undercards Konst render cards it's equal to a function.
And of course we want to return some GSX and what we will be returning is the card component we have
right here.
We just need to map and return a card for each.
So I'm going to import cart from that that forward slash tails for a slash and then cart.
All right.
So can enter I'm going to say prompts that list and if we do have something we return something.
Now if we do have something I want to enter that prompts that list and I want to map.
Now whenever I map I can to get a card.
All the data about that card.
And we we turn some GSX at the end Burguet.
So what we return is the card.
So open close.
Card this card needs a key because we are looping something and this is react and I'm going to say that
begin to use the card underscore ID which is the ID of the actual article then going to go right here
and I'm going to say that dot dot dot and cart.
So whatever property I'm getting from the card you know the name the id the brands and everything else
are going to attach it to here and then are going to be passing the grid that begin to do much later.
So the grid and I are passing the probs dot grid
looks nice.
Let's see if we get something.
And we are not getting anything.
Let's see if I get a mistake honor maybe.
I'm pretty sure I forgot to do something.
That's OK.
All right well let me check what I forgot.
And drew back.
OK.
I'm sorry for this.
I made a mistake right here so I'm making reference to a lot more cars and passing products and right
here I'm sending list.
So this one should be products.
I'm going to save it.
It's going to reload and we get it you know we get the we get the carts.
Very good man.
All right.
OK.
So the next step is going to be doing the load more because right now by default we get the first six.
Right.
So whenever we get the we clicked the load more I went to get six digit results with the same properties
and arguments right here.
But you know the next six not this ones.
So let's see if I click on Fender.
We are getting from their friends.
So the filters are working.
Vendor Ivan us I get friends or Ivan us and remember that for example if I click Charvel Charvel or
Millie Jackson or something like that we we're going to get more than six results.
But the thing is that we only see sex you're not getting more results by default.
It's always 6.
Right.
And this is what we're going to be modifying on a lot more.
OK.
So let's let's go to the next section and do the load more.