OK so let's do the load more.
First I'm going to enclose everything going to undef then we're going to add a couple things.
But for now you're good to go.
So I'm going to say load then more and then container.
All right.
I'm going to wrap this inside of his pan and right here are going to say load more could be no capital
and load more so on I'm going to attach an unclick to this to this button because of course we need
to trigger an action.
Now if you remember whenever we include this component to load more carts inside of the parent component
we have a load more that triggers that function.
OK.
So the unclick is going to be equal to the props.
Of course to bar or UPS that load more.
That is it.
So now whatever we cook it is going to go and triggered this ride.
We should be getting at least a console lock.
And this is because of course the server didn't restart it and we are trying to catch something that
is good.
So if I go to load more we get a lot more if I click at the consulate.
OK.
So it's out of here we will trigger a function called of course something related to load more.
Right.
OK.
So this dot load more carts open and close to the function.
Right.
We don't have that function.
Let's add it right now.
So I'm going to go to load more carts.
This one is going to be equal to a function and blah blah blah blah blah blah Burguet.
So now what we need to do and this is a we are part of the load more carts whenever we load more could
happen that we are in a different place than this.
Right.
We have maybe the application loads.
All right.
We have six results on our screen.
If I click load more I don't want to replace this sex with another sex.
What I want to do is bring the next sex.
If you remember you have a skip and the skip starts at zero and the limit starts to six.
That's why we get the result from the zero result the first result on the database and we get from 0
6 that's why we get sex.
So the next time we click load more instead of starting from the zero on the database I want to start
from the sixth result and bring the next six.
So when we do what we click load more we need to change this skip right here to 6 and then the next
one is going to be tough tough on the next one is going to be 18 whatever.
All right.
So first I'm going to go right here and create create up Barville called Skipp.
And this one is going to be equal to this that state.
That's Kyp which is going to be a zero at the beginning.
I'm sorry it's going to be 6 because we are getting six results.
I'm sorry.
It's going to be zero.
Of course on the first time we load.
We can do this.
That state that limit.
So now skip is limited.
Now Skip is going to be equal to 6.
So the next time we would click it of course we're going to do something.
And at the end we will set the new state of Skip to 6.
So if we click it again you know for a second time now it's going to be six plus six.
So it's going to be 12.
So every time I click load more you're going at 6 and some 6 right.
So of course after we do this we need to you know make the actual request.
So I'm going to say this that prompts the dispatch opening close and begin triggered this get products
to shop.
Right.
So I'm going to go and get products to shop.
We could do all of this on a single function with some verbals and some conditionals and everything
else but I'd prefer to do it like this so it's a little bit clearer for you and for me and for me as
well for us because I'm explaining.
So of course we need to pass the script that is the first argument I'm going to say skip the second
argument is that this that state that limit.
Remember that we always need to pass the limit.
If not it's going to bring 100 and we don't want that.
Then we need to pass the filters because we might have filters.
So does that state that filters coma and now I'm going to add one more.
And this is what we did on the products action.
Remember we attach a previous state.
Right.
So we can use this one and I can explain in a minute why we are attaching the previous state.
So whenever we the application loads or maybe we make a filter or we filter something the state of the
application of the products we have right here is going to be inside of the store redux ricotta redux.
We have a few products right here inside to shop.
Now whenever I make a request I'm not going to bring from zero.
I'm going to bring the next six.
So if I just don't kind of mutate that list I'm going to be replacing sex with another sex sex.
So what I'm going to do I'm going to pass the previous the current list.
We have the current state are going to pass it to the year to the function.
And whenever we get the next six We're going to merge the old six with the new six and maybe later if
we click on load more on the previous state we can have 12 so we can merge the previous 12 with the
new six.
That is the idea.
That's why we are passing the previous state.
So this prompts the products dot to shop.
We are just passing everything we've got on the on the state on the store sorry.
And of course then what I want to do and to do that we're going to do then and I'm going to do something
that actually we need to do.
Not the next time we clicked load more it's not going to work I'm going to do this.
That said state and since we got a new state of KIPP right every time we do this we're going at six
to skip.
I'm going to pass the new state of Skip So the next time we click it instead of zero or 6 is going to
be 12 or 18 or whatever.
All right.
So now we need to make some changes inside to get products to shop.
So we're going to go to get products to shop because now we have a previous state and this it's not
going to really work.
Now what we need to do instead of just returning the response that data that articles that we get from
Iraq from the server.
We need to kind of do something first.
So I'm going to go right here at the top and create let new state and I'm going to create a single rate
array.
So what I'm going to do I'm going to first inside this rate put whatever we get from the previous state.
Now if we don't have anything by default it's an empty All right so nothing is going to get going to
nothing right here.
So OK.
So I'm going to do coma and now instead of here I want to attach whatever we get back from the server
so that that that response data articles.
So at the very end we're going to get everything that we get with the pre-state.
Right.
Could be nothing.
Or maybe something.
And then we just merge what we get back from the server.
So at the very end when we return to articles to the actual reduce or is a new state with more with
six articles or 12 or 18 or whatever.
OK.
So I'm going to save it and if we go to products reducer this is what actually we don't need to change
this one because we are already setting it to start to shop with the articles and we are actually doing
the all the logic right here.
OK.
So let's go right here.
I got to reload and.
OK.
We get the first six.
If I click it again we get the all the sex.
All right.
So it's been working.
So we have one two three you have six of course.
Seven eight nine ten.
All right.
Maybe we don't have that much articles inside products.
So one two three four five six and yeah that is.
That is why we are getting that kind of incomplete.
But that's OK.
I'm going to add some of the products and I give you the file so we can add much more products.
But again I'm going to take my time and begin to do it.
Am I going to do it a little bit later.
I'm going to take my time and you know make a better database because some of the names are really really
fake.
So I can enter a bunch of elements I'm going to give you that in a minute.
Now first before we just move forward because a lot more it's pretty much done.
We are done with this whole section to look for every time we click on the low bar.
If we get if we don't have more results inside of here they load more.
It's still showing.
So that is a problem.
If I click no more we are making the request.
But you know nothing really happens.
So what I need to do I need to hide the load more.
So I'm going to go to load more carts.
Now if you remember from the server we are returning a size.
So the second time we clicked the size is not sex.
Right.
It's not the actual limit.
It's going to be five.
It's less than the sex.
So we can we can actually do some logic right there.
I'm going to go here and I'm going to wrap everything inside of a check.
So I'm going to say OK if this props actually props this because this is not a class props that size
it's greater than zero greater than zero.
It means that we are getting results.
So we should display a lot more.
OK.
That's good.
This is not the problem.
And I'm going to add one more and I'm going to say if the props I mean do it like this if props that
size it's greater or greater or equal than this.
Oh sorry.
This that prompts that limit begin to do something if not going to do nothing.
So what is the thing with this.
Of course size.
It's what we get from the server could be 6 or Kuraby are actually from 0 to 6.
If it's equal or greater will never be greater.
It's just going to be 6.
If it's equal or greater than Propst that limit you know the number six in this case we are not going
to of course we can show the actual load more because it's 6 and we might be getting more products the
next time.
But if it's less than 6 it's obvious that the server has no more results for this.
So in this case of course we are not going to return anything that's why return no.
Now there's one more catch with this.
Of course what happens if you have 12 products so we will be still displaying the load for.
But of course the next time we click it it's not going to show because we don't have more.
It's going to be equal to zero.
So we have six good.
I click it.
We have five and we get no more.
So let's try to change this with a filter if I click an offender everything.
You know we get a lot more and we get just fender.
Ivan is all right.
No more.
Now we should be getting lot more and we get more.
We're going to get Jackson OK.
We didn't get anything.
And of course if I click on this it's just going to bring me everything that it's related to the filter.
We applied everything works OK so we are almost done.
We are almost done.
So we get to go to the next section and I'm going to do the grids.
It's going to take us just five minutes is something very very simple and then we are done with this
and everything all the rest of the rest of this.
I'm going to be adding is as a bonus section.
It's just if you want to know more.
Right.
So let's go to the next one and do the Gritz.