All right.
So let's do the grits.
It's going to be really fast if you're feeling lazy than we need first up to the degree it's just like
this.
We need the actual icons.
So we need to bring the icons.
And again if you're listening if you're feeling a little bit lazy just like me you can go to Budenz
inside you tildes and copy the import.
Yes I'm cheating.
I'm going to paste it right here.
So for fun.
Awesome.
That's Day One we need and this one of course we need something else is going to be a and then bars
just like this change on the free solid.
I'm going to copy this one and this one.
It's going to be F A T H.
Right.
So there you go.
You're done.
Let's go at the bottom to the container of the grits which is chopped grits and right here.
We need actually two elements.
You know the left and the right.
Pretty much it's.
So I'm going to create a them open and close.
Now this div..
We need to pass some things because whenever we click it we want to do something.
And besides we want to change the class names to greyed out or not grade out.
All right.
So I'm going to add a class name.
I could close this because we need to see pretty much everything.
So I'm going to use a template strings and I'm going to say the good the style of this is greed VTM
right.
Then if the grid that we state of grid that we have at the top this one has a value you know a name
where class whatever we want to attach it there.
You know we want to check if we have something and if we do have something we want to attach a class
of active.
So we go record one and say OK open it clubs.
If this state that the grid has something we're going to do this.
If not we're going to do active.
Right.
And he said Oh and I will attach a class the unclick listener that we're going to do in a minute.
So unclick and whenever we click it we want to trigger a function called handle and then a grid can
be so simple and it's out of here.
We need to do the fun.
Awesome so font awesome on the closet and the icon it's equal to f a th Breguet.
So I'm going to copy all this and paste it at the bottom.
Of course we need to change some things because now the state the class active is going to be expecting
for it not only of this I can put this in front and that is that now the handle Gretz still is that
we just need to handle Gritz because we just tackle something.
And this one it's a.
And then bars that is it.
So now we need to create to handle grid function.
So we're going to go right here at the top.
I'm going to say it calls handle Gred opening close.
Now the handle grid is just going to set the state of something or it's just going click it.
So I'm going to say this.
That said state opening close grid.
And now if we don't have anything inside this let me do this first.
This state that grid.
What are we going to do.
We're going to return grid underscore bars.
Right.
If we do have something we not going to do anything.
And you're not going to do anything.
We just toggling between a class and not a class.
Now if you remember whenever we make or we include the component for the cards we are passing the state
of grit so the cards are going to get a class of Man-Thing or the great bars.
This is a class.
So at the bottom for example load cards we get grid that the state quits.
So the cars will be getting a class or nothing.
Now if I go to cart I have it right here.
We say that we are passing of course the props and everything else you say OK I want to get the credit.
So this is going to be a class or it's going to be nothing.
So if you're going to go to our project yes and get to select it ok.
Change in the grids.
But it's a little bit broken.
So of course I've already checked on this one a possible deal.
And of course check out what is the problem.
And I made a couple mistakes.
First I'm going to go to the cart component and right here I've closed the container so this should
be inside of a container.
Now I'm going to put this right here.
All right.
Now I'm going to go to Lloyd Gibson.
Lorem Ipsum Actually I'm going to fit into real content right here.
We are just under description because now we are going to be showing us we are showing pretty much nothing.
So I'm going to put a paragraph right here p tack and I'm going to bring the props that description
that comes from the actual server.
So corruption.
All right.
Let's try it again.
So the application reloads.
And if you go here now we get it.
Now there's one more one more mistake.
I'm going to delete this.
I'm going to type whatever
I'm going to.
I'm going to reload the application go here.
And of course the class for this one is wrong because the image should be you know should be a little
bit smaller.
We are setting.
I didn't change the default image.
So of course if we bring it down it fits.
Now if you want to do this on the styles on the card I think were great bars.
You can you can actually do it.
No problem.
I'm not going to do it.
I'm going to leave it just like it is.
Because again the CSSA are not that important right here of course.
Yes because it's really actually.
But again we are not focus focusing a lot of the on the C Ss.
Like I said before don't take the CSSA as a reference.
OK.
So we are changing the grid and everything works.
Everything works right.
Later I might be adding some more more filters but for now we are done with this.
We are done with a shop section of course later are we going to do the add to the car but you know that
that logic comes from the actual cart and the user the user data.
Right.
So we are done with this.
Let's move on to the next section.