OK so let's bring the imports.
We need the user layouts.
So user layout user layouts and with a capital L and it's from of course you tell us I'm sorry the H.O.
sees that for Slashdot for us.
Last one more and H.O. see forward slash and the user.
All right.
And of course we can wrap everything inside of this user layout well and we just do it now so we can
get something at least on the screen.
Because right now it's not really we actually.
All right.
So you know we get our product and then decide that right.
So we need to import a lot of more things we need to form fields remember.
So I'm going to say important.
And actually we can we can just save time right here.
Remember that we have some form fields on other parts of the application maybe we have the other log
in of course or the register.
So if you go to we're just log in and then you go to register you have it right here.
So I'm going to copy this because we can really use it.
So I'm going to add products and paste it.
Of course they are not on the same place.
There are going to be inside one more data that forward slash and I'm going to do it right here.
One two or three up and there we go.
So then we of course would need to import connect import connect because we're going to be dispatching
actions of course.
And remember that we are entering products and they need woods and they need brands.
So we need to import the list of brands.
So I'm going to say good brand remember that this is the name of the function.
I'm going to just double check it going to go to actions product actions and we have the category which
is get brands.
Right.
So that's one that when he's done and then we have to get woods so so get puts coma and we're going
to have a one more.
But we're going to do it at the end.
It's going to be the dead dispatch of actually publishing you know storing everything on the database.
So we go to actions and that product actions right.
We are always done right here at the top.
Of course we need to we have connect we need to operate the components.
So connect open and close and begin to add the product.
All right.
We're going to do my Up-State props.
We could use it.
So I'm going to say map state to prop's own prompts and we're going to use the products and then we
bring state products and begin to put it right here.
All right.
So pretty much done everything that we need to import.
Now the first thing of course it's the state of the forum right.
We need to do a lot of things right here.
So we're going to go to the top and say state opening close.
So we have the form error.
So this one will be false at the beginning.
Then we have the form success you know form success and then again it's false coma.
And then we have our form data right.
So the form data will have many many things.
Ryan will have a name and are going to go again to register and copy the name because they are very
very similar if not the same.
So we still have an input.
We do have a value right.
We have a name a type and a placeholder.
And if you remember maybe on the previous project with the label thing.
So we're going to do it right now.
Again we're going to still do this so we can add a label and we're going to say product name right.
I don't remember we added this but if we don't we don't have it we can add it just very simple anyways.
So we have we still have ballot touch validation message.
And remember that to show the label we need one more prop which is show label.
And this one will be set true because we want to show the label.
Okay.
We have more things going to copy name go at the bottom.
And this one is going to be the description.
So this Christian Right and this one will be a text area so text area and this one product description.
The this one description input Yeah.
All right.
It's going to be just Stillwell type text does matter.
And then add your description validation is going to be required Matt it is still touch and show level
will be true.
All right.
I'm going to copy the one that has the name.
So we're going to copy the name and I'm going to go right here at the bottom and I'm going to close
this because they bother me right now.
So this one will be the price.
What is the price of the guitar.
So input product price and then price.
All right then the type is going to be number right.
And you can do this on your own.
Right.
And the price then valid.
Everything is the same and show Leavell true.
All right then we have a brand and right here we have a different element.
So with the brand just like this instead of unempowered it's going to be a select begin to load all
the brands right here.
So this one will be a select.
We don't have a select.
We're going to create it in a couple of minutes.
So brand and then brand input right.
That type is going to be whatever Actually we don't need a tiebreak here.
And the placeholder we don't really need a placeholder.
So there we go.
OK.
So now what we need in this one is going to be the options.
So the options is going to start as an empty array but much later we going to fetch the brands and then
we're going to inject the brand so we can pretty much update the state of options inside brand.
All right.
The validation is still required.
Show level 2 everything else.
It's just the same.
Now I'm going to copy the brand.
We go right here at the bottom and then we have the I have the shipping.
So the shipping it's pretty simple.
We don't need to load information inside of the options.
We can just add it right here.
So I'm going to say shipping this is still select and it's product shipping or could be just shipping
right and then shipping impot now options are going at it right here.
We're going to open it close.
And if you remember we have a key a coma and then we have a value right.
This is what we used in the previous project where we're going to do the same thing right here.
So we have a key and a value of.
Yes.
And unmangled it goes we are using of course the true false type of Moul you know we're using booleans.
So this one is going to be false and this one no.
All right everything good the still required.
And we will show the label.
All right.
Next.
So the next one is going to be if it's available or not.
So I'm going to go right here and the available key is going to him is going to.
Right now we are not really using it on the products but when we go to the.
Let me just go right here.
Well of course we are doing it when we go right here and we go to the product.
It says Free Shipping and Return and none available preorder only.
So you know just that detail is something that you might have on real life of a level we call it available.
We're going to check later anyways.
So it's a small select and available and it's dark and of course this one will be available to copy
from here and paste it here.
And again this one will be the same key.
True false yes no.
Right.
It's a validation.
Everything else is just the same.
Then we have the wood and the wood again.
It's just like this.
I'm going to copy and paste it.
I'm going to say a word.
So I still select and then word material.
Now this one actually is kind of a fake with guitars.
I'm not sure if I told you already of this guitar guitars you might have.
Of course any time which one word that could happen.
But most of the times that guitar guitars are made of different words sometimes most of the times.
Could have.
You could get a guitar completely made in mahogany for example.
I get it.
Meanwhile do this in mahogany but most of the times you just get a guitar.
And of course we will load the words from the server so we can leave this empty.
You're going to get a guitar with a buddy of basswood and a neck of mahogany or something like that.
You know most of the times you get a mix.
So next one it's the frets.
Now with the frets we pretty much have another select but this one we just need to fix.
Put the hard coded information right here.
You are not going to load everything from the server because we just have about three four options.
It's really simple.
So this one will be Fretz And of course instead of wood it's going to be Fretz and we are almost done.
We are almost done and we are using the key value person going to copy this and paste it right here
and say a key of number in this case.
So we have 21 Fretz which is very uncommon.
We have 22 Freda's 22 frets.
And then we have 24 guitars with 23 frets that doesn't exist.
So 20 and 20 Why 24 frets is the longest because it's two octaves.
That's it.
That's really why so OCHA.
So we have Fretz select frets frets and put everything else.
It's just the same right.
And the last actually we have two more but we are not going to do the last one because it's the images.
I mean going to do that at the end is the public the public option.
So I'm going to copy the one that's available because we have a yes no value.
So we're going to paste it here and say publish.
Remember this one.
This is the one we use to show the product or not are not to common users.
So publish and then publish then the key is still true false.
But we can say instead of yes we can say public and then hidden.
All right.
Still the show labels just same everything else the same.
A lot of things.
All right.
So let's let's include the form fields right here for all of this feels write so let's do the form fields
and I made a mistake right here at the top.
Maybe you noticed and I didn't.
So it's re-act redux.
That's why nothing is working right here.
So let's of course reload and we should be getting something at least.
OK.
So that is good.
Again just like with the Before we go we're here we don't need it.
And you know that this exists at this point this is this should be very very familiar to you.
So I'm going to close it because you know it's a lot of information and I don't like it.
So I'm going to go inside.
We're of course going to delete everything.
I'm going to put a wrapper div and inside just an 8 one stack the form it's not really that complicated
it's real simple.
That was what I did it this way on purpose.
You know so we can spend less time doing layouts.
So we have a form we have an ounce of met just like before.
So the answer met again.
We open and close.
We pass the event.
So just like this.
And then we just create a function that calls the submit forms of meant submit and then form right.
Then of course we pass the event.
Same same same as always.
All right.
So now instead of here we just start adding inputs.
So I'm going to go to predict actions.
No I'm going to go to register and I'm going to copy one of the form fields so we don't have to type
type it again.
I'm going to copy the form name on it.
I'm going to go to for Maime paste right.
Let me do this first form of selection.
All right.
So OK so the form fields just in this case it's just a name right.
Just like this.
Name form date a name and then the element.
So that one we are get later right here at the top right here.
We will be adding the image file a file upload.
But for now this is good.
OK.
So right from the start we have a problem.
We didn't have.
And let me just do the log in
right from the start.
We didn't have the attack names so we need to add them right.
OK.
So if you remember this it's inside you tells form form fields right here.
So we need to start adding the the tax form here and then the next section maybe I'm not I'm not sure
we're going to do it right now but on the next section we need to add all the select and the text area.
Remember that now we have a select and we have a text area.
So we need to use them.
So I'm going to go to below the foreign block opening close and going to say okay if we have a form
data that show a label on here not a capital L label then of course we want to display something if
not no.
So what we do we just pass a div with a class the class name it's called to label inputs.
And inside we would just put the form data so form data that config dot whatever we are passing to the
label.
So we load it.
Oh sorry.
There's one problem with this.
And the store is just keep logging me out.
That's OK.
So we have the password one two three.
OK.
That is get so we get we get the tag.
So all right.
So that works.
So OK so let's keep keep moving forward.
We do have a select ride.
So let's do the select right now.
I don't know if we have time.
Now it's already too long so let's go to the next section and begin at the select and the text area.