So let's keep moving forward.
Right now we're going to be doing the ad products section beginning go to the log in since we are our
admins we're going to get this option we're going to create this part for the app.
And then when we click our products we're going to go to here.
So it is pretty much a form just a form.
We did a lot of this.
So we need to do it again of course but it's going to be very simple this time.
And then at the end we can add the upload image and we're going to use this we can upload to a service
much much later.
And I've already wrote this down on a note as a bonus to this project.
I will add pretty much the same behavior than uploading an image but to you know to our directories
to our server instead of using everything as a service I would still recommend doing this service and
you have a bunch of a bunch of services for this.
You can even use firebase for this.
Yeah.
So OK.
So after after we do this before doing this we need to do the nap now before doing the nav.
I want to give you I want to tell you something I forgot to do from our project right here.
What we did right here.
Now let me go here and to the road 380 and I'm going to check the last entry.
It's a 700.
So this is the one we get right here.
Seven hundred and the public for this one.
It's false.
So we shouldn't be getting this image.
I forgot to block this.
Now there's two ways you can do it.
You can go to the carts and say Dude if it's published false don't show it.
That's it.
But you will still be loading the from this.
The actual data from this product.
So what you can do you can go to the service to the server to the route.
Actually whenever you reload this routes there's a product you can enter and pie and pass a new arc.
For example going to go right here and we're going to say find Arkes and the key for this is going to
be publish just like this publish.
So I'm just adding the art I'm going to say publish and.
And the art and say OK I want to bring all the files as long as they are true just like this.
And this is a public route so you can do whatever you want right here and you're not using the admin
of course if you use the admin you're going to block everything if the user is not locked in.
That is a problem.
So if reload this used not there anymore it's just blocking the products that are not published.
That is it.
That is the only thing you're doing.
And of course later if you want to fetch things from the server and they need to be admin you maybe
need to export this and create a function maybe and then create a different route or modify the hour
an admin so you can put it right here.
But you know that's not a good idea.
All right let's get.
So we're going to do this right now.
So we need to create the route I'm going to go to my account.
We need to create the NAF right here.
So I'm going to close everything.
We don't need it and I'm going to go where we have this now which is going to be user inside h o z.
OK.
Just like the links we need to add a new viable Konst and I'm going to call it admin equals right because
the admin section open and close.
They're going to copy this one and paste it right here.
Now the first one it's going to be the site info.
So site and then info.
So this one this one we will be able to change some things on on the on the side to the global bbls
but that's got to do it later.
It's just some information about the above the Web site.
OK.
So then I'm going to go to app products which is the one we're going to be using right now an advent
inside info no it's going to be a product.
All right.
And I'm going to copy this one.
Go with the bottom and paste it.
And this one is going to be managed categories later.
Of course we need a place where we can enter brands or what so we'll create a tiny little thing for
this.
So manage categories and instead of admen it's going to be manage categories.
OK.
So we are pretty much done.
Now the thing is and the promise that we want to show this is show this only if the user is authenticated.
And remember that the South is a different agency so it's kind of an a different place.
We cannot really really use it right here.
We could but I prefer to do something else since we have all everything injected in Propst after we
load this component because this is the wrapper of a parent print component that actually it's inside
the router.
What we can do.
We could just written redux right.
We can bring the maps data to props and get and get it from there.
So I'm going to say map state to props to the own prompts and begin to bring user user.
And I'm going to say user right.
Of course we need to bring connect on the top.
So import import than it connect just like this.
When they make it right connect to connect and then from re-act redux.
Right of course we need to wrap everything inside of here.
And now we have reductions here so we can access the maps data props.
Of course we need we need to go we need to pass the maps stage props.
Forgot to do that.
All right.
So now of course it will make a reference to Propst inside of there is here we can access the data.
So I'm going to go below this and I'm going to say if prop's that user that user data remember that
we have it inside user data user data done.
And we have as admin then begin to show it.
So if not we going to do no good you know same as always.
So now I'm going to go right here and enter a new div and the it will contain an H2 called Atman.
And inside of here are going to create a new div with a class name of links just like with it before.
Notice at the top we pretty much have the same thing.
I'm just going to copy and OK now it's going to be GeneDx links.
But in this case it's going to be admin you know a different list.
So if we check it we have the admin and everything else.
So that's good right now.
Later of course we shouldn't be getting this right.
If you're not anatman but remember that we're going to be going to be using anatman out.
We are actually using the admin.
So if we want to poll the user you can break this and enter and tried to post something.
It's not going to really happen unless they have the correct token.
OK.
So if we go to our product we have this route.
We don't have the route defined Let's create it.
So what are we going to do.
We're going to go inside user because this is in use or use around.
So I'm going to go inside and I'm going to create a new directory called outman and instead of admen
of course we will have this at products that.
All right.
Of course this is going to be a re-act class based component.
We need to do a lot of things right here.
So I'm going to call it ad products product in real life product.
We just enter a single product from here.
OK.
So our product and our product that's the same thing as product.
So now of course we need to add the route.
And we're going to do this.
And then just move on to the next section so we can start from scratch with the product.
All right.
So I'm going to go two routes and I'm going to include it.
Import product from that forward slash components forward slash user.
And then Aben forward slash and end product.
All right.
So I'm going to copy the same dashboard route because it's had been round and noticed that I'm putting
all the things right here in the last public or semipublic right here.
So it's instead of user it's admen and it's add product and product.
They're going to copy the name of the component paste it and in theory we should be getting the product
and we can do of course we didn't have the Napp we need to add it right now.
But we are pretty much ready to start doing this.
So let's go to the next section and we will start with the easy part which is going to be creating the
state bringing the lay out you know all the imports and then and adding the form fields.
That is the easy part.
So let's go to the next section into this.