So what we need to do now is to add the textarea and the selects and I get to go off course to form
fields and we need to do it right here.
And I'm going to do both right now the text area and they select because of course we're going to use
them right now.
So first I'm going to create a case of text and then area opening close and never forget to do the break.
So of course we pretty much need the same thing so I'm going to copy the form take the form template
and paste it right here.
So the show label stays the same.
Then of course when it's going change it's going to be the input to delete everything inside of here.
I will do text area and then of course it could be a self-closing tag.
And then just like with did before right here we need to pass the form data and config.
We do have a value and we do have a number and a change.
So I'm going to copy and paste and that is it you know really really simple.
I just got to love your reusable components.
We don't need to do anything else.
Yeah.
Let's get.
So now we need the select when it's going to be a little bit different in the case right here at the
top.
So if we have a case of select on we do it correctly select opening close and never forget the break
never if not of course nothing is going to really work.
Maybe the impact is going to work but not now and if anything else is just not going to work I'm sorry
the text area because it's the last break.
OK.
So instead of here we just do pretty much the same thing right now just going to copy the form template
and I'm going to paste.
Of course we need to change something.
So we still have the form block and we still have the label right.
So I'm going to delete the text area.
So what we need right here is to select a right opening close with the select just like we do have with
the beginning at the top.
We still have value on Bloor and a change and we don't get to form data to fit into form data config.
We don't use that on the Select because we don't need to inject everything inside of the tag.
All right what we do get it's options.
So the first option is going to be select and an empty value.
And right here you could choose to do whatever you want.
Maybe select the disabled value or something like that.
Or maybe a default one.
So the first leg is going to be a value of nothing.
Then of course we need to loop the options that begin to be getting from the server or from the array
with keys and values.
So we enter to form data and I'm going to close this so we can see all that and get a do config DOD
options dart map and I'm doing this a little bit faster because we did this a few times already.
So I'm going to open and of course we need to return some GSX so parenthesis then of course we have
option opening close.
We have a key now.
So it's key of item dot.
And remember we are using a key and that's key.
It's not the key is the key of the of the loop.
Right.
Remember we have an object right here we key in value.
So then of course we have the value I'm going to drop this.
So it's a little bit more organized.
So value and the value is equal to the same item and the send key.
All right.
And that of course inside of here instead of the option we just have the value right.
OK.
So item that value and that is it.
We don't need anything else.
Hopefully I didn't make any mistakes.
So we're going to go back to our product and now we can start adding the rest of the form fields.
So the first one was the name the second one was the description and that is the text area.
So I'm going to go here and say description can to copy and paste it.
Let's see what we get.
And we get product description and you know it is a text area.
Of course you can change this to whatever you want.
Now I'm just going to leave it the next one is going to be the price.
So copy paste and price price and then price.
Do we get it.
Yeah we get it.
We were getting an error message because we didn't have the added form so far.
And it is a type of number.
Very good.
So I'm going to go back here and say that I want a ruler.
Now the thing is that the ruler looked a little bit weird for me.
D'Harmental ruler so I'm going to add a class name of a form divider just like this.
Now I just realized that I have a couple of stakes you need to fix them right now of course.
If not the application will fail.
So the next ones are pretty much all selects right.
We need the Bran's the shipping the available and everything else.
So I'm going to copy one of the top just maybe the first one doesn't matter.
They're all the same.
And then we need to add the brand and then the brand.
All right.
They're all the same.
Again just like with it before you could create just a function to render all at once you can do that.
Yeah no problem.
So rant and brand now of course we get this.
And this is actually my mistake if we go back to the form fields and we go right here.
It's not option it's options.
And then it's not option Upton.
It's option.
Sorry.
All right let's try again.
So Adelies we get to get no armis of course the information is empty.
And he of course tried to do something.
Nothing really happens.
And we my getting we might be getting an error message but that is OK.
OK.
So I'm going to go to back to our products and the next one are the shipping and the available.
So going to copy paste.
I'm going to say shipping and I'm going to say shipping the next one.
It's available.
So go right here available and then available.
Right.
I will add a new form divider horn when Varner point form divider.
Then I'm going to copy the brand.
And now we need the words.
So for the word is just what similar to what I believe on the avi.
But you know pretty much it's really really close.
So I'm going to go to after.
We have Fretz.
And remember that the word we will get the data from the server.
So that's the next thing we're going to do.
So after Fretz are going to copy a new form divider are going to go right here at the bottom and we
need to put the publish notice tell if the product it's public or not.
So we're going to say publish right now at the bottom.
And this was the last one.
We need to enter it when you get the button and the forms access messages and everything else.
So I'm going to go to register and I'm going to copy them from here.
So we're going to paste them when I get them trying to make this a little bit nicer.
Kind of a failing but that's OK.
So instead of creating an account we will have product the form error stays the same but now we have
form success.
So I'm going to copy the I'm going to put a the big curly braces.
There's the state that forms success and of course if we don't get a success we will not do anything.
And of course of course name and then form success.
And of course if we are getting a success we just displayed success you could do whatever you want right
here.
Now remember that after we post the product to the database we will get the product back.
We could do that.
So when we get that we will get it back we can store it in a magical place inside redux.
And then of course access through prompts.
And once you access through prompts you get the idea of the article you just entered.
Right.
And you put the ID or the link to the article right there.
And that is it.
OK.
So everything looks nice.
If I save it of course we got we can it get it.
All right.
So the next thing will be populating the brands.
And for this we need to do a fat should the server to get the brands and the words and we need to create
a function that takes this values and it will go inside brands ride and enter the fields out pneumatically
can update the fields.
Let's do that right now.
All right so where are we going to be fetching the brands and the woods.
So from the component about right.
All right.
So a component that MT open opening close.
So first I'm going to do a get a copy of the form form data just like this because whenever we reach
to the component amount I'll just copy whatever we have in the state right now whenever it enters here.
So State Farm data you could just pass this state the form data layer.
You could do that.
So OK.
So first we need to dispatch to get the Prince so this that prompts that this patch just like this.
And we say get brands.
All right of course then something happens when we get a response which is you know do something now
we're going to do something of course.
But first I want to check went to make sure that we get the prance.
So I'm going to just console log this that prompts.
Remember we are inside products products products dot and then Brant's.
Ryan Okay let's see what we get.
I'm not using the readouts right here.
Just going to go to the Gudel console so we get an array of nine.
We are getting the brands.
So now what we need to do is to this can convert everything go to the state and store it on the right
place because this is going to go chest in brands.
So I'm going to delete and copy this one because I'm going to use it in a minute and I'm lazy.
So Konst form data.
I'm sorry.
New form data new form data equals and we will create a function that calls populate option.
Or it could be options yes but played option and then fields all right and this function will take a
few arguments it's going to take that form data we have at the top.
So I'm going to say form data and this form data is viable.
And then again we're going to pass this that props that product the Brandts that contains all the brands
and then we get past the idea of where we going to be hosting this insight form data.
What is the key.
In this case is just brand remember it's just a single not Brandt's just brand run to sprint.
All right.
So after we process all of this this new form data will contain the new state with the brand and all
the options inside.
So after we do this we just need to update the fields.
But for now we are just going to leave it like here.
We're going to get we're going to check in a minute what we get from new form data so we need to create
this populate option fields.
We don't have this and we will do this in side form actions are going to go to form actions cobby Popul
late let me make it ride populate.
There we go.
I'm going to go to form actions remember we have it inside your tills and we're going to add the function
just here.
Export Konst populate Opt-In fields.
We will get some Arkes and then we will do something or I'm okay.
So this public option feels will receive that form data that coma.
We will get an array of data which at the beginning could be just empty if we don't get it.
Just in case.
And then you know the field the field where are going to be modifying this saga.
So first I'm going to create a new array Konst array or it could be in your array and it's going to
be equal to nothing.
Ryan then I'm going to grab that new form data.
You form data I'm going to create a new form data sorry just like this and this new form data is going
to be equal to whatever we have inside form data that is going to happen in this case right.
We could just use the form data we get back here.
All right.
So what do we need to do is very simple which just push the values inside the key inside the new form
data.
So OK so I'm going to go right here and I call I'm going to call this array data and I'm going to grab
that array data that we get going to do dot and I'm going to do a for each on the top.
So for each value we have and the array of data which is all the the Brandt's we were getting right
here we're going to loop them and in each iteration we will convert and attach them to the new array.
Ryan kind of makes sense.
So we're going to enter the new array.
I'm going to push a new value.
But the new value in this time is going to be an object with a key and a value.
We are just converting this with we can A did this previously.
So the key is going to be the item item dot underscore ID.
All right.
Then we put a coma and going to pass the value and the value is the item that dot and the name.
And this is what comes from the server.
If you remember whenever we get the.
And then go back to our product.
Whenever we get the new form that new form data I'm sorry the the this that props the products and brands.
Let me just show you again because maybe you don't remember console that log.
This prompts that product the brand.
It's a long string.
We get nine and we get the ID underscore ID and this one has a name it's not you know maybe value or
something like that.
That's why on the form actions we are making a reference to item that name.
So we are just pushing the object pretty much the same information on a different way.
So all right.
So we have the new foreign data the copy we made right here at the top.
I want to enter the key and the key is inside field and then I'm going to say that I'm going to enter
the config dot.
I'm going to enter the options.
I'm going to say that the new array is now the new value of that one.
Now of course this function needs to return something.
So we can return new form data right.
And that is it.
Now populate option fields.
If you go back to our product and I do the new form data we're going to get that new you know the new
array so we get it let's go to Brant's and we go to config and then inside options we have key and value
right.
So the only thing left right now is to update update the state but we can run a function that actually
does this and it's going to be called update fields.
Right.
All right let's try to do it right now.
So I got to create a function that calls update fields.
So this dot update fields opening close and begin to be passing this new form data.
All right.
So let's create the function right now.
You're going to say update fields equals to something and after something we will get you know just
an argument right here.
So the object fields is going to be really really easy.
We just set the state.
The thing is that I'm making a function of this because we can do several dispatches maybe to make later
we can do more.
And you know creating a does that said state.
And then this that said state and then again kind of makes no sense.
So right inside of that feels the only thing we do right now is this.
That said state of form data equals whatever we get.
Right here is an argument.
New form data data.
All right.
That is that we should be getting this
when we go to France and we get.
That's right.
And of course it fails because we don't have the update form whenever we do it and change that is OK.
OK so let's do the brand and then just move onto the next section so we can complete this.
Now this one pretty much the same instead of get Brandt's we have the other dispatch we just get words
on the function.
So get what's published feels pretty much the same.
But on this one it's what if I save it and not notice again.
Sometimes it's always good to take the you know take a look a little bit more and instead of doing everything
here just create a different function to do this.
And it just closes on the way.
All right.
So we have the brands that is get Let's go to the wood and see if I can find a word with material of
course material.
And I get an incorrect of course get words when we just change this race Pond's response DNA changed
us to of course.
Is this a practice that would What's sorry for that.
So let's see if this works best.
Good mahogany in our right.
My favorite is either if you're wondering OK so everything looks good.
All the selects are pretty much none.
Of course if we select something we get the update form.
Now everything went too long so let's go to the next one and complete the form.
Right.
And we will try to post everything to the server.