So lets do the update form in the submit form.
The first we think about this.
We've covered this so I'm going to go to the register.
You can go to the log in that's good.
And we have the update form and the submit form.
So I'm going to copy both and of course we're going to make some changes in it copy go back to our products
and are going to go forward to component it now.
All right let's start from the beginning.
The form is just the same same code but from this one the key word would be products because we are
pushing products on the submit form.
Everything else is the same but everything inside form ballot we can delete it because we don't need
it.
We need to do something else.
Right and right here I'm going to say cancel log just the data to submit just like this.
All right.
And that is it.
That's really it.
Now the next thing of course we know Arizona and if I enter something you know maybe a price it works
description it works and everything else works.
Burguet So OK.
So now of course oh yeah I'm going to go to inspect just to make sure I can add the product.
And we should be getting an error.
So we get Please check your data.
That's good.
At least it's validating.
So now we need to whenever it's OK.
We have a VAT form valid a valid form we need to go to the dispatch and action to store that information.
And this one is going to be very simple so we don't have this we are going to create it right now.
So I'm going to call this product you can call this whatever you want.
Add product or write in a copy and same as always.
We will need to go to product actions and at the function and I'm going to go right here an export function
could be a narrow function if you if you wish.
So export function product and this one it's real simple.
We are not doing anything before we go to the server and this function just like with it with maybe
other other functions.
It's really simple we just do the request and send the payload and the type.
So Konst request equals access opening close.
Sorry post.
We passed the only route which is product server just like this.
And if you remember the route article let's just make sure because I remember but it's kind of a blurry
kind of a blur.
So sharp we have articles we have articles by id and we have article right.
And we get the success and we will get that doc back.
All right.
So Paul the actions article that we need to pass the data to submit so data to see if med can it copy
and pass it.
Then of course we do that Dan.
Open and close after a while this gets a little bit boring.
You've been listening listening to me for like I know a day 20 hours 24 hours something like that.
So yeah I know I know this is kind of a boring already so product and we are going to create a type
of course of product and then we send the payload.
Let me do it right.
Koma payload and the payload it's going to be equal to the request payload request.
We don't have the type we need to add it.
So coma and product are going to go to types.
Can you go right here.
Export Konst product equals to product.
Right.
All right.
So now we have the actions right.
We have the types we need to go to the producer.
So I'm going to go to the producer and find it first reducers product producers are going to copy the
type because because we can use it in cold type and then just add the case.
So it's going to be a case of when they do a dry case of ADD product and we make that default.
Correct.
So what we return it's going to be the state.
So we return dot dot dot state state coma and again we need to create a key were we going to be adding
this.
So I'm going to call it out product you could call this maybe admin app product or admin product or
something like that.
So action that payload and that is it.
Okay.
So of course all this circuit is already done.
So what we need to do now is to you know send the product or let's see what happens.
Let's go back to the to the form and first I want to make sure that everything is correct.
We are getting the data to submit.
So I'm going to enter whatever information right now.
All right so whatever information description whatever price brand the shipping available would the
frets and the Polish.
So at product let's see what we get.
So we get it available look at everything looks correct.
We even get the IDs.
So all right let's let's push it.
Let's send it to the server.
OK.
So on this forum first of course we need to dispatch the action.
We have it at the top.
So we do this not perhaps just like this.
We do the dispatch open and close.
We do add product just like this.
And then of course open and we pass the data access if met then we will do something opening close and
we do something.
All right.
So if and else if and else just like we did before after we get now everything gets posted we will get
something that says this that props the products that are products and success.
So I'm going to say this that trops products just like this that product that success.
All right.
And of course if this fails this is get we'll do something if not we will just set the state of something.
So I'm going to say this that said state on the air form error equals to true.
So what I wanted to do I want to show the success message and I want to reset the whole form this is
what I want to do.
So I'm going to call to a function that says these that reset and then fields and then hndler open
and close.
It's just a function.
Now we didn't have this function going to create it right now.
So it's just going to be a function that does something.
And the main purpose of this function is to reset all the fields and show the you know show up message
saying that do everything it's OK.
So first on this one I'm just going to set the state so at least we can get a message saying that everything
was correct.
So I'm going to say form success and then true.
All right let's see what happens.
Let's try again.
Let me make this a little bit smaller so I'm going to add a name.
I going to say the name of the guitar.
I don't know a rocket whatever description blah blah blah blah blah.
The price.
One two three.
The product itself Fender because the name it's kind of weird.
Now let's do an early wall the shipping.
Yeah.
Well no it's a one two three.
One hundred dollars in the 100 billion stock.
Yeah.
Because a cheap guitar with material mahogany of course frets 22 and publish it can it make it public
so I can add the product and we get the success.
And on this tour we get success true and we get the article back.
So let me go right here.
Our product success we get the everything else sold price description and everything else so very good
man.
So let's do the reset field and then I can tell you one more thing about this.
So on the recent feel handler what I want to do I want to enter our state right here are phone data
and we need to reset everything back to zero.
Right reset the ballot reset the values and reset everything else.
So for this since we will perform pretty much the same action on all the forms are going to create again
just a form action.
All right.
So first I'm going to do Konst and new form data and this equals to this function that we will create
in a minute is it called Reset fields.
So this reset fields needs to know what needs to be reset.
So this state and we just pass the form data.
No we don't have this function.
I'm going to include it at the top and I'm going to go to form actions so we can you know create it.
So the reset form data reset fields or Kopete we set we call fields that reset feels.
So the reset field is going to be very simple.
We need to do a couple things but it's just pure logic.
Konst reset fields equals that form data data just like this.
And then we just run a function.
Now I'm going to add one more thing because we might be needing this later just like we did with the
other ones.
I'm going to add the stack and I forgot to do it right here.
So it's products products products and then products.
All right.
I'm going to go to form actions and the name and the name the form name form name we are not going to
really use it but maybe in the future we will use this right so instead of here we get different data
just like we did before I will create a new form data ECOs to dot dot dot and whatever we get inside
form data you know as usual then what we need to do we need to enter the form data loop everything and
reset the Valot the value the touch and the validation message.
So for opening close and then let me an new form data because we made a copy of this we can enter that
new form data and get a copy.
We'll make it right.
Right.
The new form data we're going to enter the whatever key we are in and they're going to enter the value
and the value right now is going to be nothing.
Later we are going to make a change here.
But for now it's OK.
Then of course I'm going to cover this and we're going to do it doesn't begin to change the ballot to
cole falls.
Right.
Then we have the new form day to make it right ballot.
We need to modify the touched so we can say touched equals falls and then we have the validation message.
So you form data and valley Dacian message just like this.
Let me just make sure I wrote this correctly.
Validation message where I get validation message.
It's nothing.
Right and the only thing we do know right now is to return whatever we have the new form data which
is the new state are going to say return new form data that is it.
So it's going to go back to ad products.
And I'm going to go to the reset fill hands are now inside form data.
We will get the news tape with pretty much everything we set.
So form data equals to whatever we get back from the function and that's it.
Now we want to do I want to get rid of that from success after a set time out so set time out and we
just run a function and I'm going to run it after four years.
After three seconds just before during I'm going to show the message for three seconds then it's out.
So opening close forms success false.
But now we're going to get one more problem with this.
I'm going to tell you in a minute.
But first let's see if everything is OK.
The product name I don't know man.
I don't know.
Over over tech I believe that is a brand.
So for that price it's $400.
It's an Sharpeville whatever.
Yes.
No mouse would 22.
And it's public.
All right.
So going at the product and we get the success and understate what do we get we just get the products
access and everything else and noticed that we are not sending images to the server.
And it's big as we are passing you know it's adding the information me just make sure overtight get
we are just adding the information to the server and with an empty images and this and sold as well.
This is because they are not required.
Brian.
OK.
And the image you know we could have no images of the product.
So that is OK.
So we were able to you know add the information.
In theory if we go to guitars we get it you know we have the rocket and the overtasked So we're adding
the information correctly and the message goes away.
Now we are.
Let me just give you the scenario.
We are just adding the information right.
And everything goes to the server and comes back whenever it comes back.
We are doing we are going to the reducer and adding a new key called a product.
Now after a while we reset the form.
You know after we add a new product we set the form but on the state we still get you know the product
success an article.
And the thing is that that information is just there.
Even if we go to a different route that article stays there.
So sometimes not every time.
And we can add that in the past I didn't do it much often right here because a lot of work extra work
for something so simple and but in real life you should very mind that when you leave this component
this information you have right here which is going to be the product actually you don't need it.
So you need to reset it.
So for this what you will need to do is to create a clearer state right a clear state of product.
So what you can do is just create a new a new new function right here call your product something like
that doesn't matter.
Call your product and you're going to do it really fast going to go to product actions can attach right
here export function clear product.
Open it close and the only thing that you return is that same password the same type.
We need to actually change it.
Clear product.
And of course we need to add it.
That's why I'm telling you I don't do this much on the practice project it's because we had a lot of
work for something so simple so export Konst clear product and then clear product something like that.
So inside action actions that whenever you this this action which is the clear product you're just sending
a type with a clear product and nothing inside.
This could be an empty array or an empty object or whatever is that you're actually using.
Right.
So then on that we do sir.
You go here of course we need to add the type you go here below the product so you can clearly see that
we have an ad and we have a clear and you just returned to same thing.
But the next whenever you trigger the dispatch that action a product will be changed to nothing.
And this could happen on the sense that timeout that we are doing right here.
Let that just copy the name a function could happen in the said time out of me find it right here.
You could dispatch an action or you can do it when the component amounts.
You can do that.
So I'm going to we're going to do it right here.
So whenever we said the state I'm going into a coma and I'm going to dispatch the action.
So this that prompts dot this patch opening close and we just clear the product.
And this is going to happen after the three seconds so if I enter or whatever again or another name
I don't know I'm looking something in my office.
The metal metal math this is a pedal.
So whatever the price four hundred they brand the shipping.
Yeah whatever mahogany.
And then public.
We're going to see it right here at product that is OK.
And then after a second you know we just remove it.
So if we go back we do have that key but it's empty.
We don't have anything.
So you're ready to enter a new product again.
In this case right here on our product we don't we need to clear it because there's no reference to
that product.
Whenever the application loads.
Right.
So the next time you enter to the same route there's no reference to this state of product.
We are not really using it but maybe if you want to output something from the our product right here
you might be need to store it and then show it and then query it.
So that's where you need to do it.
But the best example I can give you is the guitars if you go to a new page what say new route going
to go here.
Right.
So the state owned redux of this new page is going to be right there.
So we are fetching everything and storing and relax and everything else.
Now if you move out if you go outside the component let's say two guitars.
Again that stayed inside redux steaks the same with information about this.
So if you enter to a new one the server is going to try to fetch the information and you will see the
information of the previous state until the next state kicks in.
So that is a problem in that case you will need to clear the state and just like we did here you could
do a clear product just like with this with it we do it with a single function and then a single type
where you could do.
For example if you don't want to write one clear for every action that this patch is to create maybe
a common function where you can receive some arguments as props and just return the type that you're
passing in props and the payload of whatever it is that you want to do.
Maybe set it to an empty IRA or something like that.
So you just create create one common clear that actually you can do it.
It's simple it's just a function that takes a switch with some arguments and return something.
If the if it matches the type.
Right.
OK.
So that is going to save it and we are pretty much done with this.
We are done.
We are able to post information.
Go to guitars.
We get the metal MUF everything is good.
So now comes the fun part.
We need to do an upload.
We need to create a nap load and we will use a service and we're going to use cloud Inari because it's
so simple right it's very simple to use.
And of course like it's all before and a bonus section will do with a do it with matter which is the
in Cavitt in house hosting upload uploading function.
We get from node.
You know it's a kind of a helper.
So we use it to up to store images on the server.
Like I told before I don't really like it with node applications.
If you are using P2P or an Apache server that is OK.
You know that is OK.
But for this one from node I would not recommend to store the images right here and you could do it
with firebase you get a storage service just like with it before it.
Same idea.
All right.
So let's go to the next section and start with the file upload.