All right so now we're going to do the file upload.
So for the file upload first we're going to use a service we're going to use cloud Inari.
You can go to Carbonari create an account and everything else.
And once you're in go to the dashboard and or the dashboard the first thing you can see is the account
details with the cloud name API.
An API secret.
We will use this in a couple minutes and then at the bottom you have other plans.
We are on the free plan and they give you you know a lot of starch.
And if you want to change to a more professional you can use this and you can contact cloud Narey and
tell them what you really need because the plus plan it's pretty big.
Two million images maybe you don't need that.
You can contact them and they will give you a new plan.
More and of course cheaper plan.
OK.
Let's get.
So go to Clarie create an account.
Go back to our project.
So this is what's going happen.
Right now we are just posting data into our database.
Right.
So what we're going to do it's not to upload at the same time we posted data.
We will do the file upload.
We will upload images and get the image.
Your help once we get we get the image your l.
Then of course we enter more information.
And what we will be posting is the image you are L..
We are not doing the upload while we are posting the whole product.
All right.
So for this we going to create a new component.
So let's do that.
It's going to go right here at the top are going to import and I'm going to call it file upload file
upload from that for Slash and I'm going to host it inside you Tilse.
Let me do that first.
Inside details and forms.
I'm going to call it file upload just like this.
Ass could go back here.
And from dot dot for Slashdot that forward slash you tells We go to form forward slash and file upload.
All right now since we are not going to do the upload from within this component we're going to do the
upload from within file upload file upload upload something.
It's going to return to the parent component which is this one the Eurail or the images that we are
just uploading.
So we need to store them inside of the form fields.
So whenever we send this to the server the images will be there.
Right.
That is the idea.
Kind of pretty much did this already on the second project.
So we need to create a place where we can be hosting the images just like this.
So we're going to do coma.
I'm going to say images opening close and we pass an object of the rules.
They need to follow the same rules right here.
So what we will do we will out of value just like this value and value an empty array.
We need validation because we can go through validation.
But on this one they're required which is the only validation we get is going to be false.
Remember that the image and the images are not required that we have the ballot the touch the validation
message and then we could get the show Leavell.
But you're not going to really use it.
So I'm going to copy paste and the valid will be true because they are not required to Targett still
false no validation message.
And the show label is going to be false.
We're not going to use it.
And that is that whenever we upload something it's going to go through here.
So let's go at the bottom and let's add the form field which is not a form filled.
Now it's going to be called file upload.
So I'm going to just make a reference to that component.
And we need to pass some props.
Now the prompts that we need to add are just to the image handler images and then handler.
And this one will be a function whenever we upload something to file upload it will return something.
So we are going to catch it.
And then of course whenever we catch it we run different function called Images handler.
And I believe I forgot to delete it because I was just testing.
So maybe we have that function yet we do have it.
Don't worry we just create a function to avoid any errors.
Then whenever we upload something of course we're going to reset the form and we need to reset the images
as well.
So we said reset open it close and I'm going to be passing this state that form success.
Don't worry we will get back to this later.
All right.
So let's go to the file upload and start doing all of this.
So this is a re-act class based component and I'm going to change the capital F and that's it.
Now for the file upload we will use a third party library called dropzone re-act drop zone.
So let we find it drub soon.
So there we go reargue dropzone.
And this is a very simple very very simple.
You have all the documentation right here and right here at the top documentation and examples.
If you go there and of course you get pretty much the same thing and you get you get all the prompts
and a basic example.
I'm going to try to use the same example they are giving us because again you might be reading the instructions
in the future.
So if I teach you or show you on the same way it's a little bit simpler.
So this is what Johnson as we just get square.
And if we drop something or we click something we just get the file upload and after we upload it you
know it's going to go right here.
So this is what we get whenever we drop or we do something we upload something drop on drop method drop
and we pass the files.
So whenever we get on drop we going to do that requests to our server and stored images enclaves in
very very simple that that's good.
So let's go back to our project and start with this.
We will need a few things.
So import import.
And first we need dropzone and we've already installed it.
So if you check it under dependencies you can and you can see it there.
Jubb zone right.
The next thing it's important.
The board actually knows I'm not going to go through a redux.
I'm just going to use the NEC network request from here a little bit simpler than we need.
Awesome.
So import phones.
Oh and it's fun.
Awesome icon from that weird forward.
Awesome.
And react for it.
Awesome or phantasm.
Now the icons we need is just one icon.
It's a plus.
And then circle from.
And now we need the fort.
Awesome but it's going to be free solid.
All right.
Forget.
We need one more thing.
I'm going to import a circular and then progress from you guessed it material.
I this is the last of the imports.
So add material I core and that which is being circular or progress.
Good.
You're done with the imports.
If you check the example on dropzone they're using a constructor.
So let me just do this constructor open and close we do we pass the super and then we say this that
state this is exampled that they are giving us right now of course this is a template they give us the
Cubas but you can do something like state on this new version of react.
We just can do state inside state will be handled by reactive backgrounds and it's the same thing than
doing this all right.
So once we are inside the state we need two states the app loaded just like this and then files with
a capital F files which is going to be starting as an array and empty.
Right.
And then we have to get a different property called uploading which is false.
And this this property is going to be like if we are uploading with Send that we showed true changes
to true.
And we will show this progress and whenever we are done uploading images and we get a response we will
change it back to false and hide.
They progress real simple.
So right.
Let's go to the render method.
So on the render what we do pretty much is to put a dev are going to put it inside of a section just
like this.
Let me do it right.
Section right inside of a section I will create a song so Deb I can add a class name of dropzone and
I going add the class clear does OK.
Now instead of here we will put the actual job something you know that square where we can drop things.
So we will need to bring dropzone from the top so dropzone and we need no opening close closed.
Now instead of the drop zone we need to pass them some properties.
Now we have this drop method that is going to fire every time we drop something.
So we say on drop in all of this is of course on the documentation of dropzone.
So whenever we drop some something we're going to get the event.
So we need to fire our function calls on drop could be called something else and we passed the event
right.
So this is our function this is not from dropsonde.
The only thing from Dab-Dab zone is this one the only thing we get is the event and then we run a function.
Right now you get the option multiple.
And in this case we upload images at one image at a time.
So it's false.
And then I get to add a class name of drop stone underscore box.
Right.
So instead of the job.
I want to add this icon.
So I'm going to say Dave I'm going to add a class and this is my code.
Is our code a class name of rap.
And I'm going to add that font.
Awesome icon.
So let me do it right font.
Awesome icon opening close and we need to pass the name of the icon which is a plus circle.
Breguet.
So in theory we should be getting something and we do.
You know we get this.
Now if I click it we get the file abla.
So that works.
Of course we need to do a lot more but at least that works.
All right.
So what else.
After the drop zone right after we upload an image what I want to do I want to show the images right
here.
I want to just kind of push inside of of an array and show the images right here.
So I'm going to create a function right here that says show uploaded images and this of course dysfunction
doesn't exist.
I'm going to create it and I'm going to leave it alone.
Right.
We're going to do it later of course.
Now whenever we are uploading remember that I want to show this progress bar so I'm going to create
one more rule and this one will be checking that this state that uploading now if it's true will show
the box and if it's not we will just return NULL.
And now this is something I've added after the project was completed.
So it's going to look a little bit weird going to add the class name of dropsonde box same box but I'm
adding some styles because again I am doing this after the project was completed when I was creating
the project.
So I'm going to change the text line to center.
Or you can skip this if you wish if you wish it to look ugly but the padding top of 60 pixels didn't
do much right here.
And of course here we will add the circular progress sort of circular progress.
We're going to close that.
And of course we need to pass some props.
We're going to change the style of the color.
So color opening close and I'm going to change again to put color 0 0 B C D for.
All right.
Kind of a bluish color.
And then the thickness and the thickness are going to put seven which is the biggest one.
The big one.
Yeah that's great of course we don't see it until we start uploading and check if the central when too
long now that we are going to do one more thing before we move on we go to the next section to finish.
So.
So whenever we drop we know that we are fighting this.
So we're going to go right here and say drop equals to a function and then we just do something and
what we get.
Of course it's just like we spoke before is the event.
Right now this event it's actually the files we are clicking on here.
Right.
It's opening the files when we just do it on the files.
When I do open that is when the this job is going to fire.
Of course we are getting an error message but that is OK.
So this is data when the dropzone fires this event.
So I'm going to go right here and say event going to say files.
Like.
And right here we're going to get the files going to say console log files just to see what we get are
going to inspect going into the dropzone maybe upload a file and go to console and you know we get the
files and this is just a regular is how HDMI works.
You know the regular javascript nothing new so far.
Right here it's not react.
It's not a node or whatever.
It's just a regular javascript NHT now.
So when we get the on on drop of course we need to do a bunch of things we need to go grab the files
and go to the server.
We didn't have a route for this.
We can create pretty much all the logic right now.
But then on the next section we're going to go to the server and create a route to handle the upload.
So first on the set state what I want to do I want to say that now we are uploading so uploading and
then true.
So we will get that progress.
Now we need to do the form data.
And again this is just how we handle files on the web are going to create a new form data just like
this form data right.
Then of course we need to config whenever we do a post we need to set headers of multi-stop multipart
form data.
So Konst config config.
All right.
This is going to be equal to I'm going to say headers Collon and this and this is how we going to be
using inside access.
That's why I'm doing this just like this.
So we need a content than a type and the content type is going to be equal to multipart from data.
So multipart form form data by Burguet this is done.
Now whenever we create a new form data just like this we need to append the files to that form data.
So I'm going to make a reference to form data that penned and then I'm going to use the keyword file.
And this is the keyword we're going to be catching from the server to get the actual files.
So files are going to be passing the zero because we have one file and this is of course the way we
get it.
So now we need to do the actual posting.
So we're going to do a post request to and I'm going to set the route right here.
It's up for Slash API for Slash users for Slash and upload image.
If you're asking yourself why are you using users.
Well the thing is that the user only administer a million users.
And our users can upload this.
So again we're going to be using just users because the user is uploading the image to cloud denarii.
Then of course we get a start on a product but doesn't matter.
You know the one that the DPD the person that is doing the upload is just an open air user.
So that's why I'm using users.
And of course later you might be doing a lot of uploading for different sections so you just have one
single route for uploading images.
You don't have many.
So we need to pass to form data and we are almost done then coma and we need to pass that config.
So we do the config.
All right.
So then of course we get a promise opening close we get the response and after the response we do something.
So what are we going to be doing at the end.
It's going to be setting state so there's not set state opening close.
We're going to set that uploading back to falls because we are not uploading anymore.
We got a response and then we need to set the uploaded files.
Going to say uploaded files.
And if you remember this is of course an array.
Now maybe you're uploading images and you are uploading the third or fourth image.
It's not the first one.
So what you we need to do is to concatenate with whenever you get from the previews upload.
So you might have more files right here.
So what we do we just say that that does not state that uploaded files and this array will be equal
to whatever we get from the response plus all the previous files we had on that array.
Of course from the server we going to get a response.
So then I'm going to put the response that data now the response.
Are we going to handle it we're going to modify the response we get from cloud Inari and we will send
the response just the way we want it.
We want directly from the server.
All right so once we set the state what we will need to do is to go back to the parent component and
tell them OK I do have new images just add them to your form data state.
Right.
Of course we have the function.
So we need to do it.
But I'm going to put it right here is a callback of the said State.
We say this the props.
And remember we are already passing let go here.
We are already passing the props so it calls images handler.
Right.
And what are we going to be sending back to the parent component.
Well the uploaded files so I'm going to say is that state that uploaded files.
All right man.
That is it.
Of course we need to do more things right here.
And remember that whenever we set up we upload something we do are we said.
Right.
So we need to catch that as well.
But again went too long now.
The section went too long.
So let's go to the next one and we will go to the server and create the route so we can finally upload
the image.