All right.
So let's do the server.
So I going to go to the server digests and before we can start creating the route we need to use some
more things right here.
And we've already installed them inside of the package.
Jason so we can use this express formidable and the cloud in every connector are going to go to the
server and start requiring.
And of course I'm going to explain you why we bringing that we are bringing this so Konst formidable
equals require require opening close and it's called Xpress formidable.
So just like we're doing right here whenever we get a request with Jason we use the body parser whenever
we want cookies.
We are using this middleware cookie parser.
We're formidable.
It's pretty much the same thing.
Whenever we get a request that has files inside we use formidable to help us get the files.
That is it.
So then of course we need to set up coding houri.
So chlo the Nyree are equals to require open and close.
And we said cloud Narey right.
Get it right here.
Now importing the cloud in every file.
It's not enough.
We need to configure the cloud in every instance with the API keys we get right here.
So what I'm going to do when we go wrong here at the bottom I'm going to make a reference to that cloud
in every instance and say config we're going to use that method.
It's actually a method from them.
So whenever we do config we need to pass three different things we need to pass a cloud name.
We need to give going to set it empty for now coma we need an API key API key to nothing.
And then we need an API secret just like this.
All right.
So now this.
The keys and the secret and the club name.
They will be stored on the node environments are the environment virals ride.
So if they are inside of the environment bbls we need to set it on the EMV.
And whenever we go to production we need to set the Virals right there.
Right.
That's why we are using the dot M-B.
So of course you can go to cloud named API you can and you can just copy them.
I'm going to have them right here so I'm going to paste right here.
So cloud we are going to create a cloud name cloud API key and cloud API secret just paste them tried
to create your own account don't use mine if you can of course.
And now since we have everything inside the data EMV we can use it right here because we are requiring
that thought be all right.
That is good.
So I'm going to go here.
And again the same process that TMB and the key word for the cloud name is going to be cloud name.
I'm doing a copy paste so I can avoid mistakes.
So I've got the second one is the API key.
So I'm going to say process that EMV and the name is going to be cloud API key.
You can call this whatever you want.
It's completely up to you then process that M-B and it's the cloud API secret or Burguet.
So we are done with this.
So I'm going to answer right here.
You know it's Mark it's so me.
You're wrong.
Why am I wrong.
Am I wrong.
There we go.
So now we have all the information we need to perform.
Of course the uploader.
Now we need route.
Now if you remember we are using a user api for this.
The user around.
So we're going to do a post with API for Slash users just like we get it right here.
API users so I'm going to go and do it at the bottom of users.
Why not.
So it's app that post of course opening close and we pass the API that users and the ride we are using
which is upload image right upload image.
All right.
Now of course we need to do more things right here because whenever we get a post it means that we are
adding data to some place.
So for this one we need the AUF.
And of course we need the admin.
Now since we are getting data from the files and we are using formidable we're going to use formidable
as a middleware and at the very end whenever this is done we will get that request and that response.
Right.
So it's like a chain now uploading to cloud the Narey.
It's so simple.
We use cloud denarii dot we use the key or the uploader.
And then we do upload.
Open and close now inside of the upload.
Sorry.
We need to pass two things.
One is that we want to upload and then the kind of for the callback.
All right.
So they actually have three arguments.
It's the what we need to upload the callback.
And this is weird.
And then the configuration.
Yeah.
That is the way it works.
So how can we get the data we are posting from within the middleware.
Formidable.
So we have it inside request that files and that file Remember we are using that keyboard file right
here.
If we had images right here that would be images instead of file.
And then we say path and it's going to get it from there because everything is memory of course then
we get the callback.
So I'm going to do this.
And the third one.
The third argument is going to be an object with the configuration.
Right.
OK.
So first I'm going to do the configuration and I'm going to.
And then I'm going to go to the of the other one.
So we get a public I.D. and the public I.D. would be you know what are you going to use to display the
image.
You know the idea of the public file so you can use whatever you want right here going to do something
very simple and to use templates strengths.
And I got to say that the name to date now.
Now you can attach whatever you want right here.
Maybe you want to create maybe some hash.
So of course you can do the hash right here.
Doesn't matter is completely up to you.
Then it coma.
And now we have an option that says that it's called resource type.
So we source underscore and then type we can tell cautionary what what is the kind of file we are uploading
now.
If you don't really know or you know you don't really care much.
You can set it to auto.
So if you're using a G they will recognize that you're using a JPT that's it.
Or maybe a PMG or something like that.
So.
OK.
And of course you get a lot more configurations.
You can even do transforms transform stipes which sample you upload an image and you want to crop it
maybe on a 200 200.
You can use transformations right here and store the image in different formats so you can do that.
It's Turner it's it works really really get used to it in the past.
Never had a problem.
But of course we're going to do something very simple right here.
So on the callback whenever you do the upload to clouting Ari now we will come back and then trigger
this callback function.
And this one of course will get a result as an argument.
And inside of the result we will get all the information we need about that file and we're going to
do console log.
And that result right.
And of course we need to send the response back from this route if not you know everything is going
to fail.
We're going to get a frozen screen.
So I'm going to go and say responds sorry that status I'm not out of that cold yet.
Then it's status 200 do that.
And we do a send.
So whenever we send something we're going to send the same thing we did right here file upload notice
that we are getting the response data and everything else so we are just need to return whenever we
are going to be using as a value on the on the parent component.
So we need to be careful right here.
Now I did cancel logs so we can inspect what we get back from it from a coronary.
And it's a pretty long object.
We have a lot of things right now.
The only thing I want to return from this route.
It's the public I.D. and the u r l where we can you know get the image and maybe show it right here.
So I'm going to go and say public I.D. equals real salt dot and that public I.D..
All right.
CONAN And then I'm going to be passing the urinal so we can get to two entries right here we solved
that.
You are al and that is Ed man.
So now of course we're going to try to blow something and we're going to get a console log on the server
on the terminal and then we should be getting our response back from to our client to the client side.
And just for fun I'm going to do the same thing on the console whatever.
What happen.
Cancel that log.
And then responds that data.
Right.
Well see if this works.
Hopefully there are no mistakes.
Of course it could happen that we get sent.
We have some mistakes that it's normal.
So are going to reload the application are going to bring the inspect and the cons..
All right.
That's right you blow something up.
Oh and one more thing in the inside of the project inside public an image just you know the folder I
gave you you have a guitar.
And you have like seven guitars so you don't need to search.
They are all honest because I went to their website and get that I got that image from there.
And but you know if you want to go to to the to the browser and get your images.
That's cool.
No problem.
So like guitar's going to it's like the R and going to blow this one.
And whenever we upload it we get a mistake.
All right.
So that is get old.
Actually it's not that good but that's OK.
We get an internal server error.
So local host API users upload images so upload an image or images image the route API users for Slash.
All right.
So let's do the following.
This actually might happen.
We installed new dependencies so maybe we need to.
Oh cannot we property file fun defined ha.
Right ok.
Um no.
I know what is wrong.
Maybe you saw it and didn't fix it.
I'm going to fix it right here with you right here.
Says on the server and always you always need to check the server.
You know the command so it cannot read property file of undefined an outpost.
All right so a request file file no files or go.
Hopefully everything is OK.
So let's try it again.
I've got to reload the application.
I'm going to try and send the same image.
And I do open we get no mistake.
And at the end of course we get a response but now we need of course to create a function that rules
this part.
But we get something back from the server which is the public I.D. and we get the your L and this is
a URL where we can actually do some copy pasting on the browser.
And you know get the image right.
OK.
That's good.
So let me show you what we get on the server.
This is the whole object that they give you and this might be my change of course.
If you pass more more things you might be getting a trim your e-mail or maybe something else you need
to check the of course the documentation.
It's pretty well documented.
So you get the public I.D. and you are now you're just using this once but you get how much is the image.
What was that tie your tie.
You know they were sourced type when it was created.
You get a lot of things.
And of course you get the original file name.
All right.
So you can use whatever you want right here.
Depends on the on your application.
All right.
But the important thing right now is that we are getting our response right.
We're getting our response right here.
So whenever we get a response.
And if I upload a new one let's see this one.
Whenever I upload it and we get it.
So of course now on the state since we are doing.
Let me go here since we are doing this we can have on the state two images and our parent component
is going to be receiving two images right.
All right.
OK.
So now what are we going to do before we go to the parent begin to do the show uploaded images we can
catch whatever we have inside this uploaded files and begin to show it right here.
Right let's do the show uploaded images function.
So I'm going to go here and what we need to do is pretty pretty simple.
We just return whatever we have inside the uploaded files.
Right.
We just do a map.
So I'm going to say does that state that uploaded files and first I'm going to change this.
Let me copy this because we want to return some GSX.
So we need to do this.
So this that state that uploaded files that map.
And then we do we get the item.
And again there's no need to do this.
We get the item and we just return again more GSX.
So Dave open it close and we will use that drop soap box class name right here.
Drop soap box.
Then of course this needs a key.
So I'm going to add a key and the key is going to be equal to.
And remember that if we get two things that you are l and the public I.D. I'm going to say item that
public I.D. You could use whatever you want right here maybe the iteration.
All right.
Now later when we have the when you get the image right here.
When I went to click it if I want to remove it.
So I'm going to do something very simple.
I'm going to add an unclick of course in real life.
This is going to get much complicated.
You need more success in real life.
This is going to create on remove that begin to do later.
So this remove will go to cloud denarii and remove the image.
Right.
Because again if you don't need the image maybe it's better to remove it.
And whenever we remove it I'm going to be passing the item that the public and the ID and of course
on the on remove.
I'm going to pass the I.D. right.
Of course we're going to do this later because we need to create a route to unset the image from cloud
Inari.
But it's it's going to be real simple.
So OK.
So after the remove of course we need to show something.
Just like with it with the wrap right here with wrap we do pretty much the same thing.
So we just create a div with the wrap inside and the wrap will contain as a background image.
The file that we just uploaded.
So I'm going to go right here at the bottom.
Maybe some space and I'm going to say OK.
I want the class name of rap but as I said I also want the background image.
So I'm going to say background.
Open it close.
We just passed a u r l and then we say open and then item dot and you are l and it's going to be a note.
Repeat Repeat.
All right.
This is done.
So let's see what happens.
Of course the server needs to restart are going at it going to maybe a different one.
Why not this one.
I'm going to upload it and when we get the response we get the image.
Now if you're if I have a new one this one should be staying here and we can add one right there.
So let me.
There we go.
So going to upload this one
right.
All right.
OK.
So we get it we get it works.
So.
So when I click I want to remove it.
Of course now nothing is going to happen when we click it because nothing is happening right here now
in real life you might be creating a Hoeber where you can show something maybe a next or something or
move.
I'm not going to do it because it's something very simple and it's going to take us time and we need
to do us still we need to do a lot of things right.
OK.
So what we are able to create images now what is what is happening right now is that when we added We're
going to images that handler and we are saying OK now you get the uploaded files so we need to go back
to our product and go to the images handler because we are getting new images and you know process and
add them to the state.
You're not really doing this.
So let's do it right now.
OK.
So the images handler.
It's very simple.
We will be getting some images and we will create a new form data.
So I'm going to say new form data and this new form data equals something.
So dot dot dot this dot state that form data like before we are just making a copy of the form data.
Now what we want to do we want to enter images and add the value add to the value whatever image we
get from here.
So I'm going to access this form data I can access the key of images because that's where we are storing
everything.
And then say OK now the value of this one it's whatever we get back from Image.
Yes.
All right.
And that is it of course if the case is that the new form data images has a ballad of fonts we just
need to change it.
So I'm going to say valid just like this.
Ballasted equals to true.
Because you know just in case.
And then of course which is this.
That said state opening close and we're going to say that form data that we have on the state let me
do it right form data contains a new contains the you from data which just updating the state.
All right.
OK.
Looks nice.
Of course we're not going to really see it right now.
We reload.
You're not going to really get it because this happens when we submit the form and we need to do a few
things before we go there.
Just one thing we need to add some rules to the validation but again went too long going to go to the
next one.
Do finish with the data to submit and we're going to do the on remove.
So we can remove the image.
And that is that we are done with the file upload.