Good let's finish this.
So OK so now what we need to do we need to do that we move image.
But first I want to go back to the images hndler and well another image is remember that for example
when we submit the form right after wards we set the fields.
So this one is going to be a little bit weird because all the fields if you go to the when we find it
we go to the utility and the form actions whenever we we set fields.
We are we setting this to a string and the array of images.
The images actually turn right.
So where we need to do is side form actions that well there's actually two things you can do.
You can create a conditional right here and catch the key it's images.
So by default with images we will have an array.
So if it's images we just set it back to an array.
If not you'd set it back to a single string and empty or you can since we are passing and that's that's
why we are doing we are passing the keyboard right here.
Products you can evaluate if you have products and then you can evaluate if you have an image and then
reset it to you know the NRA going to do it just like that.
I got to say if it was like the other one sorry going to say else.
So if key Tribble equal images just like this.
Then I'm going to grab and do the new form data value just like this.
I'm going to copy this one at the bottom and I'm going to set it to an end right.
And if not and it still change it to a string that is it you can do the same thing with ballot.
But we are actually on the on the on right here whenever we we've said everything we are doing that
job right there.
That is good you know.
So now let's do the file upload on remove.
Whenever we click the image which is removed from the server and of course for this we need to create
a route.
So first let's create that request right here so we can clear that I'm going to go and say Actually
those that get open and close and the request that you know your bill is going to be for Slash API for
Slash usurps camp plural and then remove image and I get to use Christ's drinks.
Why.
Because we just need to pass on one value.
So whenever we do remove We are passing the public ID and that is the only thing we need with Clogher
Narey to remove the image.
So we're going to say public public and then I.D. and it's equal to you know the IP we are passing as
argument right here.
So Id then of course we will get a response so we get a response and you might do this in a different
way.
For example I'm going to do.
I'm going to filter everything and read and read and then send the state back.
But you might be evaluating that response because maybe the response from the Claudian Ari maybe the
server was down or something like that and instead of a good response you get a response.
So you can check right here if the response.
It's not equal to true or something you get back from the server.
And then of course execute whatever you want to execute.
But I'm not going to do it because it's going to take us more time and I don't really want to do it.
And besides if you are not if you were able to upload the image most likely you were not able to remove
the image right because the servers now.
Right.
That's fine.
So since we are deleting the image we have the ID and the ID we have it right here we have a set of
elements and inside of course the I.D..
So what we need to do we need to filter.
We need to remove that image from the from the state.
So going to create a new viral called Images equal to this.
That state that uploaded files and we're going to do a simple feature.
Now this filter of course we need to run a function and we're going to pass an item on each iteration
and afterwards of course we run something.
Now what we need to do whenever we use a filter we need to return something and create a new array.
So we're going to return all the entries so long as they don't have the idea that we are passing because
you know it was removed from the server.
So I'm going to say item that public I.D. It's different than the ID.
And this will generate a new array without that particular ID is going to remove that entry.
And then of course we just said the state so this that set stayed pretty close.
And we say that now uploaded files is going to be equal to the Whenever we get back from images.
And of course since we are updating the state right here on this we need to tell the parent that now
the images changed so this that Probs not images handler opening close and we pass the new state of
images just like this.
All right.
So now of course we need to create this route.
We don't have this route so let's go to the server and I am going to go and maybe create it right here
at the bottom.
Now to remove an image from Cliveden.
Again it's just like uploading images.
It's very very simple.
So we can have an app that get open and close the route.
It's still forced lasht API for Shlash users and then remove image.
We still need the south and the admin.
And now this time we don't need formidable because we're not sending files right.
We just go to the callback so request and response.
Right.
So we will be getting from the query from sequestering the image IDs.
So Image ID or it could be public ID.
It's actually the public ID but doesn't matter.
So we get the request that query that and then public ID right.
So now we have the ID we need to tell clouting houri to Ansted this image.
So we say cloud denarii dot uploader dot this Troy.
Open and close.
And again the first argument is going to be the idea of whenever we want to destroy.
And then of course we get the callback.
So open it close run a callback.
Now this callback contains an error and this is where you can catch that error and send that response.
And of course catch it from the client and do something else.
So a result that is the second argument.
OK.
So if we do get an error we are going to send an error back so error we can every turn responds that
Jason at this point is not necessary because we are not catching it from the client.
So were going to say success falls.
So now in the kind you can check for success and if its true you move forward.
If its not to do something else.
But for now we're just going to send something simple status of 200 and then send.
OK.
You know send something like this send.
And that is this will we will remove the image from cloud.
So let's let's try it.
So for go to add product up file AB load we know that we have the unclick on the remove.
So hopefully everything is going to work I'm going to add an image.
Whatever doesn't matter.
And if I click at uncut promise request fail arrived a new problem.
So users in public ID and from here from the server we are not getting anything.
All right.
OK so it's four or four.
Maybe the route.
It's incorrect.
So public ID and if I go to the server API of course the route is incorrect.
That's why we get a 4 or 4.
It's not finding the correct route.
So file upload its users.
That is the problem.
So API users now should be working.
That's right again.
So it's impossible to code without making mistakes.
You know that even do.
I'm I'm looking at the final code.
I click it and he gets removed.
Right.
If of course if we go to clown denarii we are not going to get that image of course.
I mean just reloaded it was the guitar.
You know the back of the guitar is a little bit slow.
And you know we get a free account so it should be slow.
So there we go.
We can get it right here.
Let me just upload maybe a different image something that we we actually don't have.
I don't like that guitar or no way at it.
That's.
This is my guitar.
So such a good guitar man.
Not for everyone.
It's just for I would say professional but you need to have some mileage before grabbing that guitar.
So here we get it.
Very good man.
Everything works.
So I'm going to delete it and I'm going to go back and we shouldn't have the image anymore.
So we don't get it.
I mean so that is good.
Works.
Now before we move forward we need to check that everything gets uploaded to the server.
Now again before I do that we want to handle the success.
What happens when we finish uploading.
And we said everything if that happens we will not be able to reset the images.
We are we setting everything else but not the images.
Right.
So we need to unset the images from within the file upload component.
When ever we said we will reset products but not file upload.
If you remember we passed a property called reset.
So whenever we catch the success whenever it changes to true begin to catch it from here and change
the uploaded files back to an empty array.
It's actually something very simple.
There are many ways to do it but I'm going to show you this way some from the file upload when what
I wanted to do I went to get that derived state from prop's we could do that just like this.
So open it close and we will get prop's coma and this state.
Now we want to do it that if I get the prompts and resets with the queue we're true you know it's true
props and then reset.
Then we want to return state with the uploaded files back to nothing.
All right.
And of course if nothing happens we will return NULL.
OK.
We are.
We are done.
We just need to test that everything works and we just move forward to the next section.
All right.
So I'm going to reload the application again to add an image.
I'm going to add maybe a different guitar.
Ivan is the R.G. to 5:5 is a good guitar.
This one is the I believe it's a version from the steep Bay guitar and maybe a couple of more one more
one more OK.
So their name is RG to 5:5.
We get that scription going to copy from.
What was the name of this.
The lawyer remembers them and a mental breakdown right there.
So on them copy something whatever it doesn't matter.
A copy of this.
Why not now maybe something small.
Maybe not too much text.
I'm going to copy.
I'm going to paste.
Cut the price for this guitar at least 151.
Ok now it isn't even us it's shipping.
Yes because it's an expensive guitar.
We do have it in stock now.
I believe they are older and the frets of course 24 frets and publish is going to be public.
All right.
So let's see.
This is the moment of the truth.
I'm going to add product and we get success.
And if you go to the state we will of course we removed it.
So let's check the rebel mood go products.
And we got the R.G. to 5:5.
Everything is true.
Everything is good.
And if we go to images we have three fields with images.
Right.
So in theory in theory if you go to guitars we should be able to see it.
So there we go.
We get the first image of the ivory All right.
OK.
So we are done with this.
I'm going to snip everything.
So you can compare code or you know maybe something is not working on yours.
So you can check you know my code and on the next section we're going to do something related instead
of app products begin to finish with the admin parts.
I know that it's boring but it's not going to take this long.
There are going to be it's going to be very fast maybe 10 10 or 20 minutes on each and then we do it
to do the match category so we can and you can terrorist and the site Imphal and for this one we need
to create a new model.
So we still need to do a few things but again we're not going to spend a lot of time there they're going
to be very very simple.
And then we're going to go to be Tarz.
And whenever we view a product we're going to get the product and after we do that then we can to go
to all the logic inside the user information and then my cart ride whenever we add something to the
cart.
We want to update the number right here and whenever we go to my card we can see all the items in the
Do the math.
And how many will the how many we need to pay the quantity and everything else it's going to be a little
bit long.
And then of course we're going to use paypal the sandbox of PayPal.
All right.
So again we still need to do a lot of things.
So let's get the side info and demands could take a piece out of the way so we can go to the user account.