OK so now we can do the managed categories.
So if I go to manage categories of course we don't get anything but we will get the user lay out and
we will add categories just like DeFrantz and the woods.
And we will create two different components because they are two different models.
And then of course we will create a new component that will rule them all.
Just like The Lord Of The Rings now we are not going to do anything new.
Not at all.
Hear it's going to create forums and update you know the state and go to probs.
We already did this.
You're not going to learn anything new right here.
So if you wish for it that you manage France and the manager woods you just can go to the section where
we move forward of a different to a different topic and you just can copy the code and you know get
it done.
If you don't want to do it again you're are not learning anything you write here.
Right now you're not going to learn.
So OK.
So if you still want to do what I want to do with me of course you have the chance of do it.
So first we need to create a ramp for this and a component that will rule everything.
So I'm going to go inside admin and create new file called manage and then categories that jazz let
me do it right.
Taggart's So this is going to be a reacts.
The last component just like that and then manage categories.
All right of course we need to use a user layout so import user layout from and are going to do capital
L or we go from and it's dot dot for Slash.
One more time one more time.
And then we get a chose C and then for Slash and then user.
Now we will have two different components.
We need to include it right now so I'm going to create the components right now and wrap everything
inside the user layout.
So I'm going to go to admen create a new file starts in the same way with manager underscore and there
will be categories that G-S and I are to create a new one called manage.
And then what's that jazz.
First we're going to do the manage the Manage Oh and same name is going to be mench brands.
I'm sorry if this so let me just open the one that it's empty and it's kind of weird that it led me
at the same name.
This is not very common.
So I'm going to delete categories and say brands.
This is what we're going to be doing here.
OK.
So instead of here I'm going to import the manage and then Brant's from Dad forward slash and then match.
France and the same thing with the other one but it's going to be managed.
It's so simple right now manage what's right.
Of course I need to include them right here so I'm going to make a reference to this manage brands and
then manage what could be managed Woods plural OK.
Now I'm going to go to manage Brant's creed every act class based component because they are going to
be a class and then say manage.
And then Brant's same thing and are going to go to manage woods and do pretty much the same things are
going to copy and paste.
And this one is going to be words woods and then brands.
Oh sorry what's And what's OK.
So on this one I'm going to say a word and the other one.
It's brand.
Right.
So at least we can get something on the screen.
Of course we need to create a route.
So let's go two routes and we need to include the first the parent component we'll just manage categories.
So import MENASCHE categories.
Right.
It's from that forward slash components for Slash.
We go inside user we go inside admen and then managed categories.
Now this is going to be a restricted restricted route.
So I'm going to go to the upper part and then it's admen and then manage categories.
And of course we use the correct components manage.
I mean the mistake right here.
Manage categories manage categories Burguet.
So we get Brant's or I've managed categories.
We are not getting the check why this is why it save the file.
So it's going to reload and get brands and books.
OK.
So let's begin with Brandt's.
This is for simple.
We need to import a lot of things and most of the things we've already kind of did this.
So if we go to add product could it go at the top and we need a few things from here.
Right.
We need to form fields.
We need to update that we need to form actions are going to go and paste it and from different actions
we need the update to generate data and that is form ballot.
And the reset fields that populate options not really we don't need it.
We will use connect.
So I'm going to import connect and then action products.
They're going to copy that code and paste it.
Now here are the bomb.
I'm going to leave the app open because we can begin to use it in a couple of minutes.
So right now we just need to use get France from here.
It's going to delete everything else later we can any to create a new a new dispatch in your function
so we can add a brand because we don't have that route.
We have the route on server but we don't have a function.
So we need to state again we are working with forums so we're going to create a state and now the state
is going to be very simple.
We have a form for a forum success and we still get a form data.
So I'm going to go and copy this.
And of course close the form data.
So the only thing we add is the name of the brand.
So again going copy name I'm going to go back to France and then paste it.
And that is it.
This was fast.
All right.
The only thing we need to do is to change the attack which is going to be I don't know brand name.
And then of course brand and we are using name and not brand because among geuss we store this name
inside the brand model enter you enter the brand.
Required true but false touch false and show label could be true.
That's fine.
You're not going to use showily or just going to delete it and the labels well.
OK so now what we need to do first I would like to show the existing brands right here and in the ride
I would like to get an input so I can you know select that out of brand and then it will be reflected
right here.
That's what we're going to be doing.
So of course we need some kind of a layout for this.
So let's go to the upper.
The bottom of the render right here.
I'm going to add a class name and the class name it's admin underscore category underscore wrapper or.
And of course I'm going to add a title of brands and I'm going to wrap some are going to put up one
more wrapper.
So a class name equals to admen underscore to and that it column.
OK so we can get inside of each column two sides.
The one of the left and the one in the right.
So I need to create a left in it.
Right.
So class name laughed and the old one the other one.
It's going to be right.
So on the right one will get the forms I'm going to say.
Right and I'm going to type o form whatever.
Now what I want to do I want to render a container with all the brands.
So I'm going to create a div very simple class name.
And again to say Brant's capital.
Sorry plural.
And then container.
Now of course we are not going to get anything right here.
But you know right now we can see that we got something right here.
H.H. but that's OK.
So I want to render all of this inside of a function.
So this show category and that items.
This is the name of my function you can call this whatever you want.
So I'm going to say equal to a function and then of course we will do something.
So what we will need to do here is to graph the brands we have inside of the inside of the props.
We can do a request.
Get a triggered this get Brandt's begin to get the brands and once they are inside Propst we can grab
the props and we can loop them right.
All right.
Very very simple.
I already did this.
So of course right here we will return some GSX.
But for now it's just going to leave like this because we're going to do it in a minute.
First we're going to do the request of getting the Brandts.
OK.
So I'm going to go right here the one and we need to do component mount opening close.
I'm going to make a reference to this that props and then I get a dispatch something.
And I gotta get the operands.
Now there's that thing missing is that we don't have Connect frank here.
So this will never work.
So I'm going to go and say connect open and close and then we enclose the managed brands.
Right now we need the maps state of props to inject the prompts in this component.
So map state to prop's we don't need the prompts and this one will be going to products and we will
say state products and go in a little bit fast because guess again could it did this at this point.
It should be mastering all of this.
What we are doing.
So if we get the brands and in theory inside prompts we should be getting the state.
And we do we get Brandt's right here.
We'll be open and we have one two three four and we have many more.
All right.
OK.
So now we're going to get to grab the brands from these props that products that and brands.
Right.
And we can loop them inside of the show category.
That's why we are using that function.
So now we will be returning some GSX.
So we do this the probs that products that Brandt's And if we do get this we're going to return something.
If not you're not going to do anything because we don't have a valid rate.
So this prompts the products that Brandt's we could create a Konst someplace where we can store this
promise of products that Brandts or something like that.
So map up amp no map map opening close and we will be passing the item and iteration.
I don't know why every time I type item the iteration.
OK.
So we will be returning something simple.
It's just a div with like with an item inside.
So class name category item and we need to add a key and the key is going to be equal to item dot ID
underscore ID and the.
And then of course the name so item that name.
All right.
So this is going to loop whatever we have inside Brandt's and return a div for each and then we can
show it right here inside of a Brandt's container and that is what we get.
Right.
Very good.
We're not going to create a function to delete Brandt's because again it's really simple and you can
do it.
You can do it on your own.
No problem.
You shouldn't have a problem doing this.
So now we're going to do the inter brand.
Can it go in and create that form.
Right because we need to made a new brand.
So I'm going to go to the right and we're going to do the same thing then add products for now that
we go here which is save some time going to go to form.
I'm going to pace that and of course close the form.
Right.
That is that we don't have a submit form we're going to create in a minute now instead of here we just
get one single form element.
So I'm going to copy the form field of name because we have the same key so name is still name and everything
stays the same.
And I got a copy of the bond and we have the Erol labels.
So I'm going to copy this and paste it right here.
We could do a success but not going to do it.
So at product in theory is going to be at brand and then please check your data.
If you have a message again and we can add just as a success or a message or a success message right
here.
OK.
Everything looks nice.
Now we need to bring the uptick in the support for him because if not everything is going to fail.
And so far we are good.
You're getting the input.
All right.
So I'm going to go over here at the top on the products.
I'm going to copy the submit form and first the update form.
This is something that we really really need.
So going a pace that right here the top every time we update form this function will cooking an update
to it.
And of course it's not France I'm sorry it's not products it's going to be brands and everything else
stays same.
Same thing for the submit form.
So I'm going to copy submit.
Going to go to manage Brown's pasted at the bottom and right now we need to change Brant's right here.
I'm going to delete all of this and say console log data to submit.
Right.
So let's see what happens.
I'm going to go to the counsel law to the counsel actually counsel.
I'm going to type whatever and we get name whatever let's get.
Of course we need to reset a feel after we submit to form but we are not there yet.
So OK.
So why do we need to do now.
We need to create new action so we can dispatch and action and you know store something on the server.
And if you remember we already have that route.
So let me go here right here.
We have the post and the brand.
All right.
So let's do that right now.
So let's go to the actions when we find it prudent actions we need to create a type and I'm going to
call it ab brand right here we have to get get Branston going at it.
Just below that at brands could be brand because you know we are getting just one brand.
You're updating entery just one brand right.
Of course we don't have the time but I'm going to create right now.
I'm going to go here in after this export Export Konst brand and it's going to be at brand right.
Times.
We don't need any anymore.
So now I'm going to go where we have terrorists right here we have a terrorist and just below that get
France going to create the function to add a brand export function at brands opening close at brand
singler.
So we were going to get the data to have met and are going to add it right now I think and explain you
in a minute.
The existing brands brands.
So whenever we submit the foreign press submit right we go to the server and we're going to get only
one brand.
This is what's happening on the server.
We just returned that brand.
And the thing is that whenever you of course get return you need to update the state of France.
Remember that right here on the left we have a list of friends.
So well there's actually three three things you can do.
You can get the existing brands from the from the actual managed France ride that we get right here
from the company demand.
And you can merge the new brand that you just posted with the old brands and then return the whole state.
Right.
Or you can after that dispatch make a new request to get all the brands because.
But it makes no sense you're just making two requests or you can buy directly from the server whenever
you return something instead of returning a single brand.
Go to the brands and we turn the whole documents of France.
It's completely up to you.
So what I'm going to do I'm just going to merge the brands inside of the of the action right here.
So I'm got to create it right now.
We're not going to say Konst request equals X-posts post open and close.
There you are.
L is going to be pretty much the same parted server but it's Singler brand.
And then of course we pass that data to submit.
All right.
Then of course we will get a response.
Open and close again to do it here.
We get our response and response and I'm going to do something before I return something.
And just to clear that error.
I'm going to say return opening close type.
We will use the time I believe was at brand brand.
Let me find it.
There we go at brand coma and the payload it's equal to whatever we get back from their request.
Now we're going to modify the request like it will be for maybe the server was down and you got a different
response if you got the success false.
So in real life I'm not going to do it right here to save time but in real life you should be checking
the response.
You know if it's false or if it's true before you push new elements maybe you want to send an error
message maybe the server was down and you want to show an error message maybe something else went wrong.
Right.
And that's why you get a success false.
So you should always catch the false error.
And of course whenever you do then then you need to catch the error from the server and not from the
action that you're creating.
We are not doing a lot of this just to save time again.
So I'm going to create a Barville called Brandt's and then dot dot dot and we will grab the existing
Brandt's and I'm going to push it right here.
Right.
So now brands contain all the existing brands not the new one that we get from the response that they're
going to do.
Coma they're going to attach whatever we get from Bruin's pawns.
Rhys pongs dot data dot and we are returning a keyboard with brand.
So I just merge everything.
And then at the end of course we return something.
So what I'm going to be returning is the success that we get back.
We are returning we get two things back to success is the brand.
So I will send attached a response that data that success that Acoma and whatever I get from brands.
All right that is good.
So our brand now we'll get a request with two properties success and brands.
So we need to go to the producer let me go to the reducers so we can pretty much fantasists product.
We do serve get Brandt's now we have brand and after brands are going to do it right here.
So pretty simple we just need to get the brand so case ad brand right then return open and close dot
dot dot state.
And now we remember that we have two things.
We have the brands right.
And we have the brand.
Remember.
OK.
So the brand is going to be the success pretty much.
So I'm going to say at brand so I'm going to put right here that the action you know everything was
successful.
You don't really need to do this but just in case I'm going to put that the success scenario and then
of course we have the Brant's remember that when we get Brandt's we are storing everything inside brands.
So I'm going to say OK I want to update brands as well with whatever we get from action that payload
and Brant's ride brands just like this.
Let me put it right here.
It's a little bit better.
All right.
And that is it when the server returns the response with the Brandt's.
Of course we are all very good at reading the probs.
So the list will get updated.
Right.
That's what should happen in a in a real life scenario.
I'm not sure if this is going to work.
Of course we might need to do some testing.
So let me add one more.
I don't know a different brand.
Whatever writer doesn't matter are going to add the brand name writer.
OK.
Of course we need to search for this.
We need to go to the Manage Brandt's and dispatched a proper reaction.
We are not doing anything just yet.
I believe it went too long really long.
So let's go to the next one.
The only thing left is to do this.
It's going to take take us like three four minutes and then we're going to do the woods and the woods.
It's pretty much the same code than this.
The only difference is that we need to create the do and everything else.
But it's pretty much the same code is going to take us five minutes.
Well let's go to the next one.
Finish with the words and then start with the I'm sorry fringed with the Brandts and then start with
the what's.