OK so let's finish this.
We need to include to get Brandt's.
So remember the product actions we created the brands sorry the rants.
And one quick change I did success with 1c should be with two C's So now we need to go to the submit
form and instead of doing the Council look we need to dispatch the action right.
So we're going to go here on the bottom and say this not Probst that dispatch open and close and we
pass this brand.
If you remember this brand as a first argument it will take the data to submit and then the previous
you know the current state of all the brands and I'm going to store this inside of your existing brands
maybe with a capital P system Brandt's and this one is equal to whatever we get we get inside this stuff
prop's the products that Brandt's.
So this Prawle props props that products that brands right.
So instead of passing this string we just pass it like this.
All right.
Then of course the promise gets resolved.
So we will get a response and then we just do something.
Now we are now going to do something very special right here we're just going to listen for the success
of the payload.
We are not going to do the this that problem even though you could you could listen for that Probst
and then go to our brand to see if you get a success.
And then of course take action.
And but if we do that we will need to clear due clear brand then to change the brand to nothing.
So I'm going to take the simple road here the easy road.
So I'm going to go and say response that payload that success remember that from the action we get the
success so we can catch it from there.
If everything went okay then of course we want to do something.
So what we'll do we will reset reset fields and then hndler we don't have this function we can add
it right now of course if something goes wrong we're going to say this.
That said state and begin it add to form error to true for error.
Burguet so we don't have this function again to create it.
So we set fields handler open and closed and then we do something.
If you go to add product we can have this field and are we going to already get it right there.
So I'm going to copy the first lines right here.
The first one and the second one and we don't need to time out because we are not doing a form success
and we are not dispatching anything to clear the product in real life if you're not using the payload
as a validation of you know to check if everything went okay you should do the dispatch and that clear
just a heads up.
Okay.
So right here we get that we said form Hanafi of fuel handler and Brandt's and that is okay.
So everything should work.
We did it a little bit fast.
Everything was really fast.
So let's try it should be working and let's try it.
Okay.
So I'm going to add I don't know Buddha or whatever not that a real name but doesn't matter a real name
for guitars of these.
So going at it ok it clears and we go to Buda.
All right.
So again this was really simple.
We could you know add an hour to scroll then go to the bottom and show you know successfully added.
But again we kind of already did this.
There's no need to do this.
I'm just adding because I'm trying to get the project as complete as we can get and without a managed
category's know no ability to enter France.
Well it's not a real sick and we can get.
But of course we are saving a lot of time.
We spend like I don't know.
Creating the third project what 12 hours.
Ten hours.
So in real life you're not going to create a real application a real web site with all of this in 10
hours not going to happen is going to take like a month or month and a half maybe more depending.
Depends on the project.
But again I'm just trying to save time so we can do other things things that are a little bit more challenging
like the cart and everything else.
So now we're going to do the Brant's are going to posit BDO have a glass of water and we're going into
the woods sorry and this one is just pretty much the same the same than here.
But the requests are going to go to what's right.
So I'm going to take five and then we can finish what's write so let's do the words real quick.
So I'm going to go to manage what's going to put it just here.
So we need to import a lot of things and most of the things are going to be the same.
You're going to realize right now they're going to copy the fields are going to copy the connect and
I'm going to paste it right here.
All right.
So now we don't get get France we get what's so what's and delete the ad BRAMs then we're going to at
the at what.
Of course now instead of here I got to go to manage brands and copy the state because it's the same
exact state pasted so element input name impled still in it.
The same could be would it but that's OK with you.
So enter the word.
Everything else is just the same.
All right what else we need to copy the content you know the layout.
So I'm going to go to manage France I'm going to copy pretty much the whole thing right here.
Just going to copy and paste it.
All right.
So even though even in class the container the name of the containers are the same because when I was
building this the final one they put in the previous one.
What I did before I was going to do something else with what's pretty much the same actions to enter
to a list and everything else.
But it was going to be a different layout and then I stopped for five minutes and say OK this is not
really that important.
So I'm not going to spend a lot of time.
OK.
So Kateri items everything else is the same.
The form field is the same.
Everything just here stays the same.
All right.
So I'm going to go to manage France and go at the top what else.
It's just the same.
Well then we need to show contemporary items.
So I'm going to copy and paste right here now instead of doing brands we are doing worse.
So whenever we get the props it's going to be what's right.
OK.
Then we loop Woods and what we do we return the same thing.
Now to get the props first we need to connect this to of course to redux.
So I'm going to go with what I'm going to copy the maps the props pretty much the same and then connect
again pretty much the same and manage what's in it copy and say manage what's an almost done.
All right.
So I'm going to go back to mench France.
What else is going to be the same.
So we have the shark attack where we did this and the update form it's pretty much always the same so
I'm going to copy this and I'm going to paste it right here at the bottom and instead of France now
it's going to be words.
Either way we make a mistake right here.
Nothing is going to really happen.
Of course if we reload we get it but we don't get lists of France it's because we need to do the component
dismount to fetch the list of ports.
So add the component about and instead of get Brandt's it's get worse.
All right.
Let's see if we get it.
OK.
So we get it of course we need to change the title to what's around.
So enter word.
Of course the name of the button.
So at word.
OK.
So then of course we need to submit the form.
Right.
All right.
So we're going to go to manage France and copy they submit form.
This one is going to change a little bit.
So I'm going to I'm going to copy and then paste it.
All right.
So instead of France we will use words.
Now the existing words and we will be getting the props the products that Woods.
Right.
And for now I'm just going to do this because we need to create dispatch.
We don't have that we don't have that action.
OK.
But everything else just looks nice.
Of course we need to add that dispatch this create the action.
So we get to go to product action.
And I believe we can call it at what's right.
Right here we have a brand.
So we need to add words and Singler of course.
So at in that word.
OK.
COMO of course we need to add it to types.
You know the usual stuff export and it Konst word and word right now if you push me up if you push me
in just a little bit I could have created a component just to render this reusable component.
That's OK.
All right.
So we're going to go back to productions and I'm going to go right here at the bottom we have the two
categories we have the brand.
Make it a little bit nicer.
All right.
So the brand and the woods they will be actually they're going to do the same thing.
I'm going to copy paste now instead of brand is going to be what the existing Brandt's is going to be
existing good.
Right.
The products server.
Now we can add would know the other one was brand singler.
This one is what.
OK.
So on the response we will that will be getting worse instead of exists brand is going to be existing
what you can do this on your own if you want to try it at home alone.
That's OK.
So then woods and woods and instead of at Brant you had that would the rigor add.
What.
All right.
And then of course we send the request.
Now we need to go to the douceur.
And of course change all of this right.
And existing existing words sorry for this should be plural existing words and existing ones.
Okay.
So now let's go to the products reducer and first we need to add to copy the type.
So that would product reducer and then go right here.
I know changing tabs and everything is a little bit confusing but in real life this is how it goes.
It could be changing tabs every time.
So I'm going to copy the brand and do the ad would sell it type ad would right here at the bottom what.
And then we have the state.
This one is going to be wood and instead of brands if we can have of course what's so what's And that
is it.
OK.
So words would everything looks correct.
So it should be working.
We did a lot of pacing so we might be getting in our.
But that's OK.
It should be working.
So let's give it a try.
So before we get to trial of course we need to dispatch an action so the action was called.
If you remember I don't remember have a bad memory.
So add what.
So I'm going to copy and paste.
All right.
We're going to go to the submit form and of course we need to dispatch in action and right here just
like we did before.
We just need to pass the second argument of what's so this not prompts that dispatch opening close and
we passed this at what this one will be taking the data to submit coma and the second argument is the
existing one so we can merge everything later than we get it then we get a response and everything else
is just the same.
So if I open and close and I'm going to copy the other one products actually Nope manage rants.
There it is that we pretty much have the same code.
We don't need to change anything else.
So I'm going to copy paste it.
And that is it.
All right.
OK.
So let's try to check if everything is OK so we can get this out of the way and we can go to the site
info.
That's what is going to be a little bit different.
So I don't know.
Hard would I believe that it would.
So add word and OK something fails it's because something fails right here and that what maybe we are
not returning words from the server.
Oh let's check it out.
At brand word you're getting word or ride.
So notice that on the word we are changing this to true right.
And the words we are not getting anything.
So let me just double check why and I'm pretty sure I know why but I'm going to check it without you
right here.
No.
Actually we were able to add this to the server.
So when everybody reloaded the page of course we are getting because it's going to the server.
The problem is the reducer that it's not injecting the prompts.
All right.
And if I go to the producer again.
Well it's actually that payloads.
And this is the problem from the server you're getting what.
So that that one should be would.
Right.
OK.
What.
So actually it's woods if we go to products the actions we are returning what's all right.
Let's try it again.
And I don't know any other I don't know.
Let me just think about one.
Oh I have one.
Ebony.
It's a very common not very common but we could use it.
So I can add it and we got it.
All right man.
So we are finished with this.
OK so everything is ready right here.
Of course sip everything so you can get it if you didn't do this and it can go to site info.
So on site info what we can be doing is just adding the side information it could be called managed
site or something like that.
And later much later we're going to add more things.
But for now we're just going to add this.
And for this we need to create a new model where we're going to be storing everything else.
So it's like a site in vord site data inside the server inside mongoose.
All right.
So I'm going to skip everything and let's go to the next one and do the site info and then we're going
to do something a little bit more interesting.
We're just going to be the guitars whenever we go to New Product.
We get to be product and of course we have the we have this.
So this is a little bit more fun than the other one.
All right.
So let's go to the next one.