OK so we're going to start with the third project of the course.
Now make sure you have everything installed just like robo 3D and postman because we get to use them
a lot.
If you don't have this an unpretty sections you know previous this section I've added a couple of ones
into how to install everything in your computer so you know make sure you have all the tools you can
need.
And of course we will start with a clean project I've entered you know the commander here to that directory
so we can it run some commands and at the end the very very end we can have something like this so we
can create a guitar Web site.
So pretty much this side.
They sell guitars.
Why guitars.
I love guitars.
I have tons of guitars.
I've been playing for like more than twenty three or 24 years so I wanted to create a project of something
I know right.
I wanted to create something because we get to use you know brand pictures and you know the prices and
categories so I wanted to get to create something.
I have no trouble in creating you know the logic everything else because most of the times when someone
hires you you need to learn about the product about what they do.
The categories you know you need to learn about a lot of things.
In this case I've already know that's why I'm creating a guitar website so.
OK.
So of course we will do a lot of things logons logout everything with Mongo and everything else.
This is my guitar my new guitar.
So OK.
So this is going to do at the end but of course whenever we start we need to start from scratch.
So the first thing go to your code your editor or your ID and then just navigate to your directory.
All right.
So the first thing is to create to create a project.
Now we are not going to use it just now create re-act app.
The first thing we need to do is to create a server because right here this project and we will make
a lot of requests to the server.
And it's not a firebase server.
It's going to be a NOIA server with Mongo DVH.
So first the first thing we're going to do before we create the client side of things we will create
a server.
All right.
So first we're going to go to this command and we get a trigger and PM in it.
So this will create packaged adjacent in everything else so we can start installing things.
So first NPM in it.
So asked after we do this the package name it's waves.
Then Burreson just going to keep pressing enter.
Not really important right now.
And then enter.
And then we get our package that Jason now to run the server.
We need to install one more thing.
Maybe you don't have this in your computer.
Maybe you do.
I'm going to install node Monda so NPM install mynahs G and then gnomon.
I could use your brain going and I'm going to use NPM.
So what.
No.
Mon Dieu.
When we run a server right.
We're going to of course have a file right here and the server is going to be running OK.
So if we make a change on the file then we need to kill the server from the command and start the server
manually.
So gnomon what it does is going to listen to your files and whenever you make a change it will restart
the server of the medically.
That is the idea because of course we don't want to go back be a back and forward to the terminal to
do everything manually.
So I'm going to do clear but we're going to use this later.
Right.
OK.
So inside our project we have two different points the client side of things and the server.
So I'm going to create two different directories one with client and another one with server.
Right.
And of course we need to install a lot of dependencies before we start.
So OK so inside waves because this is the main directory we're going to install pretty much everything
for the server and everything else when we go to the client we can enter the client directory and we
can install them there.
For now this is good.
OK.
So inside of ways I gave you on the press section a note where you have the commands of what we need
to install.
I'm going to bring it right here.
So I'm going to make this a little bit bigger because we have a lot of lines.
So this is what we need to install.
Decrypt is to encode passwords and hash passwords and everything else.
Body parts are something we do with the express.
Then of course we install express to use the server.
We get to much much later you use close Narey and I will show you later on a bonus section how to upload
images instead of using clone Cloncurry to your directory to use your server.
I will not recommend this but if you want to do it you can do it concurrently.
Again we're going to check this later.
It's very specific cookie parser's something that we use with a server that EMV is decreed embarkment
virals.
And then of course Jason Webb tokens to create web tokens moment for times for parsing times and mongoose.
And then of course MULHER it's pretty much something we use to upload images.
We will do this at the very very end.
So are going in this what are we going to need to to use in our server.
So going to press center it's going to take a while and I'll be right back.
OK so everything was install.
I'm going to do.
Clear and right now we need to define which file is going to be the main entry of our application.
In this case is going to be inside server.
So inside server it will create a file called Server dodgiest.
And this is the main starting point of our server.
Now before we start anything we need to tell the application our project where are we going to be starting.
Just like would we do would react when we do NPM run or start.
Well same thing right here.
So we need to go to the package that Jason and start enter enter the logic right here so we can have
two commands.
First we have start which is opening close.
And this one it's equal to starting the server.
So we do node then server just like this for Slash and then server Dungey asked which is the name of
our file.
So whenever we do NPM start we will go to start the application is going to go to start and start there
from this file.
So the server is going to run.
The thing is that again if we do this we need to go every time we make a change on the server then yes
we need to kill the server and start again.
And I don't do that.
So I'm going to do coma and I'm going to create a new command which is going to be server now server
instead of using node the start server Dungey as is going to do gnomon and then server that jazz non-jazz.
So this ones are pretty much the same thing.
The difference is that this one uses node and this one uses gnomon and we are going to use this one.
Gnomon.
So now whenever we want to run the server we do NPM or yaun start at run and then server.
All right.
OK.
That is not going to save this.
Now of course if we do this nothing is going to happen to close the console.
Nothing nothing is going to happen because we don't have any logic in site server.
So OK.
We need to we need to start doing some things.
So first we need to create an express application sorry for this.
We need to create an express application.
Right.
So first Konst and then express it's equal to require open and close and we say Xpress just like this.
All right.
What else.
For now nothing else.
I'm going to say Konst I'm going to say app and what we do inside app we can host the instance of what
we are bringing from Express.
We just fire everything.
So Express just like this.
Open it close.
And then we start an express instance right here on app.
All right.
So now whenever we want to use something using the exper server we make a reference to an app and you
know then do something whatever doesn't matter.
OK that is good.
Now for now the only thing we need to do is to create a server now the server needs a port.
So I'm going to say Konst then port calls and now we need an environment Barville I'm going to quit
right now.
We didn't have it.
We can add it in a few minutes.
So I'm going to say I want to enter the process which is an environment viable and I want to bring to
port.
Now if we don't have this I want to run this on a different place and I'm going to run it on the port
three you to then we can use this app that we brought right here and say OK I want to start an app and
I want this application to listen for something and listen to the port.
I just create it at the top.
This viral now of course after this happens are going to create a callback.
This you can add this if you want.
It doesn't really matter.
And the only thing we're going to do right here is going to say console log and use tempera strings
here server running.
And this is you know pretty common.
And then I passed port which is equal to whatever we are running right here.
The environment larval port or the three us you are too.
All right let's get.
So if I save this and I start our application at least we should be getting a message of server running
and running.
So we do server.
OK.
So I'm going to go right here and do.
Clear again and then your own run server and a presenter and no one is going to start
and that we get this OK.
No don't we start at any time and we get server running at 3 0 0 2 so everything works.
This means that our server is actually running really simple really simple stuff.
So let me bring the other one.
OK.
So now we know that we are running.
We're running a server on the local host 3 0 0 2.
So I'm going to go through 2 3 0 0 2 and we can get this.
So if you're getting cannot get it's actually OK.
This port is being used but by our server but we don't have any logic right here saying that whenever
you get a request for this location you know show something on the screen.
And this is what we're going to do much much later with the client.
This part the server dodgiest the only thing is that it's going to do is going to listen for four slash
API and then whatever it is that we want to get.
But of course we need to do this first.