All right so later you're going to be pushing things in to get help.
But of course you're going to store this some place on the cloud.
So of course if we do it just like this we add the note modules and we don't want that.
So I'm going to go create a new file and create a get ignored of course on this project we can send
things to get have or you know get lab or something like that.
You of course you need to do it your own way.
But of course the year the final project which is the one to have right here it's a store it's a store
everything in Hogan-Howe.
And this final project this person is going to go to you so you can inspect it.
So on that get ignored.
We need to we need to put what we want to ignore when we push.
So what I do we ignore the modules later we can have a build a client with no modules and you know the
Yorn files and this one is for a Mac.
Now we have this one the dot E M B.
So this is an environment files right.
Inby so we don't have this I'm going to create it right now.
And it can explain you why that M-B So we're going to save that get ignored and close it.
So later much much later when you push things into production you will need a file that hosts keyboards
and passwords and maybe locations and you know you need the API keys or something like that.
So you need to a place where you can store them.
And that's why I'm going to store everything on the EMV and I'm putting this as a get ignored.
So whenever we send this to have we don't want to show this inby file with our all our keywords right
out passwords and then of course on the real life when you go to production when you push this to production
you're going to send the keys and the passwords directly on the server.
That's why we use a process that IOM report in production you have access to this environment virals
that you set manually after you send everything to production and it's going to consume the passwords
and the keys and everything else directly from the server because the only person who has access to
your server.
In theory it's you.
All right.
So that's this M-B of course we need to add some passwords.
But before we need to bring Mongo divi and everything else to this server because right now it's pretty
empty.
Now later we're going to use body parts or we use body parser to bring things bring Jason for example
from from the from from the actual request.
When we make a request a post request maybe we send the Jason.
So this body parser will get the information from that you know that request.
And of course this works with Jaison or maybe body human body or maybe a query strings.
So we need the body parts or something very very standard.
So we do require and we do body body and then a parser just like this.
All right.
So OK.
So required body parts or an exit.
OK.
Now this is actually installed right here.
Body parts are.
We've already installed this.
Now what else we're going to need.
We're going to need cookies.
We're going to use cookies.
So I'm going to say call Konst than a cookie just like this.
And then parser again we're going to read cookies whenever we get a request.
So we use the cookie parser's so require.
Open it close and then Kuki parser right.
OK.
What is next.
We have the express and we need to put mongoose right here.
So I'm going to say Konst money goose equals and cons not Kanzi Konst and mongoose and we need to require
mongoose could do this at the top.
I'm going to do it right here.
Mongoose Now this mongoose needs some configuration if you remember we do a mongoose connect and we
use the link on the database and notice that my process for Mongo DVH it's run right here.
So make sure you have this running.
OK.
So where are we going to store the location of our database.
You know inside Mongo DVH at least in our computer.
So from the dot that M-B.
So on the Dandan Emmy I'm going to say database just like this equals.
And then we're going to be passing that Mongo divi link.
Remember we did this I did this on the previous section.
Localhost 2 7 0 1 7 and the name of this is going to be waves.
That's the name of the project waves.
So now what I can do I can bring this dot EMV to our server.
We can not use it.
And imported just like any file.
We cannot do it now.
That's why I'm using this.
When we find it that N.B. This library.
So this library what it does.
It grabs a M-B and makes makes this whatever we have right here available for us to use right here.
So first I need to require just like this opening close and then dot EMV and then I'm going to do config.
This is the way we bring it right here.
Now of course we need to set up mongoose So first we need to do mongoose promise.
If you if you're going to use you're going to use promise.
And we said that global and then promise now promise with a capital P song and copy and paste it right.
What is next.
We need to sell it to do mongoose connect.
So mongoose dart we connect to the database inside mongoose and I have the location right here with
the key word database.
So what we do we access process that EMV Jambi dot database.
So this is what that EMV does.
We can use this keyword process that M-B database and we need to we don't need to do something like
this.
Right.
We don't need to hard code data is going to be always process that EMV and then database on the production
on the actual the real server not on development server.
So by using this like this we make sure we don't have to make changes in the future.
Right.
OK.
So we are already using the final the final process that M-B keyboard.
All right.
Now to use body parser and grim cookie parser we need to register this as a middleware.
So I'm going to use app that use and this is the way we register middleware.
So we're going to bring this body parser just like this.
We do dot and we're going to use equerry strengths.
So we'd of course strings we use you are all encoded.
And later we are going to be adding something because we're going to get a message but don't worry for
now and then app that use opening close and we're going to use body parser again but this time to parse
Jaison.
So whenever we get our request we're going to be able to read it again.
We use cookies.
So app that use and then cookie parser and again is a function method actually so everything is good.
We have the port.
We have everything else.
And if you go right here we're going to get this provide extend their undefined extend that provide
extended option.
So when you are Ellen coated we need to do this extended just like this and we say true.
If not you're going to get a warning and the warning is gone.
All right.
OK so everything's it's run is running around.
We have the embarkment marvels right here we added they get ignored and the servers are still running
even though we added a bunch of things.
Now on the next few sections we're going to be using this bunch of things we are doing right here.
Right.
So let's go to the next section and start with that.