All right so one of the things you're going to do in the final project in our application is registering
users logging users and everything else.
We got to do with users.
So we need to create a more user model right so because we use in Mongo DVH.
So OK.
So first make sure you have this open of all the projects we can get our waifs project right here in
a in a couple of minutes and more open.
We need to open post-meno.
Right.
So make sure you have a postman open.
So now before we can add things to to Mongo DVH that got to do with users before we can do this we will
need it of course a route.
So we're going to go right here and say users.
So everything below this is going to be related to users.
So the first thing we're going to do we're going to register a user so I'm going say app I'm going to
say post and we're going to be listening for post requests and all the locations are going to go to
forward slash API then forward slash users plural and then register and all the requests in our server
are going to go to API.
All right.
Then of course after we do after we get a request from this we're going to get the request the actual
request and the response is pretty standard.
So of course right now we can to do something.
The only thing that are going to do is send a status of 200.
So I'm going to say status and then 200.
We're going to send a send a positive response.
We're not doing anything just yet.
So if I go to hear from postman for example we're going to get a status of 200 are going to be going
to do it later before we can do this.
We need a user model.
We need to go to the server directory and create a new directory called models.
So inside models we will store all the models in our project.
We'll have users we will have products.
So we are going to get a lot of models one for categories and a different type of category so we're
going to get a lot of models the most to complete one are the user model which is the one we're going
to do now and then the products I'm going to go to models create a user model.
So inside the user model we need to required mongoose.
So Konst mon geuss mon and then it goes and require opening close and then Mohn goes all right.
So now whenever we start a schema we need to create a schema right before we put the model in.
So we say Konst and we always start with keyword that actually we are using since we were working with
users.
We use user.
And then the keyword schema its equal to mongoose dot and we use the schema method of mongoose opening
close.
Now this schema takes an object and inside of here we will need to put pretty much everything.
So at the end we need to export this user schema so we can use it on the server.
So I'm going to go at the bottom I'm going to say Konst and make sure this one is capital and I'm going
to say user.
So this user is equal to mongoose and say we are going to create a model out of this user schema and
the name of the model is going to be user capital user.
And we're going to be using this user's comment and at the end since we have a new model created right
here we need to export that Marvel user so module that exports equals and then user.
And now whenever we include this file inside the server we will be able to work with users inside Mongo
DB.
All right of course we need to do a lot of things first the user schema needs some configuration.
So we will have a lot of things.
First we need an email.
So I'm going to say e-mail opening close and this is the value the key pretty much of our entry.
So we need to define the type the type is going to be a type of a string and noted that this is.
Notice that this is green.
This is actually for mongoose.
And if you missed this not going to really work.
So make sure you have a capital S. so we can said we can tell to the database to Mago the be that this
value this key.
It's required every time.
So we're going to say required and it's going to be true.
Coma we're going to trim it.
We don't want one.
Whitespace is right here.
So if we store something it's going to trim it and then we won this email to be unique because the e-mails
are unique.
So we say unique just like this and we say that this one is true.
All right and that's it.
That's it for e-mail.
Then we didn't have passports.
So passport open and close and the password again it's a type of strings on that copy paste is going
to be required.
True.
So required.
True and a minimum length.
I'm going to say men and then length just like this.
All right.
And the length is going to be five.
Doesn't really matter.
Right now we're going to check that later.
So I'm going to say name and we're going to need in the name of the user and this one is again required
when a user registers.
We need the actual name.
So I'm going to say required I'm going to say type string.
Pretty much the same thing.
And this time you know a name could be really long.
So I'm going to add max length so the max length it's 100 characters.
All right.
You know one hundred characters for name is too much.
So OK so pretty much the same thing would lead with last name.
We have a last name and again type string required true and the max length of 100.
Now much much later on the application and I'm going at it now because you know then if we do it then
we need to go back to users.
So I don't really want to do this.
I want to do it right now.
We're going to have cart users are able to Bubbe Shaab from our place you know and maybe at night into
the cart.
So whenever they do that we need to store that value or whatever they added inside the user database.
Right.
All right.
So type and they might add many many things many products.
So we need a type of an array.
And this a raid is going to start as a default of nothing.
All right.
So if they don't have it they don't have anything inside the value of this.
It's nothing.
Now sometimes up pretty much if they buy something they're going to have a history history of purchases.
So open and close and same thing type array and default nothing.
Later of course when we reached a section we'll see how they work.
Now whenever a user registers they need to roll.
Now most of the times and actually you can check where you can decide what you want to do right here.
You can decide to use a string or maybe a number or maybe a boolean if you have different types of you
know roles.
Maybe it's a good idea to use a number in this case we just have two which is the user and the admin.
All right.
So I'm going to say roll opening close.
And this is type number capital and and the default value which is not administrators is going to be
user.
So the only way to give admin rights to someone it's for a different administrator to change the role
of a different user.
Right.
And then of course we're going to get tokens.
So I'm going to say token open it close and the type of the strain and of course it's not required.
So we will do a lot of love tokens in the next few sections.
So right here promotor we have our whole user schema and we are passing it right here.
So now to use it inside the server as we need to bring it.
So we're going to go right here and say models are right.
So Konst open and close user and this user it's equal to require open close for Slash models and then
user.
So now whatever we want to do something to the user or store something or whatever we can make a reference
to that user right here and it's going to work.
All right.
OK.
So far so good.
So now we're going to really begin to be doing.
We're going to I'm going to open post-bin and we will start registering in user.
So let's go to the next section and start with this.