OK so now we can start using POST man right here that B is the project I've already built my hear this
one and we're going to do pretty much the same thing with you right here.
So with postman you can create collections where you store all your requests.
Since we are using waves as the name of the product and then we use weights.
So create.
So every request is stored inside here now.
Right now we're going to make requests to the local host 3 0 0 2.
Now every time we make a request we will have to do age TTP Collen forward slash localhost 3 0 0 2 and
I don't really want to do that.
What we can do we can create firewalls right here and use them.
So right now I'm going to select no environment I'm going to go right here and to the settings and at.
So what we do we end bond with ADD an environment.
So I'm going to call it wipes.
Now we can add keys in this case the key of this is going to be named you are l So this is just like
creating a variable just a key value pair and right here you can pass what are we actually doing where
where what is the value of this key.
And this case is H TTP Kallen for Slash localhost.
And then I'm using 3 0 CO2.
All right.
So whenever we make a request I'm going to save it.
Right.
We have it inside waves and that rival We can select the environment right here which is waves and I'm
going to I'm going to do localhost Oh sorry I'm going to do this.
Got them Stosh Mars.
And then you are l and this will be equal to any PI over to local host 3 0 0 2.
So there's no need to type it which is doing well and that is it.
All right.
So backing our project we need to start creating all the logic for this.
Now whenever we register a user we are asking right here on the user schema and email because it's required
a passport name and a last name right.
This for fields are required.
So I'm going to go right here and whenever someone makes a request to delay this for now for a post
request for this route we need to create a new user schema wrap data from the body from that Jason we
we're going to be sending and then store it.
So first I create a new virus called user and this user is going to be equal to new and then user just
like this new user and this new user.
It's a new user right here this model.
And whenever I do this I want to get whatever I get from the request.
Remember that when we send we receive requests for this we are expecting some values from the body in
that Jason format.
So when we create a new model we're going to be passing us in arguments that data we get from that from
this request from this route.
Right.
So then since we have a new model and we have the data we need we need to create a new user you stored
inside the database.
So I'm going to say a user save this is the way we stored things in Mungo.
And of course after we save it we have an error.
And the actual document whenever we store something the server will return back that the user that was
stored inside of the Mongo DVH.
So if we get an error what we do we return responds with Jason.
All right.
So what we do.
Going to say success just like this and then falls and I get to attach the error.
So whatever we get from you are we going to show it on screen.
Now of course if everything goes goes OK and we are able to register a new user it will not go to this
this this return which is going to move forward.
So we know say we do arrest for response and we send a status of 200.
All right so now that the browser is going to get a status of 200 response.
And of course we need to send them some JSM back.
And what I'm going to do I'm going to send this same success but this time it's going to be true.
And then I'm going to be showing the user data.
Remember that when we whenever we store something Mongo divi they give us back what we stored.
So this is inside the dock.
So what I do I'm going to say dock later are we going to change this a little bit.
But for now it's OK.
And that is it.
So we should be able to store some user.
Now I'm going to go to postman and right here.
We need to pass the actual route.
So I'm going to copy the route and put it right here.
It's going to be a post request but we need to send some information.
So I'm going to go to the headers and I'm going to send the content type content type of application.
Jason and I did it incorrectly.
Sorry for this QAnd.
We need to press enter.
There we go.
And then application Jason.
All right.
Now of course we need to send some Jason data so we need to go to body.
We need to select Rawle and we need to select Jason application maybe you have text.
Make sure you have Jason.
So we open curly braces and inside of here we start adding things.
We need an e-mail.
So the e-mail is going to be Francis at gmail dot com.
All right then a coma.
And I'm going to add a password so password.
It's going to be equal to pass word.
One two three coma we need a name so name equal to Frances.
Right.
Coma.
And then a last name and last name and the last name Jones.
This is a nickname.
FRANCES JONES Doesn't Exist.
OK so now we are ready to make the request and see what happens.
I'm going to send a request and okay and we get a response back right here at the bottom.
So we made the request and our server it's returning whatever Mungo divi returning and what we do we
get the success true and then the user data with the card empty and everything else.
So we have the roll which is zero and now we have an ID and this ID it's our two generated by Mongo
DVH.
And of course we get the e-mail and the password and everything else so we are able to store a new user.
Now if I go to robo 3 I'm going to refresh this and we get the waves project.
It's going to go open users.
And we have a user.
So we are able to register a new user.
Very good.
Now of course we need to still do need to do a lot of things because when we just are a new user we
are adding a password which has some string.
So we shouldn't do this.
Never ever do this.
What we need to do is to hash out a password.
So we're going to do some logic inside of the user schema in the next few lectures into you know how
to hash a password how to generate it generate a token after they log in and everything else.
Now right now we are returning on the server all the user data.
What you can do if you want to do if you just want to return maybe the name or the ID.
Remember that this is Jason Jason File.
So Jason Jason value Bible.
So inside user data you can just pass name right.
So instead of doc you do name now.
Notice right now I'm going to do the same post request with the same information and I'm going to say
Send we get success false because key error collection user index duplicate key.
Remember that the email read Mark this is unique.
So this is not going to work.
I need to change the user.
I'm going to say Francis to whatever.
Doesn't matter right now.
I'm going to say send.
And now we get success true.
And we just get the name of the user instead of the whole document.
All right.
For now I'm going to get the whole document because we are just creating this.
Are developing.
All right.
OK so let's go to the next section and let's start with the hashing passport part of things.