OK so let's hash out the password first.
I'm going to store this inside the waves project so I'm going to store it and that's when it's going
to be called the register and I going to start inside waves.
So now in the future if you want to add a new user or do some more testing we can just go to register
and this will be stored with the RA and all the data right here which just need to make a few changes.
This no need to do all over again.
So this is very very cool.
OK.
So inside the server of this logic it stays the same.
We are able to add a user.
Now what are we going to be doing.
Is that before we store the user before we store it just like this.
We're going to do something before this happens instead of this file instead of the user file We're
going to do something before we save.
And we're going to grab that password.
The one that the user is entering we can hash it.
And that's what we're going to be storing at the end.
OK.
So let's start with this now first before we can start.
We need a few things.
I'm going to go with Tom sorry.
So what are we going to do.
We can do we can encrypt password right.
Can empower encrypt strength.
So for this we need dependency.
We've already installed called Big crypt.
So we need to require So Konst and I say Konst then big crypt is b c r and then Y.
P and T.
All right.
Now this one require open and close.
And then of course we need to say the crypt just like this.
OK.
Now when whenever we encrypt something we going to use a salt.
Now if by default the salt is 10 and I'm going to host this inside of a Barville you can just put the
number directly on the function going to get there.
Don't worry for now if you want just do this.
All right.
So OK I'm going to go at the bottom and what we need to do we need to tell the application that before
storing before we store a user we want to hash that password.
So I'm going to use the going to enter the user schema and going to do Prete.
So three with prie is that before we do anything we want to do something all right and then we specify
what action we want to do first.
It's safe.
So before we save anything before we go to here we're going to do this now before we after we do this
after the we pacify what we are going to be listening we need to run a function.
So I'm going to use five right here.
You could use ESX doesn't matter.
The thing is that sometimes depending on the version you're using it fails with the A6 or not you know.
So I just want to be sure that everything works.
So going to use iOS 5.
So we're going to run a function and we're going to be passing this next.
So this next whenever we want to move forward which is mean after we hashed a password we're going to
call this next and next is going to do you know the rest of what needs to do.
Don't worry we will get there.
So first I'm going to make.
If you know about is five and six is that with iOS 6.
We didn't need to.
We didn't have a problem with the scope.
We can use this.
And there's it's always you know this this environment now with iOS 5 we need to create an alias for
this.
So I got to say bar user it's equal to this.
So now whenever I make reference to user it's going to be the user of this and not this function.
Right.
Very common as five Ennius x.
So what do we want to do.
I want to encrypt the password.
All right.
So I'm going to call script just like this and I'm going to generate a salt and there's method.
It's actually from big crypt now whenever we generate a salt run we need to do is we need to pass the
salt.
So we got it right here.
So salt.
All right.
After we generally Dassault going to run a function opening close and we pass an error and the actual
salt.
All right.
And then of course I can open and close.
Now if we do have an hour so I'm going to say if are we going to return next with an error.
So what next does it kills whatever we are doing right here and move us forward to the next thing.
So again what we're doing great here is that we are receiving a request we are going to do the pre safe
and then when we go next we just keep doing whatever it is that we want to do which is this you know
outputting the response and everything else.
All right.
So of course if we get an error we're going to kill and we just can't move forward if we don't get an
error.
We can do something else.
And this case we're going to Dubik crypt and we're going to do the hash method.
Give us now what we're going to be using is the passport of the user to hash it.
So I'm going to say user that password why am using user.
Because right here emitted a reference to user.
If we're using iOS 6 we can do this.
But in this case we are using user and he has five.
So I do hash.
I pass the user password.
That's what we're going to do.
And we need assault.
So this is the sort of first Genner dissolved.
And this will return a sort which is kind of a hash.
So we pass the salt then are going to do this and we need to run a callback function.
All right so this function will have an error.
If we do get an error and then hash which is the hashed passport of that's all right again we need to
do the same thing if we do get an error.
We need to return next with the actual error.
That's it.
OK.
If we don't get an error we want to move forward and what we want to do we want to said this user password
the one with you know the normal trend without hash.
We want to say OK now this user password instead of the string that they are providing to us we want
to store it as a hash instead of this.
So I entered the user password and I say this one it's equal to whatever hash we are getting from this
method and that's it.
Now the user password it's equal to the hash.
And then of course we call them next and we move forward to the next thing.
All right.
OK let's let's give it a try.
We need to add one more things right here.
But for now it's going to work.
OK.
So I'm going to go right here to our saved register and I'm going to change to Frances three whatever
and I'm going to make sure that I'm returning the whole document.
Yes we are doing that.
Going to do sent.
Let's see what happens.
OK.
So we get the user data back and we have the hashed version of this.
Why are we hashing.
It's not secure.
To put it like this.
So later now we are registering later the user needs to log in.
So when they log in they provide their password.
And what we need to do we need to go to the database grab the passport compare with the hash one we
need to decrypt not encrypt decrypt.
And if the passports match we let the user move forward.
Of course we are not there yet.
Now later we will have a section where the user can change the name or the last name or maybe the e-mail.
Right now if we do it just like this we are saying that just like this sorry just like this you're doing
on every action that it save just to generate a new hash of the password.
So maybe they are already richest stert and they want to change the name and after they change it we
are rehashing the passport.
So this is a problem because we are pretty much changed and hash over and over and over again.
We just want to hash out a password when Navy whenever they change a password or whenever they of course
do register.
So for this we're going to do.
We're going to say if open close if they're going to put all of this information inside of the if now
we have something inside of a user you know actually it's from Mungo that it's called is modified.
So malty find and this is a method.
So what we can check if we can check if the user is trying to modify the password if not if they are
doing of course we are not going to do anything which is going to generate a new solid whenever they
register which is the password.
If they are doing something else that it's not related to passport you're going to move forward.
So right now I need to pass to it's modified and I need to pass what are we changing what are we listening
to go to this scenario.
And in this case it's the key word password.
So if they are changing the password then we do this we need to encrypt if they are not changing the
password.
We need to move forward and not encrypt the passport again.
All right.
OK.
So this is done.
So let's try it again.
I'm going to go right here and say Frances.
Number four send and we're good to go.
Very good man.
All right.
We are able to handle everything now on the next sections.
We will need to log in a user and we need to create a new route for this and new logic for this not
for this.
We're going to do something else but we need to add more things.
All right.
Well let's go to the next one and do the luggin section.