OK so now we need to read the log in route.
Of course the users are going to log in with their e-mail and their passport.
All right.
We don't have this route.
So we need to create it first.
So I'm going to go right here.
The bottom just at the bottom and I'm going to say app just like this and I'm going to use post y post
because they need to send the user and the password.
We could use get but you know I'm going to use Cox.
So app API for Flash users same thing than before.
But this time it's going to be log in now when they log in.
Of course we have our callback with a request and our response so we're going to do this.
A lot of time times.
So we need to do three things.
First find the e-mail.
So if the e-mail of the user it's not on the database it means that the user is not registered.
So we're going to say do you need to register it.
So if the e-mail is on the database we can grab the password and check the password right.
That's the next step.
So if the password they are entering they're giving us matches the one we have on the database because
they are already registered.
We're going to let the user end if not begin to kick the user out.
And finally if the passwords and the email are correct we can generate a new token.
So we generate raid a token.
Right.
So we need to complete three different steps.
First is the e-mail.
So we're going to do this.
We don't need it.
So first is the e-mail.
So whenever the Antar going to be passing an e-mail and a password so we can use that user we brought
the top this user model.
We're going to enter there and we're going to try to find the user on the database and to do this we
use the method find one opening close.
Now find one.
Of course needs to needs to know what is going to be searching for it.
So in this case begin to search the e-mail of the user on the database.
And where do we have the e-mail.
Well we're going to be we are doing a post and we will be receiving some Jason.
So we have it just like here on their request that body so request that body that e-mail.
All right.
After this of course we need to run a function the callback function and this function will contain
an error.
Let me go back with one an error or the actual user.
So if it's not finding anything it will give us back an error.
If not is going to give us back a user.
Now either way this find one what it does.
It's not going to give you actually an error is going to give you no user.
If we cannot find a user or is going to give you the actual user data back.
So what we can do.
We're not going to use the air right now.
We should add it but you're not going to do it right now just to keep it simple.
So if no user begin to return responds that Jaison and we can send something back.
So we're going to say log in success just like this log in success.
And this one is going to be equal to false because you know that the user is not able to log in.
We are not finding the user back and we're going to say message and we're going to display the message
on screen.
So our failed e-mail not found very good.
So out of there we go.
So of course if we are not able to find the user We're going to go to this scenario.
Now if we are able to find the user the application will not enter this and it's going to go to the
next step of checking.
Now what we need to do is we need to compare the passports and for this of course we need the database
again.
But we also need for this big crypt we need to grab the password they are giving us in this case pass
2:59 we need to compared the one with the hash one they have on the database and check if they match.
And again for this when we need decrypt.
So what I'm going to do are going to create a method inside of this so we can add methods to two Mongul
D-B and use them inside of schema and use them with a server request.
So I'm going to go right here at the bottom and we need to create a method to compare a password.
So first just like with that before we use that user schema I'm going to enter and add a methods and
then the name of the method compare passport.
And this one could be whatever you want.
Ryan kind of makes sense that it's a compair password.
Now compare passport it's going to be just a function that it's going to do something.
Now this will receive two different arguments to candidate password just like this.
Let me do it a capital P the candidate passport and then a callback function.
So when we are done checking the passport either the passport match or not we will run a function which
is callback.
And of course this call was going to get executed and it's going to go back here.
So this Seabee its callback is just a function.
All right.
So for now we are going to go back to the server and we need to make a reference to this compare passport
since we are using user we have user that Methot we just added to the user model.
It's already there.
So I'm going to go right here and I'm going to make reference to this user.
All right.
Why am I making a reference to this user.
Now the thing is that right now we are connected to the do the model right here and we are finding one
whenever this is done it will return this user and this user kind of in the background and this object
which is all the data of the user has a lot of things that are connected to this model.
So whenever we say user we are sent We're talking about this user and not the whole schema.
We are making a reference to this user.
So if we make a reference to the user that we come back we can even either get the password or we can
access all the methods inside here in reference to that user.
So I'm going to say compare password which is the name of the here the name of the method and opening
close as it is we are doing this user and not these user.
We have all the data the user Mongul divi it's going to know that we're talking about Frances and not
some somebody else or maybe the entire schema.
OK.
So this compare passport and passport expects two different things the passport so we can match it and
then a callback function.
All right.
So compare passport first we need to pass the first argument with this request the body and then the
passport.
Right.
And this requires the body the passport it's this passport the one we are getting from the request and
then we need to pass the Colback.
And if you remember the callback it's function.
So I'm going to do this and this.
So again if you notice it's just a callback function it means that when we are done checking we trigger
this callback and this function will be executed whatever function that says.
So this function at the end is going to get two things could be getting an error and it's going to get
something called mismatch.
You can call this whatever you want.
It's match you know password good or whatever.
So match is going to be true or false is going to be true if the passports match.
You know they decrypt encrypt it in the past where they're giving us they match on the database and
it's going to be false.
If of course the passport don't match.
So I'm going to create if it's match just like this if the password of course they are wrong we're going
to return something.
So what I return are going to say return just like we did before a response in a Jason format and I'm
going to do something.
We're going to add these log in success equals to falls coma and then again a message.
But this one is going to be different and it's going to be wrong passport.
Right.
Because the user accessed the password.
It's wrong.
All right of course if it's good it's get begin to move forward to the next thing which is generally
talking.
But first we need to go to a user and check create a function that checks if the password is OK or not
so how do you compare the passwords.
First we need to use the script that Crypta give us.
Just like generating the salt or salt or hashing.
They give us a method back so we can compare password rules were simple.
So I'm going to go right here.
I'm going to say crypt dot then compare.
That's it.
That is it.
And what we take is the candidate password which is the non hashed passport.
And what we do we pass the data off the user.
Now since we are inside the function we are not inside of a function of a function.
We there's no need to do this.
We can use this dot and then password.
And this is going to be equal to the user password.
Right.
OK.
And coma and what is going to happen after we do all of this after we compare the candidate password
and the password that we have stored on the database which is this one.
All right we need to run a function.
So a function opening close.
And if you remember this function will be returning an error and is a match.
So what we do we pass the error and oh sorry error and coma is match.
Now if we do get an hour we're going to say error and are going to return the call back with the actual
error which is not going to really happen.
But if we get if you get a response from Decrypter saying that the passport matches are not going to
get that error in a it of no we're not going to get really an error.
And then we're going to get an S match.
So if the password they match this Barville right here this argument's going to be true if they.
There is no match.
It's going to be false.
If you go back to the server we are already checking this.
If it's false we do this.
But if it's true we can move forward right here and that is it.
All right next we need to generate a token.
All right.
So again we need to create a method for this.
So we're going to just created right now are going to make a reference to user dot.
And again the user is the same user.
So Bungo divvies going to know which user to check.
Right.
So my function is going to be called generated token opening close.
So again after we run this we will run a callback.
So with an error and then a user.
All right.
So let me make this a little bit nicer.
So we don't have this function.
We're going to create it right now.
We're going to go this method actually going to go right here make a reference to user schema to add
methods and then generate token.
And it's going to be just a function opening close Virga So now on this one since everything is OK and
we have the user id the user data the passwords and everything else we need to generate a new token
now.
Right here at the top we are not importing anything to generate tokens so we need to bring it in if
I go to a package that Chaisson have it right here we are including Jason weap token.
All right.
So going to go and say Konst date w t short for Jason Webb token and then require opening close and
Jason.
Well tokin OK.
Now.
Sorry I was going to add something but I'm going to add it in a couple minutes because if not you're
not going to get it.
You're not going to get one.
OK.
So now we have this library this dependency so we can generate tokens.
How this works.
Again I'm going to make an alias of user and say this because we need to use it inside of a function.
So user now it's equal to this.
So the application will know which user then we need to generate a token token it's equal to.
And then we use that JWT we've imported at the top and the how can we get generally token.
We use a sign now sign needs several arguments and how some web token work is that they take something
of you user could be the user id let me write something here.
They take the user id just like this and they generate a token which is kind of a hash.
It's a very long strings.
They code this right.
It's a encryption.
All right.
So the thing is that the a web token we just need we would not use Cester user ID to generate the token
what we do we generate a token based on this string which is the ID plus a password.
And this is not the password of the user is our passport the password of the environment we need to
set a super secret password that the server is going to only know again what we can do.
We can use this M-B file we can use dot and B.
So we're going to go to that M-B and we can add a secret password later when we send this to production
to Heroku for example.
We need to go to the environment variables of the server and add the super secret password.
So right now are going to do something very simple are going to say supersecret password which are three
of course of course in real life.
You need to do something more challenging than this.
So but we have our secret password.
Now we need to bring right here at the top.
We need to bring that M-B so we can make use of that process that Jambi and password so require opening
close.
And let me make it right require opening close DOD EMV then data and then Ficke open opening close.
So now we can make use of process that M-B that secret secret right here.
All right.
And then go with the bottom and what we need to do this JWT sign what it needs is what are we going
to be using to generate a token ride.
OK.
So what we do we use the user id so user that underscore Id remember that on Mongo DVH we store the
users within the Mungiki be will store an ID of the user with their score ID and then I need to convert
this to strings so to has X string and its a method.
All right.
And then what do we need to do with it to pass the supersecret password.
So this is inside process that EMV dot and then secret.
All right.
So after this function of course this method runs we will get a new token But what we need to do is
we need to enter the user and store the token just like with it at the top.
We are entering the user and putting the new version of the password.
All right here we create a new entry or we enter actually token and we store the token with whatever
we get back from JWT.
All right.
And after this we need to save the token inside of the user.
So going to enter user are going to do save.
Open and close and then I'm going to run a function.
And of course we pass an error.
And if everything goes OK we get a user back.
Now if we do get an error.
So if error we will return open and close the callback that we have at the top.
I didn't include this or for this callback begin it pass a callback as an argument with the error.
If everything goes OK we will return the same callback with no as an error.
But the actual user.
As a result.
So this version of the user if everything goes OK is going to be pretty much the same thing than this.
But with a token.
All right.
So we will get the token.
So if everything goes OK we run this callback.
Now we are not doing anything right here on the server.
We are just passing this function which is the actual callback.
Now when this go this comes back we could get an error or we could get a user.
So I got to say if we do get an hour we're going to return something else return a response of status
and then 400.
Which means that no Something happened.
Something bad happened and we just send the r back if everything goes OK.
We need to store the Kuki and we can see are we going to store up the token as it Kuki later much much
later when we reach the bonus sections and everything else.
I could show you a different way maybe the local store or maybe a different way of authentication that
it's not this one.
But for now this one is OK.
So response cookie opening close.
So what do we need to do is we need to set a cookie.
So the first argument inside cookie is the name of the cookie.
My one mind is going to be w out.
Yeah.
You can use whatever you want X out.
It's very common.
So I'm going to do koma this cookie we are setting the name and then the value of the cookie and the
value is going to be the actual token we get back on this callback function from the user.
So use user.
And then tokin.
And if you're asking yourself it's really secure or not secure in storing tokens or as a cookie.
Well there's a world of discussion.
Some people they breed they say that it's better to store cookies.
Some other people they say they should use local storage.
All the people they say we shouldn't use tokens.
So again it's just the discussion never ends by using a token and storing as a cookie after that for
example the user is going to log out of the website for example and the cookie is going to remain there.
We can actually delete it but the cookie will remain there.
And that cookie with the token it's not valid anymore because remember that we are hashing the ID with
a super secret password.
And of course there's a lot more hashing.
So again the token will not be found anymore.
So it doesn't matter if you store it on a cookie because when they logout or if we change it or something
happens no one is able to decode this unless of course they have all the keys all of your passwords.
And in either way it's not that easy.
So get that suport.
If we are setting the cookie and we say status 200.
All right.
And then I'm going to send a Jason response because I need to get something back and to send something
back to react.
So Jason and I are going to say luggin success and true note is that at the top we are always sending
false but now at the end it's going to be true.
All right.
So let's check this out.
I'm going to copy the route I'm going to create a new entry which is going to be a post just like this.
And of course we use the moustache bars.
You are all forward slash and opps sorry.
And then API users log in.
So same thing than before.
We need to set the content type just like this and application that Jason that it's OK.
We need the body and the body Raul and Jaison.
So what we are passing is the user the e-mail and the password.
So e-mail and the user we have so far it's Francis at gmail that come that coma and we need the password
and the passport is password one two three.
All right we'll see what happens.
I'm going to send that and we get wrong passport.
Maybe I'm in a mistake on this one.
OK.
I'm sorry if that's a mistake.
Actually it's not a mistake.
The first user we we've entered it's Francis Aggi that they come.
But this one has no hash.
That's why we are getting from passport.
At least we know that it's working with the wrong password the past passport.
We we've got it's for Frances for at G.M. that come and I probably use the same passport once you're
three.
So I got to say Pat Francis for Jamail I'm going to send it.
And OK let me do it again.
Maybe the server went down.
Yeah the server went down and it's TDX string.
That is my mistake.
It's always good to have to get back to check the console whenever you're lost and you're not really
sure of what's happening.
Just go back to the con..
So send again we get success.
True.
And right here we get the cookies and if we go to cookies we can see R.W. out.
And if we go to the database to that particular user of the Wonham we get the actual token.
So now we're going to be using this token throughout our whole application to check if the user it's
actually registered and able to enter two private routes or not if the token changes or goes away or
whatever.
You're not going to let the user end because now we have a token.
Right.
OK.
What happens if I enter the wrong e-mail consent and we get luggin success fall out fails.
E-mail not found so it should be failed failed Burguet.
OK so now we are able to log in users.
Of course we need to create a log out.
We need to log out users and you know to do a couple more things with users before we move out of this.
All right.
So let's go to the next one because this one went too long and keep moving forward.