OK so now we're going to be creating an out route going to cause this.
So every time we go to a new route just like there is for example this is the final one we go to a new
route.
We are constantly checking if the user possessed the correct token if I go to go to the console at to
cancel the actual application.
Let me find it right here.
Sorry.
Application and I go to cookies.
We get a lot of things of course.
But we have our daylily out so we are constantly grabbing D-W out from the cookies going to the server
and asking the server do is this guy allowed right here yes or no.
So when we need to create a route where we get him he of course constantly checking if the user is authenticated
or not.
First thing going to this store this I'm going to save it as a log in because we might use it later
logon.
OK.
Saved two ways.
I'm going to create a new route.
But first I'm going to do it right here.
So this is going to be called an elf route.
So I'm going to go right here at the top because it's pretty important and I'm going to say of course
up up.
And in this case we're going to use a get.
We don't we are not really sending any information.
We just we are going to be passing Christic cookies with them oath.
And whenever you do this again or a post or whatever the cookies are inside the request you get that
information easily.
So I'm going to do this.
I'm going to do for Slash AP I then users for Slash and then out and then of course just like before.
After we do this we just run a function and the function will contain a request and our response.
All right just like this.
Now we need to do this not just in the south but we need to do this again later on different requests.
What happens if the user tries to post something to our database.
We need to check if the user South indicated.
So it of makes sense for us to create maybe a different function or something else we can use on different
routes to pretty much Check the same thing.
And for this we can create a middleware.
So we're going to go to the server and create a new directory called middleware.
And if you're asking yourself what is a middleware.
This is a matter where the body parts are.
So this middleware acts before or maybe adoring of what we are doing in this case what it's doing it's
just converting what we get on the body from the Jason in getting it back to us.
So that's what the middleware is doing.
So what we can do we can create our own middleware and use them right here is simple.
OK.
So this middleware is going to be called of you could have a lot of middleware.
So let me make it right.
Rename it.
Yes.
OK.
So on this middleware we're going to create a new method right here.
So we need to import the user model the same one we are importing right here.
So it's going to be pretty much the same thing so I'm going to copy this one I'm going to paste it but
the route is going to be a little bit different.
Let me just change it.
So it's going to be that for Slash I'm sorry dot dot for Slash middleware.
Oh sorry.
Dot for Slash dot dot.
Forward slash.
And then we enter models for Slash and we enter user right so we have our users Kema right here.
So what we do we just return a function.
This is what a middleware.
This is just a function that does something.
So I'm going to call again to create an oath just like this.
And we will of course execute a function.
So this auf will receive our request response and next we can talk about this in a minute.
Of course we need to make this function available this middleware available so module exports equals.
And then we export this out.
All right we're going to go back here in a minute.
Now how can we use this out.
Well first we need to import it just like we are doing right here.
We need to import the middleware.
So I'm going to go right here at the bottom and say Merrill Where's whenever there's one it's going
to be called Konst and then south equals to require open and close that forward slash middleware for
Slash in out.
So how can we use the outcome from where in our right.
Well we do it right here.
We're going to put middleware you know the outs and then coma.
So what is going to happen.
We're going to get a request from this round.
Right.
So what do we do.
What this is going to do is going to go to our allies is going to do something and it will receive the
same you know request and response everything we get.
So we get right here.
So now right here we're going to do some checking and depending on what we get we're going to move forward
or not.
So if we choose to move forward with this next we're going to go to the next line of code which is the
callback function.
If something goes wrong instead of next we're just going to you know send the message try here or something
like like you're not allowed to enter or something like that kill it right here before going to the
next line of code which is the callback.
That's how we use a middleware.
Of course we still need to do a lot of things.
I've got to go back to the south and what we're going to be doing right here is checking if the token
is OK.
Right.
We can find the user check if the token IDs ride and everything else.
So first I'm going to create a marvel called token and this one is going to be equal to the token that
we get from the actual request and they go back to postponement whenever we make a request.
We pass this.
All right.
So we need to catch it from here from the server so we can access request and we have the access to
cookies dot and our is going to be called ours is going to be called Donnelley out.
So whenever we enter here we have the token right here.
So now we need to grab the token and check if the token it's OK.
So for this we can add a method called find by token again you can call this whatever you want.
So going to make use of a user the user model are going to say that they're going to find find by token
this is my own custom name.
So what we do this find by tokin is going to receive the token that we get from the cookies.
And after it's done it's going to execute a function and this function will get a narrower and a user.
OK.
So of course we don't have this we need to add this to the server.
I'm sorry to the user model so I'm going to go right here at the bottom and the middle of this.
OK.
So just like we did before we need to add this method right defined by tokin so we use user schema d'arte
statics just like we did before statics.
Oh sorry.
It's a little bit different.
The study is it's kind of a own custom method but you know kind of in a different way.
But don't worry it's just a method.
So we do find by token or a function opening close.
And what I'm going to do I'm going to create a token and the callback.
Remember we are passing the token.
And the callback function just like we did before I got to say bar user equals this.
All right.
So now this function this method find by token it will be receiving a token and a callback which is
the function.
Now what we need to do we need to grab the token read the one we have right here we need to decode it
with JWT with Jason Webb token this we need to decode it and from there we will get the user id of the
of the user and we can check if the token it's ok on the user.
All right.
I know that sounds simple when I say it but it's a little bit confusing.
So first to verify if the tokens are correct we use JWT then we use the method and it's actually from
them but very fine.
And we what we do we pass the token you know the token that we get from the cookies.
And we need to pass the secret super secret password.
And what it does it's going to do it's going to check the token and it's get it checked the super secret
password and if they are OK we move forward.
If not of course we can.
So the supersecret passport it's inside process.
Jambi and secret.
All right and after warts we get we run a function or a function.
So this function will get an error if we get an error and a decode.
So what we do get here on the de-code is going to be pretty much the user ID whenever we verify with
the token they generate code or something you know a very long string with the password and the token
but whenever we decoded we decode that we get the user ID.
So if we are getting the user id it means that the token it's valid if we don't get it.
It means it means that it's not valid.
All right.
So we get to decode.
So what we do I'm going to access user.
I'm going to DOD and I'm going to find one find one open and close.
So what do we do.
We grab whatever we got back from the de-code and inside de-code we have the user ID.
All right.
So I'm going to say I want to find one and I want to find the one that has ID of decode and then coma
and I want to find the one that has token of whatever we are passing as a token.
So pretty much we are finding a user with these user ID that we only get from this de-code from this
JWT fine.
And it was of course it needs to match the token as well if not of course everything is going to fail.
And then of course we run a function opening close and this function we will get an error if we do get
an error and a user back.
All right so if we get an error.
Pretty standard stuff.
We return a callback with we return sorry the callback with the error.
All right.
And if everything goes OK and you know it's there's no problem with a server or something like that.
We will run that callback with no as an error and the user.
Now if the user of course exists we will get something if the user doesn't access is still going to
run the callback.
But without a user and we can check on out if we do have a user.
All right.
So this is pretty much done.
So now we need to go back to us because this find by token will be receiving this callback.
And now we of course we need to do some checking.
So if we do get an error from the server that maybe that server is down we're going to throw a new error.
And this one actually is going to happen on the server.
Doesn't matter right now.
Now if we don't have a user it means that the token it's incorrect to use if no user is going to return
a report our response in Jaison or an opening close.
And what are going to be returning and this is actually for re-act for redux it's going to be false
and then error.
True.
We're going to get there later but you need to know that if we don't have a user we just send this Jason
that it's not outdated antiquated and an airbag.
Now if everything goes OK if the token is correct and the user should be allowed to enter what we sent
is a request with a token right.
Now why are we doing this.
What I'm doing.
I'm entering the request that we are seeing from this route and I'm entering I'm just pushing a value
that calls token ride.
We are not going to use it right right now.
But we're going to use it later.
Right.
OK.
Don't worry.
We're going to use it later.
Now what I want to do I want to add to the request whenever we get back from fine by token if you remember
right here at the bottom if we are finding the user with the token in the ID we and all the user data
and the user data is whatever we have on the database which is the name and password maybe the name
the last name the email and everything else.
So this wealth will be receiving that document.
So what I want to do I want to attach it to request.
So I'm going to say now inside request we have something that calls user and we have all the user information
inside of there since we want to move forward to the next line of code we call next.
So now we're going to go here we're going to add the token to the request and ask the user data to the
request.
So now this function it's done.
So we call next and we move forward to the next line of code and the next line of code is going to be
here.
Since we attach a lot of things to the request we have inside the request the user data and the actual
token.
All right.
So I'm going to go right here.
And of course we need to do some more stuff.
So if the it's OK what do we want to do.
We want to send a response right.
If the out is not OK we exit it here.
This line of code.
The next one which is the function will not be executed if the user is allowed to enter.
I want to send the response with a status of two hundred.
Then Dodd and I are going to send the Jaison response.
Opening close.
All right.
Now I'm going to just show you right now I'm going to say user and I'm going to attach right here whatever
we attach to request and the user around is going to do that.
So I'm going to copy this route.
Going to go to postman and we already have a valid token right here.
Remember that I'm going to go to a new tab and I'm going to make a get request to our u r l and then
forward slash and then API users and Alf says we have a valid token we should be getting a good response
and this is what we get.
We get the user the card history and everything else.
All right.
So everything is OK.
So if on react on the client side we are getting this kind of response.
We let the user and from the client side if not we get to kick the user to a different place.
Makes sense.
Now the thing is that I'm sending back all of this information and I don't want to do that.
I want to maybe pass some of this information.
So what I'm going to do I'm going to go right here and say is outman and remember that we have a role.
So I'm going to be checking if we do have a role.
User requires a user role and the value for this one it's zero.
I can send false as the value of this one if not I'm going to send.
True.
So pretty much whenever we do we're you can check if these areas have been straight or not we're going
to add more rules later but not by now then coma.
I want to add one more thing.
I'm going to use is our if so if the user is south antiquated I would say.
True.
All right.
What else are going to send e-mail and this information whenever we go to new routes.
This information about the user is going to be available for us to use in react.
That's why I am attaching all of this information.
All right then I'm going to say name we do need the name request.
Oops.
Let me do it like this.
Request that user that name.
We need a last name so a copy paste.
I'm going to say last and last.
Almost done.
All right.
Let's get.
So we can add the roll.
I'm going to add it.
Why not so request that user that role or the way for the role we're going to use this as a checking
when I'm going to attach it anyways.
Now if we check it we have a cart and a history.
We're going to use them later.
So I'm going to put it right here.
So request that user dot and then cart and the last one is going to be history the history of purchases
so request the user and then history.
All right.
Now if you remember when we were just passing the user data on I don't want to do this I don't want
to send the all the user data.
I just want to sex.
SS true.
You're going to see why when we get to react so let's try again.
I'm going to go and and now we get some different information with all the IDs and everything else a
little bit cleaner.
As a user it's not an administrator.
Of course we get false.
All right man.
So everything works.
So now of course we need to log out and for the log out begin to do something very simple.
All right so let's go to the next section and do the log out.