OK so let's create a log out route.
Going to be very simple.
So app that get opening close and I'm going to say for Slash API users and then log out.
Now the user can only logout if there are log in if they are authenticated.
So I'm going to use that Alv middleware.
And of course if the user is not authenticated and they tried to go to this route the out is going to
kick them out.
If not it's going to move forward and do the log out so.
So open and close.
So we will get a request and a response just like before.
So what are we going to do.
It's very simple we're going to enter to the database right here the database and scenes from mouth.
We are getting the user data.
What we can do we can grab that user data and we can update the user.
You know a record inside that database.
All right.
So I'm going to use user which is the model then find one an update.
So going to open and close.
So what I'm going to do I'm just going to find a user by ID because we do have it from our inside of
the user request that user and I'm going to just set the token to nothing and it just does chip pretty
much destroyed the token.
So the first argument is that what we want to find in this case we want to find by ID.
So we say there's core ID.
All right then I'm going to say request that user and we use that underscore ID Vergon.
Going to a coma.
And what am I going to do.
I'm going to enter the token and I'm going to just delete it set it back to nothing.
And of course after that we get a callback function just like this.
We get error and we get a doc.
All right.
So if we do get an error.
So if error I can return Jaison.
Why did what happen.
So read my response Jaison and we sent some objects to project success falls and then error.
But of course if we are able to you know destroy that token we say return response then status just
like this opening close and we say 200.
What we do we send our response and what we do is success.
True.
So at the end from redux and from react we are able to destroy that token we going get inside of something.
Of course we're going to check that later.
We're going to get this success true.
And if that happens of course we're going to log out of the user from the front end of things.
And that is it reasonable.
So now let's try it out.
Going to go right here I'm going to save this I can save it.
And going to call it auf and I going to create a new one.
Same thing you are l mustache.
You r l r u r l and paste it.
We do have a token.
And this one is for the Francis Ford.
So I'm going to send it and we get success.
True.
So we are able to log out.
And if I go to user and this is the old version I'm going to open a new one to see the updated one.
We don't have a token.
So on the next thing we the users can log out if they are trying to enter someplace where they need
to be authenticated since they don't have a token the indication is going to fail and it's going to
keep the user back.
So they need to lock in again and generate a new token.
Right.
Makes sense.
All right so we are pretty much done with a user on the server side.
Now we're going to go to a different different thing.
We're going to do a lot of more things with users but not right now because we need some context.
For example if I go to the final one the users they can create actions like a store or something on
the account or go into a card on actually making the purchase.
We need to store more things into the users information.
And for example right here we have the cart and the history.
So whenever we have to card we need to go back to that user's part in the server.
But again everything happens in context after we update or we enter a cart or maybe when we when we
add things to history we need some context because if we do it right now is going to be really hard
to explain for me.
So we're going to just keep going forward.
We're going to do most of the things we need to do from the server and when we reached the section where
we need to add to the cart or to the split history.
Can go back to the server and create the routes a little bit more context.
Right.
Okay.
So let's go to the next section and we're going to start with a different thing inside the server.