OK so now we are going to be entering Brandt's And what we're going to move forward out of the users.
So.
And I'm locked in as a as an administrator and in the final project.
And we get to manage categories and we will be able to add categories things to different categories.
In this case we have the Brandts category and then what's now for each begin to create a new model.
Now in the future when this course is already out and everything else and I'm adding bonus sections
are going to add a different way to manage categories because you know we are going to create two different
models and maybe that is a lot of work if you have a 10000 category categories.
But right now again we are just practicing.
So we need to practice the model creation and everything else.
So we're going to create two different models.
The way it's going to be reasonable.
Don't worry.
So first to make the requests at least for brands we will need around.
So I'm going to create brand and I'm going to create two different routes.
Now of course the route needs to start with a different location so it's up just like this post open
and close and still we make a request to API for Slash and now I'm going to say product this is the
key word for the products related things.
And there's one brand now of course since we are posting things the only people can upload things to
our database need to be authenticated.
So I'm going to use that.
Our middleware and after that happens we're going to run a function.
Now we're going to do one more thing in a couple of minutes right here.
So request coma and a response.
Now we need to create a new brand new brand inside of the database.
The thing is that we don't have a model.
We have only a model for users.
So we need to create a model for this.
So we're going to go to models and file and then brand that jazz.
Now a lot of things if they just look like user so I'm going to go right here.
Copy mongoose and paste mongoose right now we need to create a schema.
So we're going to go right here.
The bottom Konst brand the key word of what we want to use and then schema equals to mongoose and always
schema.
In this case because we need to pass an object.
Now the brands are going to be real simple we just get a name.
So I'm going to say name the name needs to be required so we're going to say required equals to coma.
What type of this.
So it's going to be a type of a string not a number.
Then a coma you're going to use unique.
So all the brands are unique so unique one coma and are going to add a max length just like this of
100 max length.
All right.
And this is it resample.
So first I need to create a brand and this is what it's going to be equal to a mongoose and we create
the model.
The model is going to be based in what we do as a brand schema and we need to assign a new name so it's
going to be brand coma and brand schema.
All right.
So now I'm going to go right here and say module module loops module that exports and we export brand
with a capital B.
All right.
So now the brand it's ready to be used.
So I'm going to go to server and of course we need to put this on the server so we can use it.
So again we're going to go right here and say Konst brand brand equal re-acquire And you know brands
are going to copy this models and then brand.
All right.
So now we have the brand right here.
So inside of brand what we need to do we need to create a new brand.
So Konst brand equals new and then brand
OK to open and close and what are you going to be getting is the request and whatever we are passing
inside the body.
All right.
So next we entered that brand.
We do save opening close and we will be getting an error and a document back from mongoose or Mongo
D-B.
So if we do get an error what I want to do I want to return our response with Jaison response and success
just like this falls.
And if not of course we will attach the error is simple.
Now if everything goes OK I went to send that response with a status of two hundred a coma Jaison and
adjacent response success.
Just the same thing we did right here.
But the opposite success.
True and I got to be sending back the actual brand we just enter which is going to be dark again by
default.
The safe returns whenever we just enter to the database and that is it.
So let's test the route.
Can it copy this.
And first are going to do the following going to go to waifs are going to add a new folder.
And since this is going to be related to users I'm going to store inside directory users.
All right.
And I'm going to close this because we don't need it don't save whatever close it close it.
So again it's going to be a post request and we are using the environment virals So you are l and then
we paste the location.
Of course we need to set the headers of content type content type and then application that Jason and
I did it again.
Whoops sorry.
Content-Type then body Rawle and then Jason The only thing we are accepting accepting on the brand model
and schema is the name.
So we just pass an object which has to name some going to say name it calls and again it put my favorite
brand.
I have many favorites.
So this one it's my favorite.
OK.
So I'm going to click consent and we get is all false and are true.
So why is this happening.
And it's because the cookie we do have a cookie.
But since I locked out the cookie it's not good anymore right.
So we need to log in again how we can do it are going to go right here.
I'm going to go to log in and we can log in again.
Remember we can we store all of this.
So there's one it's not France is 4 5.
France is for our consent.
And I'm logged in.
So I'm going to go back again and again to send the same request again and we get success true.
The brand name it's Ivan S..
And the idea is this.
So if you go to Wake's right here with me do a refresh.
We get a new brand of evenness.
Very good.
So this is working.
So maybe you noticed a tiny tiny tiny tiny problem.
So I am a user.
This Francis 4 is a user right here.
And of course the token now it's OK and everything is OK.
But the role it's zero.
So this actually is incorrect.
Any user that the normal users they are not allowed to store brands you know they shouldn't be allowed
to store whatever they want into our server.
So what we need to do we need to create a new middleware that is going to be checking not only if they
are antiquated but they're going to be checking.
It's going to be checking if they're an admin.
So you can do it on out.
You could really do it on the same out.
But again just to show you that we can chain middleware is going to create an admin matter where it's
going to go to.
We're going to be real simple and I'm going to call it admin.
Yes.
So this mean that GST thing is going to do is going to check the role really simple.
So let admen equals.
We still get that a request response and the next.
Just like with with the with request response and next.
And then of course we get NF and we're going to do some checking if everything goes OK.
We're going to do next.
All right.
So sorry next.
So if the request that user that roll it's triple equal to zero it's not allowed.
Ron let me do three equals.
It's not an out.
So I'm going to return.
I'm going to send a response and the response I'm going to send.
It's going to be very silly.
So you are not allowed.
Get out now.
Something like that whatever.
So again right here.
You made might have different roles maybe a zero.
It's common users.
The next one it's administrators but they cannot post right because that could happen.
And of course what you're going to do.
You can do just several things.
You know several levels of of Abyan check.
And what you can do you can also check that request because maybe what they are trying to do is maybe
a post or maybe they can update it when they can they can update things but not post.
So inside of the request you can check if the user is doing what is the nature of this route.
If it's a post it has an update or does it get.
So right here for example you could say OK if the user eats one it means that it's allowed to update
and it's not allowed but it's not allowed to you know to post.
So I hear you could check if the request for example it's update or post and let the user move forward
or not.
Real simple right here.
We just have two levels.
Come users in a ministry years the administrators can do whatever they want.
All right.
So if the user is trying to post something to this route and it's not an illustrator we're going to
send this message.
If not they are allowed to move forward so we can get called next.
Then of course module that exports calls and we need to make this available from other components.
So I'm going to go back here and we need to import middleware.
Right.
Just like with it without going to copy and paste so outman and the require It's going to be admin.
So now we are making a reference to our.
Which is the first level check and then they were going to check it can check if it's been going to
save it.
They're going to try to add a different name.
Maybe Fender are not going to do it again.
And remember that this Franz's for it's not an administrator.
So I'm going to send that and we get you're not allowed.
Get out now.
So it's get it's not passing.
Of course if I go back and manually change this to roll of one I'm going to save it.
I'm going to try it again.
And it's passing.
Right.
So that is good.
So now we need to get to France and this is when he's going to be really simple.
So app that get and it's going to be forward slash API product and instead of brand it's going to be
Brant's what you can do YOU CAN DO get Brant's whatever doesn't matter just whatever name you want.
So from this route we will be receiving of course our request our response and what we do we enter brand
this brand because we've imported right here the top and what we're going to do.
We're going to find all brands that this is the only thing we're going to do with Brant's why we are
fetching all the brands because we need all the brands.
The only place where we can be making this request is from the admin side of things when we enter a
new product and we want to get all the brands right.
Okay.
So that is good.
So we say find and we say Bring everything that you have on the database.
Inside these documents so our brands model actually.
So brands and of course if we get an error we can send error and churn down.
So we return responds with a status of 400.
The usual stuff.
After a while you get bored doing this just like the way it is then response.
And we said in a status of 200 everything goes OK.
And what you sent is you get an object back from a mongoose or Mungo you sent the Brandt's which is
this brand and right.
What we get from the Find that is that we make a request from here.
Does it matter if we are of authenticated or not they're going to go here are going to save this and
Kloser users are going to save it inside of brands.
I could save it inside a product that doesn't matter.
So brand going out of course create a new one.
This one is going to be a good mustache.
You r l groups u r l I paste and of course I sent and that is that we get Ivan as an offender the only
two things we get on the database now one more thing before you move forward later when we are done
with the server we need to have several brands just like we get right here.
And we're going to we're going to get several words and everything else.
So I don't want you to know start going to postman an ad and adding several brands manually so far on
the server.
So I'm going to give you I'm going to put it right here.
A directory called Jason's And you can get a Jason with our adjacent file.
It's going it looks like it is file with all the brands and the IDs.
So what you can do you can grab that file delete what we have inside Brandt's so far this and you can
import that Jason File and you will get all of the list of brands.
I already did the job of entering all the brand so there's no need for you to manually enter everything.
All right.
I'm going to do it right now.
I'm going to bring the file and then I'm going to import it right here with you.
OK.
So it's a directory called Jason's.
And I'm going to give you several Jasons.
And this one called Brandt's and we get all the brands.
So I'm going to pretty much copy all of this.
I'm going to go to robo three.
I'm going to select pretty much everything and I'm going to delete documents.
Yes.
I'm going to close all of this because we really need this.
Now instead of Brandt's are going to do a right click and insert documents.
So what we need to do we just need to paste all the brands right there and then do save and open Brandt's.
And there we go.
We get all the brands.
All right.
OK.
So the next thing is going to be adding the types type of words.
So let's go to the next section and do that.
But now it's going to be much much easier because we've already have the admin and everything else we
just need to create a route and that's it.
So let's go to the next one and do that real quick.