OK so let's create a Witz model.
We are quick going to be real real simple since we now we know what to do with brands.
We know what to do with books.
So of course in the guitar world you might have a lot of type of words and depending on which one you're
using on the tar the guitar sounds different.
I know it makes no sense for you maybe for not not a guitar guy.
It says you know it's just wood.
Now it's really important depending on the wood depending on depends the sound.
So OK.
So I'm going to add the round in his closet and inside woods.
We pretty much need to do the same thing.
We need app just like this.
We need a post right.
We need the wrapped.
So it's going to be API for Slash and same product then the brand forward slash and Singler what.
Because we are posting one what then we need our middleware we need the admin middleware.
And then we run a function.
Right.
And this function contains a request and the response.
Now what we do we need to we need a model.
So we're going to go to model again to create a new one.
It's going to be called Wood dodginess are going to bring the requirement Gousse just like this.
Now that would be pretty much need to do the same thing.
We need to create a schema so Konst that wood and capital schema then mongoose opening close we create
a new schema and we pass an object or this once we're just using a name.
Something Real Simple we might use a lot of things.
But for now we're going to do it simple because we are just practicing in real life for example.
This project is going to take us a few few hours.
It's going to take us a few few hours.
So unique of course just like the Apprentice it's going to take us a few hours and in real life a project
like this with different guitars and tons of categories.
It's going to take you a month at least at least a month.
So length.
So if I tried to save time it's because of one reason you don't want to stay here 20 hours.
So first we create a concept and we need to create what we need to go to mongoose and create the model
and we passed the capital W word.
Now one very Come mistake is the capitals right here.
So make sure you use it correctly.
Then we passed the schema and that's it.
Now we need to make this available so module dot exports and we say would run would not at Brentwood.
We are not selling booze.
OK.
So we have the wood available.
So we need to go here and we need to import it.
So Konst is going to be equal to wood of course.
So what.
And models for Slash what.
So now we can here's what's so I mean it is going to go right here at the bottom.
Say Konst we create a word which is going to be equal to a new word.
And what we do we are going to be passing the request and then the body.
All right.
OK so now I'm going to answer that would that you would.
And I'm going to save it and I'm going to run a function of two ports and if we get we get an error
and we get a document back.
So if we do get an error.
So if error we get a return response that Jaison and we send a success of false and the error just like
with it before real simple.
And of course if everything goes OK we need to return the wood.
So tell us 200 Jaison opening close and we say success equals to true coma.
And we say what if we send whatever we are storing.
You know what if we get back from the Mongo am a goose Burguet.
I always like to do that there's no need to do it here but I like to do it.
OK.
So we are good.
Now let's create the get and then test it on postman says Now we know what to do.
We can actually do it.
So I'm going to copy the route.
We just need it.
And instead of wood it's going to be what's.
And of course we get a function a callback so request then responds we enter the wood model we have
right here top and scroll down and we can find everything find everything why we are finding anything.
Everything because of the same we a brand.
The only place where we can even be touching the all the other list of words it's when we enter a new
product.
So coma opening close and we're going to say error and then what's OK.
So whenever we get back we send an error if we get an error and we return response with a status of
400 or something like that.
And sorry for this I returned a response with a status.
Four hundred.
And then of course we sent our Roback just like we did before.
If everything goes OK we're going to send the response with a status of two hundred just like this 200
and then dot send and we send to what's all right looks nice.
So I'm going to go to the server and first I'm going to try to you know post something.
So I'm going to close this once close to brand open new one we will use the U R L and then we go to
what now it's a post.
Go to header's concent type enter and then application that Jaison enter Breguet inside body.
We go to Iraq and the only thing we have right here is a name.
And one very common name for words is our other word.
All right.
So let's write a note remember that we are of the educated and we are administrators so we sent and
we get true and we get back the other and fight refreshed us we get wood and we get what we get.
So going to store this way it would.
And now let's try to let's try to get it right to get the words so open close.
And now the route it's going to be a little bit different instead of what we get what.
And that is that I sent and we get all the what's.
All right.
We're going to store this and I'm going to say once again what's safe to waves now.
Just like before I give you the the read me file with the Brandt's are going to give you one for what's.
We just have three words.
Now in real life we have at least the most used words.
It's like no 20 20 categories 20 different types of what I just added three if you want.
You could add it manually I can just tell you Basswood for example either is one or mahogany.
You can add this manually.
We're going to do.
I'm going to give you the read me file with the what's OK.
So if I go to once we get this you know Basswood mahogany and other very good I got a copy of this.
To go to robo three.
Going to destroy this one just delete document and I'm going to right click insert.
Select everything.
Paste it.
There we go.
We have three different ones.
Burguet Zarka.
Later of course we're going to use it.
All right.
We are done with words.
I'm going to give you the zip file of what we have so far on the code.
And then we're going to move forward to the next category which is not a category.
It's going to be that the actual products that begin to be using that one.
It's going to be a little bit more challenging.
OK.
So let's go to the next one.