All right so now we're going to be working with products and if you ask yourself what kind of products
will that guitars.
Man if I go to guitars and open the you know the first one new product we get there's another name.
Either way.
So we get the images we get the price the shipping the not available and some specific actions which
are at the frets.
Maybe they would.
And something else that's good you know very simple.
So now what do we need to do we need to create an endpoint where the administrator can enter new guitars.
Right.
So we're going to do that.
So for this of course we need a model and I'm going to do that first.
I got to go to models and create a new one and I'm going to call this product instead of guitars.
Again you can call this whatever you want.
It's your practice project as well.
So product that jazz.
Now of course we need to bring a lot of things because we have a lot of things.
So this one is not going to be just like Woods and Brant and Brandt's much more complete.
So what I'm going to copy is the require.
OK.
So that is good.
So I got to go at the bottom and I'm going to say Kunst and product schema just like before.
Equals to mongoose.
Dodd schema and of course this one takes an object and I'm going to do this and I'm going to you know
close and complete everything we can to create a concept called product with a capital P equals Montagu's
dot model.
We create a model based on the schema and this model is going to be called a product with a capital
P.
Right.
When we pass is the schema right.
Of course we need to export this.
So module that exports equals opening close and we say that we want to send the product very good.
So now we need to do this we need to enter all the fields.
So each product will have a name saag and to say name open and close required.
Yeah.
Is required then a coma what type of this it's going to be a strength.
So drink comment coma.
It's unique.
Well yes the name is going to be unique because you might have one model of the same guitar.
You know you can have only one model you have different things.
You know maybe different colors you can attack and most of the times if you go to buy a guitar or something
like that it's like going to a Fender Stratocaster than the model and maybe you have the same model
but you have a different variation of the color of the type of food maybe.
And they have an additional name.
So OK so unique are going to do max length and max length of 100.
All right.
An Eminem mistake right here is length.
So Como we need an inscription.
So we're going to copy this and go right here at the bottom and this corruption.
So it is still required.
It's going to be a type of string.
It's not going to be unique.
And I'm going to add much more you know much more news right here.
You can do right here whatever you want doesn't matter it's up to your your project.
OK.
So then we have a price.
Now if there were a price is still required so require.
True.
Now the Taieb is going to be a number.
We're going to use a number right here.
So we say number and we have a max length as well.
So the max length is going to be 2 5 5 just like you know bar.
So we're going to go brand open and close and now this one it's a little bit special because when we
start something on the database what happens if I store the name of the brand.
Let's let's go right here.
I'm going to store something on a database and say that the name of this one inside rubber Mongo it's
fender right.
We store this just like with the real name inside of the database.
What happens if in the future a Fender change they change the name and now they are Fender or something
like that.
You will need to go through all your products inside the database and manually changed the name friend
or friend or and it's not a good idea.
So what we are going to be putting right here inside a brand it's the I.D. of the brand we have on the
collection of brands which is you know this.
So maybe in the future if they change Fender we can change it from here and it's going to change throughout.
You know he's going to change it in pretty much and the whole application because when we've fetched
information we fetched the ID and then we make a reference to this name right.
Pretty standard stuff for for servers and actually databases.
So what do we do.
How can we tell Mungo's that this brand it's up.
It's an object or is an idea is an object idea.
So I'm going to say type and I'm going to leave it like this.
So what we need to do we need to use mongoose that type we talk to access schema then types just like
this types dot and then object ID.
We get it right there.
Object ID.
And for this we need to bring mongooses Kema right now at the top.
We are bringing Mungo's but not making a reference to the schema.
So we can have you know begin to need to bring it.
So when we go right here the top end to the filing.
So I'm going to say Konst schema just like this and we're going to bring it from mongoose Dodd and schema.
Now if I use it just like let me fix this if I use it like this.
Mongooses dot schema dot.
This is going to work because we are still bringing bingos friends came out fron mongoose.
But now I have a barbel called schema so I can do schema types.
So again the only way with it is just an alias to just a typeless code.
That's good.
Now the next one is a little bit weird to explain.
I'm going to say Raphe and I'm going to say Brandt.
Now we know that the reference of this is going to be the database called Brandee the collection called
Brand.
Right.
OK.
And if you remember if you go to brand we call this like this.
So I'm using the exact same name later when we fetch some information from the day from the database
this reference is going to be very handy.
Right now I'm going to add it and you should add it as well.
And we can discuss this later.
So we're going to do a coma and the brand is going to be required.
And all right what is next.
We have shipping.
Of course if you're buying a cheap guitar you don't have any shipping.
But if you buy a very expensive guitar required you do have shipping.
Actually I'm I'm having a problem with that right now.
I'm about to buy a guitar and it's a really expensive guitar and it does when it's and of course boo
Leon.
So it's going to be true or false of course.
And they and they of course it's a very expensive guitar and they give me no shipping and I'm buying
it from a different country so that well I need to call them in and ask them OK.
So then we we will check if it's available or not.
Sometimes of course if you're buying something it needs to be available for you to buy it.
So we're going to give you an information of the to the user on the react end of things saying that
the guitar is available or not so required and true.
And this one really is going to be just like the other one a boolean.
All right.
Then we have the wood and the wood.
Same thing then brand.
Same idea.
So I'm going to copy brand I'm going to do koma I'm going to paste it in right here going to say wood
and its schema types object.
But now it's going to be what.
And remember we need to use the same same name that we have a different category called friends.
You know the guitars they have frets.
So this one is going to be required and it's going to be true and it's going to be a type of number
of guitars.
They have like 20 24 or 22 frets.
So you don't have.
We didn't get a lot of options.
That's why we didn't do a model of this.
So then we need to add something.
We need to add the sold what we can to track how many guitars we sell because at home we need to fetch
the best sounding guitars.
So we need to add this.
So I'm going to say sold open it close and type of number coma I add a max length.
I don't want to type it.
I'm going to copy from here.
The max length is going to be 100.
And what we can do if we don't at this is going be a little bit weird.
If we don't add it at the database whenever we search we show something is the default the Isold is
going to be equal to nothing.
So what we need to do we can set a default saying that whenever we enter a new guitar we sold zero of
this item.
So we can set a default like here that we have publish.
So I'm going to say publish
publish and this one will be required.
I get it copy require and that type is going to be Boullion or why we are adding a polish.
Maybe you are entering a new guitar in your database but maybe it's not ready for sale.
You can at least start selling it the next month or something like that so you can put the type required.
I'm sorry they publish false and it will not be displayed on the client.
You know pretty simple.
What else we are going to add we an image just not right now are we're going to do it much later.
So ima just open it close and this type is going to be an array.
Why.
Because we might add different images.
And just like with it before I can add a default the fault of an array an empty array.
Of course if we have an empty array we will displayed.
Is this you know sorry.
Image not available.
If I go to the product sorry image not available.
If we do have images of course we just play the images.
That's why we are doing that default right.
There there's one more thing.
Sometimes when you enter products or you enter things in your database you need to know when this item
was entered in the database and when maybe was updated.
For that we need time stamps and what we can do right here instead of creating one value 1 property
for this.
We can say just like this and say Time stamps.
Just like this time stamps and true and they will be generated out magically by Mongo when we enter
a new product.
So I believe everything is ok either way if I made a mistake we can see it on the console or reflected
on the database.
So let's go to the server and create the route for this.
All right so I'm going to create a new section for products so products.
All right.
So of course this is going to be post so OP post opening close the location.
It's still API and products just like this.
And since I've already have products I cannot do products I'm going to say article now make sense its
products because we have dumped model.
But you know that's fine.
Of course they need to be authenticated to do this and they need to be administrators to do this.
So at the end we will run the callback function with a request and a response.
Forget Now we need to add a new product.
So we need to import the product right here at the top.
So I'm going to say a product with a capital P product and we will require this from models and product.
So going to go Kunst product equals to new product and we're going to get the data from the request
and then the body.
Very good.
So of course then when you just we just need to save.
We've done this many times before.
You can try to do it by yourself.
So I'm going to say product Dodd safe open close.
And after we saved everything we will get something back with an error and the actual document.
Now if we get a mistake we're going to catch that error and we're going to return something else.
So Rob responds with Jaison saying that you know dude something is wrong.
So false coma and error.
All right.
Of course if everything goes OK we will send a response with a status of 200.
And then we will send some JSM back and we will send its success just like this success.
True.
And I will I want to send the article back so we can see it on the front end.
So article and make a reference to the doc that we get back from mongoose right.
Resample So now we just it's going to copy this.
I'm going to go to post man.
There is a movie with post man right.
And this is actually forget about this.
This is actually from the all the other product.
It's the same project but it's the one that it's done.
I was just inspecting.
So I'm going to open a new one.
And we are now on Waites.
So it's going to be a post open and close.
We use the euro.
We do have a cookie and I believe this cookies ok you know the token it's OK.
So API product an article when it said headers of content type you know usual stif usual stuff Content-Type
an application.
Jason got the body wrong.
And Jason so right now we need to do a lot of things because we have a lot of fields.
So open close.
First we need a name.
And of course if you don't know about guitars I'm going to give you the name of my guitar.
I'm very proud of this proud proud 2 2 4 2 2 2 0 4 I forgot 2 4 0 2 0 2 4 0 2 wonderful guitar very
jazzy.
So the name is that is the name of the guitar not the brand.
The brand is different than coma.
We need a description so this corruption me it correctly description and description super awesome guitar.
In real life you will get a lot of you know a pretty large string because the description now you know
there's no need.
Now we need to price the price.
It's going to be two thousand and this is the real price.
So yeah a lot of money but I do a lot of playing That's why I paid.
So let me get to brand.
I cannot say Ivan.
I can not do that.
Because remember that we are storing the ID of this on the database.
So what I need to do I need to pass the ID of I have an s.
So if I go to robo 3 t and i go to France I tried to find one is one and it's this one I'm going to
select an edit document and I'm going to copy the ID and then I go back there is it next to the brand.
Note the shipping.
So we say shipping is going to be equal to true.
Then we say it will check if it's available VEI level and it's going to be equal to true this in real
life.
It's not true.
They never have it available because it is an expensive guitar.
So that what.
And of course need to do the same thing with this and if you're asking yourself why are you buying expensive
guitars.
Do you have a lot of money.
No I don't.
I'm am addicted.
So I spent money that I don't have.
So I'm going to click on this.
This one is OK.
So the word the idea for the wood is going to be this.
Then of course we need Fretz.
And again this one has 24 frets coma and then and it's the last one we need to select.
We need to put the Publish the publish is going to be true.
All right man.
Everything is good.
So this is this should be it.
We shouldn't be getting any palms of course we might get a little problem a tiny problem because we
did a lot of coding and I'm human.
All right.
So we have everything just going to send that and see what happens.
And I couldn't get a response.
And we're going to check the server.
I'm pretty sure we get them stick right here.
So module export that product.
It's mondial.
That's a new one.
So let's go to product and module exports.
All right let's try again.
I told you I'm human.
All right.
Simple mistake.
So we get a response back with success.
True.
And all the information about that article.
Right.
Very good.
Man going to open and refresh tapes go to products and it's good.
And notice that we are creating the getting the created ad in the updated.
And this one will it will come handy later and everything else is default images.
It's an array so everything is good.
And notice that now inside the brand we don't have just the ID between coats.
We get the key word object id just like the idea of this of this element.
Right.
So Mongo is doing this for us because later we're going to be referring to this brand and this would
as an object ID.
We really need this.
OK.
So everything is good.
I'm going to go right here.
I'm going to save this and this one is going to be products or could be article actually article save
two weights and now of course we need a lot of a lot of products right here to do the next route.
Going to be fetching the products are many products.
So just like before I'm going to put inside Jason the products and you will need to import it and going
to do it with you right now.
OK so I got the products and you know a lot of products are I mean.
So I'm going to copy all and go to robo 3.
T going to delete the one I have and delete it.
And then of course insert and select and paste all make sure you don't have any spaces at the top and
at the bottom at the end it was like this.
I'm going to save it.
And there we go.
Now whenever you add some information and you pay something you can just validate and rehab.
Jason is valid.
So you can do that.
All right so we have a lot of products right now.
So we need it.
Let's go to the next section and on the next section we're going to be fetching the products.