OK so now what are we going to be doing.
It's fetching products by something.
In this case we're going to be fetching products by id and we're going to do this in two different ways.
First we're going to get the parts by ID then we're going to get articles just articles and then a product
buys something.
Buy sell or buy a rival.
Don't worry we will get we will get there.
Now the first thing we're going to do is to buy I.D..
Now there's two ways you can get information to the server right from the client to the server and it's
by using a Jasen sending a Jasen right.
Or you can use a query string.
If you're asking yourself what is the query string a query string looks like this.
It's a are you get the you know the actual Your L where you're making the the the request then you get
the question mark and then you have right here an attribute and inside of the attribute you have some
values.
And in this case it's going to be an ID and then maybe you have a different attribute so you concatenate
everything with the ampersand and maybe the type.
And just like this type and this type is going to be equal to something else or whatever.
So this is called string.
So now we're going to do with strings and later begin to do.
Jason Ryan so I just want to show you both ways.
Just in case you know so now we need to get by.
So I'm going to say app that get opening close.
And the route is going to be API product and their products could be articles articles underscore and
score by ID.
All right of course after this we just run a function with a request and a response.
Copy paste.
Now what I want to do.
I don't want to get.
I went for this route to process single IDs or many IDs.
So right here if I'm sending one ID OK that is good.
So this is one ID but I want I want to be able to put coma and put a different ID Tacoma different ID
and coma.
So this is going to bring four different articles.
So right here of course we need to make some logic to check if we have many or we have one and we do
it with type if type equals to Array.
It means that we have an array of product so we need to search for an array of products.
If we have single we will search search for a single ID.
All right.
So first I'm going to create a barbell called Type let and type equals.
And now if you remember right here we are using Jaison so request body enters to Jason you no searches
for Jason.
In this case we want to search for query.
So it's a little bit different.
So I'm going to say request Querrey Dodd and I want to cert and went to get the type.
So this viable will be assigned with whatever we have inside type.
And if you're asking yourself how can we use this.
It's because we are using body parser and you are encoded so that you know where it comes from this.
The other one comes from this.
All right.
So what else are going to create a viral called items and it's a big In the beginning is going to start
with whatever we have inside the idea.
So request Querrey idea.
All right.
Now I need to check if I have an array.
No a single ID or many IDs.
So if opening close and if I have a type just like this I'm going to say array.
There's many ways you can do this.
You can of course.
It's kept the type in check if you have any rights you could do this.
I'm just doing this a little bit simpler.
So I the way this is just come in javascript.
It's not new or node or re-act right nor react.
So let IDs inside the IDs what I want to do and when to get whatever value I have inside items or requests
to query that ID and split them like coma why am I adding the coma.
And it's because the inside of the object's ID of mongoose we didn't have coma's.
So as long as you use a character that is not being used by the ID you can split by coma.
So I'm going to say request quite nicely and split open and close coma.
I could just use this rival.
All right so we are inside an array.
I want these items.
Barbel to the national right and right here we are creating the split of IDs so I get to go to items
are going to convert this to an array and I'm going to enter items just like this items.
Dodd Oh sorry.
Items equals.
And this is going to be IDs dot map opening close and on each iteration.
I'm going to do something.
So I'm going to say items and I'm going to run something.
So what I want to do I want to return the return inside of the items array not just the idea of the
array.
I don't want to do this.
I want to do this right what I want to do.
I want to return something else instead of the array.
Because this are IDs so I need to convert them to an object id from mongoose.
So what I return is going to be Mungo's just like this.
Then we access types got and I'm going to be entering object ID.
And what we do I pass the item.
So this what it will do in the end is going to push inside of the array.
The idea of the item but converted to object ID and if we check the database the ID looks a little bit
different.
All right.
Good so this is the first.
So now since we could get an array or we could get a single item we need to make the actual request.
So I going to go right here and I'm going to bring products just like with it before product we have
it right here.
Product.
OK.
So inside product I went to find some things I'm going to do Don.
And I'm going to go right here at the bottom and I've got to say Fine.
Now inside of find we need to specify what we want to find.
In this case we are searching by ID.
Now we want to pass something else which IDs and since we have one.
We could have one ID or many IDs.
I need to pass this.
So we say in with the dollar sign inside and then I pass items now items could be one item or many items.
So this one takes a single value or an array.
That's why we can use it just like this.
All right.
And I made a mistake.
I just need to add one more curly brace.
All right.
Oh sorry.
I'm going to go right here.
I'm going to start.
I'm going to change things.
They're going to go right.
Going to go right here at the bottom.
Now if we use this we need to use the execute.
So X open and close.
So whenever we execute this we're going to open and close right here and we're going to run the callback.
So this Colback we get an error and we get docs and what are you gonna do.
Oh sorry.
Exec with the letter C.
And what are you going to do.
I'm going to return our response with a status of 200.
And I'm going to send whatever we get back from ducks.
So the only thing we are doing is just finding products by one single item or by an ID and then we execute
whatever is that we want to execute and we send back to docs.
Very good.
OK.
We're going to have a tiny problem but it's going to it's a little bit hard to explain right now without
the context.
First we're going to show we can see what we get inside postman and they're going to tell you how to
fix it.
All right.
So let's go to post-master are going to go and create a new route and this one calls API and you know
by ID so and then to use your I L and then by ID of course we need to add more things.
If not nothing is going to work.
So we have to add the attribute ID and we need to add some real IDs.
So I'm going to go and copy this one inside products.
You should do the same ID and I'm going to put a coma and again to put it different id think about it.
We have it right here inside the read me.
So again a copy a different one.
Whatever doesn't matter.
And paste that and I'm just going to bring two maybe three.
That's OK.
So coma and of course then we need to specify the type remember.
So I'm going to say type ampersand and then type in this case.
We have many is going to be a.
Right.
So let's see what happens.
Going to send it and we get it.
Man OK so we get an array with three different products with the you know specific ID.
Right so this works.
What happens if we tried to get one right.
I'm going to go here.
Going to delete the first the last two and this one is going to be single can assent and we get a single
one.
Now notice this.
We are getting a response back but the brand and the wood are an ID because in real life they are an
ID.
So we're going to get this to display at inside of here and we can output an ID.
And what we're going to do after we get the product from the server we're going to make a new request
to the server with that ID to get the brand and then to get a different category.
What happens if you have 20 categories.
So that is a problem.
So if you remember inside products we use the ref.
So what this does is that we can make or we can specify right here in this request and we can tell.
Ok dude.
Where we at a reference so I need you to code to go to this database to this model and find whatever
you get as a name or value for this object ID.
So it creates kind of a relationship if you're used to work with with with with the larval for example
or maybe this PH BE FREE frameworks.
We make a relation it's a relationship.
So how can we make it work.
So what we need to do we need to add the the method populate like this and then opening close and inside
of here not in capital.
We need to tell the application which option which field we want to populate from here since this one
it's brand.
What we do is we say okay we want to populate brand that we do DOD and we want would as well.
So I'm going to copy go other Bonnin and say what.
All right.
So let's try again and see what happens.
Right so we try again.
And now we began its brand but we get an object.
So it's going to the database bring in whatever we have inside of that idea of brand and it's sending
this response so now we get the name right and same thing with it.
So get really good works or is good.
OK so now and then the next section instead of getting by ID.
What we need to do is we need to get kind of a different kind of articles.
Let me tell you what let me just show you why right now I'm going to go to the final one and I'm going
to go to home.
So now what we need to do is we need to fetch four different products at least for home with some kind
of arguments.
This ones are the best selling guitars.
So we need to search the whole database for the for to bring the four products with more you know amount
of sense and the same thing for new arrivals instead of checking by cell.
What are we going to do is check by date.
So we need to bring the articles by date.
So for this of course we need a different route with a different logic.
So let's go to the next one and do that one.