So we need to bring the articles by a rival you know by a rival and then by cell.
All right.
So pretty much we need to create one single route that can handle this kind of requests.
So first we will get the by arrival.
So I'm going to put it right here.
And then of course you'll have I don't know for Slash articles this is going to be the route articles
and we need to be passing some quiet drinks.
We're still using coarse drinks.
So the first the first attribute is going to be sort by inside of the sore byde a sort by we can to
put what we want to sort out by if we get by a rival if you checked the database what can we use so
we can get to create it at.
All right.
So this one is going to be created created at.
Right.
Then we need to search to specify the order because this is going to be bringing in is going to break
the last.
I don't know four of the created at.
So what is going to be the order.
So in this case we can specify in order just like a regular database by descending.
Remember that we could use ascending or descending with databases.
So we're going to specify an order.
And then of course we can do ampersand in any to tell the application how many articles I want to get.
So in this case we can just limit.
And in this case we just going to bring 4.
So then the other one is going to be by cell.
So in this one instead of using the created add we need to do something else.
So when we put it right here.
So we need to still bring articles sorted by and then sold.
If you remember on the database we have the key sold.
So of course is going to order everything by sote.
Now of course we will need to bring it descending and we're going to still bring four.
So this is what we're going to do.
Now of course we need to create the route and the logic inside.
Just like with it right here.
So so going to go to app.
It's going to be a get route and again to say API for Slash products and articles.
All right then.
Function opening close and we're still getting a request and a response.
Right.
So first we need to bring We need to store inside of our of all the sort by that order and the limit.
And you can add as many as you want.
Doesn't matter how many atrophies you want.
So first we begin to set the order the order is going to be equal to whatever we get back from the order.
Inside right here now sometimes could happen that maybe the order right here it's missing and you can
have it.
So what I'm going to do I'm going to say OK I went to get the request Querrey that order.
And if I don't have it I'm going to do something else.
So if we do have it this one is going to be equal to the same thing.
But if we don't we don't have it by default is ascending.
All right then to sort by.
So let and then sort and then buy equals to request that Querrey Querrey dot and then sort by now if
we do have it then we going to use it.
And if we don't have it by default we search by ID right then we have the limit.
So let limit equals request that Kohary that limit if we do have it we can bring the limit.
If not it's going to be by default 100 and make sure that this is a number and not a string.
All right.
And and we might have a skip.
I don't know if you use a skip on the database and some database databases.
So sometimes you get to skip.
So would skip pretty much is going to be something like this.
For example we are bringing out no limit.
We are bringing 100 articles so you can add a skip to the request.
And of that hundred 100 if you put five is going to skip the first five and give you ninety five the
remaining ninety five.
So of course we didn't have this we could do it.
I'm not going to do it because it's real simple.
OK so now we need to make that request you know go to the database and bring it.
So product just like this.
We're going to find.
And we need to sort a lot of things.
So what we do we populate just like with it before with Brandt remember that we need this brand.
Let me do it just like this popular brand.
Now going to copy the wood right here on the bottom.
So whenever we get articles we're going to get the brand and the wood.
All right then we need to sort by.
So I'm going to say sort opening close and right here we need to pass an array and array inside.
So what we do we pass this sort by right here and then we need to we need to order which or we're going
to be using.
All right what else are going to do with this going to go at the bottom and we need to specify the limit.
So the limit is going to be whatever we have inside limit.
And then just like we did before we can execute.
And of course we get an error or we get the articles and we run a function.
All right.
So if we do get an error if error what we send is a return return and we turn the response with a status
of 400 dried Breguet and then send error.
So then of course if everything goes OK you can send a response with the articles.
And that is it.
Now once you figure out how this works everything else is just really simple.
So now we are finding a product we are doing a find.
We sort of get the brand and the information we need and we sorted by whatever we are passing right
here.
And then of course we are limiting.
And we are executing.
So this one it's exec.
I always make a mistake right here.
I don't know that we go all right.
So let's try again.
So I'm going to go over here and create a new route and I'm going to copy this.
It's going to be a get.
And of course we need to put the moustache you are l.
And then of course I'm going to use the first Dubai arrival.
I'm going to copy this sorry copy and paste it.
So you need to do the questionmark sort by equals to create it at ampersand or their descending ampersand
limit.
For now this is going to fail.
I'm going to tell you why in a second.
Maybe you know why.
All right.
I'm going to dissent and it failed.
It says Limit field must be numeric.
Whenever we are sending error Balios in you know as a string everything gets converted to a string.
So this number that you're getting right here.
It's actually a string and limit right here.
Take a number.
So if we don't at limit it means that we don't have it.
I'm going to send it and we get it and we get all the products because by default is going to this number
100.
So very quick fix what we can do.
Parse.
Int.
Opening close
and we save it and I'm going to go back to limit 4.
There you go.
So I'm going to send it and parse it.
Sorry Par's and
look at you know we kind of get it we get the first one.
Let me make this a little bit bigger.
If it's Laramie out maybe not.
So we get one we get to get three and we get four Burguet so we get four different articles.
We get Ben.
So OK so now we are able to search by date and of course if we checked this this one it's the a c you
700.
So this one should be one of the last products AC.
Seven hundred.
So that works OK.
Now Same thing with this the buy sell.
We need to bring this one so I'm going to copy paste and soundbytes sold descending limit and I'm using
Skipp where he uses Gip.
So I'm going to send and we get it.
You know this one sold 38 15 and 15.
We didn't have a lot of sold articles.
I just hardcoded this information got.
So we were a good man.
All right.
So now we can fetch articles by something.
So we are pretty much done with the server.
We have pretty much all the basic things we need.
The basic routes we would need to start creating the the front end.
So I'm going to skip this.
Of course this is going to go to you and you can you know download and you can add things you can do
whatever you want but on the next section we will start creating the client right here and bring in
react and creating the header and you know everything else.
So let's go to the next section and start with the client.