OK so now we need to bring the clients you know react to the client.
Right we're going to start with client so.
OK.
So we need to do create we act out.
Very simple.
Now you don't need to close the server.
Actually you need to keep the server alive for now beginning to do all the configuration but you know
keep it alive.
Now what I need you to do is to open a new tap again to go right here.
If you're Mac new tab with settings and it will open and you tap inside of waifs already.
Now if you're using the terminal of the code if you're using B as code right here when you go to terminal
you can open a new one right here by clicking the plus is going to open and you bash.
Right.
And if you're using Windows you just need to go to again command and you will need to navigate to know
this directory.
Now when we are in sort of waves are going to do CD and then client I'm going to go inside that directory
inside this directory and we can install right here.
So we do create then react then app and then of course seems I'm already inside the directory.
I'm going to put a dot and I get a press center.
It's going to take a while and I'll be right back OK so everything was installed.
So now we need to install the dependencies.
So I'm going to do a clear and remember that on the previous section I gave you a text with all the
dependencies we need to install.
So I'm going to make this a little bit bigger and I'm going to paste them right here.
So we will need to install a lot of things we will use Fonte awesome.
So a lot of fun.
Awesome to use icons.
We use material.
I actually use for making the requests.
Now this re-act images is going to be the light box when we use the light box.
We have a light box right here.
Maybe it didn't show you right here.
So that is the dependency.
So we use redux.
We're going to use redux here re-act router we use the slider Riak slick.
And then again redux redux promise we use redux thunk and this Riak drops.
It's where we're going to use this one to upload the images right.
And then we have a moment for time and then we're going to use a different dependency for Pay-Pal because
we will use Paypal right here a fake Paypal is the sandbox of PayPal so we need to install things.
So Precentor is going to take a while and I'll be right back.
OK so everything was installed.
So I'm going to do clear.
And before I start the server again.
Let me close this before I start.
Server a development server or react.
I'm going to go to public remember I gave you this already.
All the links we can all be using.
I'm going to paste them right now so.
All right.
So we will use the icons from the front.
Awesome.
So we need that CSSA the Google fonts.
Going to be using.
And the last one the last see SS is going to be for the right here for re-act slick.
And notice that we are using this CDN.
All right now inside of the source directory.
Going to go right here.
And we don't need to see a sunken going to delete it.
Just like this.
What else we we don't need the app that pass that test so I can delete it again.
The index Yes that's not going to really use it.
Going to trash logo.
Goodbye just like with the other projects and the service worker I'm going to just delete it.
So I'm going to go to this.
I'm going to delete this so that this the reference to index's.
SS Can I save it go to app.
Delete the import for the logo.
Delete the import for the CSSA.
And I'm going to say just my app whatever.
All right so now let's run the server.
So I'm going to go right here.
And how can we run it just like with that yarn.
And I did I did NPM install on the other one.
I'm not really sure.
Now I did remember.
You always need to NPM if you're using NPM.
So NPM start going to start.
Give it a minute.
OK so everything is working.
We get my app very very good.
Now we have one tiny problem this localhost is going to be 3000.
Right.
It's the default by react and our server it's working on a different place.
It's working at 0 0 2.
So right from the start we have the problem that we have this development server every act of the client
in one place and the server our server in a different place.
So just to give you an example.
And what's going to happen what's the problem with this.
I can import ASIO's from ASIO's and it can make a request to our server.
So on the component just like this did mount going to open and close.
I'm going to do actually those dot get opening close and going to make a request to France.
I just want to get the prints right.
So if you remember it's API.
I don't remember.
Let me say this.
The brands were API product brands.
So if I make a request here and then of course we can't the response just like this.
And we run a function I'm going to cancel log whatever response I get.
So response in relo the application Embryon the console and on the console we get failed to load we
source to server respond with situs of course your for now right here when we whenever we do this we
are making a request to the server and this server it's in localhost 3000.
So it's a different location different different domain.
So we're not going to really work.
Now what happens if I do.
OK.
My server it's in H.
TTP Kallen forward slash forward slash local host.
Let me do it right.
Localhost host and our server it's in 3 0 0 2.
So I'm going to do 3 0 0 2.
So this one should work right.
OK I'm going to make the request.
Not really happening because you're not allowed to make request requests from your server to a different
server.
If the other server it's not allowing you now instead of here whenever we push production this is going
to be one server a single location.
The problem is that now we react.
We are running the development server.
You're running two servers.
So what do we need to do.
We need to modify things a little bit so we can run one server and they can communicate just with one
server.
First I'm going to delete this.
I'm going to delete it and save it.
How can we fix this.
So first I get to go to inside the client.
I'm going to go inside the package and Jason now react.
They give us the ability to proxy our you know our development server.
So I'm going to do a coma.
I'm going to go right here at the bottom and I'm going to say proxy now proxy.
Of course we need to pass some values.
What we can do we can set where we want to go.
In this case for I-Slash API for Slash.
So all the routes all the requests from our server from the re-act server going to this location they're
going to target a different place.
So Target open it close and it's a TTP call and forward slash force slash and local post 3 0 0 2.
All right what happens if we try again and then reload the application.
Same prom the thing is that we are making changes to package that Jason to this one.
So we need to restart the server.
So I to go to react.
It could kill it and start again.
So now the server is going to refresh.
And now we get a response.
So we are getting a response for data with all the data we need.
Remember I'm not doing console log response data.
If we do it we get the data.
But we are getting the correct response.
This is what we need.
So now we can make a request to this and every and the application will treat it at the same as the
same server.
And then when we need to push this to production of course we need to change them settings.
But for now this is going to work like a charm.
All right.
So what is the other problem.
The other problem is that we have a right here and a batch opened with this with the server and then
we have a different one with our server where our server notes server.
So it would be wonderful if we could Dron all in the same place.
Right.
OK.
So we can do this now.
If I go to let me close the client right now if I go to the server to our main package that Jason right
here we've installed something called concurrently.
So concurrently what it does.
It can run two different commands at the same time not at the same time but will it will execute one
and then another one with the same command line.
So am I'm going to go right here into the scripts of the package at Chaisson in the main the root directory
Arayan.
So we have test.
We have start and we have server.
So I'm going to go right here and create a new one which is going to be client.
Now the client will be to will do the NPM run start.
So what do we need to do when it triggered this kind within concurrently.
Then we have to just show you we have a different command which is going to be Deppe and this def will
execute the server command and then the client commands.
Now the client the server inside the client it's inside the client so we need to go to the root and
turn the client and let the application know that we need to run this one inside the client so to do
this we do NPM Bruhn start and we need to specify where we are where can we find this MP from start.
And there's one it's inside the package that Jasen of the client.
All right.
So what we do we do.
Minus minus prefix and then a client.
So pretty much we are going to route.
We are entering client and that we go.
All right.
So inside dev to run the server and declined from the same place we need to use concurrently we have
it right here at the bottom.
I'm going to paste in it now.
What do we need to do instead of doing a four slash.
We need to do a backslash.
Now if your keyword it's a little bit weird.
And I have this problem in the past.
Someone hired me to do the job.
But I had to go to their office and they gave me a computer.
It was the weirdest computer man.
So you need to copy the one at the top the one of the tests.
All right.
And then paste it.
So we do quotes and we add and you quote and what we do we do and PM run server.
If you noticed we are running this command from this command.
This is the idea of this of course I need to close that and I need to add one more one more quote.
Now what I want to do again I want to run the server and the client at the same time.
So I'm going to do space.
I'm going to do the same thing.
Open quote and PM run clients now.
Now I'm running this one.
Then of course again and we close it.
And that is it.
So now when we do pian run Dev from a single batch concurrently is going to first run the server and
then run the client.
That is what's going to happen.
OK.
So I'm going to go right here to the terminal.
I'm going to kill it.
I'm going to close it.
I don't need it anymore.
And on this one I'm going to kill it and I'm going to close it get it to clear.
Now I am inside the root directory.
Right.
Our main route and now I'm going to do NPM from DEP so NPM or I could do John run def in my case I'm
using yarn so I'm going to run it first and you can see it right here concurrently running this too.
So first we start to server.
This is what it's doing.
Sorry it close.
So first we start the server and then it's going to run react.
And that's why the server reloads.
And we have the local host three thousand and we are still able to get the data.
So now you don't need to run two batches you just run one.
And if in the future you need to run more things.
It's just added to concurrently and that's it.
All right man so this is pretty much done now on the next section.
We will start building the actual Web site you know adding header footer the body and creating home
and everything else.
So let's go to the next section and start.