OK so inside source resources.
Yes.
And the style and the images.
Now one more thing and again I'm going to tell you don't take a reference for this course.
At least this is styles that see assess I make this made this really really really superfast.
Why.
Because of course again I didn't want to spend a lot of time doing the SS now.
When you create a Web site the real CSSA has to be neat.
And I wouldn't use just CSSA when you SAS or less or something like that media compiler but not just
this.
Now if you look at it you can check it out.
It's a mess right.
I did this really really fast.
Don't take this CSSA as a reference for real life right now.
Again if you ask me how much time took me to build this.
Everything like three days maybe four.
With the design.
And it's because of course it didn't spend a lot of time do it.
SS Now when I build the most was the times when I build things I'd spend a lot of time doing Yesus a
lot of time because of course this is a mess and you could move forward on the application.
Everything is going to be a mess.
So it's always good to have a good C Ss so don't take this one as a reference.
OK.
So of course and on the application we're going to focus on re-act pretty much and Javascript.
We're going to be using routes.
Right.
OK.
So first I'm going to go and inport the CSX import data for Slash resources for Slash CSSA for Slash
styles.
Right.
We don't have an app I want to get it routes so I renamed the routes the app to routes that get that
G-S right.
OK.
Then of course we going to change some things.
So instead of the index we are not importing it up we are importing routes then go back and bring out
routes Burguet.
So instead of routes we need to wrap routes with browser router right.
We are going to reuse routes so we need the browser router browser and then router.
OK.
It's going to be from re-act router.
Dom Burguet So we need to wrap the application with re-act browser Dom.
Now again we changed the name from app to routes so going to say routes and that is that for now they
are.
This is going to change because we need to bring redux right here.
The make some space.
So now routes it's not up any more.
Right.
So we need to change all of this right here.
So I'm going to go to app and now let me delete everything and I'm going into that component.
So it's just going to be statelets component.
So Konst then routes it's going to be equal to just a function and the function will return something.
Now when will we turn around and the switch.
So we need to bring switch and route from a re-act Rotterdam.
So import we bring switch just like this coma and route and it's going to be from re-act router.
Dom very good.
All right.
So right now we are just waiting to export of course there we go as white it was great out.
I don't know why and this one it's a mistake.
We just react from react.
It's a mistake from the virus code.
Now we need to return something where we going to be returning.
It's going to be a switch.
Right.
So switch opening close can it did this many many times.
Now we need to render a route.
We need to return a route.
We don't have any of that.
So I'm going to create one single round round.
And right now it's going to be components and inside components are going to create the home route.
That's the main route.
So home and this home is going to be in the works that Julius index is.
All right so of course right now home is going to be a class then of course we can extend this.
So re-act class based component and this one calls home.
All right.
Like E.T. then home.
OK.
So now I'm going to go back to routes and I need to import the route.
So import port home capital H home from full force slash components and then home since it's an index
we don't need to bring it up.
So I'm going to bring gert just like this.
We do need a path and the path is going to be for us.
We need exact.
And then we need to specify which components we are going to be rendering and what happened.
Component equals and then equals whole.
All right.
Very simple stuff.
Okay.
So of course if we go we get home that is good.
Now we need to render a header and then a footer.
So like we did before we can create a layout for this right just like with the before pretty much same
idea.
So inside source I'm going to create a new directory called HBC for height or their components or you
can put it inside components.
This is completely up to you.
Now we need to create the layout hato see.
So layout that.
Yes.
So this layout will be rendering the header whenever we need to get in the middle right here which is
home in this case.
And then the footer.
So I need to create a class based component re-act class based component.
And later we're going to be extending this layout.
That's why I why I'm creating a class.
So I'm going to change the name to lay out with a capital L default layout.
So right now we are just going to render a container.
So this class name and then page container.
And inside we will be rendering this that prompts the children.
So I know this is going to boring because we did this already so it's all the usual setup of course
nothing happens because we need to import inside routes and wrap everything with layout.
So import layout from that for Slash HSC and then lay out a graph layout and wrap everything inside.
I get the bloats and you know we get this letter.
And then at the bottom we get nothing.
So I'm going to go to lay out and in this case right here we're going to create a component for the
header and we can create a component for the footer.
So if the up readouts I mean get the header and footer.
So that works.
So now we don't we don't have headers.
So I'm going to go to component's create a new directory for this and I'm going to call it Hetter underscore
footer so you can choose whatever name in that footer.
Inside what we will get of course is the header and footer.
So going to add a directory for each.
So I'm going to say Hetter just like this header.
And then we will get a footer.
So I'm going to say footer.
OK.
So inside of the header We just have one file.
We could have many files.
It's completely up to you indexed.
Yes.
Now the header right now is going to do something really really simple but it's going to be a class
based component later.
You can extend this so react class based components.
This one is going to be called Hetter so Hetter open and close and hetter open it close.
Now for now we are just going to return some you know some template.
So we're going to say we're going to wrap everything into the head or tack just like this and we copy
and make it right.
All right.
So we're going to add a class name to the main header.
So class name and it's going to be b c k.
You know for the background B and then light all right then we're going to have a div with the class
name of container and this is a main class and then if you check the original define one we have all
kind of a left and right.
So we're going to create a div for left and a div for the right.
Very simple stuff.
So class name is would be much easier for me to use bootstrap But again just using a long line of class
names I don't like this.
Right now it's a lot of typing.
It's better but a lot of typing.
So instead of here instead of the left we will have a logo which is the name of the Web site.
And for this one will have Wake's.
Now on the right side going to say class name and I'm going to say right Hoopes right and the right
side we will get the top links and the bottom links.
So this one will have a class name of top just like this.
And the other one will have a class name.
Bottom right make sense just the opposite of this.
So bottom and I'm going to put you know something like links links and links.
We're going to do this later why we're going to see why later.
Don't worry.
So we sort of we have kind of a header so we need to import inside the layout.
Right.
So import import import header from DOD forward slash come down for Slash components for Slash head
or footer for Slash than hetero's we have an index that's it.
So I'm going to make a reference to the letter and that is it.
All right.
So let's go to our obligation and we get it ugly but we get it so we get Hetter and everything else.
So let's do the footer right now.
We're going to go here and inside of the footer.
I'm going to create a new X that ass.
And of course the footer could be a classmate's component.
But I'm going to make it up re-act stateless component Oh sorry stateless.
All right.
So this one is going to be footer.
And I know that this footer looks simple right here but we need to do a lot of stuff because we use
icons.
So before we do that I'm going to bring the icons if you remember whenever we installed everything we've
installed.
Fonte awesome right.
So I got to go right here and I'm going to start importing.
Awesome so I'm going to say import then font just like this.
Awesome and that icon and from opening close we need to use the at font.
Awesome re-act font.
Awesome.
Actually this is my mistake it's re-act phantasm.
Very good.
Now I'm going to close it and I'm going to go at the bottom.
So we need four different icons.
We need the this one this one and this one and this one right.
So if you want to use it we need to import it.
So the name of this it's f a.
And I'm going to bring the Compaq's.
So that is for the location.
So from opening close and we need to import it from and to band that it's not Imedi out to complete
them.
See if I can get it right.
Not really because it's a pretty long string.
So let me see if I can find it.
If not begin any to type it.
So it's going to be fun.
Awesome.
And yeah I got it.
Font awesome awesome and freeze solid.
We are using the free package of phantasm.
So if you want to use a professional.
Of course you need to pay that.
Everything is free.
So we have the face of a compass.
I get a copy of this because I don't want to type it again.
And the next one is going to be the phone.
So it's F A and then phone just like this.
Same thing here.
Get a copy of this one pasted the next one is Clark.
So Clark I know this is boring but we're almost not going to copy this one.
And the next one is going to be envelope.
So envelope
All right below target we are done.
Now I'm going to go right here the bottom and we need to start creating this.
So everything is going to be wrapped inside of the footer just like this food or so inside of food.
We will add a class could skip the class.
But the thing is that the filter has a kind of a background so b c k underscore B underscore dark.
All right.
Now we need to wrap the inside inside of a container so class name and then we have container.
All right then in the we have a logo.
If you check the origin one of the top we have the waves and then the line.
So we need to create a new def and inside of the def we're going to say waves.
And the class name of course it's logo.
Real simple.
So after this we have a wrapper.
So Def open it close and a class name of wrapper.
All right.
So I'm going to go right here and we have two different places.
We have the left side and the right side of the wrapper.
OK.
So inside of the wrapper I will add a div with a class name just then with a class name of left because
we have two sides and and the other side I made a mistake and actually named it equally and same because
it's actually using the same property so I didn't change it.
So in real life again you should do a different thing.
Don't take the.
This s.c.s CSSA as a reference.
So in the left in the new Dewani on the left not the class you know the box in the left will have the
contact information.
So I'm just going to go create an H2 and say contact information.
Now each side will have some tax.
So the wrapper for this one its class name and then business info this this and that info it was taken
there.
But that's fine that it's the actual name of the class.
Now out of here we will have tax.
So I'm going to create a class name with attack and later we're going to be copying and pasting to create
the rest.
So we don't need to type all the way.
So right here we need to add the font awesome icon so font.
Awesome.
I can open and close.
So this one takes the icon as a reference which I can we want to display and since we are importing
here at the top we can say I can and that's it.
We're going to adding an additional class name of icon.
And then after the icon we create a new div with a class name of.
Now inside we do have we need to put the values address working hours phone and email.
Now later this information will come from the server.
Of course we didn't create a place where we can store that that we begin to do it.
At the end because it's not that important right now.
OK.
So Dave drew Yes and then we put the address so you address.
I don't know.
Kramer.
One two three four or whatever.
Doesn't matter.
OK.
So if I save this and I go we get nothing of course because we need to include it.
So I go to lay out import then footer from the dot for Slash components for Slash header footer and
then we just bring footer.
All right.
Of course we need to make a reference to this
there we go.
And we get a footer and we get the they the tag.
So let's do the other tasks real real fast.
So we're going to go creek.
Copy the tack go at the bottom paste attack.
And this one instead of compass.
Is going to be fun with a capital P just like this.
And of course the name it's different.
We get phone
phone and I don't know whatever doesn't matter.
The very simple phone then we have a new tag.
And the next time the next task is going to be the clock this one and they copy the name put clock and
this one will be equal to working hours so working hours and again right here you can put whatever you
want to put.
Monday and Sunday till 9 until 8 p.m. you know business hours and the next one is going to be the envelope
which is the e-mail address.
So I'm going to go right here and select a envelope and this one is going to be e-mail.
You're almost done on more than I know.
I know this hurts but we need to finish and info and then wave stuff com doesn't matter.
We might change this later.
So if I save it and check it we get pretty much everything that is good now in the right we can get.
We're going to get something different.
Be the first to know.
So I'm going to go right here inside of the on the left and I'm going to say to be the first to know.
And then we get a dev with some div inside could be a paragraph or something like that like that doesn't
matter.
I'm going to copy right here.
TEXT I have to find one you can type whatever you want doesn't matter.
All right.
Let's check our project.
Very good.
So everything works.
We have had header and footer and then we have a home component that will be doing that on the next
section.
Now all of this later we're going to fetch this from the server and right here and I'm going to add
this one as a bonus we can begin to create a place where we can at the user e-mail that Nippert and
the user can enter the email and we will be adding ourselves to the e-mailing list to the mail list.
Right.
OK.
So far so good.
I'm going to sip the code until this point.
And you can download and you can start working with this particular code if you wish.
OK so let's go to the next one.