Write so under section we will bring redux into our project.
OK.
So first I'm going to go to source story and I'm going to create an actions folder and then of course
we need the reducers.
So I'm going to create reducers.
Now what you could do if you wish.
It's completely up to you.
You can create a different directory called undernote store or redox or something like that and put
the actions in the reducers in there.
And of course you will need to change the routing.
You can use this in you know in your own fashion.
OK.
So I'm going to leave the directories empty and I'm going to go to index where we need to do all the
set up for redux.
So first we need to import a lot of things.
So I'm going to go right here below route and I'm going to say import and the first import that we need
it's the provider.
So space provider now after that provider I'm going to say from and it's from re-act redux.
So the provider something that actually connects with redux so we can use it because really redux is
a third party library.
So then of course we need to import some things from redux.
So I'm going to say from and then redux.
So what we need to import to use it is to create store create store.
Now we're going to use something more because we will use middleware in our project we cannot actually
really work without middleware.
So we need to use the Apply middleware.
All right.
And if you notice I've updated the portion of the code.
So now it's not great.
It's kind of you know darker color.
That's good.
You know it's a it's nicer.
OK.
So if I go to the package that Jasen of the reactor project you can see that we've installed redux promise
and redux tunc.
So they are of course different but they pretty much do the same thing right.
We will use promis redux promise and we will not use redux thunk but maybe I'm going to use it much
much later.
But of course I'm going to set this up first.
Now first we need to import them so import import and then it's promise and then middleware just like
that promise middleware and it's from redux promise.
There we go.
Then when Ruddock's thunk so import and then redux and then thunk and it's from redux thunk redux nunc
Vergon.
OK so now of course we need to import the reducers so we can use them right here whenever we create
the store and we're going to import it of course we don't have a file for that.
You read the reducers just yet.
But I'm going to create it in a couple minutes.
So I'm just going to do the import.
The application will crash because you know we didn't have file for that doesn't exist.
That's OK.
So I going to bring the index of reducers.
All right.
Now before we can we start setting up everything right here with the provider and everything else you
need to know that I'm going to be using the redux dev tools extension.
So go to the chrome and just type this and you're going to get it from this developer and right here
at the bottom.
This is what we're going to be using.
If I go to the final project and go right here at the top I'm going to get depth tools for redux so
we can see what's happening on that with the state actions and everything else.
So that's really cool.
So you will need to install it for Chrome.
You have it for Firefox and will excel lecturn.
But again you will need to use Chrome or find Firefox and right here you can use it to inside of other
browsers.
Is I'm using Chrome.
You will need to go to the Chrome Web store and install the extension.
That's the first thing.
Then of course we need to do some setup right here.
You know I know our project to use it right here you have the instructions but don't worry I'm going
to do it right here.
OK.
So I'm going to save it and I'm going to say Konst.
And what I need to do I need to create a store with middleware so create store with middleware.
Now this is exactly our function.
Our Barville so you can put whatever name you wish right here.
So what we need to do we need to apply middleware and open and close and right here we need to pass
what are we going to be using for middleware.
And we have this promise middleware that's one thing.
And we have the redux thung so I'm going to put redux thung and at the end we do remind with the create
store.
That's why we were going to do this.
We do this all right.
So now we have this apply we have to create store and we are applying the middleware to the store.
All right.
So the next thing is going to be using the provider we are using right here we have bring in right here
we need to wrap our application inside of the provider.
So okay I'm going to say provider open and close and I'm going to put the rest of the code inside of
here.
Okay.
So now this provider needs a store.
So I'm going to say store and this one it's going to be equal to the create store with middleware.
So I'm going to put right here now this create the store with middleware meets the reducers in order
to work.
So going to open and close and I'm going to say Okay use that reduce or file.
Now if we want to use the tools extension we need to put a coma and pass a second a second argument.
So if I say window nothing happens I don't get an hour to complete.
So if you don't want to type this because we need to do a lot of typing and you want to avoid mistakes
you can go right here to the documentation and we can copy that's just this line Vesak store windows
redux we tool extension and percent window extension.
And then just like that.
All right.
So we're going to copy that and then go back to the reducers going to put Coomber and then I'm going
to paste it.
All right.
I didn't copy it is TWIGGER all right of course it's a little bit where some going to do the word wrap.
And just like that we get them we do a search and then the windows dev tools extension and that is it
for now.
I'm going to save it.
And of course our application not going to really work because we didn't have a valid reducer so we
can go to reducers.
And again add an index that yes.
OK.
So instead of the index Nagios of the way we do.
First we need to combined all the available reducers.
We don't have one but going to create one right now.
So first we need to import this combine and then reducers from.
And this one comes from Braddock's OK.
Now we don't have a valid reducer.
We don't have it.
We're going to create it.
So we're going to be using users at the beginning so I'm going to create user.
And then from opening close dot for Slash user underscore reducer.
OK.
Now we need to create a marvel called route reduce her route reduce or with a capital R and then this
one is going to be equal to the combined reducers we're using at the top and it's a it's a method and
we pass an object.
Now what are going to be using We're going to be use inside of the reducer all the available reducers.
Right now we just have one so I'm going to say user I'm going to close it.
Now of course since we are including this file inside of the index yes we need to export it.
So export default and then route reduce or.
Right.
Pretty basic stuff for Rydex.
Now again we didn't have this file.
I'm going to create it right now so inside reducers could it create a new file and it's going to be
user underscore reducer.
OK.
Now inside of the user reducer what we need to do we will need to return a function that returns a switch
or you know it has a switch inside but returns the state.
So export then default default and we need to return a function.
Now this function of course needs two arguments.
First the state with an empty object and then begin to receive an action always in action.
So we passed the action.
Now instead of here I'm going to say switch open and close and begin to be checking for the action that
type.
This is pretty basic Rydex configuration is the main set up we need to do for regex.
And of course if we are not finding that type we need to return default with the return state and the
state is going to be equal to whatever state.
OK.
So now if we go to our project everything works and we are not getting any errors and warnings.
So we are actually good to go now before we move on to the next section.
I'm going to go to actions and I am going to create Now I'm going to create a new file.
And for example we are saying that we're going to use user so I'm going to create a file with user actions.
We're not going to do anything just yet.
We're going to do it later.
You're just setting redux right now.
And we're going to use axioms to make the requests.
So import Scio's from expose axioms.
Now if you remember whenever we were going to make all the requests and all the actions and everything
else.
So we need to bring the or else now on the server if we go to the server we have different types of
or else API product for product related routes.
And then we have we have we get API end users everything that's related to users so we can have different
action and different actions right here.
User Action product actions.
I don't know side actions so we might have different actions.
And in real life you're going to get a lot of files right here.
This one will get Widick.
So and most of the times are going to be making requests to the products you're out if you're working
with products to the user or you're out of your work and your users and everything else.
So what if the Eurail changes you're going to need to go through all your functions and change to your
manually.
So what you can do you can create a viral right here or we can click create a Google Barville with all
the locations.
And that's what I'm going to do.
I'm going to go to resources.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to go to right here.
Components.
I believe we didn't have it just yet.
No we didn't.
Yeah I believe we do.
Now we don't want to agree to you till fall or so we don't have you Tilse So we'll get a lot of details.
So inside details I'm going to create a new file called misc.
You know our misc file.
This one will have you know just global general data.
So I'm going to say server then routes just like that.
And I'm going to go and export Konst and I say a user server for all the server and could be use or
routes or user requests but I'm using server because you know it so that server routes so API for is
for a slash and then users.
I believe that that is correct.
So API end users.
All right then we have the export then Konst and we have product server later are we going to be adding
more but for now this is OK.
So we have the API for Slash and we have product.
All right.
So now from within user actions are going to include this file because you know we are going to use
this virals so import and from this one that is the user are going to say user server and its from opening
close for Slash components for Slash Eutelsat details and then Misc and thats it.
Of course later were going to be using this and we might be adding product server and doing something
else.
But for now all the set up its pretty much complete now.
We are going to use types on this one.
So going to create a type's file just like this.
And I to leave it empty.
Of course we are going to be adding types.
Right now we are not going to do it because we are not going to use redux right.
Right now we can do something else but redux its already ready to go.
If you don't know how to work with types when we reach a section where we need to make a request and
use the redux logic I can explain you explain your why we use types.