OK so now we're going to do the log in.
I was going to do the sections you know the featured and right this right here.
Just like the discounted promotion.
But you know the log in log out it's a little bit more fun and useful for us right now because after
we log in and we get no we can know if the user is authenticated or not and show some other routes and
you know we can do the routes right here.
So we're going to do this.
We're going to go to log in registered log in every district customer.
If not we can go to a different component where we can you know register with the best personal information
account information and everything everything else.
So OK so first we're going to go and create the register log in route.
All right.
I'm going to close everything here.
I don't need it.
I'm going to go to the index and of course we need to create a component that is going to be ruling
all of this.
And of course since this is the first section we do forms we will need to do all the form fields and
everything else so it's going to take a few a few lectures.
Right.
So inside component are going to create a new folder register.
Let me make it right.
With a capital R register and then log in because we will host both things right here.
Now we will have an index where we can do the actual log in.
So index that.
Yes.
And then of course we will create a couple more files.
So the index yes it's going to be class based component.
Right.
Makes sense.
Could we react to the last component because we didn't have a lot of logic right here.
So I'm going to do it just like this.
On the other example in the final example I have it is class but we could use a stateless component.
So I going to call this component register log in just like this.
Or just log in and we can export it.
And of course we're going to save register log in or something like that whenever So we need to bring
this route to routes.
We need to imported there so I'm going to go two routes and we need to import it so import import and
register and then log in opening close.
It's going to be from components then just log in and that's it.
Right from.
OK.
So let's see the routing going it company the one we have so far I'm going to paste it here.
And then when we have the ability to authenticate users this is going to change a little bit and it's
going to be different than the previous project.
Can to do it on a different way.
So the route for this calls register log in.
All right so I'm going to pait paste.
We're just logged in.
We will use the component register log in.
All right.
Now if I go to this route on our project let me go here we get wrister So that is good.
So I'm going to go to our component and we need to start doing all of this.
All right.
So first I'm going to rub everything into a div.
I'm going to call it class name of page and then wrapper.
And this is going to center everything.
And then of course we get a container class name of container.
Actually the page from something else doesn't matter.
Container.
OK.
So instead of here we get two different things.
Right.
We have the left side.
If we go to the final with new customers and the right side we did register customers.
OK.
So first are going to create a container for this a different kind of container.
So I'm going to call it class name and then register underscore Lagann underscore container.
Doesn't matter right now just C Ss OK.
So I'm going to create a div opening close and a class name off left just like this.
And of course we have the the left logic right here and I'm going to add the right one right now.
So this one is going to be right.
OK.
So this one will be h one opening close and new customers.
All right.
So again we will have some tests.
I have some large ipsum right here which is going to copy and paste.
I got to put everything inside of a paragraph just like this.
Let me do the word wrap.
Let me paste.
There we go.
So now after the text if you go to the find one we have a button and we have the same button right here.
And then at home same button.
Then pretty much we have all the running balance but we will use the same button several times.
So it kind of makes sense for us to create a reusable component.
Right.
OK.
So I'm going to store this inside Eutelsat and I'm going to call it button.
So I mean a new file called.
But in that.
Yes.
OK.
Of course this button that just is going to be just a function right.
Just a stateless component just a function.
All right.
So going to save it and I'm going to import it import them and I believe I'm going to call it my Bunin
that my band.
Or could be my buttons.
But we are going to you know it's just my button Singler because whenever we request we conclude this
component it will bring just one button so I'm going to say one that you tels for Slash and then button
could be buttons but that's OK.
OK.
So what else.
OK we need to create this.
So what I wanted to do I want to create a component and pass some props we might have different points
for example.
This could was one could be a link or maybe it could be just a button with data link or you could be
a button that it's going to trigger you know maybe maybe a function is going to happen with this one.
This one will actually not link when we triggered this.
We're going to go to the database and that this to the card of the user.
So we have different kind of buttons.
For now we're just going to say my button just like this opening close and going to just include this.
We didn't have we didn't have any logic right here but we can add it in a minute.
So I need to know how to paddle the boat in what type of button we're going to use.
So by default we can have one which is the link you know the most used button so I'm going to say type
default and inside button we will create different scenarios as we move forward through the actual project.
Now of course the button needs to say something.
So I'm going to add a prop title and this one will be create an account.
Right now since this is a default it's a link we will need to link and then.
And it's equal to forward slash and register.
All right.
We don't have this round we will create it in a few minutes.
Now sometimes we will need to change the stylings of the Bunim for example right now.
We will they all the balance will have the same styling but maybe in the future we want to add a button
that no.
Same thing but with a different background.
So we can include the styles property we did before the styles property and begin to pass them see SS
and of course this will override the default ones.
So Martin actually will be merged with the fold once so I'm going to say 10 pixels from the top zero
0 and 0 that's OK for now.
All right something very simple.
Now of course we need to create all the logic inside the button.
So I'm going to go to button and create out re-act stateless stateless component.
So this one is going to be my button just like this and change the name at the bar on the bottom.
Now this one.
It will return at the very very end.
It's just a button with a class name my link I use this.
This class could be whatever class because it's actually could be my but it makes more sense.
But I've used my linked.
Then you should change it.
But it did.
So this one is going to call function is going to go to a function inside of my button and this function
will decide what kind of a button we want to return.
Right.
If it's a link or if something else the default it's a link.
That's why you test my link.
Then I was when I when I was making this and you know I was advancing through the sections I decided
to use a component for all the buttons and forgot to change the name of the class.
Right.
That's why we have my leg.
All right.
So now we need to create this function called balance.
So this function the only thing it's going to do is going to check the type of the button we are specifying
right here.
And depending on the type we're going to return some GSX and this is what it's going to get return are
at.
So going to create a lot a template to begin this template starts empty.
And of course at the end of the function we will return that template.
Now in the middle of what you will need to do is we need to check the type and if you have a default
we will put that kind of code we want to return.
So we did this previously actually on a different practice course talk at Switch we get it checked the
props and the type Actually there are props.
Not this the all complete went wrong there.
OK.
So switch and we always need a default case so if we have a default that actually we didn't get up and
we are not getting a type or type it's not being recognized by default.
We're going to still say that the template it's equal to nothing.
Or it could be no.
OK.
So if the case is that we get a default type Then we going to return something.
All right.
So I can open it close.
And in this case actually with this no need to do this.
But that's OK.
I'm going to do this.
And we need to do break.
All right.
So if the case is default I'm going to return that template.
But with some code code inside what are we going to be using.
It's a link.
So I'm going to open and close a link.
All right.
Now we didn't have a link right here.
We need to import it at the top.
So import opening close and we can import link for arm and then re-act router.
All right.
Now of course this link needs some configurations so I'm going to go right here.
And first I'm going to be passing the title if you remember we have it inside props.
And then title I'm going to add a class name so class name.
Open it close and the class for this one it's link default.
All right then we have the two property and this is a native property of link.
So we need to pass the link and we have it inside prop's that link in that to our link to and then of
course since we have other we are.
We need to overwrite some stylings that we might be attaching with the class name.
We can add the prompts dot at styles.
And this is this is the one that we are passing right here.
Right.
OK.
So in theory this actually should work.
So let's go right here and prop's is not defined it's because I'm not passing prompts of course prompts.
All right.
So that's good.
We get the title the text and we get one.
If I go here we go to register.
So that works.
Now this but it is very simple.
We will get different kinds of buttons inside of here just like here we get this button and we have
the ad right here.
This one will trigger function is not a link.
So we're going to do several things.
This file is going to get bigger.
But for now you know this one it's OK.
OK.
So let's go back to the register log in the next part is going to be this one which is the right where
we have the log in code.
So I'm going to go and say age 2.
I'm using it to tack.
So register at customers
now inside of the text I'm going to say if you if you have an account please log in for a stand.
And right here we will have the log in you know for pretty much.
So if I save it and go back we get it now we're going to be adding the log in form and we're going to
go to the next section because all the logic of logging in and logging out we are not going to do it
right here.
We're going to do it on a different component which is going to be a class because we need to do a lot
of things we need to go to the server or come back and you know we need to do all the form logic.
So let's go to the next section and start with the log in component.