OK so let's read the log in component.
So I'm going to create a new file called log in that J.S. of course log in that yes and of course this
one could be.
It's going to be a re-act classic class based component.
And I'm going to call it luggin makes sense right now.
We need to import a lot of things.
But first we need to create a lot of things.
So the only thing getting port right here because we're going to use it later it's disconnect because
after we look again you know we are trying to log in we need to go to the server and check if the user
has the correct passport and e-mail and everything else.
So we're going to use redux.
All right.
So whenever we use a connect we need to go right here on the bottom and say we want to connect it and
then we're going to open it close and pass the name of the components.
All right.
That is great.
So now I'm going to go right here Rick in the middle and say class name equals to sign in just like
this and then wrapper.
And then of course I'm going to bring a form.
So I'm going to say for open and close remember that when we do submit we have we have an answer.
Handler.
Now on the previous projects we did this on a different way.
Now they all submit all the functions and all the checking right here.
Well actually doing this on the actual components.
Now you're going to do a different thing.
We're going to use reusable components we're going to outsource all the checking of all the forms inside
the project.
So this selfmade form we don't have this function of course and we will be passing an event.
Right.
So you get a copy of event and paste it right here.
When you have a function I'm just going to say submit form equals to a function and not return nothing
for now.
OK.
So if you remember we have form fields and we use a reusable components for this.
But for this we need to have a state first with all the forms we need to all the form fields we need.
And as in this case we will have to the email and the passport.
So I'm going to go right here and create a state opening clause.
We can do this on the priest project so this should be easy right now.
So we have a form error.
If we get an error at the end of course is going to start is false.
All right.
Then we have a form success form success just like there is success and it's going to be equal right
now to nothing because at the beginning it's empty.
If you get a success you can show a message right here.
Now then we have the form data.
So inside of the form data we have all the elements.
So I'm going to go nuclear create an email and then we have a passport.
We're going to do it later.
So for this one we need to tell the elements.
So I'm going to say that the element of this is going to be an input.
All right.
They're going to do koma are going to select the value and the value of this is going to start ads nothing
that we need to pass some confect to this.
Just like that before and each input has a you know some options some attributes like the name and the
name is going to be in this case email input.
You know just a regular.
The other one is going to be type and the type of this its e-mail you know because an email input and
then going to add a placeholder place holder open and close.
And you know enter your email.
Now of course will have some validation so we need to add some validation rules.
So open it close and we're going to say that this one it's required and it's true.
All right.
And then one then we can add a new rule which is e-mail true we need to validate that the user is entering
a valid e-mail.
All right.
We are almost done.
So we need to tell.
We need to know if the element is valid at the end.
So it's going to start false as soon as we start we start entering information the validation will kick
in and a little changed of ballad to true of course.
Now we need to add the touched so we can now we can skip that validation right away.
And at the end we're going to add a validation and then message.
All right.
So it's going to start.
It's nothing because we don't get any errors.
If you get an error we're going to store it right here.
All right.
So I got a copy this one.
We're going to put a comma and paste it right here.
So now we need to do the passport.
So this one is going to be password the type of input.
But instead of e-mail I'm going to copy a keyboard.
It's going to be passport and passport and passport but it isn't required.
It's not an e-mail just required.
And that's it.
That's it for the state.
So now what we need to do we need to create a usable component that is going to take the form data and
it's going to show the e-mail if we are passing an e-mail and the passport for passing a passport.
Right.
All right.
So first just like we did before.
I'm going to go the bottom and start we can put in we don't have this component.
Are we're going to do it now so we can know what we need to be passing to that components.
So we're going to call it foreign field form field just like we did before opening close.
And this forum feel we need to pass the I.D. of you know what we want to add in this case on this one
we're going to just add e-mail.
We need to pass the form data so we can to say form data equals opening close this that state that form
data.
And you know the actual input in this case we are passing all the data of the e-mail and then whenever
this is change of course we need to run a function.
So I'm going to open and close and we're going to be passing the element and we're going to run a function
to update the the form so update and then form.
And of course things from this form field we will receive an element we need to pass the element to
update form.
All right.
So we don't have this function going to go right here at the top and create an empty function so we
can skip that error message.
All right.
So now we need to create the form field component.
So of course we're going to do this in details and we are going to have to have a lot of things for
forms.
So I will store this inside of a directory and inside of forms of course we will add the form field.
So could open and close.
Am I going to call it form field dodginess.
All right now I'm going to go back again and I'm going to include this right here sample.
So import form of capital F field from that dot for Slash utils for Slash form for Slash form field.
All right.
So I got to go back to I'm going to go to Fairfield's and we need to add all the logic right here at
the top.
So this one is going to be a re-act stateless component.
It's just a function.
And I'm going to change the capital F to form field.
All right.
So from the from the actual components from this one at the bottom we will receive three different things.
So I'm going to make use of the structuring and I get to say that I want to get the form data form data
coma.
I want to get that change.
Now I want to get the idea.
All right.
Form data change in ID.
Very good.
So can it go right here at the bottom.
And now whenever we return something we need to do some logic first since we need to figure out what
are going to be returning.
So we're going to say render template just like we did before.
All right.
So this render template is going to be just a function.
So I'm going to go right here at the top and say Konst and render a template There you go it's going
to be just a function opening close.
So first just like we did with the button we need to decide what are we going to be returning.
In that case we have an input.
You know we have this an input.
We're going to return an input.
We have a text area or maybe a different select for example but we just have input so for now we're
going to create one single case and when we get a select for example on the admin side of things we
will create that inside form field.
But for now we just have one.
So let's form a template.
It's going to start empty.
Or you can put.
No no we did empty with a button where you can return no.
It's completely up to you.
And at the end we will return return this form template.
All right.
So in the middle just like you're looking for you're going to do a switch.
So inside the switch we need to check what we're going to be using for you know checking.
And it's inside for data form data on each element.
And in this case inside elements right.
So impot So we're going to do that.
So we're going to grab that form data and we're going to check the elements on it.
Of course if you have a default as an area we always need to do default opening close and we return
the form template with again.
So we just set it back to nil.
Now if the case is that we do have something in this case we will be putting input.
Say what we need right now.
So if the case we have an input.
Of course never forget forget to do the break.
If the case that we have an input begin to say OK well if we have an input.
Now the form template it's going to be different.
It's going to be different to something else.
Now what are we going to do.
We're going to be returning some GSX.
So I'm going to open it close right then because we need to do some ternary operations right here.
So we need to use this and not just just a component or maybe a dip.
All right.
So what we will be returning is going to be a dip in the distance.
Has a class name off form and then block it.
Now of course we will be returning and impot in this case.
And he said of the input we need to put all the configurations inside log in we have the config with
the name type in place holder.
So right at the beginning of that that that formed data just like this data dart and config.
And we will you know by default do all of this attach all the properties from data that confect our
what else we need to add value and let me do this.
All right.
So now we need a value.
If you remember inside the form data we do have a value and it's inside form data diet value.
I know maybe you went you did this on the first project and on the second project.
So I'm kind of repeating myself because maybe you didn't do the first one or the second one.
You were interested in the.
And there's one.
So you know I'm just going it's not that slow but you know explaining what I'm doing.
So we have a tumbler and an on change you know whenever we change we will update right here.
Let me go.
We will update the form but we also have a number.
And with the blurb going to do a couple things so well first we're going to be passing the event of
on Blar And then of course we're going to trigger this change because whenever we do on blur we actually
change the form and we're going to be passing the an object.
So with that object we pass the event so we can catch de-value then we're going to be passing the ID
and at the end we're going to be passing on a blur.
And I'm going to say true all right now I'm going to do onchange
open close and now of course this one makes no sense.
We will get there don't worry because we need to do it in context.
Now on this one we will be passing the event and pretty much do the same thing.
So I'm going to copy now just to save some time.
I'm going to delete the blogger.
We don't need it right here.
So every time we are doing change all we do on blur we will fire this function that will update the
state of the form data and we will see the changes reflected right here.
In the case of on Bloor which is which means that we click on the on the form and we go out we will
need to check if the if the input it's empty or not.
That's why we are passing on a blur.
We can check if this event it's a type of change and blur and begin to you know show the validation
message saying did you need to enter something here.
That that's pretty much it.
Now of course if I save this and I go to our component nothing is going to happen because we didn't
include this.
All right.
So I'm going to go to the register and include the log in.
So import Lochend from DOT for Slash and Lagann and right here are going to make a reference to log
in.
All right.
Open it close.
So let's see what we get.
OK.
We get another e-mail.
Of course if I type something nothing's going to happen I'm typing.
Nothing is going to happen because we need to do something to that update form.
All right.
So OK.
So what we need to do.
Let's first do the update form and then add the errors and everything else.
The section went too long.
Yeah it went a little too long.
So let's go to the next one and do the update form and we still need to do something else right here
because if you have an error message maybe validation message we need to display it.
So we need to complete this.