So now we need to create this update form function.
Right.
And now is going to slow a little bit because we're going to do it on a different way.
It's pretty much the same idea but we can host everything on a different file.
So I'm going to go to you Telles form and I will create a new file called form actions that Jack's right
here we're going to include all the logic.
So now whenever we do this this update form and I need you to remember this we are passing this bar
this argument the element and this element contains the event on the of the change or the on blur and
contains an ID and contains a blur right.
In the case of Blart which is true by default and the ID is going to be you know what is the name of
the form field.
In this case e-mail.
All right.
So whenever we go to update form I'm going to go right here.
We're going to be doing is just call to a function call to an outside function so we can validate all
of this.
So I'm going to say Konst new form data data when we do it like this data.
And this one is going to be equal to a function.
I'm going to call it update.
You can call this whatever you want.
Not update form just update just like this.
The hour to complete is just breaking my balls.
Sorry for that update.
OK.
So this update is going to be just a function and this function will receive three different arguments
element which is the actual element we get from the from here element.
So we're going to pass it.
We going to pass it.
And now what do we need to do we need to send the copy of the state of thinks of the state of form data.
So the second argument is going to be this that state that form data and as the third argument just
in case because we might need it in the future going to be passing what is a type of forum that you
know it's performing this action.
This is triggering the update.
And in this case it's going to be log in because we are on the log in component.
All right.
Now we don't have this function so we need to create it and we're going to go to form actions and start
creating all the logic for us.
So we're going to go right here at the bottom and say Konst and we need to create a viable that's you
know and we need to export actually export Konst.
And it's called update.
So this update is just a function and it's going to be receiving.
If you remember the element just like this coma a form data form data coma and the form name which is
the idea that we are not going to really use right now.
So first what we need to do we need to grab this form data and mutate it.
Now what I want to do I want to create a new form data just like we did previously because I don't want
to change the original that we are getting from the prompts we could do it but I don't really want to.
So dot dot dot and we say that this one is going to be equal to form data.
So now we can mutate form data a form date whatever we will as much as we want.
And we are not going to be mutating the original argument.
All right.
So now what we need to do.
I'm going to create a contest and then new elements of this new element is going to be whatever you
know to be equal to whatever field we have inside this form data.
When we make it right form data but it's going to be equal to the key of whatever we are getting remember
that this element has the ID.
And in this case it's going to be email.
So I'm going to say OK.
Inside the new element.
I just want to store the ID data so I can access the new form data you know the copy we have.
I'm going to say I want to put inside whatever I have to get inside the element and ID.
So this one is going to be check the email data.
We have D.M. state we have inside for data.
And of course if you have password you're using passwords there's going to be you it's going to be the
passport on the next component that begin to do here.
And I'm going to do it right now.
Why not.
So form field and remember that this one is password and this one is passport and that is it.
So OK.
But we're going to take the e-mail for example as a reference right now.
Now since we have a copy of the new elements we can mutate the element as much as we want.
So I'm going to go to new elements.
I'm going to enter the value and remember that inside of the element we have the event that we get back
from foreign fields and right here from the onchange and employer.
So I'm going to say OK now the value change that changed.
So I'm going to say elements I can access the event that target and this is you know just just javascript
the element at Target and the value.
So now new element has the new value of thanks.
All right.
Now of course we need to do a few more things we need to check if the information is valid.
So we need to add some validation right now remember that we use that PLR right here.
And this one is going to change you know if it's PLUR.
So if the element was was selected.
You know we went inside of the.
Let me show it right here.
When we went inside and then outside then the blur changed everything to true.
So now this property right here this e-mail for example will have a blur of true ride.
This one right here.
So later we can check if the element had a blur or of true or not.
So if the element has a blur of true it means that the user clicked on it and went outside or clicked
enter some information and then went outside.
Since now it's going to be true because the user did that.
We need to start validating and not before that.
So I'm going to say opening close.
So if the user of course did the blur element dot blur we can do symbolization later of course we will
change the state of things because right here remember that we have touched so touched it's kind of
like the blur.
There's one is false but at the end of this form actions is going to be true.
All right.
So now we need to create something so we can validate.
So I'm going to say let valid data that there's valid data is going to be equal to a different function
called validate.
So we don't I don't know what it's doing this is just I need to delete a lot of plugins.
Valley date.
All right.
So this validate is going to be just a function that we're going to be creating in a couple of minutes
so export cans.
Yeah.
Sorry mental breakdown and then validate and you know just going to be a function.
All right.
So this validate is going to do a few things.
And it needs something from here so we can start checking because you need to enter the state of the
actual field and check what are the rules that it needs to validate.
All right.
So what are we going to be passing.
Is it new elements which contains all this rules and then coma and it going to be passing the form data
later you're going to see why right now we're not going to really use it.
Of course this function is going to fail because you have nothing.
Now this bad data is going to be returning an array.
Right.
Let's do the validate first because not just going to tell you something that doesn't exist.
So it's kind of hard to understand.
All right.
So let's go to the Vulg. and do it right now.
So this validate will be receiving an element which is the new element and it's going to be receiving
a form data.
Now if we don't have form data the form data by default is going to be empty.
So form data data equals an empty array.
All right.
Now if you remember at the end we will read we will return an array and this array will have two things.
If it's Mallat which is a boolean true or false.
And the second position of the array is going to be the actual error message.
So let error and this is going to start as true.
In this case and the second error in the second value is going to be that the actual error message.
So by default the input is going to be valid because we have true and no error messages.
All right let's go right here and I'm going to do the required because it's the easiest one.
After that after we do we have the required.
Everything else is going to be really easy.
So what we return at the end this function is going to return an array with this or with something else.
All right.
So what we need to do first we need to check if we have a required validation inside the actual element.
We go back.
We can see that we enter validation and we have a required.
So if we do have inside of the elements that are validation just like this validation that and it's
called.
And we have one that that is if required then we're going to do something.
So we create Konst valid and viable cons.
And this one is going to be equal to the value of the elements and we will check if the you know if
we do have something.
So first I'm going to say OK this one is going to be true or false only if the element that value exists.
Now I'm going to say that I'm going to trim it to remove the white spaces and if it's different than
nothing.
So right here we are trimming the value of the actual element and we are checking if it's empty or not.
So if it's if it's not empty it's going to be true.
And if it's empty it's going to be false and it's valid it's going to be equally false.
And is it.
And when we return the error we will check it right here and we will return or not.
All right.
Now remember that we have a message.
So I'm going to say message and this message will be just a template strings to string.
So opening close.
Now if it's not valid then we want to return an error message you're going to use a tertiary right here.
If it's not if it's you know false.
We want to return this something something silly.
This field is required.
Let's get.
Of course if we don't have an error message it means that it's valid.
We're going to return nothing.
Pretty simple.
This is just javascript it's just logic.
So I'm going to say error.
And now we want to do we want to return this.
Whether you have false or true or whatever.
So what are we going to be sending right here.
It's not just this of course we're going to do something else.
We're going to say OK if it's not valid which is it which means that we have errors.
When are we going to send an array with the valid which is going to be false.
And the actual message that we get from here are right.
If not we're going to send the default error that we have at the top which is true and nothing.
Now I'm going to go back to log in and I can let know.
Just change remove the email right now so we can get a validation check for required and make sure that
you know everything works.
Now let's go back to the elemental are now this valid data will be returning true or false and a message.
Or maybe no message depending on the back nation of course.
So after we do that we need to start changing things inside of the value right here.
The Valot and validation message and teched because of course we are updating these fields.
The state got.
So after valid data are going to enter new element going to Siddhant I'm going to say valid equals and
remember that this valid data returns in a rate so going to save body data opening close and I want
to know when to get the first banya which is true or false depending if it's valid or not.
Then remember we have a validation message so that and right here we have the validation message.
I'm going to say OK now the validation message.
Going to be equal to whatever we get back from Bali that data and the position number one right there.
The error message and then after this says we get beat we actually touched the element.
We're going to say that the new element that touched just like this.
It's equal to whatever we get from element player.
Which is true right now.
Remember that on the form field we are saying true on this one we are not really saying true so if we
get to this point and we didn't trick a trigger on nobbler this one is going to be false of course.
All right so I'm going to go right here but I'm not going to say OK now the new form data has a new
element.
Remember that we are storing.
We're making all the changes inside a new element so we need to put this new element inside new form
form data.
All right so going to enter your form data.
I'm going to open it close and I'm going to make a reference to the element that Id remember.
We have it the we have the ID right here.
Since we are inside there we need to say OK now all this information changed and it's equal to element
of two new elements.
All right so we have a new state of form data.
So we're not going to do.
I'm going to return that form data because it's a return form data from data.
So this one will contain all the changes it's going to be pretty much a copy of all of this.
But with all the changes w the valley at the touch the validation message.
We have an error message.
All right.
So now on this function on this update form we are getting back this new state of things right.
So what we want to do is just said the state so this that set state when it's going to be a form error.
Begin to turn it to False just in case and then we going to passing the formed data and the form data
is equal to new form data.
So the update States at the state and we will get the I'll get up to date update.
It's not defined it's because I didn't include this at the top.
Very nice.
All right.
Well that's.
So import opening close.
Update for mom and dad that you tell us for Slash form for Slash form actions.
All right let's see if we get everything working.
So if I type something I should be able to see something right here in the works.
Right.
And if I remove everything we go to that on blur.
Of course not.
OK so this works.
Now the thing is that this actually has an error state.
But the problem is that now inform feels we are not catching the error.
We are not showing anything.
Let's do it real quick because it's going to be real simple.
So after the after the input I'm going to say I want to run a function that calls show error.
So this error is going to be just a function that of course is going to be checking the form data.
So OK I'm going to go before the render template Konst show error.
It's going to be just as you call to a simple function.
We are almost done.
All right.
So I'm going to say let error message and this message at the beginning is going to be null.
We are pretty much doing the same thing here.
So it's going to be No.
Now if open and close if the form data that we are getting right here has validation because some inputs
might not have a location then we want to move forward.
Remember that on the log in we have validation.
All right.
So we do have a day on this one.
We're going to move forward.
But I want to check something else and I'm going to say ampersands let me find it.
All right.
Ampersand.
And if the form data just like this it's equal to false inside of the ballot then we want to show it.
So we're going to say that we're going to grab this message and we will be returning some GSX because
we need to put it here.
And this one is going to be equal to a div with an Arab label.
So class name opening close.
Error level and inside.
Remember that we have a validation message that we are attaching from within form within form actions.
So we are going to say that this one it's equal to form data dot validation.
And let me copy to avoid mistakes cubby very good.
It's equal to form data and validation message.
And at the end of course.
Never forget to return the actual error message with no or with the Gas-X.
All right.
Real fast.
So if I type something and go out we get the field is required.
All right.
If I type something it goes away.
If I click go outside this field is required.
All right.
Let me check if the section went long ok.
Not that that long.
So if you remember the e-mail it's actually required.
It's actually we have a rule for this one which is e-mail and then true.
Remember we had this.
So we need to add the validation right here in some form actions and we're going to do it really really
really quick.
Now I'm going to go right here the top this one needs to be the last one.
All right.
I'm going to go.
If I open it close if element it validation it's equal you know just like this.
Then we want to do something now pretty much begin to do the same thing here.
So I got a copy.
I'm going to paste.
Of course this rules are going to be different.
So I'm going to delete this.
I'm going to say OK it's going to be valid and we're going to use some regs.
Now you can go to the Web site I'm sorry the Web site to the web and try to find some rag X to validate
e-mails because you know typing this just here.
It's just silly.
Just go to the web find it if you type Reg X and then email validation.
The first one that you get is going to be good.
All right.
So first we're going to do this reg X and we're going to do test opening closed and what are we going
to be testing.
Is the element that value.
Now if we of course if it's not valid again to say must be a valid email.
All right.
And of course this one will stay the same.
If it's not valid we will return an array if not an error.
All right.
Let's get.
So I'm going to save it and let's see if it works.
If I type nothing and go Tydfil is required if I type something and go away.
Must be a valid email and if I do G-mail that COM it works.
Now remember that on this side of things on the site on the server side inside the models with the users
we are already validating this.
So if we make a mistake a mistake right here this will not go to the server because the server will
check that schema.
The data that matches what we are doing right here that you know that emails type of string and everything
else.
So again if there is something wrong we have a second layer of validation with the with the server.
All right.
OK.
That is that is.
So let's go to the next section and begin to do of course we're going to keep doing this.
We're going to try to finish the form and then of course we will do that request to register to log
in the server the user.