OK so let's finish the log in of course after we enter some data we need to submit the form.
So for this week we need to know some balance right here.
But first we can look at the error state so if with this that state that form error remember that at
the top we have the form or state.
We will be returning DEP and if not we can at return nothing.
Just like with it before.
All right.
No.
OK.
So I'm going to create an open and close.
This will have cost name of error label and text.
Please check your data.
Now most of the message right here in this application at least they're going to be very general.
Of course you can try to catch the error from the server because you get a code back from Mongo Magoo's
so you can you know create a special thing for this of different types of messages.
But it's completely up to you.
So then of course we have a button opening close and on click just like this what we will do we will
fire the same band that we do with the unsufficient same thing.
Now I notice that you're passing any event.
So let's go to this function.
We're going to catch the event just like here.
And of course we need to do event prevent default events oops event that doesn't prevent default.
All right.
Now if you remember we need to catch 22 kind of a convert all this form data all the keys to just a
key value per to e-mail and the actual value right here and everything else.
We actually don't need it.
And the same with password.
So just like with that with new form data we will create a function to do this.
And later when we were working with different forms we just need to do this.
And maybe you if you're coming from the second project hope.
How much easier is this.
How much cleaner is this ride.
I told utility before.
So data to serve meant.
So this barbel will host the data we're going to be submitting.
The end.
So I'm going to create a function called generate and then data kind of makes sense.
We are going to generate the data and we need to pass two things I need to pass that this state that
form data and then coma.
And just like with it right here because we might need it and we actually going to eat at home the next
sections in the next few sections is the name of what we are doing in this case.
We are.
And so we are saying logging it.
So we're going to go right here and console log the data to cement just to make sure you're getting
everything back correctly.
So we don't have this function.
I'm going to put it right here.
Coma generate data and I'm going to go back to form actions and we need to you know create the function.
It's going to be a very simple function.
So export Konst generate data equals to a function.
Now if you remember we are getting the form data coma and the form name right.
Just like with the brain here the top form name.
All right.
So first this data to submit so data to serve met is going to start as an empty object.
And of course we are going to be entering form data.
So we're going to do a four good old for opening close and for let key in form data.
We're going to do something so for every key we have inside form data.
We have a few ones right here we're going to just grab the one we need which is the value right.
OK.
So we say now data to submit.
We passed the key which in this case email or password.
And we're going to say OK just returned for this one for us as a result of this one which is the form
the form data right here.
This form data and then we enter the key.
And then we say that we want to banlieue for this one.
So now at the end the only thing this data out of MIT will host is just a key and a value.
Right.
All right.
And then return data sets of mid.
Very good.
So now what are we going to be doing.
We're going to.
You know got we believe everything is going to work.
So now let's go to log in.
Let's try it again.
And I didn't ask and text forgot to do that.
Let's do it right now so we can pretty much finish with this section.
So each side of the button.
What are we going to say.
Log in or log in or sign in whatever it is that you want to use.
So try again.
Going to type an email.
As a matter of making a request right now and a passport in and going to open the console locks so we
can actually see it.
All right console log in and we get it we get e-mail and we get the passport Vergon everything works.
So now of course this data is going to be the one that is going to we are going to submit.
Now we have one more thing.
We are just going to form the data.
We are entering form data and we are adding this but we are not really checking if the form it's really
valid.
We actually did some validation but maybe the user enter some information did log in and the the validation
actually we have to get the message right here.
For example let me just show you with an example.
So inspect and if I go to cancel and log in again we are still getting value but the values are wrong.
So we need a previous step or maybe actually a new step at to check that the there's is a valid field.
Right.
It's actually correct.
We're good to go but we are not that we are going to post the data into the web to the server.
OK.
So I'm going to go right here and I'm going to create a viable and the Vrable going to say form is valid.
Makes sense.
So if the form is valid we can move forward if not not.
So this one at the end is going to be a true or false.
So if it's true we move forward.
If it's false we don't.
So is form valid
I did whatever form about it.
All right.
So I'm going to be passing the same thing that this that state farm data and that log in.
So at the end of course we need to create dysfunction.
It's form ballot.
So let's go to form actions and I can add it right here.
So export Export Konst is form ballot.
Open and close and it's just a function and the arguments are going to be the same that once.
All right.
So what are we going to be doing right here.
Really really simple.
The only thing we need to do is pretty much what we did here.
We need to loop everything and make sure that they have the ballot keyboard remember that we are looping
the state of this.
So if they have valid they are valid.
Going to move forward if not we're going to return false.
So are going to say let form is valid.
Let me do it careful about it.
And there's one by default.
All right.
So I'm going to do for opening close.
And again I do let key let key and form data just like this.
So what do we do we loop the form is valid.
I'm sorry the form data and this one will be true or false.
So what are we going to do.
We're going to enter the form data to enter the key then begin to check if it's valid if it's true.
And we're going to check.
Of course when we go right here if the form is valid because we are not just validating a single impot
we're going to validate multiple inputs.
So this one should be always true.
If you get it to false it's because something else fails.
Right.
So I'm going to go return and we returned the form as valid.
All right.
That is it.
So I'm going to go to log in I'm going to go at the bottom and at the end of course we will get this
form valid with true or false.
So we just do a simple operation.
If the form is valid we move forward.
If not error.
Right.
And when we do when we get an error we do this that sets state opening close and we set the state of
form error to true.
All right.
And we will display the error message that we have at the bottom.
Please check your data.
All right there you go.
And of course if you are able to submit we can see the data to submit.
So let's try again.
We're going to open this.
I'm going to log in.
Please check your data.
So we are going there.
If I type something wrong and I type the password which is OK.
Please check your data.
If I add an email gmail dot com all the data is correct.
So if you're able to do the submit.
All right man.
So everything so far everything works.
Now what we need to do we need to make the actual request and remember that for this we are using in
redux.
So what we will need to do we will need to go to actions create a function to do the request imported
here and you know we need to do all that logic would redux and it dispatched the server.
Right.
So let's go to the next section and do that.