OK so now we need to submit with dispatch an action to redux and read is going to go to the server and
at the end we're going to get a response back.
Whenever we log in.
OK.
So we don't have an action.
We're going to go right here the top and created right now of course we will need to create it later.
So I'm going to import import opening close and I'm going to call it logging user so there's logging
user will be coming from dot dot for Slashdot that force lasht actions just like this and user actions
all right now instead of user actions we will need to create dysfunction.
So right oh components there we go.
So we need to create the function inside user actions.
So export function opening close and there we go.
Now we will be receiving a data to serve meant right here.
Now what we need to do right here is just a request.
We've already have a server working and it's expecting for this location for this rumped.
So I'm going to say Konst request is equal to accedes.
And remember we are importing axially at the top and it's going to be a post request and the post is
going to be to the server to the user server route and with the logon.
Now the second argument it's the data we are actually minute.
Then of course the problem is that then we are going to get a promise back so we can say then open and
close and we will be getting a response so we're going to say responds and we will we we want to return
the response that data.
So at the end inside of this marvel there request we will get this response that data now would redux.
We need to return.
I mean do it here.
We need to return opening close a type and a payload now for type we can use the file types we created.
If you don't know why we are using types don't worry at the end of the section I can explain why I'm
going to show you why.
If you already know of course you don't need to do this.
So we are doing log in data method.
Everything looks correct.
So the time logging user we need to create the type but of course what we get at the end to begin to
send the request as a payload.
So let's create Dhia the type I'm going to go to copy the name going to go to types and create the type.
So we do export like it's only for you if you don't know what why are we doing this just do it.
And then again explain why.
So this one is going to be log in underscore user and I'm going to do it the other way.
Log in.
Underscore user right.
So now instead of just making a reference right here to the inside of the user actions so viral that
doesn't exist.
Here.
We can import it from types.
So import opening close logging user.
And we bring it from DOD forward slash and types.
OK.
So now we are going to dispatch the action from here.
The action is going to go here.
It's going to make the request will return something back and the server will be returning logging logging
success and then it's going to go to the reducer.
Now let's go to the user reducer and he said of the Jews or Jews or I'll read this.
I was just saying we need to import logging user from the types.
Right.
OK.
So I notice that it stands out for us.
We are entering auctions and then types.
All right.
Let's get over this.
I thought I did this.
OK.
So instead of here we need to listen for this logon user.
So case logging user.
And if we do have a case of that we want to return the dot dot dot the previous estate and we will be
returning a log in success and then action that payload.
So this is this should be working.
Now if we go here at least we get no errors we get that the luggin use a function right here the dispatcher
step will be fine but we are not using it and it's because we are not really using it.
So let's go back to log in.
Going to copy the name and I'm going to go to right here to there is formatted.
So the form is valid we want to you know dispatch this action.
So I going to say oh sorry are going to go right here.
Going to dilute this for now.
And what we want to do we want to dispatch the action.
Remember that we are using redux.
So whenever we import and we use connect and everything else we inside dispatch we have everything available
to dispatch in action.
So I'm going to say this that prompts that this patch this patch just like this.
So the dispatch of course comes from Britax.
So of course we will dispatch the loving user action and we will be passing the data to submit.
Now after we do this we will get something on the state.
So let's try it right now.
Now on the database what I did.
I deleted all the users and just the left.
Francis Edgemont that come with the passport of one two three.
So I believe the password was once you three.
So I'm going to say passport one two are going to log in.
Of course we get nothing back.
But if we go to the state we get the log in success of true right.
So that works right leg and success and success true we could just return true from the server.
So instead of just adjacent what we could do that we're going to do it later.
So right now we are getting the on the stage.
We are getting back to redux the response from the server and we are storing it inside of the store.
OK.
Now there's two things you can do right here.
After you get the two that response you can get.
You can do.
You can do it then or you can go to the component at Mount or you can go to map what we see probs or
something like that and get the new probs and check if you have a success log in true.
And if you do then of course do something or you can take the shortcut which is actually we are kind
of overwriting the the behavior of redux.
And you can't just catch the promise that we get from this function.
You can do that you know we are using the den of the dispatch.
So whenever the dispatches on we can get the it went whenever that prompts gets resolved we can catch
that then and then we will get a response and the response is going to be equal to whatever we get inside
the response that payload.
Right.
The same thing that right here used yet redux is catching.
So in theory if I do response DOD payload DOD log in success we will of course get the message.
So if open and close and then going to say else and this is one way to do it begin to do it different
ways throughout the whole application.
So if response that payload DOD and then remember that we call that in success so log in Access.
Yes I believe was the same name Logan success.
I actually did with one single the luggin success.
What we will do we will console log responds that payload payload.
I want to see when we get back and at the end what I want to do I went to push the user to a different
route.
But before we do that I want to do something else and to say this.
That said state opening close opening close and I guess a form error equals truth.
Because if we are not getting this response the lag in success.
True it means that you know it failed.
So we are going to do something else.
All right I get to reload the application I'm going to go Francis Jamail passport one two three passport
one two three.
In we get the luggin success.
True.
So and then of course we get the state.
So we are entering this scenario.
Now what I want to do I want to send the user to the user for Slash dashboard route.
We dont have that route.
We will create it in a couple of minutes but I'm going to say this that prompts that history history
that push review remember this is how we push how we send the user to new routes use in re-act router.
OK.
So dashboard.
All right.
So this is not going to work.
Going to tell you why in a minute.
So Francis then password one two 3 we log in and we get Cannot we push of undefined and this is because
this loggin is a child of index an index is the one that its child of routes.
So inside of the index of register log in right here this is the one that is getting the props right
here with the route with the routes.
So with all the methods from Riak router.
So from within Lagann which is the child of this one we don't have access to you know the prompts that
push that history even though we catch the props inside the log in inside the main index of log in.
We catch the props right here and we pass it as props.
We still don't get it.
So there is a way to fix this re-act Roder they give you a module or actually a method that we can use
in our component that will inject all the properties of that particular route.
And its called with a router.
So I'm going to go right here.
Import open it close and call us with router and this one comes from re-act then router and then domm.
Now this router how can we use it.
We need to wrap our function right here our main component.
Sorry with this with router.
Now we are using we are still using connect so I'm going to go to log in with the router and I'm going
to wrap it.
So now all the props will be injected inside logon.
And then of course redux is going to do pretty much the same thing.
So now if we try again Francis G.M. that come past.
One two three.
We are going to use our dashboard so it works.
And of course we get long and success through on the console log and we are logging the user Burguet.
OK.
So we are pretty much done with this with the log in of course later we will create that dashboard and
everything else.
So on the next section what we are going to do is the Create an account.
Now since most of the logic for the forms and validations and everything else weve already did this
is going to be a piece of cake.
Now if you already know why we are using types right here the user actions go to the next section if
not state again to give you a tiny example of why we are using types OK why using types and not just
a string.
So let me just give you an as in Ario if I do that just like this the usual way I say log in I save
it and I go to the user reducer and I say that we are listening for a string called in user.
Of course this is going to work because they are the same string same value and everything else going
to say password.
Let me type it again.
Passport one two three.
Log in.
OK.
That is luggin success.
That works.
Now what happens if I make a mistake just like this.
The user actually is logging user and right here the type and this one is logging use.
I just make a mistake you know that could happen.
So I'm gonna do the same thing password one two three.
I'm going to log in.
We can get this.
It's kind of a going because we are dispatching and we are catching something else.
But if we go right here to the state nothing happens.
We are not updating the state.
This didn't happen.
It's not going through this because of course they don't match.
You know this logging use and this user action.
But notice that what that what's funny is that we are not getting an error message.
And of course this is from a different something else we are not getting a warning.
Not a single error message.
So we didn't know that there's something that is actually wrong.
The only way to know is it's you know to be make sure to keep them to know that actually we need to
store something here check on the store and check that we don't have value.
So there's no way for us to know that something is wrong.
So that's why we use types.
The types are not strings.
They are variables.
So if javascript they know the browser it's not finding the correct Marvel they will give us an error
message of where of what went wrong.
For example I'm going to do same things same example going can you know go back to the Bible and and
this one I'm going to say log in use and notice that this log in use doesn't exist.
So of course logging use is not defined instantly we get we are getting a message Eastham is saying
that there's something wrong with this logging use viable.
And if it's even giving you the name of the file in side use a reducer and then you go here and say
oh it's because it's the user.
So there we go.
Fixed.
So that's why we use types.
Now right now we just have one type but later.
And let me show you the final one.
If you're Yeah if you want to know why use the using marbles we use and types this is the final we can
have all these types.
Yeah.
So imagine that if you make a mistake and this once at least one inside the user reduce or all of this
well meant you can to do a lot of debugging.
Yeah that's why we use types.
All right.
If you're using a single very small application you can skip the types because you can have a few types
just not all of types.
OK.
That's good.
Let's go to the next section and create the register.
User.