OK so let's keep going with this.
Of course now we have the we have the ability to log in.
So now we need to register new customers.
So if I go to create an account we're going to go to the register route.
We don't have this route.
So we need to create it.
So I'm going to go to register or log in I'm going to create a new file and call register ride that
yes of course we need to add this route to routes.
So I'm going to go two routes and of course import register from and then opening close.
We're going to get components for Slash and register Lagann no register sorry for that for Slash or
just log in sorry and then register again.
Right.
So now of course we need to include the route.
So I'm going to copy this one I'm going to pace that down here at the bottom.
And of course the route will be just register.
OK.
So paste you know the usual stuff.
So register.
OK.
So now of course if we go to register I'm going to close it close everything else because you can and
of course use some of this but not right now.
I'm going to leave the log in open because a lot of things will be the same.
And instead of typing everything again I'm just going to copy from here.
I'm going to go to the register and this one.
It's going to be a re-act class based component.
So opening close going to change the capital are to register.
And if I do register right here and reload the application we should be getting register Burguet.
OK.
So we're kind of a good to go.
So just like we did with the log in we will need a few things from here.
So I'm going to import the form fields just like with the log in going to copy this just form fill we
will need the update to generate data and is formatted from auctions.
So I'm going to copy this to first first copy paste.
Now we will use connect.
So to port connect and of course then we will need to import something from user actions just like this.
So for now I'm just going to copy paste this one we're going to delete this one because we don't need
this one.
Now I'm going to leave it now.
Just like the Lagann at the bottom.
We are doing the can connect.
And since this route will be you know like the main component inside routes we didn't need to bring
with router so it is going to go to register what happened.
There we go.
Let me just close this right.
Doesn't matter.
So I have a cable right here which is a cable of the microphone.
And you know it's in the middle of the mouse.
OK.
So I'm going to copy and just put the register right here.
So now we have pretty much all the things we need.
We have redux.
We have the form fields and everything else just like we did with the log in we need to state with all
of this.
So I'm going to go right here at the top and create a state of equal to something.
So we need form error and we need to form data.
So for now just going to copy and do this.
All right.
Now if I go to the final one and I go to this one and we go to the register we have this tiny box with
a name last name email and then we need to confirm password I'm sorry password and confirm confirm password.
So we need to create different fields for this one.
So first it's going to be the name I'm going to copy this one going to copy the mail that we have inside
log in and I'm going to paste it in of course changed values.
So this one will be name and the input still an input instead of email is going to be name.
Same thing right here.
All right.
So enter your name.
So validation we need to remove the e-mail and it's just going to be required.
Valid false touch false and validation message.
All right so everything it's just like we need to be then I get a copy of this one I'm going to paste
it at the bottom.
And this one will be last name.
And then of course I will change all of your other inputs.
Last name.
Input type of actually name actually here.
The type should be text.
Sorry for this text.
And there's one text as well.
And then enter your last name still required and everything else.
Then we have the email going to save it.
And again the e-mails same configuration so I'm going to copy the one from the log in and they're going
to paste it down here.
Then we need a passport to go to log and copy the passport and paste it because it's going to be the
same code.
So paste.
Very good.
Now when we the last field is going to be the confirmed password and this one is going to be a little
bit a little bit weird because whenever we send this to the database to the server we just need to add
a new user with this name last name email and one password.
So this one will not pass.
This one is just for validation.
So when we need to do is we need to create a field and then when we send everything to the server we're
going to remove that field.
Now this confirmed passport needs to match or try to match whatever we have inside passport.
So going to go I'm going to copy the passport and say confirm and then with a capital P passport still
going to be any input it's going to be a password input going to say confirm.
Confirm underscore equal to you know again type passport and then on this one confirm your passport
all right now the validation is what it's going to be weird because it's still required.
But we need to add a new rule.
We need to tell the validation that this field needs to be equal to this one.
All right.
So I'm going to go right here and say coma and then confirm and then passport you're going to say this.
So by doing this whenever we reach validation and we will need to added Of course you're going to say
OK this field that begin to be band aiding the value of this one needs to be exactly the same password
is the same as passport.
Is this field.
This is why I'm making reference to password.
So then when we reached a validation we're going to check ok with it what is the value for this one
and what is the value for the other one we have the top they match.
No.
Yes.
What are we going to do.
So that's the the main idea of this.
Now of course we need to start creating all of this.
So I'm going to delete this.
I'm going to go to class name opening close and Page underscore wrapper.
All right then we have a container so I'm going to add a container.
There we go.
Dev of class container.
All right container.
What else.
Right here.
Going to create a new wrapper div opening close and this div are going to add a class name of register
underscore in underscore container.
All right.
Now if we check what we get right here on the final one we have kind of again a left side and an M a
downside Ryan on a bright side.
OK.
So it could be a left side or it could be just one div.
Does it matter.
I'll come up with the following.
Because I'm out in the class and maybe I did this in a different way just like this.
And then I change it back and I forgot to change the name of the class because right now it makes no
sense because I going to say class name again.
I'm going to put the left.
This is proved very much because they've made a mistake when I was creating this.
But doesn't matter.
Just one tip.
All right.
So I'm going to create a form.
Open and close and just like with it before this form will get an on sieve met.
All right open and close and just like with that before we need to be passing the function that we're
going to be doing with the actual event.
All right.
And then this that serve mid form opening close and we pass that event.
So I'm going to say some form opening close and we just you know do a function.
OK.
So now at the top we have a title.
So I'm going to add an H to tack which is says personal information.
All right.
Now we have two blocks.
The one at the top and the one at the bottom.
So I'm going to wrap the first block inside of a div just like here.
Let me do it like this.
OK.
So I'm going to say div and there's declasse Oh sorry.
The class name I gave to this container which is going to be a form underscore block and then to that
some of the clauses make no sense but that's OK.
Then Dave and I are going to add a class name again of Block.
All right.
And this is what we care we need to add the form field right here.
Now of course we have two blocks which is this one.
And it's this one.
So the first one we need to add the form filled.
I'm going to copy the one we have right here which is the one for name and then the one for last name.
So I'm going to paste it and this one will be name and this one as well.
All right.
So in theory at least we should be getting something just going to keep going forward.
I'm going to copy with the block with the div and class block.
And then going to paste it down here at the bottom.
And this one will be last name.
So last name.
Copy paste.
All right let's see what we get.
And I got a can I get it.
Then we have a different feel which is going to be a complete block a width of 100 percent kind of thing.
So this one is going to go outside of the form block.
Just going to be a div.
So outside of the form block two are going to create a div.
Open and close and this one will be an e-mail and I'm going to just copy the one we have right here
from Lagann and paste it real simple.
OK.
Let's see what to get.
And there we go OK let's get now we have the accounting formation.
So it's pretty much just like the form block too.
It's pretty much the same thing.
So just outside of the email field I'm going to create an age to tack.
And there's one account could be instead of account information.
Oh and I will remember because of the personal information I was getting at the field for last name
e-mail and everything else in a county formation is going to be the address the phone and that kind
of things.
But we're going to do that after we are logged in we're going to do that later.
Maybe I didn't just I didn't change this.
Forgot to change it.
So this one should be verified passport
very fine passport.
Kind of makes sense.
And on this one just like before going to copy the tag.
It's a form block too.
All right.
They're opening close.
And again we will have two different blocks so I'm going to copy this ones from here and I'm going to
paste them right here.
All right.
So now this form field instead of name is going to be password.
This one passport.
And remember that we have a confirmed passport so confirm passport and confirm passport on the.
On the other one.
Very good.
OK.
So we are kind of not going to go but we are much much closer.
So I'm going to go back and check how this goes.
So Burguet we have everything we need.
Of course if I type something the application fails.
Right.
So we need to add the update form function.
So we're going to go right here at the top and say update form.
Just like we did before date form.
Now this time is going to be much much easier.
Why is going to be much easier.
Because we've already have all the functions and the helpers that we created on the privy section.
General data this for Balad and the update form.
So now the update form is going to be pretty much the same on this one.
We just use the same thing.
The only thing we change is the keyboard of what we are actually doing.
So I'm going to copy this and I'm going to go to update form and paste it.
All right let's try again.
So I'm going to type something.
And now it updates.
All right very good.
So that is get now on the submit form.
We need to do pretty much the same thing.
And now right here are going to say this one is register going to go back to log in copy what we have
from submit form.
Let me make this Nizer copy what we get from submit form.
I can paste it right here.
And of course everything else is going to be the same.
The only thing we're going to change is the keyword keyword.
And inside of the form ballot.
The only thing we can output right now it's a console log for the data to submit just so we can make
sure that everything is going as planned.
All right.
So you know pretty much pretty much ready.
So OK.
I'm going to be adding some.
The button the buttons at the bottom because we didn't have them.
So let's go right here at the bottom and right here we have the last block which is the close of the
last block.
We have the div and then we have the form.
So what I'm going to do is before the close of the form I'm going to add the buttons.
So I'm going to go right here for you to decide.
We are almost done now on this one.
We need to pretty much do the same thing than before.
Again we're going to go to the log in and I'm going to copy this.
I'm going to go right here and paste it and make it a little bit nicer.
All right man.
So please check your data.
If we do get an error could be something went wrong.
Try again.
Does it matter.
And then of course instead of log in is going to be create an account.
All right.
Everything is the same.
So right there we go.
So now what we need to do and what we're going to be doing is to of course submit the form.
Make sure that everything is OK and we need to fix this.
You know we add this rule to the validation to confirm password thing because of course we need to validate
they have the entering the same passwords right here.
And then of course when we log again we are not going to work when we were just or we are not going
to log in the user directly.
We're going to say OK everything went OK go to the log and we're going to take you to the log in.
And you know enter your information your user and password and log in.
So we're going to do that.