All right so now what we need to do we need to fix the problem we have with the confirmed passport on
the validations.
So I'm going to say this I'm going to go to the place where we can validate things.
And you know I'm going to go right here and of course we need to add a new validation because right
now we are saying that the validation we want to do is something called confirm and we don't have this
rule right here.
All right.
So first we need to create it.
So I'm going to go right here and say OK.
If open and close if element just like with it before validation dot and confirm just like this then
we will you know do something.
All right.
Just like here I'm going to copy this and we're going to change this a little bit.
Now what do we need to do.
We need to check the value that comes for this field.
Right.
So we just do the same thing with it required we access the element the value and we do a trim because
we don't want white spaces that are going to equals to something.
Now we only say that this element is valid that it's true as long as this is equal to what to the input
we have right here to the passport.
And if you remember we do have access to form data when devolve the accent.
So what we need to do is to enter form data sorry and enter form data and say OK we want to check and
we want to do that to check inside form data for a field that calls passport.
So what do we do.
Again we say element just like this element dot validation because we have the key right there and then
confer.
And it's going to enter to that particular field.
And then of course we want to match it against the value of that one.
So of course if the there's value on this element it's something and it's not matching the one of the
other elements.
So this will be true I'm sorry.
False.
So we will have a validation error message.
So OK.
So what we do is say well we say passport do not match or passports do not match.
Right.
And then we pretty much return the same thing.
All right.
So again if you check this we could do something else maybe create a function or something like that
where we just returned different error message messages and we just returned that function because right
now we are kind of repeating a lot of code.
So this could be something we could change in the future in the future.
All right.
So we do have a validation.
What is the next problem.
Now when we registered.
Everything is going to be valid it's assumed that everything is valid and we just go to the server with
the data to submit.
Now inside of the data to submit we will get the confirmed passport.
Let's check it out.
So we're going to inspect going out reload just in case I'm going to enter a name and I have the I would
have failed.
So I'm going to do that.
And then password one two three and then password 1 two three can create an account going to go to cancel
and pretty much get it.
So it's to confirm password the e-mail the last name password and password.
So the thing is that we need to remove this confirm password.
We don't need it on the database.
All right.
So how can we do this.
Now if you remember whenever we are doing this we are generating the data that we need to submit.
We are passing the action of this form to what are we doing.
This is the Register's section.
So what we can do inside the form actions we can enter the place where we generated data and say OK
do all of this.
But if the form is register don't do it.
Or maybe if the if the key it's Kimper X confirm password don't do it you can do it.
No it's just just a single rule.
So what I'm going to do I'm going to use the Confirm password because we don't need it here or in any
other place I'm going to say if the key of this one is different then confirm password which is the
thing we are using right here Cf. password.
Then we want to do it if not of course don't do it.
So I'm going to copy and put it inside.
Real simple just logic.
So let's try again again to Phil and then whatever and then whatever.
Of course I need two matches so pass word one two three and then password one two three and they match
Frigga.
Create an account and we get email last name and password.
So a very good man.
So now what do we need to do.
We need to grab all of this information and send it to the server.
And just like we did with the log in we can create an action dispatch the action and everything else.
OK so let's create the user action for this one.
I'm going to call it we're just a user.
Pretty clear register and then user.
OK.
We will still use user actions.
So this is the name of our function.
So I'm going to copy this and I'm going to go to user actions now instead of user actions.
We just need to create a function.
So I'm going to go right here the top export function and then the name of the function just like the
log in we will be getting data to submit.
Pretty clear.
All right.
So right here I'm going to go and create a contest called request.
You can call this whatever you want X CEOs and we will do a post request that you are all just like
the luggin is going to be users server and then for Slash.
And if you remember because I remember it's register.
All right then what do we need to do is we need to pass the data to submit data to submit.
Then I'm going to go and say OK what we want to do we one then return a response and would the would
the response along with the response is going to be response that data just like with it before it's
over turn opening close and would read up.
We always need to return a type and a payload so type and then payload.
I'm going to go and create a type for this.
We don't have it.
So at the time are going to call it register and then user whenever a creed types.
I always attach something related.
Well you know what we are doing in this case is user so it's going to be user.
We don't have the type we need to create it.
So it's going to be export Konst register user equals to register and then user.
Now we have a type.
Now what we don't have so far is going to be the the of course the reducer.
So we're going to cope a copy register user.
And what we send back on the payload it's going to be the request.
Very good.
And they make this a little bit nicer.
All right.
So now let's go to the producer go to use a producer.
And of course we need to bring that type.
So copy and paste.
All right.
Now in case we have we just are users so case register user in case we have a return opening closed
we returned the previous state coma and then we have a register something like this you could call register
success or whatever you want to use and then action that payload not from the server the register.
And this is something I don't remember.
I'm going to check it right here.
Whenever we were just our end user when we find it we are sending SS to.
OK.
Let's get it enough so we will be getting this.
So now the only thing we need to do from Register is to dispatch an action and use of course this right
now if five of the application at least it's not failing so it should be OK.
OK.
So let's go right here.
Going to delete this log of data to submit and we need to dispatch the action right.
So what do we need to do is go right here.
We say this that prompts that this patch this patch opening close.
Where will we be.
We will.
We will this patch is that register user along with the data to submit.
And just like with that before going to use the promise.
So then open and close.
OK.
So we will send a response back and oh sorry sorry.
We will get a response.
And then of course we're going to run the callback right.
So if you remember we have that success from the server.
So we will pretty much do the same thing before we're going to do.
We're going to do this on a different and different weights different ways later.
For now we're going to do it just like this.
It's a response that payload that success this is what we get from the server if we get a success we
get to do something.
Of course if something fails we're going to do something else.
So I'm going to say this.
That said state opening close and we're going to save for form.
Error equals two.
All right.
Of course if something else goes wrong we need to do the catch.
And this is more laded of error with the server itself not with the actual request or what we get back
from Mongo.
So we pretty much saying say the same thing we just say Do try again.
Something is wrong.
All right.
So what are you going to do.
Whenever we log in what I want to do I want to show a message right.
I want to show a message in a dialog box and then redirect the user back to the log in.
So what I'm going to do I'm going to say this that said state opening close and I'm going to say that
the form error.
Of course we can change it default because we have no errors and are going to change the form success
to
and after this happens I want to re direct the user to someplace else so you can do a callback right
here on the set state.
You know after the state which can trigger something or you can do you know maybe a set timeout or something
like that.
So I'm going to do set time out and I'm going to run this function after you know a couple of seconds
going to three seconds.
You can put again whatever you want.
Since this route it's completely is directly related to react Roder.
We can do this that prompts that history history that push opening close and we will send the user back
to slash register underscore Lagann so they can you know log in with the user and password.
All right man let's try again.
So.
Oh of course if we try again after three for three seconds this is going to happen for sure for sure.
Now before this happens I want to know at least show something.
So we will use a dialogue.
And we're going to import it from material to you.
So import dialogue just like this.
Make it right.
Capital di di lock that from open and close and at material you I core for Slash and the name of whatever
we are importing.
Now we need to create a dialogue going to go at the bottom and begin to put it at the very end of the
of the actual template because you know it's just a dialogue.
Let me do this and go right here at the bottom.
Now of course the dialogue will never show unless we want to.
So I'm going to open and close the dialogue now with mature UI and dialogues.
We need to tell the component if we should show it or not.
And since we have a form success we only want to show this whenever we have the form.
Success on the true state.
So you know it's going to open.
Now get him attached.
Maybe we're going to add some maybe a dev.
Oh that's weird that we're.
Well sometimes the code fails but it works really good and it's free so I can attach a class name of
dialogue just like this underscore alert.
And on this one we will say I don't know man dev.
Congratulations something like that.
Congratulations.
And of course a message saying I know you will be redirected to the log in in a couple of seconds something
like that makes sense.
Of course all of this dialog and the contents and everything else is going.
It's going to come from the client or maybe the designer.
Pretty much the designer but that is good.
So I'm going to save it and I got an error message.
Fill up open string model.
Open.
I made a mistake with open double check it.
There's that state that form success.
Now it looks good.
I don't know when I'm getting an error message.
I know why.
Right here we have this.
That state that forms success.
It says right here that open the open of typed string supplied to dialog expected to boolean.
So I'm pretty sure that on the default to form success I'm using a string which is actually this so
form success.
If we do false begin to clear the message there we go OK.
So let's try again.
Of course I'm going to go to robo 3D because then the user will be receiving a new user.
So I don't know what does the user have right now is Francis Francis at gmail dot com.
All right so I'm going to use this one because I've already have the information.
You can type whatever you want and the password is the same password one two three.
All right.
I'm going to create an account.
Congratulations you'll be redirected and blah blah blah.
And then we go to the log and never go to rubble with.
An update.
We do have a second user and everything is cool.
So now I'm going to go to this and say pass word.
One two three.
Log in and log in success.
So everything works very good man.
So I'm going to sip this so you can you can compare the code with the one you have in your computer.
And then we're going to do something very important because to set up begin to create the preventing
router things because right now maybe the users log in and if they goes to user then dashboard is going
to be able to log in you know able to enter.
So we need to create a high order component with the south route we created on the server.
Remember we we've created it now with that so we can decide if the user should be able to log in or
log out and once we have that what we can do we can check with the out if the user of course is logged
in or not and show some options or maybe some of the options if the user is not locked in.
Right.
Something like we do right here right now the user is not logged in.
So we get home guitars and just log in.
But if we log in we will get more options like my account my card and things like that.
So on the next few seconds we're going to be doing that and I'm going to sip the code so far to give
you a download sip or the way remember that the final code of all of this is a good help.