OK so before we start preventing routes we need one more route.
We need to pre-event which is you know the use or dash for it.
If I go two routes we have the register and the log in which are not really private routes because they
are public.
If you're not logged in and then of course we have a public.
So now we need to create one completely private route and that could be the user dashboard.
All right.
So inside of the components what I'm going to do I'm going to create a folder or a directory where we
are going to be hosting all the private routes.
You know the user private routes are going to create a directory called user and he's out of here.
And this yes this is going to be the user dashboard.
Now the user dashboard is going to be up just of reacts like this component.
We don't need a class based component and I we call this user dashboard copy paste or I get to say dashboard
right now and I'm going to add the routes right here.
So import user dashboard from that for Slash components.
Now we have user.
And now of course we don't need to bring it.
So I'm going to copy this and I'm going to paste it down here.
And we're going to be using the user dashboard route right components of the route will be different.
So user forward slash dashboard.
All right.
So if you go to use a dashboard now we get dashboard that is now on the final one this is what we get
at the end.
So the user dashboard should be looking like this.
Now if you notice we have right here the contents and in the left have the nav ride and the nav it's
always the same.
So it kind of makes sense for us to create a high order component to show the nav and then of course
we will need to change it to show the admin routes which is on the same high or that component.
But we're going to do the admin part of things much later.
Now we're going to create the the high or the components so we can show the children's and the now.
All right.
So I'm going to go to h o CS and create a new file and I'm going to go.
This user could be called user lay out or something like that.
So this user will show pretty much the nav and the children.
So this is going to be a re-act stateless component.
We don't need a class right now.
So instead of user going to call it user and then lay out copy paste Raggatt.
So again we will have links.
So I need to import link from re-act router Dom.
All right.
So OK.
Now first we need a lynx and we need some links and we're going to create a marble where are we going
to be hosting this links.
It's going to create an array of objects with the links inside.
Now each link will have a name and a link to ride.
Need to pass where are we going to go when we click here.
So in this case the first link is going to be my account that a coma and we need to tell where are we
going to go.
So we're going to go to user and the main one which is dashboard right that I get a copy this.
So we don't need to type over again.
And this one will be the user information.
Now on user information is going to be pretty much a form where we can update the user profile.
So again user profile and we will be able to change the name and you know some user data as we move
forward through the project of course this is going to get much bigger.
So of course whenever the user add something to the cart they need to of course inspect what's inside
the card and make the purchase.
So my cart capital-T and this one will be inside user and then card of course we don't have all these
routes who will create this much later much much later.
So we're going to be displaying children.
I want to get the props from the you know the components.
Now I'm going to go right here inside and say that I want a class of container.
And inside I will create a new div with a class name of user Container container.
All right now in the left will have the user now in in the right you have the it will get the props
that children so div class name of user left now.
Now there we go.
And there right.
We will get the class name of user and then right now if I do inside you are right.
Right.
Yeah.
And then props the children we can get whatever content we get from the parent component.
In this case right now we do we only have dashboard so we can get this keyboard just dashboard in the
left.
Of course I need to add a title so I will add an edge to saying my account and after my account I'm
going to wrap all the links inside of a container called lynx.
As a matter right now what I'm going to do instead of rendering press here I'm going to create a function
that calls generate links and I will pass the links we have inside the firewall.
All right.
Pretty simple you know.
Not not so hard.
Really simple stuff.
OK.
So I'm going to create a viable call Konst and then generate links and this link this function will
be receiving the prob of links.
You know the argument links and then we will do something now.
I want to return single sex.
So I need to return this the prentices.
Now we're going to grab this links.
You're going to say map opening close.
Sometimes when I say something and then a pause for two seconds it's to give you time to you know just
write this.
Of course like it's all the four at the bottom of the BDO you have the go slower option or go faster
if you want to go faster.
Now on each iteration will you will be oh my god the hour to complete.
Sometimes drives me crazy.
I don't know why it's doing that.
So I put in place besides data transfer item.
What is that.
So item and then we get I need to go to my plug in inside B-S code and disable all of them.
So whenever we run this function we want to return and Jane sex.
So we will do parenthesis instead of brackets and each time on each loop we want to return a link right.
OK.
So like now each link will have a name and the name is going to be item that name which is the one we
have right here at the top and the then we need to pass it to.
And that too is going to be item that link to.
And then of course we need to add a key because we're looping something and we will pass that iteration.
This is pretty much done.
So now every time we want to render a private route we need to display the user layout.
So I'm going to go right here to index which is the user dashboard and we need to import user layout
from that that force last one more time a Tosi for Slash and the user.
All right.
Now what we want to do is we want to wrap the complete rout inside of the user layout.
So now every time we just play around with it with an app in route we need to wrap it with the user
layout and at the end we get this right.
We get the NAB and then whatever content we have inside.
Now on the dashboard and going to do it right now and the next section we're going to prevent the routes
and then arrange all the links right here at the top so we can have something a little bit more complete
inside of here.
We will have two different sections.
Let me just show you the user information where we can go and edit info and then history of protasis
if we do have a history and all that is going to come from the database and we going do it much later.
But for now I'm just going to create the minimum layout so user info underscore and then panel any sort
of peer who will get the one with the title which has user information.
I'm putting this here because I need to put it someplace and just create a single route for history
a single route for using information and everything else to have makes no sense we're going to do it
right here now instead of here we'll get a div and expense and span it's going to be the information
above the user.
In this case we were going to put the name the last name and maybe the e-mail.
So again you can choose whatever you want to put right here.
Now of course we need to fetch using information but for that we have the outof route.
So we going to do it in a couple of minutes.
So after here we need a button so we can send the user to edit the account info.
So since we are using a button we're going to import my button at the top and we will use reusable components.
So you tell us for a slash and then button.
All right.
So if you remember with the button we need to make a reference to it and pass some props.
We have the type which is default we're not going to do anything you write here.
So the default then title equals and we no added account info.
All right.
What else.
Since the default link is the default button it's a link.
So we have to look at the property link too.
And this one is going to go to user for Slash.
And if you remember we can did this and it's user profile right user profile now but it's got user user
profile could be user information or something like that.
But this one's OK.
So if I go to user information we just use a profile we kind of get it.
All right.
OK.
So this is get now at the bottom.
We will have the history of protasis are going to create the place where we're going to be putting this.
But begin to do this much later because we need to have.
We need to get on the database at least you know maybe history or something.
Right now we don't have the ability to do that.
So when we get to that section we're going to fill this.
So on this one I'm going to put in each one of history so we are almost done.
Car chases one of our purchases.
All right.
And instead of here and this is actually a pretty important class for this one because this is kind
of a table.
So I'm going to put the class right here.
And then it will be put the history so class name equals two and I use user underscore product user
block and then wrapper and then of course we got the history and we are done.
I'm going to reload the application right here preloaded and look at it.
But of course we need to do a lot of things.
We will create history later.
But all of this it's pretty much done.
All right.
Go to my information user profile.
My cart my cart everything works.
So now we have a private route a completely private route not so private.
And then we have the plug the public one.
So let's go to the next section and start creating the logic of authenticated user of indicating users.
And then actually creating private and public routes.
And if you remember on the previous the previous project we did we created our own component that managers
of this logic right here.
But right now we are not going to do that.
We're going to do that pretty much the same same exact thing but on a different way.
So let's go to the next one and start with this.