All right.
So they home which is pretty much finished.
There's nothing else we need to do now the next thing is going to be creating a log in.
If I go to the final project you know this is what is on a different port and I go to for Shlash sign
n we get you know the place log in and we will be able to enter an e-mail and a password and it will
go to the database check if we have a user on that database we can enable authentication.
And of course if the user is on the database of the you know our users if it's OK we're going to let
the user and if not of course.
OK.
If not of course we going to let the user out of course.
So if we go to authentication if we go to firebase and we go to authentication of course we get that
we get this just like this.
And I'm going to say OK when we get an AD user and whatever version of this is OK and it says to add
users man it manually enabled password and password e-mail and sign in Methot.
So by default we need to provide firebase to tell firebase what kind of what kind of method to be using
for signing in users.
Because firebase they give you several waste to you know log in a user or log out a user we can use
email and password by phone.
You know they have an Gool connector.
You know we can sign end with a Google account with Facebook and you know whatever for now we're going
to use does want to use e-mail and password so I can get email going to enable.
And for now I'm going to say just this.
All right.
So if we go to users we can manually add users so I'm going to do that right now I'm going to add Francis
at G-mail that come and are going to add a password very simple password pass word 1 to 3 that's the
password.
So I'm going to add the user of course they will need a token and everything else will hash the passwords
and everything else.
This is the user ID.
So now if you want to connect and check if the user can log in to this you're going to do it from here.
We don't have it so far.
We get it created right now.
So let's go back to our project first.
And this log in section.
This one is going to be pretty pretty similar with that right here.
So we can do copy paste of a lot of things on the next section on the next section now and the next
project begin to use a different way of sign an end of this a big forms and the reset forms and everything
else we will use it pretty much the same but on a different ways going to be much much nicer.
All right.
So first what do we need.
We need a route right.
We need a way to go to four SLAs sign in and get at least the screen.
So OK I'm going to go right here close everything we have home because home is finished and I'm going
to go to components and create of course a place for this.
So I'm going to call it sign n now inside assign n I will add an index that is of course sign in it's
going to be a reac classmates component.
So let me go and I'm going to change it to sign in.
All right.
Copy paste and say sign in doesn't matter right now.
OK so now of course we need to create a route.
We need to set the routes so we can listen for this route.
So I'm going to go to routes and I'm going to import import just like this and then sign in from that
forward slash components for Slash and sign in.
And of course I'm going to make a reference to this route so I'm going to copy the one we have right
now.
I'm going to go on top of this home route and of course I'm going to pass this sign in and the route
is going to be signed underscore in.
All right.
That is that.
Of course the application reloads.
And if I go to sign and of course we get this but if we inspect this we should be getting that you know
that sign and text inside of the main div..
So let me let me just try to find it.
There we go.
We get it right here.
And so we are able to render the route.
Now we need to do all the logic for you know showing what we are doing right now.
You know showing the the contents and the inputs and the everything else.
So just like the end role we have right here we need this state.
So I'm going to copy all of this and get a copy the state overall and leave and roll open because we're
going to do some copying from here.
And I'm going to go to sign in and I'm going to say OK.
So we want to get a state with the form error from success and inside form data we'll have an e-mail
right.
And for now everything else is the same.
The only thing the only thing right now is that we need a passport input.
So I'm going to copy this one I'm going to put a coma.
And of course I'm going to add one different one so this one is going to be password right.
Makes sense.
Passport and the element is still going to be unemployed.
The name of course is Passport input passport.
The type is going to be of course passport and enter your passport.
Right.
The validation it's not an e-mail.
And the only thing I'm going to be using right now is going to be required.
And of course we're still getting the ballot and the validation message now just like we did before.
We need to use the form fields we created on the roll you know.
So again going to grab grab the form fields and I'm going to put it right here at the top.
Now the location it's a little bit different.
We need to do dot dot force last July and then form fills.
Now just like here we are using the validate methods.
So I'm going to copy validate can it go right here.
Paste it at the bottom.
And again one directory down.
All right.
Of course if you reload the application nothing happens.
But we're not getting any errors in saying that we are not using this but you know it's a warning not
an error.
OK.
So now we need to start creating the lay out where are we going to be putting the input input the name
the username the e-mail actually and the password.
So I'm going to go to the render.
And of course going into this and inside I'm going to say class name and it's going to be container
can are there go inside of here.
Another div is going to put another div and the class for this one again is going to be sign in wrapper
class name sign an underscore wrapper.
No camel case.
And I'm going to add some styles to this I can add a margin.
There we go.
Margin and the margin is going to be 100 pixels.
Let me do it right.
There we go.
It's winter in my country so my house right now it's a little bit cold.
My hands are you know kind of frozen.
So of course we're going to get a form in the form if you remember we will add this on submit equals
and of course we will get a function just to function right.
And we will be passing that event function and we will call a function that calls this submit form.
Just like with the before mid form.
All right.
And of course who will be passing this event.
We don't have the submit form are going to be created right now.
So it's bad form opening close.
And for now that is inside the form.
Of course we will have a title.
So I have used an h.
So please log in.
All right let's see what we get.
All right so we get to get the log in when we close the console.
So please log in.
So now we need to add the form feels so right.
We kind of know this so I'm going to go to and roll back and go back to the bottom and right here we
have the form fill and it's pretty much the same one.
So going to copy this one and paste it right here on the bottom where you still have the idea of e-mail
the form data is is still the form data and we didn't have this update form so I'm going to go right
here and copy the name and create a function update form.
Right.
Of course we have one more field which is the password.
So copy paste and then password.
All right.
Now right here this that state that form data e-mail no is going to be passport and then changed.
Same thing.
Does that update form with the elements if we check it out.
Enter e-mail and enter password.
So we are get you know once you create one you know for the forms and everything else everything else
you know gets a little bit easier.
That's why it took us a long time to do this and roll.
All right.
So what else.
We need a button.
So are going to go back to enroll and you know copy the same button now instead of in roll.
Of course it's going to be in.
Right.
Makes sense.
So log in.
OK.
So far so good.
Now of course we need to fill the submit form and the update form right.
So OK.
So we have it right here.
So I'm going to go to enroll and go to the update form because we need to update the state just like
with it before.
Now what are we going to be using right here is the exact same thing.
So I'm going to copy this function going to go right here and pasted right here.
Now in theory if this works OK.
Whenever we go to here and we type something know we are getting everything and we are even getting
validation.
So again why typing all of this again.
We just need to copy paste.
Like totally for in the future we're going to use this in a different way so we will not be doing copy
pasting.
We're not going to copy paste.
All right.
So what is next.
We have the submit form right.
OK.
We go to submit form.
Let me go right here submit form.
We have this so I'm going to copy the whole segment for him for now.
I get to go to here submit form and paste it.
And of course a lot of things we are not going to really use which is to firebase and everything else
stays the same.
The only thing I did I did the I deleted the firebase request and for now that is it right now.
We're going to right here.
We're going to do.
We're going to send the request to find ways to check if the user is healthy and decayed and if not.
But first we're going to check.
We get everything we need inside data to submit.
So I'm going to do console log opening close data to submit.
We make this a little bit bigger.
So inspect.
There we go.
So if I go to console and I type whatever and then whatever doesn't matter I'm going to log in and we
get the e-mail and the password.
So all right.
So everything works ok.
Real simple like it's all there once we have this one all the logic for this one.
Everything else is just you know piece of cake.
Ok so now in the next section we're going to go to the next section and we will make this request we'll
make a request to firebase and check if the user needs really authenticated or not.
And if the user it's authenticated right if the e-mail and password are true we will send the user to
the admin dashboard that we don't have so far we can create it of course.