OK so now let's connect with firebase to check if the user e-mail and the password are allowed to enter
so we can if we can indicate to user.
So first we're going to use firebase right here so we need to import firebase right here at the top.
So I'm going to put import opening close and firebase just like this.
And then from DOT DOT forest lashed out for Slash and then firebase.
All right.
So now we have firebase right here.
Now I'm going to go back to the firebase Julius dodgiest and we can see that we are actually exporting
this.
So you know that's why we can import it.
Now there's one more thing we can give you using a very specific method inside our base and it's going
to be called out just like we are using app and we are using databases.
We need to import this.
This package is part.
So it's going to be out.
That's that's the thing.
We just need to import firebase force lashed out.
So now right here inside of the index we can make a request to firebase to check if the user can't move
forward.
Now the first thing we need to use of course is we are importing firebase.
It's firebase right.
So firebase then we're going to use this method which calls auf.
And then since we are using a very specific type of indication we need to use sign in when we do it
like I guess everything is income OK sign in with email and passport just like that.
Sign in with email and password right here at this method again.
What it takes is going to be the user name.
These are e-mail and they use a password and we have everything inside data to submit.
So I'm going to say data to submit DOD e-mail coma and data to submitted and then passport.
And that is it.
So now this of course will return a promise then opening close and inside of here we will run a function.
The callback function.
Now if we get some erste we're going to do some catch.
And you know we could have that error.
And then of course we run a function.
Now if you get an error I get to do this that said state opening close and on the inside of the state
are going to change the form error we have on top on the state to true.
Remember on the enroll we pretty much did the same thing.
Now we need to add the the the label to our template.
It's going to go at the bottom and paste that one.
So if we do have an hour we're going to show the URL label.
You know something's wrong.
Just try again.
And that is it.
Now of course if the users or authenticated use begin to do something else.
But for now the only thing going to do.
Going to do cause a log you know user is out.
All right.
So the application will reload.
And I'm going to put the wrong e-mail right now the only user we have in the database on the other education
part it's Francis at gmail that come with a password of password 1 2 3.
So if I go here and put the wrong passport and put whatever it doesn't matter.
Going to log in and of course we get something is wrong.
Try again.
So we are entering this catch state because of course we get a not authenticated OK.
So what happens if I put the correct e-mail.
So I'm going to go right here and say that Francis at gmail dot com and password one two three are going
to log in and we get user is out.
All right.
So he's going to the console log users out.
So the user is it.
These are it's antiquated for sure.
All right.
So now if this happens what I want to do I want to push the user to the user dashboard.
Right.
We don't have that route but are going to do it anyways right here.
And then of course on the next section we will create delay out for the user dashboard.
So this that prompts that history this is how we push users to a different route.
And this is because we are using re-act router right.
If not we're not going to be able to do this inside the prompts whenever we render our route just like
this.
We can do this.
That prompts that history push and tell the application where we are going to go.
In this case I'm going to call it dashboard just like this.
You're going to read this in a minute.
Now there's one more thing with this.
If for example right here inside routes this is we are redirect directing the user within the index
yes.
Which is the sign in component.
We are importing at the top right.
It's the same one.
Now if you have a child component inside signing sign in inside this component you have a different
component and you just render it right here.
And instead of that component you're doing this that prompts patisseries that history that push it's
not going to work because you're not passing the props of their re-act router.
There's a different way to do it.
We're going to discuss.
And we're actually going to do it later or maybe on the next project but we're going to do it don't
worry.
But for now this is going to work.
We're going to push the user to that for it.
Let's see what happens.
Going to re load the application I got to do Frances and then passport one two three.
I got to log in and we go to dashboard of course on the next section we're going to do the dashboard
so we can have that ready.
But then we need to fix different problems right now.
In theory I am of antiquated.
If I go to application and check the local storage or session storage What's the local storage we have
you know something we're firebase of course we get a lot of cookies but we are pretty much a authenticated.
Now the thing is that if Phi of course if I am not authenticated I shouldn't be able to go to dashboard
and if I am I am authenticated for sure.
And if I go to sign in we shouldn't be able to go to sea to get the components signed in because we
are already authenticated.
Right.
So we need a way to prevent public routes the private routes and a way to prevent that if the user already
authenticate it.
Go to dashboard instead of instead of rendering.
Is Logan going to do this on the next few lectures.
Well let's go to the next one and we're going to create the dashboard component.
It's going to be really really simple.