Right.
So at the end this is how the dashboard should look.
We have in the left a bar that it should be only displayed the site admin routes whenever the user goes
to the dashboard.
You know in and route that it's only for administrators that we can show this the same navigation bar.
So just like the header and footer we will create a high or there component for this one.
And of course right now the dashboard is empty and on the matches or at match.
We can add the logic on that once for now.
This is what we get.
This is what we have so far.
So let's go to our or obligation or project and start creating this.
I'm going to close and roll and get close index and get close to the fire base that is just going to
leave routes.
Now all the admin routes I went to store them inside of a directory called admin.
So I'm going to go to component's create a new directory sorry new directory and this one will be called
admin.
Right.
Kind of a make sense.
You call this whatever you want.
Doesn't matter.
Now the first component inside admin will be dashboard because is the component where you go after you
log in.
Of course.
So I'm going to call it dashboard with a capital D dash board.
Yes.
Now dashboard dodgiest will be our re-act stateless component because the only thing we are doing right
here is just showing the layout and kind of redirect.
So that's the diff.
The main div will be called class name and add a class name of user dashboard user or underscore dashboard.
And inside here just the device going to do something very simple saying this is your dashboard whenever
it doesn't matter.
Just something very simple.
OK.
So of course if I reload the application nothing really happens because we need to add everything to
routes.
So I'm going to make a space in all the other routes are going to be right here.
Right.
So I'm going to import then dashboard from DOT for Slash components for Slash at men forward slash dashboard.
And I'm going to copy dashboard.
I'm going to copy this one right here to duplicate us and I'm going to say route.
It's dashboard whenever we want to go to.
You guessed it dashboard just like this.
All right.
So if I reload it you know we get this dashboard.
So now we need to create this now.
And this is going to be high or other component.
So I'm going to go back to dashboard and right now of course we don't have this we need to create it.
So inside a Choe see we're going to create a new file called admin and then layout just like this.
I've been laid down yes.
So the only purpose of admin lay down dodgiest is going to be returning the container of this coat you
know the admin routes.
So it is going to be a reacts the Blitz component just like this and it will be called I've been lay
out that has get in some some part of the application will be receiving some prompts.
I'm just going to put props right here.
Now the the wrapper for this are going to add a class name that calls up men underscore container.
And now we will have two two main parts.
The one in the left which is the now and then all the contents in the right.
So I need to create two deps one for the nav and another one for the of course the right side of the
screen.
So the main one which is the nav section are going to call it admin.
Underscore left now.
Now right here of course we're going to put the now navigation.
Now of course the other one will be class name mean underscore.
Right and right here we need to to enter to put whatever content we get from here.
You know the children.
So that's why we get props.
So I'm going to say props that children of course if I recall the application we get nothing because
we are we do we do have this and been lay out but we're not really using it on the dashboard.
OK.
So I'm going to go right here at the top and we need to import this to the actual dashboard.
Right.
Makes sense.
So of course import import or go import men then lay out then from and make it right.
I've been lay out from that that for Slashdot that for Slash a chose C for Slash and layout.
So every time when we have a we have an amazing route.
We need to wrap it.
We need to wrap the components inside.
I mean lay out components.
And of course all of this will create what we are actually doing right now with a choke seat.
So if I reload the application you know we get this block.
Now of course we need to create this right now and everything in the ride is going to be the actual
content of the components.
Now we need to create that now and then going to store it not on HBO series are going to start an admin
because that NAV that navigation bar belongs to admin routes.
So I'm going to say now now inside of the app of course we need the admin now.
So I'm going to create a file called admin.
Now could be could be next.
If you want.
OK so I am now going to do several things.
We don't need a class based component.
So I'm going to say re-act stateless components.
Been very good.
Now we're going to be using LINQ because they are just links.
So import opening close link from re-act router.
Dom very good.
That's the first thing we're going to be using a maybe list items we're going to do later.
Maybe firebase But again we're going to do it later.
So for now the only thing we need to do we need to just render some items.
Ok so I'm going to go right here and I'm going to create a function called render and then items just
like this just turned right it's just a function and I get to go right here at the top.
And of course create dysfunction called render items.
So Konst render items.
Now since we're going to get several links in this case we have matches at match players or players.
And then logout we need a place where we're going to be rendering all the sites.
So I want to put them on a list right.
And they begin to loop them with render items and begin to show the actual item.
Right.
Makes sense.
So first we need to a place where we going to be hosting this links.
So I got to say Konst that links cole just an array of objects and right here we're going to be registering
the links so they have a title and they have a link to you know where are we going to go after we click
on this one.
So this one is going to be matches which is the first one.
And then of course the route where we going to be going so I'm going to call it outman matches.
All right going into coma you're going to copy this one do one more.
This one is going to be at match and I know that this is boring right now at match and I'm going to
host this one inside.
I've been matches and added match just like this could be added or outmatch or something like that doesn't
matter.
We're going to go back to this round later.
Don't worry I'm going to copy this one.
I'm going to go right here.
And then we can have an end point.
An important to administer players.
So I'm going to call it players and just like I've been matches this one will be I mean players.
Right.
Of main players.
And just like this one we will need to create an end point to admin the players to our players.
So this one I'm going to call it I don't know at players doesn't matter right now.
OK.
So what do we need to do now is to render all this content all this links in the in a linked form.
Right.
Because right now we have an object.
So you're going to say links that map over the course now every each iteration we will be receiving
a link.
And of course then we will run an up function.
Now if you noticed I'm using and this is actually my mistake.
I'm I went to render.
I went to return some GSX but I'm using not princesses.
Nothing is going to work.
All right.
So on each iteration we get a link and what we will do we will return a link from Briac granddaughter
of course open and close.
I know what I'm not getting the complete for link.
I don't know why.
And.
So of course with each link we have two and we two we need to pass the where we're going to go.
So we have an inside link just like this dot link to.
Of course we are looping something.
We need to add a key so key opening close link dot and are going to use the title as a key.
You can pass the torsion number and pass the Teuscher number.
Now just a little before if we check the or find one we get to use the material.
I list items.
So I'm going to go right here at the top an important list item for material you eyes so import list
I mean make it ride list item.
All right.
From opening close at material the ice core for Slash and the name of whatever we are importing from
the court.
All right.
So now I'm going to copy this name list item I'm going to go inside the link.
And of course we need to pass this link items up link list item sorry.
So open close.
Now instead of the last item we need to put the name of the link which is inside link that title.
And of course we need to specify what kind of item we want from material.
In this case we want a button and it can add Bassam stylings are going to modify the default stylings.
So going to create a viable when are going to be hosting this style.
So Kansas style and this is actually very common.
So color is going to be white which is three four five six.
Then I want to make it make the phones a little bit bigger.
So Fonte that wait and I'm going to use oh sorry Lider 300 then I'm going to add a border bottom so
border and then Boneham are not getting more their bottom.
All right.
And we'll add one pixel solid solid color.
It's 3 5 3 5 3 5.
And of course I will just pass these tiles to this.
So Style style style.
Right.
All right.
Let's see what we get.
So the application should be reloading and we are not getting anything because I forgot to do something.
Maybe you got it right.
So I've created the nav component but I'm not including this inside the H O C right.
So I'm going to do import just like this.
And I believe we call this at bin now.
So I've been Napp from that that forward slash and components and abdomen and then Nav. and then admen
now.
Now of course make reference to this really simple at this point.
This should be really easy for you.
So we get matches we get match players and players I made a mistake and that's why I'm going to change
you right now.
So if I go to Majerus we go to the matches at at least the link works.
So let me fix this.
I've added players.
So what we want to do we want to add players
that is get now in theory we are locked in.
Right we are locked in because we did the log in and we got the information so we get some some some
logic inside the application right here.
Let me just show you inspect inside the application begin to get the storage the local stores.
Maybe the session source.
There we go.
So we get this.
So in theory we are kind of authenticated.
So we need to log out button right here.
And for this one of course we need to use firebase and it's the signing out method a fire base is just
like the other indication it's really really simple.
So what I'm going to do I going to add just right here and I'm going to add it manually list item I
could do it you know from a different place but I want to add an unclick handler.
That's why I'm adding this manually.
So let me do open close and this one is going to be log out.
So but then of course the style is going to be the same style we are using at the top.
We are almost done with this.
I know that this is simple and a little bit boring but we are almost done that unclick equals two and
I'm going to create a function which is going to be the log out log out and then handler just like this
handler.
All right.
And now this function of course is going to do all the locking out when have this function get created
right now.
Konst logout handler.
And this one is going to be equal to a function.
And of course we can do something.
So what are we going to do.
It's real simple just going to show you first we need to include firebase at the top.
So import than firebase firebase then from that for Slash that dot for Slash and dot dot for Slash and
firebase.
Right.
So just like we did with the owls.
This is the same thing.
I need to use firebase and use our opening close and I'm going to use sign out this is the method they
provide us to sign out users.
And then of course after they are signed out you get you get a promise.
So whenever you get the promise back you just do whatever you want.
In this case I'm going to do a log and then log out.
So successful just something like that.
Really simple right.
That is it.
And this is the first the first one.
All right.
Now of course on the second right here what we could do we could add a different function.
And of course this one is going to be error.
So if we do have an error we're going to do a console log and error logging out
so this way this way of doing things.
It's just like the documentation for all this this this is the actual the condition just like this.
So if you go there you can find the same example.
So right here where you could do you could push the user back home or you know whatever you want.
Right now I'm just I'm just going to add a con..
So OK so we get export default imported firebase now found in firebase.
Let me see why.
What did I do.
I know I'm important in putting a default and it's not a default.
All right.
So dashboard if I go to inspect log out log out successful.
If I do it again you know it's just going to log out.
But nothing really happens.
OK.
So everything good so now we have a problem if the users log in.
I just lock down the user.
And if I reload the application we're still able to enter dashboard so you know this is a big big mistake.
So what do we need to do.
We need to go to routes and prevent users create some function or create some logic to prevent users
by going going from a to dashboard or sign in if the are authenticated or not and dictated so we can
create a function to prevent routes.
Right.
OK.
So let's go to the next one and do this.