OK.
So now we're going to be creating all the logic to prevent users not authenticated users into entering
to private route Ryan because we need that and I'm going to go a little bit slower.
I was going a little bit fast because you know we can and did all of this already.
So again I was going a little bit fast now and right now this is going to look a little bit weird.
So going to go slow because it's new something you never talk about this.
So OK.
So first we need a way to check with firebase if the user is authenticated or not.
Right where these are is going to enter here.
Maybe some other user is going to go to this route.
And if we don't have the correct logic they will be able to enter.
So we need to check if the user that it's trying to enter is indicated or so firebase they give us a
way to check this.
So I'm going to go to index dodginess you know the main index of our application and this is going to
be our starting point.
So again just like with that before we can add that this part already are going to go right here the
bottom and import something.
I'm going to import firebase right from the dot for Slash and then firebase.
All right.
So now what they give us is this firebase not mouth and they give us a method called an oath state changed.
So whenever the alpha state change if these are indicated or they logout they get to this for this function
this method is going to fire a function.
So how can we use it.
OK.
So first I'm going to say Firebrace then I'm going to use an hour and then I'm going to use an hour
just like this on out with state changed and this one of course is going to be a method.
And after doing after it's done doing its job it will run a function.
Now this function after we you know we checked this the only thing we need to do is just return this
app you know return our app and let me show you how this works.
Of course whenever we add the out states change changes we will receive a user.
So before before rendering this I'm going to do Konsole that blog and it get a console this user.
And let me show you how this works really good.
So of course going to bring the costs a lot.
All right.
Right now we'll get no.
And it's because the user is not authenticated at all.
So the application starts we entered to the south and host of the state changed and is checking if the
users are authenticated.
So I'm doing a lot for the user but of course no one is logged in.
We don't have a user.
So this index doing the comms log user it's full.
And of course then it will render our app.
All right.
So what happens if I log in.
So let me go back to console.
Make this a little bit smaller right now.
And I'm going to go to sign in.
All right.
So inside sign and we are still getting know I can do Frances passport one two three.
I'm going to log in and of course we are going to the dashboard and that user Barville you know that
use of Marvel will return the correct information.
It will tell.
OK so the user South indicated.
Here you go.
Here you have all the information above the user.
You know some a lot of things that tokened refresh tokin and a lot of information that we actually don't
really need.
We just need a copy of information maybe an e-mail or something like that.
But we do get something right.
It's not.
No.
So now what we can do every time something happens on an application or a user or a user logs in or
logs out we can pass some props.
You know this user Propp and that's what we're going to be doing.
So I'm going to go right here now.
Every time we render our app I'm going to be adding a prop called user which will contain all the logic
of this user.
So are we going to get this object or no.
And note is that now the application is going to is going to reload.
And we are still able to see the app.
And of course if I do console log user just like before you're not going to get all on the first attempt.
We are still getting the information because I am blocked and right now.
So now every time we render our application we will have a user prob with no.
If we don't have a user or with all the data of the user.
And right here we are rendering our app.
So what we can do we can pass the props just like this props and whenever we rendered component route
which is this one we can pass a new prop with the user insights inside.
So I'm going to say that that prompts.
Now if I go to route and I go right here at the bottom and I do console log props and let me make sure
to Liddie the console right here.
Let me fix it or go.
I going to save the application.
The application will reload and we are getting this user prob..
And this comes from route's ride from this prompts.
And with all the user information right here if I log out when we do log out we get log out successful
and the user is equal to no.
So now inside routes we have the ability to check if we do have a user or we you know we don't have
an user.
So now what are we going to do.
We're going to create a new place a new endpoint and there are there are there are very different ways
of doing this going to show you this right now and the next project on the next one or the third project
we will do pretty much the same thing.
But on a different way.
So what we will create.
It's a place where we can check if we have a user.
And if we do have a user we will send the user to Dasch where we can and let the user end.
But of course if we don't have a user we will not we will kick the user out to a different place and
maybe not dashboard maybe the sign or something else.
So for this we need to create two different components one for private drought's because we have private
routes just like this one.
But we have other routes which are public that anyone can enter this route.
OK.
So first we need to create a place where we are going to be hosting this files.
So I'm going to go to component's new directory and I'm going to call out routes routes just like this
out routes now inside out Froude we have two different things the private routes and the public routes.
So the first file is going to be creating it's private and then routes Dodge's and him first we're going
to do the private then we're going to do the public because the private is less code.
All right.
So now we're going to go right here at the top and import private riped from.
And of course components for slash our throats for Slash private Droughns.
All right.
So now the logic is that instead of rendering this route from Briac rounder we will render a private
round and this private route we will send all the probs with the user and all the properties we need
to render a route and we will send this route on a different route.
All right.
So I'm going to go right here right.
And I can say first I want to render a private route.
Everything is going to fail right now.
I'm just going to ride everything all the things that it's need.
So private routes.
Right.
OK.
So I'm going to open and close Macinnis self-closing tack.
Now what we need to pass to this component because it's going to be just to function we need to pass
the props we get from the parent component.
This case going to open and close and say Dad that Dad props right.
The next one is going to be the path where we want to go on this route.
So the path for this one will be dashboard just like this one dashboard.
All right.
What else do we need.
Remember that we are getting in on this routes we could use exact.
So I could use it right here on a normal route.
So I'm going to still use it right here.
Going to tell you why in a minute and notice that right here we have a component.
So we still need to pass the components just like this.
And I'm going to delete that dashboard route.
Of course if I reload the application nothing is going to really happen.
And if I go to dashboard of course it's going to fail.
Right.
We get a big fat error message.
All right.
So now this function this component needs to take all the props.
We are passing and evaluate if you're going to let the user end.
All right.
And it's going to be exact not exact or so inside private route.
We're going to go to private drought's.
We need to create re-act stateless components just for now and are going to change the capital piece
for that it's going to be private routes
OK.
So if you remember on this private drought's we're getting a lot of props.
Now I'm going to make use of these structuring just like this.
They're going to bring it back just like this just to make some space.
Now what do we need inside of here.
What are we going to be bringing from props.
Well we're going to be using all the props pretty much.
But I need to change some names.
So first the first thing we're going to need you going to use from all the props we are getting right
here is the use of props we get from the parent.
So I'm going to go right here and say OK I want the user right.
So I have the user on a separate marble.
I can just say I make say user right here and we're going to be making use of that user object.
All right.
What's the first thing.
What else do we need.
We're going to need the component so I can say component.
OK.
I'm going to bring the component but I will change the name to come up later.
We will render whatever component we are passing right here.
Now I cannot make a reference to components.
I cannot do this because remember that to render a component we need a capital C just like this.
So by doing this the only thing I'm doing is just renaming components.
So now whenever we make a reference to component we need to do it like this.
So if I make comp it's going to be an actual component.
Right.
That's the second thing.
And then of course we need all the other props that path the exact and everything else.
So I'm going to do coma and we do dot dot dot.
They're going to say rest this rest could be whatever could be you know remaining or something like
that doesn't matter.
Just going to call it dressed.
So whenever we make reference to rest it's going to be the rest of the props that we are not bringing
in right here at the top.
All right.
So now we need to return something.
So what we need to return it's a rout.
Right.
OK.
So I'm going to delete this and I'm just going to say OK I need to return just to route just like this.
Now let me make it right right.
All right.
Just right now of course route it's reserved component from Briac router.
So we need to import it at the top so import route coma and re direct.
All right.
And it can be from re-act router Dom.
Later we are going to be using the redirect going to tell you how to use it resemble.
So now we are using a router.
So we need to return a route.
In this case of course we're going to be returning this one but only We're going to be turning over
this one.
If the users have authenticated or not so we need to do some checking.
So first I'm going to open it close and I'm going to pass the rest of the props into this components
I'm going to say Dot dot dot.
Rest.
Now if you remember the rest are going to be the exact the path which is the thing we need on routes
components and everything else that it's not component and it's not the user.
Right.
OK.
So now if you know with routes with this component from Briac rotor Domm we can say components just
like this and we instead of just rendering that component in this case that dashboard for example what
we can do we can return a function and that function needs to be returning a component.
That's why we do it like this.
All right.
So now this if you remember roud whenever we use a around inside Riak router re-act router will inject
a lot of props like the history.
Remember we do history that push now a lot of information so we can grab that props and this props are
from reac router not from our props right here.
So we can put them we can select them right here and get we going to be passing them to whatever we
are going to be returning right here.
Now if you remember right here at the top we have a user.
So what we going to be doing is just say okay if I have a user I want to return a components just like
just here.
If I don't how to have a user what I want to do I want to read direct user to and maybe the sign in
page and point no make sense sign and that's it.
All right.
OK.
So of course we need to do something right here.
So for now I'm going to I'm going to do this because I want to show you something else.
Comp There we go.
So now we're going to be doing of course if the user is not authenticated we can every direct user to
sign in.
If not we're going to render a component.
Now right here I'm making a reference to come up and come up.
It's equal to the component we are receiving as props from the parent.
And if I check the parent the component is going to be equal to.
In this case dashboard.
So comp it's equal to dashboard.
So it's just like we are pretty much doing instead of comp we are doing this same thing.
We are just changing the name.
So we're going to return a component get a graph all the props we get from re-act router This prompts
and begin to inject them inside of the component.
And then of course are going to be passing again that user and we are willing to do this.
But you know we might need the user information inside this component.
So of course if the user South indicate it will be we will be displaying whatever component we are passing
right here.
And with all the props inside and of course a user in the using information.
All right if the user is not antiquated and they are trying to enter a private route we will kick the
user back to sign an.
OK so let's test this.
Let's see if this works.
Right now I'm not allowed to dictate it.
So if I go to dashboard just like this it's getting us back to sign in.
So you know it's can work.
And if I tried to log in we're going to get kind of a flushing screen but that's OK.
For now I'm going to put password 1 two three log in we get the flashing screen but that's OK.
We're going to fix it right now so we get to go to dashboard and since we are authenticated it's letting
us go in.
So that is good.
Now if I do logout of course we go back to sign in and if I try to go to dashboard not happening.
Very very good.
So now what is the other problem and begin to go to the next section of course.
So we do have a private route so we are restricting private routes but some other routes are public
just like home and some other routes are public just like the sign in.
But we are not going to let the user go to sign in if they are already authenticated.
What.
What's the point of doing that.
So for this we need to create a different place called public routes and do some more checking.
All right.
So let's go to the next one and create the public of rights.