Write so let's create the public routes.
It's going to be pretty similar to private routes but with a little twist.
So inside out routes new file Pavlik and then routes that yes of course I'm going to import it from
here.
So even port Pawlick route from DOT for Slash components for Slash I'll throw out ans for Slash and
then of course public routes Burguet.
All right.
So we do pretty much same thing are going to start with home right here at the bottom public route open
and close.
So what we do we pass the props just like we did with the other ones which is past the props.
What else we need to be passing a path.
So I'm going to be passing a path and the path in this case is some doing home is going to be home again.
We pass exact and this is actually from Riak router and the next one is is the actual component.
So I'm going to copy component and I'm going to paste it right here at home.
I'm going to delete this.
I don't need this anymore.
Now I'm going to do the same and I'm going to copy the public route pasted the public out path.
It will be a sign and with an underscore and that component is going to be signed in.
And that is it.
So now I'm going to go to public routes and I'm going to create a re-act stateless component react to
stateless components.
Right.
OK.
I'm going to change the to capital P public routes and this is going to be pretty much the same with
private drought's.
I will need to import everything from Briac router you know route and we direct I will still need to
you know use some destructuring bring the user grabbed that component and rename it to come.
Same thing with it before.
And grab the rest of the props and at the end what we will be returning is just a rout.
Now this route will be injecting we will inject the rest of the Propst and then at the end we will re
return a component with a function.
Same thing we did before same thing nothing new so far.
So this one will be of course getting the props and injecting the props inside of here.
Now if we check the private sprouts The only thing with that is checking if the user eats authenticator
or not.
So now I'm just going to copy paste.
Now we have kind of a problem because we have a public route.
Right now we have a problem right here.
Doesn't matter.
So right now what do we need to do.
We need to return a component.
In this case we are not redirecting and that's why we are getting this.
So I'm going to go to come.
I'm going to paste it right here.
And what we want to return is whatever component we want to pass because it's a public route.
Anyone can enter this.
So come up opening close.
And we do dot dot dot.
Perhaps space and up right here we're going to delete that too because we don't really need to.
What I need is a user equals and then user.
And for now I'm going to do this because we don't need it.
All right.
So we get the comp we get the props we get the user that is OK.
Now of course everything works not going to really work but that's ok.
If I go to home.
OK.
We were able to go to home.
Now if I go to sign and sign in just like this we can go to sign in.
Now the problem is that after a user is locked in.
Right.
We shouldn't be able to go to sign in.
And this is what happens right now if I sign in put passport one two three and go to sign and we are
going to go to dashboard and if I go to dashboard we can enter but if I go back to sign and we can enter
too.
Now the problem is that the sign in it is still a private route.
Right.
It is still a that we are returning milk as white Nothing gets returned.
Return the sign in.
It's a private drought.
Only if you're authenticated right.
OK.
So we need an additional check right here to check if this route is kind of restricted are not.
So what I'm going to do.
I'm going to add one more problem.
Only two private two public routes are going to say restricted equals opening close.
And I will add a boolean.
So if I do falls it means that this route is accessible by anyone.
Anyone can access this whether they are Lagann or not.
But the other one is going to be true.
So if the user is signed in then they are not going to be able to see this screen to access this component.
They are going to go directly to dashboard.
So right now inside public routes we have the ability to check if we have a restricted or not restricted.
All right.
So I'm going to go to public routes right here and it instead of returning uster and then checking user
and just know I'm going to say rest because we haven't on the rest we have the prop inside breast.
I'm going to check for restrict it.
Let me just copy the name just to avoid any mistakes restrictive.
So if we do have restricted what are we going to do something.
If not begin to return to component right here again we're going to check if the user is south indicated.
So I'm going to say user opening close.
So if the user is both educated and going to do something if not I'm going to do something else.
Now if the user is authenticated I don't want the user go to log in to sign in.
I want them to go to dashboard so I'm going to use the redirect.
So he directs me to a drive and read direct and to.
And where are we going to be sending to dashboard dashboard.
And of course then because it if the user of course is not often think of indicated we're going to let
the user go to sign in because they are not authenticated.
So it's calm probs and user.
All right.
So let me let's try again.
All right we are signed in and so the application reloaded detected this and send this back to dashboard.
So it's going to this scenario.
It is a restricted route.
We are out we are authentic hate it and we go to dashboard and if I tried to go to sign in not happening
go to dashboard.
Now if I log out we are still able to go to sign in and if I go to dashboard we cannot go just of course
this is entering private routes section.
So if I log in again that that flashing that we were getting before not going to happen.
So passport one two three.
Logan and we go to dashboard.
What is happening is that whenever we see the application reloads of course it takes some time for this
logic to kick in.
So it's going to try to it we are logging in going to dashboard and says no you're not authenticated
yet.
It's going to go in back log in and log in says Oh you are authenticated right now so go to dashboard.
So this is what is happening just behind the scenes.
But we are good we are able to you know prevent users not that ticket users from going to administer
routes.
And you know and backwards with public routes.
So you know it's Scott so I'm going to skip this.
These state know this code.
The the state of our application right now and incipit going to added its resource in the section and
on the next one we will start with something new.
We're going to start with all the admin sections.
So let me show you this one.
So if I go to the dashboard we have matches we have at match and inside the same match we will be able
to edit the match or create a new match.
So first we'll start it start easy going to create the matches and point.
So we're going to get this from the server create a created table.
And if you want to edit we will be able to click on one get all the data from that ID from the server.
And you know pre-populated the the form.
Right.
So let's go to the next section and do the matches section.