Good so now we're going to create this is going to be the end point of mattress so we can you know check
the matches we have on the database.
If I go to the database and a little it's slow but it's OK if I go to the database.
Inside the data we are going to get matches.
So all the matches we have of course special properties away the thumbnail of the team that plays away
the date if it's final the local And you know everything else we're going to check this right now.
OK.
So first of course we don't have a component to render the mattress so we need to create it.
So are going to go to admen going to close the app are going to create a new directory inside admen
called matches.
Of course since this is an admin route I'm going to put everything inside admin and inside matches is
going to be the index of mattress Burguet.
Now of course this will be a class based component so re-act classmate component and it calls me admin
and then matches you can call this again whatever you want.
Since this is anatman route I will put admin at the front of it.
OK.
So we need a few things.
I'm going to import I'm going to import link just like this link from of course re-act rotor Dom from
re-act router Dohm.
Very good.
What else we were going to use that and mend layout.
We've been using you know the bar right here so we need to import it aswell.
Import admin and then lay out from that that force last deadly that force lashed out that force lash
and then of course it's going to be a for Slash at mean layout and a good copy the only out and put
it right here.
All right that is get so inside of this.
For now I'm going to say table instead of this we will create a table.
So this is the final one and this table comes from material.
I say it's real simple to do but we need to import a lot of things.
So my recommendation right now is for you to go to material you.
I go to component's demos and this is what I'm going to do.
Go to component demos and search for tables that would do it right now.
When whenever you go to tables of course you can get a lot of examples.
So we're going to use this one.
The first one.
If I open this they will give you the code of you know whatever is that you want to do.
And right here you can and you can get all the inputs.
So we need to type all of this so instead of typing.
I'm just going to copy from here.
He's going to copy.
Go right here to the top and I'm going to paste that you know.
Typing all of this.
Bar.
So we are going to use Table Table body cell held head row and paper and then we can to use something
else.
But going to do it later.
So OK so before we do anything we need to link this route.
This match's route two routes so lets go two routes and we need of course to import at Bin matches so
I'm going to go right here.
Import at men matches from DOT for Slash components that for Slash at men again matches.
And since this is the US there's no need to put index.
So now we need to create the route.
So I'm going to copy the previous route which is the private route.
This is a private route and I'm going to paste it down up here of course is that the component it's
going to be at mismatches and the location it's at Main underscore matches.
All right so if we go to our components I go to Dasch more.
I go to mattress and we get that table so everything works ok.
Of course now we're going to fix this now before we do anything in order to render the mattress.
We need to bring them from the database from mattress.
So again we need to bring the firebase database right here.
OK so I'm going to go back to matches and are going to open the firebase thing.
Now we do have a firebase matches so what we can do.
We can't just import it right here at the top.
There's no need to create a new a new of Barville for this.
So it's called firebase mattress participate firebase matches.
All right.
And it's from Dot dot dot dot for Slashdot for Slash and then firebase.
Now maybe you remember what we did at home that we were using that function we have an misc called firebase
Luper to get the data in the way we want and then we reversed the array.
Well we're going to do the same thing right here.
So I'm going to import import opening close firebase.
Luper.
I love that word.
I don't know why.
Maybe because of the movie and the reverse array.
Very good movie.
So from there of course that for Slashdot for Slash you I for Slash and then misc OK so pretty much
everything everything we need.
Of course whenever they could they can put in loads on the component amount.
After remounts of course we need to make a request to bring the list of matches.
Now I'm going to store everything inside the state after we get the data and I get it create two different
places is loading something like this which is going to be true and then matches are right and matches
is going to be just an empty an empty right now.
Of course since we can go to the database until we get the matches it might take some time maybe a seconds
maybe milliseconds depending on firebase.
So what are we going to do.
We're going to check right here.
If everything it's loading it's loading the matches and we will just call this play a progress bar.
And of course after we get the matches we're going to clear the state of it's loading to falls and we
will remove that progress bar.
So if we go to materials I and we go to progress we can get something like this so we can use this in
our website.
So let me open this.
So what we need to import.
It's circular progress from matyr core and everything else.
So I mean to copy and paste it down here.
All right.
So now I'm going to go at the bottom and I get to say OK I'm going to create a div and add a class name
just like this.
Of admin progress.
Write correctly.
Progress.
OK so instead of the progress we need to check if we are still loading if the state is slowing so does
not state that is loading.
If we are loading which is true we can display that progress.
If not you're not going to do anything.
Just an empty empty string could be Nouel doesn't matter.
OK so I'm going to copy that circular our progress and put it here.
Now we have some props we can be.
We can pass to this component.
Either way if I go right here we get something at least.
But we can pass some Starling's we can modify that a little bit more.
So I want to change the thickness so thick ness just like this.
And for this one we can pass a value from zero from 1 to 10.
I'm going to use 7 which is pretty thick.
Ok then we can stay a style the color.
So I'm going to say style equals opening close and say color.
Then make it right.
Color equals to that light blue.
We have on the website so 9 8 see 5 9.
It's the same blue we have on the top.
Light blue and there we go a little bit nicer.
All right.
So now let's fetch the things from the server.
Did the teams so just like with it before.
We're going to go to the component did mount opening close and after everything mounts we get a call
that firebase firebase matches just like this.
We're going to bring the ones and we're going to bring the value of course this will return a promise.
So we will grab that then.
And just like with it before it will return something.
And what's it going to be returning is the snapshot now again once we get the snapshot the information
we need is going to be inside a snapshot that BOL and we need to use the firebase Luper to get the data
inside of a normal array.
So going to create a variable called matches just like this and this one is going to be equal to firebase
Luper and I'm going to bring this snapshot and convert this.
All right.
So after we do this we have the match's information in the way we want.
So what we do we do this that set stayed open and close and we're going to change this state of loading
two files so we can remove that progress and begin to say that now matches equals two matches.
But the thing is that we need to change the order we need to use that reverse array just like with it
before at home.
So reverse array equals to this.
No matches equals to reverse array.
And then matches.
OK so now I'm going to go to the render and do console log just to make sure that we are getting all
the data we need.
There's that state BRIGADA going to reload the application and after a while we get the we get the you
know we remove the the progress bar.
We check the state.
We do have all the matches.
So you know it works.
So now what we need to do we need to add to table this table.
All right it's going to be simple but now that's simple because we need to type a lot lot of things.
So I'm going to go right here after the first I've been lay out I'm going to remove the console log.
This we don't really eat it.
And inside the layout will just pretty much wrap everything in a dish.
So I'm going to say Divx open and close and I'm going to put the diff at the ends.
All right.
Now inside the first div we need to create the table so I'm going to start with paper and this of course
everything is on the documentation of material you I first are going to wrap everything in paper right.
Not real paper.
Then we do a table opening close.
Right.
So what do we need first.
We need the table hetter you know the table head just like a normal table.
So table head opening close and then I'm going to put all the head and the heads inside.
Now inside the table head we need to create a table row.
All right.
Open the table road and we will put all everything inside.
So what we need to add is going to be the date that match the resoled and then the final are still getting
something.
All right.
So for each we need to add a table cell just like this.
Open and close the first one is going to be the date.
Then me make it right.
Date.
We need a table.
We need to match.
We need the results.
And then the final.
OK.
So it's match then resold and then final.
All right.
So OK so if I have the obligation.
That's nice.
OK.
So now what are going to be doing is pretty much adding the content.
You know the table body.
We have table we have table head.
So after table had it's table body body.
There you go.
So now inside of the body pretty much we need to add a row but each row is going to be the match they're
going to be the matches.
So for each row we add a match.
And for this we need to loop this that state that matches remember.
All right.
So I'm going to close this so I can make some space and I am going to start writing some logic.
So we just need to loop something so this that state that matches if we do have matches then we're going
to move forward.
If not are going to remove I'm going to return.
No all right.
OK.
So instead of here if we do have matches what do we do we loop something.
So I'm going to loop this.
That state that matches just like this.
That map opening close and we will be using two different things.
Which is the match and the each situation.
And of course we will return some GSX at this.
All right.
Again we need to return a table row.
Open and close and do it correctly.
Table row and inside of course the table Rosens we are looping something we need to pass a key.
So it's going to be key off and the iteration number in this case.
Now on each part on each cell we need to pass a table cell and just going to copy this one and I'm going
to say table cell.
So the first one is the date.
So we're going to mix a space and say match that date.
And this of course comes from the server.
You know we get to date.
So that is cool.
What else what else do we need to do.
We need to add a new table cell.
This one for the in the match you know the match.
And this one is going to be a little bit different.
Now the thing is that what I want to do whenever you find one if I click and this match is going to
take us to match and the ID of the match.
All right.
So so of course this is the edit section of the of the match.
We don't have that yet.
We're going to create it later but for now we're going to leave it ready.
So first I want to create a link.
Again it's not doing the out to complete the task.
I don't know why.
So the link of course we need to pass the two so to opening close and we'll be using template strings.
So we need to CO-2 at men then matches.
We didn't have this right.
So the edit underscore match and then forced laugh or last four slash.
And the idea of the match which is match that ID.
Of course we didn't have this component or route we're going to create this much later.
And of course we need to add the team that plays away.
So match way everything is on the Jason and I going to add a strong just like this strong and a dash
in the mill.
And then of course we need to pass the match that local.
And if we check it go get it.
And of course if I click on this we go to matches at that match and the ID of the match.
All right.
So everything so far so good.
So next next it's going to be the result.
So this one looks just like this one.
We don't have a link on this one.
So it just will create a table cell table cell and make some space.
So on this one we will output to match dot resoled and then away.
And again we will do this strong line just like this and we'll say match dot and the result and then
of course local.
All right.
That is get and if you were the application were simple.
Didn't put much thought on this one.
This is one.
This is just something very very simple.
We're going to spend a lot of time doing the edit match and the match.
Of course that's I believe that it's what you care the most of the section.
All right.
So what else instead of matches.
I go instead of after and the result which is this when we get the final.
Now on the final show you the original one and find one you get the red with the final.
If the game was already played and the game that was not played of course we get a green and nothing
on the result.
So we are still getting anything.
Nothing on there were sold.
That is good.
So now I'm going to go and create a table cell.
And this is the last one.
The last thing we're going to do and this component going to makes in space and I need to check if the
match final is equal to something if you check the database we don't have a boolean.
We have a yes or we have a no.
So I'm going to check.
Match final match dot dot final it's equal triple equal because we are matching everything.
Yes and if it's equal to yes we're going to do something or do something else.
So right here we will return as Pan non-test Pam as Pan.
There we go with the class name off matches then tack then red.
This is the red one and this one should be same final.
And then the other one it's pretty much the same thing.
But of course with a different closet a different text.
So which has returned his pen which match tock and then green and not played yet
yet there we go.
All right let's see how it goes.
So get you know looks nice really simple but looks nice.
Now the important thing about this is that now we can click on it and click on something and go to Edit
match.
And this is what we're going to be doing on the next section.
Right.
So everything it's done in this one is going to give you the code just for the you know the code of
the our application to this point because an edit match we can spend a lot of time.
All right.
So let's go to the next section.