OK so now we get to create the edit match.
This is the final one so we will grab the ID from the route from the right here the L and we going to
bring this from the server and populate everything.
Now we're going to spend some time because we have a lot of inputs.
You have a lot of fields and of course we need to do a lot of checking and you know it's going to take
some time.
So if you want to get a coffee go and get a coffee maybe some cookies too.
The cool thing about this is after we create the edit batch we can it create we can use the same disks
same exact exact components same file to add a match or to edit a match.
It's going to be the same file.
So again we are just doing two components on one.
All right.
So first thing first if I click on this we don't really have a route for this so we need to create a
file and then a route.
So I'm going to go to matches and first I'm going to create the file.
So I'm going to call it at edit and then match something like that.
You can use whatever you want.
And of course it's going to be re-act class based component.
Oops sorry.
There we go.
And I'm going to change the capital a to a very good so at it.
Matt For now doesn't matter.
OK.
So I'm going to go two routes and of course we need to put around for this.
So import and edit match.
And it's.
It's going to be from opening closed that for Slash components for Slash.
We get the atman for large matches for Slash and add and match.
And the route pretty much what we did right here just going to copy admen matches and of course we need
to add more things.
So we have two different routes.
In theory we have the added patch and then we have the edit match by id the edit match is just going
to be the at match and you match.
So we are still entering edit match of matches.
But this time it's going to be forced let me do it right here for Slash.
Then we access edit then match.
And if you check the your L after edit match we get the ID.
So to pass dynamic IDs to to the to the re-act router we do for Slash and we need to use the colon and
then keyboard which is going to be the ID.
Right.
This is the way we catch you know dynamic values on the you are allied with reac router and of course
we need to pass the correct component added match.
So at the closes at match.
All right.
So in theory if I go right here you can enter this round and of course we get nothing because right
here we have nothing.
So we are loading the correct route.
OK.
So on a match we need to bring some things first we need to import the admin then lay out just like
this.
Been been layout from DOD for the DOD for Slash one more and one more.
And HBO sees an admin layout.
Of course we need to wrap pretty much everything on admin layout and if it were load we get the bar
and at match.
Very good really easy.
Now of course we going to be working with forms.
So it's import and we will will bring for form just like this and then field I believe I call it fields
or fields.
I'm not really sure.
Let me just double check form fields and we bring form field Singler form field.
From that that force lasht that out for Slash.
And I believe it was you I for Slash and then form fields.
What else.
Remember we use to validate.
So we bring Baali date from DOT for Slashdot dot for Slash you I for Slash misc.
And then of course we need to bring firebase but begin to do that much much later.
So far so good.
Okay.
So now of course we need to handle the form through state and we can get a lot of things.
And I can explain you as we go.
So first whenever the application loads we need to check if we do have an ID it right.
If this is an edit or match so we could get a match ID so I'm going to create a state of match ID.
Of course this is going to start empty then we're going to get this much much later.
Now this form could be add or edit.
So we need to know what form type.
So after we know the form type we can store it inside the state just like this.
And of course then we get the form error.
Just like before which is going to be false and then we're going to get a form success just like before.
Same thing we did before which is going to be empty.
And I got to add one more teams.
Why am I am adding adding teams.
OK.
If I go to the final one on the EDID match whenever we have to select a local in a way we have a list
of all the teams in the league.
Right.
So we didn't have that.
We didn't have that and we're not going to manually at this.
So what we're going to be doing we're going to be fetching this from the server because we have it right
here.
So teams and begin to fetch all the teams with thumbnail the short name and everything else.
So of course beginning whenever we fetched a list of teams we're going to store them right here because
we are going to need them.
OK.
They're going to do.
Oh sorry.
I'm going to do coma.
And the next thing is to form data just like this and no capital formed data.
This is going to be an object with many many objects inside.
All right.
That's good.
I'm going to say.
So the first thing we need is the event date and we're going to do it step by step no input by input
because they are kind of different so the first one is the date.
So first we say don't open and close.
We pass an object if you remember we use the element just like this element open and close and other
other think about it while typing all of this over again are going to go to a place maybe the sign in
where we have this logic inside the state that's called sign index.
I'm going to copy this one.
Now there's no need to type everything we just need to change some things.
So this is going to be date.
The element is an input the value is empty and the config of course is going to be different.
The name is going to be date input.
That type is not an email is going to be a type of date and I'm not going to use a placeholder right
here.
It's not going to use it.
OK.
Now there's one more thing.
If we check the final one we can see that we have event date right here.
Right.
And I don't want to add that tag this event 8 whenever I declare the form field right now because we
need to do everything manually.
What I can do I can add a label property just like this and say that the label for this one event date
just like that this is a title Elater I could add to this a property called Show level.
So then we can evaluate if this show labels true or false so if this is true we're going to create a
label and add it to the form fill with it.
With this we don't have this behavior right now that's at.
Why not.
So we can actually see it.
So inside form fields of course right here we could check we could ask if we do have a form a show label
of two.
So are going to go and say OK do I have a form or form data form data that show level just like this.
And let me double check.
I will leave show label capital L..
I'm going to change his show label a show label of true.
Yeah.
OK.
So if we do please show a label.
If not.
No.
All right.
So what I'm going to do I'm going to just put a div with a class name off label input that exists label
input and he sort of hear whatever I have.
I get inside a conflict that level.
So I'm going to say open in close form data dot config dot levell.
All right of course we need to add this form field.
So I'm going to go back again to look in design and Im going to copy that impaired form field.
And we don't need any anymore for now.
So I'm going to go to an edit match and of course we need to do something a little bit better with this.
We need to add the title and everything else so for now we're just going to put it right here.
And then of course we can modify it.
So it's going to be date and this one date.
All right.
So if we check our code we get cannot read probably elements of undefined for data that elements AK
I may have made a mistake on this one.
All right sort of for that.
Actually everything was OK.
It was kind of weird.
I just removed that copy and paste it again.
It was working.
Sometimes the editor they add some strange characters and sometimes it doesn't works it doesn't work.
So you know that's kind of shitty behavior but it happens.
So it was OK.
So instead of Leavell input right here it's legal in it's script for that.
I'm going to reload the application and we get to the end date.
And of course we can enter a date.
And of course if we select the dropdown and this is the default behavior of the browser we can select
the date Burguet.
Of course right here this form field needs to be inside inside of a form and everything else so we're
going to do that right now.
For now just going to copy and remove it.
Going to add in a minute.
So we're going to add a dev off class name opening close.
And I look at this.
This class is at it just like this match underscore dialog dialog and then wrapper right.
We have an H2 tag which is pretty much the title and this one is going to be that this state that form
type.
Right.
Because if we go to EDID match this one the title should be added.
But if we go to add should be at.
So right now I'm going to put it right here.
It's going to be this that state that form type.
We didn't have that form type but we will get it in a few minutes.
Don't worry.
So of course out of here we need to add a div with the form inside.
So we're going to go and say form open and close Burguet.
Now the form just like before we have an on board note on men.
So the answer met and we did this many times before we have an event.
Events right.
Right.
Correctly event.
And then of course we run a function which is called this dot I've met form you can call this whatever
you want.
And of course we pass the event right.
There we go.
So now we can add our date wrapper.
Now a date field so date.
Very good.
Going to reload it and.
OK.
We get the data and it's pretty much similar Burguet.
So what else then instead of a date we need a local with all the teams and we're going to populate the
teams at the end after we have it pretty much the whole form.
So OK so now let's do it let's do the teams right.
OK.
So I'm going to go at the top just here date and I'm going to bed all the teams are going to copy date.
I guess I don't want to write all over again.
Can I copy and pasted at the bottom.
All right.
So this one instead of teams which just not teams is the local team.
Now the local and then the result we need to add local the first input is going to be local so local
instead of a on an input is going to be a select.
We didn't have a select.
We're going to create it right now.
So the config on the label could be on a no select just like select a local team.
Anyways it doesn't it doesn't matter.
Not going to use a local team the name.
Select local or something like that.
I don't know local the type is going to be a select and much much later we will load the list of teams
right here.
So I'm going to be adding on options and of course now when we create in select dynamic input we will
feed the options.
All right then the validation is now going to be e-mail true is going to be required and forgot to remove
it from here.
And we have you know just required is going to be bad and falls by the nation and everything else chose
the same.
But the show labeled this time is going to be false.
All right.
Now of course if we make a reference to this and if I copy this and paste it at the bottom and put a
local just like this and then look hole at the bottom I reload the application and nothing really happens.
And it's because on the form fields on this component we didn't have a select type.
We need to create right now.
So let's go to the next section and add the select form field.