OK so let's add the select type to form fields so we need to go to form fields and we need to add a
new case.
Brian Right now we just have input type input case.
Right.
So case open and close.
And then this time we need to put select or row of course we do a column and never forget to do a break
right.
So inside select just like with it before we select the form table for template and then this is equal
to you know some GSX code.
All right.
So the GSX code of course we need to put a div and things just like with it before right here.
And the formula all going to be the same song and it copy the form level and I'm going to paste it down
here.
There is no need to you know type everything again.
So after this we need to put this this is going to be select just like this.
And of course opening close.
Now under select Of course we need to pass the value and the On Change just like with that right here
and there is no need to put the config right now on the Select because we just add value in on change.
All right.
So form data equals Tuvan the value is going to be equal to form data value and the onchange event is
the same onchange event.
Now the only difference right now is that inside of select We have options.
So OK so the first option is going to be always the empty so option equals of sorry.
Option value equals nothing.
And this one is going to be the default one.
Select one.
And of course on this one you can do whenever you want.
You can put a default.
You can put you know maybe not one with the value but a disabled one.
This is completely up to you.
Now the important thing is that the next options are the ones that are going to be rendered.
Depending on what we have inside the options right here.
So what we need to do we need to enter that form data.
Dot com fiqh dot options dot and we need to do a map.
And of course I'm going to say item because on each iteration we will return some GSX and what we will
be returning is just an option.
Just like this opening close with the key.
Remember to add a key if not begin to get no 50 are warnings so item that key.
Because we do get a key from the server.
And of course a value so value equals item dot key.
All right that's good.
What else.
We have the item value.
So the value again is going to be the key which is the actual ID going get to see it later.
Don't worry.
So item that value which is the name of whatever we want to input.
Now with data from the server in this case the teams comes in a weird way.
So whenever we fetch this we need to modify it to fit this description to have a key and a value.
Now the key could be whatever on a D.
Or maybe the same as the value depending on what we want to use.
But we only passed two form config options to this property.
A key and a value.
All right.
Again we will see this later.
At the end of the input we have a show error so at the end of the Select we will get the same thing.
Now if we check our components of course cannot read property map of undefined.
Because of course we don't have anything on the other option.
Right now we don't have anything.
So inside the option actually options options that we get.
Anyways we shouldn't be getting anything at all.
At least we didn't get an error.
So we get the first select one so that is OK.
So now for example and let me just give you an example.
I have it ready right here.
I'm going to show you just give a second or second so there we go.
At the end when we get the teams going to get something like this this is an example from a different
input the way.
So we have a key you know an array of objects with a key and a value.
In this case yes but for now we have here we are getting good teams.
So it's going to be the name of the team or the ID right.
And then of course the name of the team which is always a key and a value.
This could be whatever name.
This is completely up to you but if I save this and go to our application then go we are going to get
this populated with just yes and no.
This is the body you and whenever we select that we select that the key of course everything fails because
we don't have the update form function but begin to be adding this later.
Of course we don't need this later we are going to populate this options with the actual teams.
So now we're going to be just going to just move forward.
Now we need to add the select one and then we can get the results.
You know when you we typed a number right here it's going to be the result so we're get to need to do
that.
Let's do it right now.
The result is just an input.
So I'm going to copy the date property right here and paste it at the bottom.
All right so the result is going to be for the local So this is local.
So the key value for this result and then local right.
So the element is going to be just an input just like before this one.
Result local local and the name lits.
I don't know resoled underscore local input make sense now.
The type is going to be a text validation just required the botted false validation message empty.
And we want to hide that label false.
So now we have the local and the resoled local because it's going to be this one and then the value
of this one and we have kind of a special layout right here.
So we get a need to do it.
OK so I'm going to go at the bottom I'm going to put this make some space and begin to create the layout
for this.
So it's very simple and begin to use it later as well.
So dev open and close the class name is going to be.
Select just like this select underscore team and then lay out any set up here.
We will add that level manually.
That's why we put a show label of false.
So class name label inputs or inputs.
There we go and this one is going to be local Ryan.
Then we have the way which is pretty much the same thing we are doing right now.
So then dev will add a class name of wrapper and inside of the wrapper we have two sections.
The one in the left and the one in the right you know left and then right.
All right so the first step inside the wrapper has a class name off left so left and then of course
we have the right one which has no class in this case so the first field is going to be this one form
fields Burguet the first one it's going to be the local right that we need to add the other one which
is the result.
And salt local So its result and then local and this one resoled local same.
Same name has to match name and one more thing.
This key This name has to be the same one we have on the database.
So if you go to players it's resoled local capital L because if we change the names right here later
when we send the data to the database the information to the database we will have to rename all the
tax to match.
This one's all right.
So if I save it and check a check file you're going to get it no local.
And then you know right here.
The actual value.
All right let's get.
So now we need to do the away I go to this one.
We have a.
Which is pretty much the same thing.
All right let's do the away one and again same thing.
I'm going to copy local and we sold local.
Just going to copy everything and paste it down here at the bottom instead of local.
It's going to be a way.
And the other one resold away right away.
So this actually was the difficult part of this.
Now everything is going to get a little bit easier.
So I'm going to go right here.
Copy this one.
Paste it at the bottom and instead of local a way forfeit from field away.
All right.
Same thing right here.
And on the result local It's going to be resold away.
Same thing here away whoops result away or so my reload the application we get local in a way.
All right.
So everything for now it's ok.
After a local New way we get the information of the you know the referee which is just an input text.
The stadium again impot text.
And then of course we get the team we solve.
So let's do the referee referee and the stadium.
And those ones are going to be really really simple.
There are Cheston pretext they're going to copy the date they're going to trim this because these are
competing too much space and I don't like it.
So after we sold away we have the what do we have.
The referee was the stadium.
We have the referee.
OK.
So it's going to be referee just like this referee.
And again it's just an empty text so input instead of event date.
I could put I a referee makes sense.
All right.
What else.
Referee input.
And the type is going to be in a type of text validation.
It's required to be not required doesn't matter and the show Leavell and this one is going to be true.
Then we have the stadium.
So I'm going to copy the referee and paste them here and say it's Tatum.
All right.
So again on the stadium.
Same same logic stadium instead of referee impaired stadium.
The type of text and everything else is just the same.
Very good.
So now let's create the levels for this.
So.
I'm going to go at the bottom right here and we are almost done with this.
And if you notice the final one has this line.
So this one it's wrapped in a diff.
So Dev and class name off split or split fields.
All right sort of here again.
Copy the form field.
After you read the first once everything else is just a little bit easier just the way it works.
So if you ask me what is the thing I hate the most about you know being a developer.
It's forms.
I hate them I don't know why but they are so useful.
And of course if you get a kind of I like let me copy this one into the stadium.
If you get kind of like a project where the user needs to buy something on e-commerce then you can do
a lot of form fields stadium.
Very good.
All right.
Almost done.
Referee and of course we need to change this.
So I made a mistake right here.
It's going to be stadium.
All right.
So referee and the stadium.
Very good.
There it is.
We are not doing the right here.
The place holder.
We could totally do it.
No problem.
So what is next.
We have the team with salt and the detail in the game played.
So this one's our select.
So we need to do something else with this once stew the last two which is which are the results and
the game play you know the team was sold and played very good.
So they are select.
So I'm going to copy maybe the local which it's a select syndicate copy this one trim it again and trimmed
the referee and the stadium and go to again right here.
OK.
So this one it's result.
So again it's going to be a select and instead of this team result or results no result.
So right here select local No select result and it's going to be a select require true validation falls.
And I do want to show the labels are going to say true.
Now on the options what we need to do we need to pass some options like Tim resoled so win lose draw
and not available.
So why are we doing none of evil.
Maybe this game the one we are entering right now.
It's in the future so when the team never played this game so the info it's going to be not available.
So we are going to be passing four different options with the key just like I told before with the with
key.
And of course of value just like this in this case devalues the same name that the key.
So of course we get when it's coma we get loose we get a draw and then we get none of it.
Right.
So coma coma coma that we get lose lose then we get a draw then draw and then non available non available.
OK so let's make of revenants up you know this.
And it's going to be the same thing.
This we have a split field.
So I'm going to split split fields and this one says it's the last I'm going to add an additional class.
I'm going to skip the last line right here at the bottom.
So of course we get the same thing on this one.
For now I'm just going to delete it and this one it's the results I believe we call this results or
we sold.
Not really sure.
Result.
Very good.
So result and then result if we reload the application.
All right we get team result and then we win lose draw and none available.
Right.
So we have one more to go.
Thanks.
Luckily one more to go.
And it's the final.
Right.
So again same as result.
It copy in to trim and you're going to opes I'm going to paste it right here at the bottom.
Sorry for that OK.
So this one instead of result will be final.
Final.
All right.
Still select and then game played and game played like that.
So select is going to be you know maybe played select play type of select and the options are going
to be a little bit different.
I did a little bit different.
Now it's yes or no.
So the key the first one it's yes and devalue.
I'm going to choose.
Same thing as could be an ID maybe a zero or a true or false.
But to keep it simple I'm going to put just yes or no.
All right OK.
We're almost done and we are still showing the level just like the other one.
So I'm going to go right here at the bottom and select the form fields.
And this one it's final.
Final.
And then finally again.
All right.
So let's see.
So we get team results with yes and then yes and no forget.
So everything works.
Of course we need to add a Bunim.
So let's do it right now before going to the next section.
And I'm going to add all the things because we can it did this.
So first we have the success level remember.
So we're going to do class name success underscore label and on this one we can output whatever we get
back from this.
Does that state and I'm going to close this go from this dot state DOT form success.
All right what is next.
What happens if we get an error.
Of course we're going to make a reference to this that state that form error.
All right.
And if this is true we're going to output.
You know maybe with an error so we're going to say Divx opening close and class name of error.
Levell I know that this is rather boring but we're almost done.
So close to finished this part.
The next thing is going to be a little bit more entertaining.
So wrong.
Right.
And of course we get no errors.
We're not going to display anything at all.
Now we need to add a button and this one it's a little bit different.
I'm going to wrap this up on a dip so adman underscore so met.
This is the class of course.
Inside we add a button.
All right we need to add an unclick so on.
Click.
Just like this.
And what we will do the same thing then before we need to catch the event event and then does that submit
form and we pass the event.
We didn't have this function of course and instead of here.
We need to output our team at match or edit match.
But we don't know that yet.
So for now we're just going to put this state that form type OK.
Of course we are not going to get anything on the button but we will get something at least.
OK.
Let's get everything ready.
Now on the next section what we will do.
It's the you know the interesting part of this.
This is not interesting.
But on the next one we will go to the server fetched a list of teams feed them right here then we'll
get the idea you know this entry we will populate all the fields you know everything that we need to
do.
All right.
So let's go to the next section and try to finish this.