All right so now let's create the logic for populating all the data we need right here including the
list of teams.
So now if I type something the application breaks because we didn't have that update form elements that
update form for a function we have an other component so I'm going to go to sign in and the update form
for this one is going to be the same block same logic same same thing.
So I'm going to copy this from here.
I'm going to go back to edit match and paste it down here.
All right.
So now the application will reload and if I type something at least we don't get any errors and we are
able to update this correctly.
But that is you know that's fine.
So now we need to populate the data the inputs with the data of the team.
And we need to bring the list of teams to the actual selects including local in a way.
All right.
So I'm going to go right here at the bottom and we need to do a lot of things.
So we need to first fetch the ID fetch fetch team for the team we have with this ID and only Of course
if we do have an ID.
So on the component that amount to opening close first.
I'm going to get the match ID so the match ID if you remember it's inside does that probs.
And we are using re-act router so we can access match we can access programs dot ID.
And of course if we do Konsole just like this console log and match ID we're going to get the idea of
this match.
So we get it right here.
So now of course if we go to Edit match we will get an ID if we go to match or edit.
And we want to add a match.
We will not have an ID.
So now we can we can check.
We know we can make a question to the application.
We can say if we do have a match do this.
If not do it do something else.
So if we don't have a match Id just like this.
What we will do we will create a function right now to add match.
So this is the form type.
This is the action we will create with this form will add and you match if not of course we going to
go and fetch all the data from this match ID we will enter the edit enter to the edit type of form.
All right.
How can we get the match from the ID we have right here at the top.
Real simple.
First of course we need to bring firebase.
So I'm going to go to firebase right here on the top and import import.
Open and close and we need the firebase matches remember and we need a few more things because we will
make a request to the teams who will need to make up requests for the teams and we didn't have this
on firebase so I'm going to go to firebase right here.
And inside firebase we will you know create something like we did right here with matches and promotions
to get the teams right.
OK.
So I'm going to create a new novel concept fire base and then teams just like this equals to firebase
D-B dot ref and then met teams.
So we have matches promotions and teams.
This is this is get of course we need to export this and we're going to export as well.
Is this firebase be.
Because we can use it in a few minutes.
So now we can import teams we can import matches and firebase DP.
All right.
So I to go back to an edit team and of course we need to require this at the top.
So first we have the teams fire base and then teams then we have the firebase Stevie firebase and that
D-B just like this.
And then the matches fire bays and then matches from Dadar for Slash.
One more time one more time and then firebase.
So then of course we need that firebase Luper from the you tale's firebase and then Luper from Dadar
force slash one more time.
You I for Slash misc.
All right.
So I'm going to go right here at the bottom where we actually make the actual request right here and
we need to use that firebase connector to bring the list of teams.
And right here instead of using firebase mattress I'm going to use firebase D-B because right now we
need to search by ID.
So if we use Firebrace D-B we can do DOD.
We can do ref and pass temp's strings say that we want to enter the matches for Slash and we want to
bring the one that has the match ID we want just like this and this much ID it's equal to this one.
So when this happens we're going to get this once we get to get value.
And then of course we get our response back.
So of course we will bring a snapshot just like before then we will run a function.
I'm going to host this snapshot inside of Orvil called match and we will you know I'm going to get the
bow out of this.
So snap shot that bow opening close.
All right.
Now I'm going to do the following console law match just to make sure we are getting the match.
So I'm going to go back in a little while we get know the the the actual match away away and everything
else.
All right.
So this is get we get the information about the match from the server.
So I'm going to delete this.
And what we're going to be doing right now we need to trigger a different function and this function
when it's going to be doing is going to go to the server fetch a list of teams and at the end at the
very end we'll take that I.D. It will take all the data we can about to match and it will populate all
the all the inputs right here dynamically.
All right.
So I'm going to call this function get teams.
So on this get teams for now it will not make any sense but I'm going to be passing two different arguments.
First it's the match right.
The all the information about the match and then coma and then are going to be passing added match.
So this is the type of the form.
And we're going to store this name later at the top on the state when whenever we have the form type.
And of course that it's going to show up on the title right here.
And on the bottom right here of course got teams is not to find me.
Mendus OK.
And this one as well the update for them.
All right.
So we don't have this function.
We need to create the function.
So first I got to say Konst get teams equals to a function just right now a function.
And we're going to do something.
Remember that this one will be receiving a match and a type.
All right.
So now instead of this one what we need to do is get the teams and I'm going to say get teams not team.
So on this one we can use firebase teams.
So fire base teams that once that value and then of course we get a promise back.
So the promise we'll bring snapshot we will open it close and run a function.
Same thing we did before.
Now I'm going to do Konst going to create a contest and teams equals two.
And remember that the information comes in a weird weird way.
So we would use the firebase Luper to get everything like we want.
Now I'm going to cancel all the teams we get from the server.
All right.
The application will reload and we get the teams.
I get a whole list of teams.
Let's get let's get now this teams.
If you notice they have the name a short name and a thumbnail and an ID of course.
And to feed this to the Select we cannot really do it like this.
Remember we spoke previously that we have a key and a value.
Let me just go back.
You have a key and a value right here.
So we kind of need to modify the list of teams and create a different rate which is the key which is
the name of the team and maybe Abbad you with the ID or maybe the same name doesn't matter.
So I'm going to go right here and say Konst and team options.
Options options.
Right.
So this team options is going to start as an empty array and then me to delete the consulate.
So what I'm going to do I'm going to enter the snapshot I'm going to say dad I'm going to do.
I'm going to use that for each.
We used to create firebase Luber same idea is out of here.
Of course we get a child oh child snapshot and the child snapshot we will run a function.
So what we will do will grab the team options and we're going to push a key and a value with whatever
we want.
This case I'm going to say we are going to enter that child's snapshot going to enter the bow and are
going to get the short name short name you could use whatever you want but remember that in future you
will need to you know change it and in real life in your application you can use the idea or maybe a
different field.
And in this one.
Oh sorry instead of team options is child snapshot.
And this one child snapshot that vowel and then OK we get again I'm going to use the same key you know
same short name doesn't matter right now just to make things a little bit easier.
So now if I do can log team options sorry team options.
What is happening team options.
We get the same thing but with a key and a value.
So this this list we get to be passing this list to local anyway so the Select can you know render this
options.
So now we have a lot of things.
We have the match which all the information about this match the type of the form we get the list of
teams unmodified from the server which we are going to need and then we have the team options which
are the options we need to pass to the selects.
All right.
So we have a lot of things.
So now we need to create a function that is going to be grabbing all the data that we really need and
populate all the data right here.
OK.
It's not going to be that hard.
So I'm going to create a function called this update and then fields something like this that fields
and I'm going to be passing the match I'm going to be passing the team option actually should be team
options team options.
All right.
What else are going to be passing the teams.
Teams we have right here the list up unmodified teams that are going to be passing the type we have
with the top so type.
And then at the end the match ID.
So we have a lot of information right here.
All right and all this is going to go to the state.
Now we didn't have this update fields function so I'm going to go right here the top create the update
Field's function.
And of course we're going to do something that's going to be real simple of course with the update fields
begin to receiving we're going to get be getting all this arguments doesn't matter.
You could use some magic if you weren't right here.
So first since I don't want to mutate the original state right now I'm going to create Konst new form
data.
Just like with it before and we're going to say data just like that and then dot dot dot dot state DOT
form data are going to make a copy of this.
Now I'm going to be looping all the keys inside the form data right here going to be looking through
state date local and everything else too.
You know populate the information I want.
So I'm going to go and create a for now for letter key in the new form data.
All right now if we don't have a match we can run this update fields whether we have an at match scenario
or an edit match.
So I kind of need to check right here if I do one to populate whatever I get from the match because
maybe sometimes I'm going to be running something going to be trying to update something.
And we don't have a match so we're going to ask first OK if we do have a match I want to update something.
So if we do have a match just like this I want to enter this new form data whatever key we get from
the 4 and change the value to whatever value it's inside the match.
And the same key remember that the Met the match comes from the server.
So it's if inside the match which is actual server.
Let me just show you a match.
You have a key that it's a way you know with the same key inside the form.
You can get the body of away and stored inside state so we can update state and the same thing with
with valid.
Can Change new form data out whatever key and then valid and invalid to true if not of course we can
get a validation error message.
Now there's one more thing on this process.
Whenever we are updating the information we update the values of the input elements of the data which
is an input.
But what happens with the selects what we we need to do is to of course we are up are updating the value
but we are not updating the options right here.
Me.
A lot of information we are updating the value but not the options.
And I can not do it right here because on some inputs they are text inputs.
They don't have the config that options that we have on the selects.
So I'm going to create one more if and this is going to is going to make sense.
Don't worry.
So inside if I'm going to check if the key it's triple equal to local and local We know that this is
a select and I'm going to put or me find it because this keyboard is a different key word or an or key
it triple equal to a way then we can add the options to the Confect.
Right.
So if you have a local We know that we need to put a list of teams right here and same thing on a way.
So I'm going to access new form data and whatever key I'm going to enter the config.
I'm going to enter the options just like this and this one we need to pass the team options right.
Not the teams.
This is an object the team in options we get the key and value and that's it.
If I cancel law and the new form data let me just open this
of course we get a date and the date notice that we have a do have a value and it's valid true.
And same thing for the referee.
We have a value.
That is true and for local For example we have a valid true value Manchester City which is the one we
have on this on this place.
And if I open the config we have the options with all the teams inside.
No really good.
Simple.
So now what we need to do we need to update state with this new form data.
But we are not just going to update the form data.
We need to update a lot of things.
So there's not set state opening close and we need to first update the match Id remember that we do
have match ideal.
Trim this at the top.
So I'm going to update the match ID then.
What else.
We have the we get the form type so we can to say form type form type.
It's equal to whatever we get on the type so form type is equal to form type.
So then we have the form data.
So form data it's equal to new form data and there would have been the list of teams.
Now the list of teams right now makes no sense.
We have teams right here with an empty array.
So we will pass the array which is the one that comes from the server and update that right now it makes
no sense but later we can use it.
All right.
So I'm going to reload the application.
We've already seen the result and we got the matchbooks because now we have a type.
The date gets pre-populated the local It's the mental City Select that Haddington town and get all the
other options.
And right now of course we can type something if we wish.
All right.
And referee we get the stadium the none available game played.
It's no.
So again we are able to update everything you know to properly populate all the information and we do
have an edit match because now we have a type.
Right.
You know this is get so.
So what is next.
What what are we going to be doing next.
Next is going to be editing the form.
You know maybe making some changes and submitting the form to you know update the the entry update to
match.
So let's go to the next section and do it.