OK so let's try to submit the form.
OK.
So I'm going to go to sign in and I'm going to copy this submit form function because most of this is
going to be the same.
So we love just on top of the render going to delay this other put it and to lead this for now.
And this one is going to be the same.
OK.
So what is going to happen to the forum something that before we prevent default we create a data submit
check if the form is valid.
And you know so on we can add that there's a couple of times already.
Now there is one more thing.
First I'm going to do a console log just like this and and.
What do we get on the data to submit.
All right.
So if by of course we get the information any file edit match you're going to get the data to submit.
It means that everything is OK.
We are not going to the error state which means that the form is not valid.
We get a valid entry you know Avali a key value pair and everything is good.
No everything is valid but we have one tiny problem.
If I go to the to the AM original database there is we have two different keys to two different properties
that we don't get right here by default.
So we have the local thumbnail and we have the A Whale away.
Thumbnail this once if we take a look at this.
We don't have the thumbnails and the thing is that whenever we select a team the thumbnails come from
the database from the database of teams.
So each teen team have a name a name a short name and a thumbnail.
So by default we don't add them here.
So we will need to do this right here before we submit the form.
Now where can we get the name of the thumbnail from the teams.
And remember we stored the teams right here at the top.
So this is what we're going to be doing.
We're going to try to grab the name of the team we are entering right here.
We're going to look to that database you know that state actually that array begin to match the name
and we're going to get the thumbnail from there.
And it's real simple we just need to run a for loop or submit form.
How can we do it.
First we need to enter the teams so this that state that teams Dodd and I are going to run for each
just like this for each opening close to each iteration we will get the team right open and close.
Now if the iteration and this team matches the team we have right here on the form for local and a way
we're going to get the top the thumbnail.
So I'm going to write just in a logical operation.
If so if the team right here this team the one on each iteration and then the short name it calls to
whatever we have on the data to submit that local remember that we are accessing local.
Then of course we're going to graph the data to see if med we're going to create a new imperf. which
is going to be local thumbnail.
You have it right here on the database local th and B.
Whoops sorry for that.
Go back.
So let me create it right here at the batch.
It's local t h m b and it's going to be equal to whatever we have on the team.
On each iteration.
For c th and B H and B.
All right.
And the same thing with the way.
So I'm going to copy this and paste it at the bottom and in this case a local is going to be a way on
the thumbnail.
Everything is going to be the same right here.
And the data just med is going to be a way thumbnail.
All right.
So now on each loop we an access we're going to enter to the submit and push this information we can
add this keys and you know this properties.
So now let me just reload the application if I go to Edit match and edit the match and inspect this
we get an a way thumbnail of Huddersfield because this is the name of thumbnail for this team.
This is the real name of team you know a little bit long.
That's why we have a short name and we have a local thumbnail for the local team.
You know they are different.
That's why we cannot use the original name because it might be different from the local thumbnail thumbnail
we have on the on the public directory.
So OK so now we have pretty much the whole data we need.
Right.
So now what we can do right here instead of doing a console log we can first check if you want to add
it to match or add a new match.
And I'm going to do if opening close.
So if this that state that form type is equal then edit match.
Remember we added this at the top added match.
Then we can enter the edit firebase logic and else we're going to add a match.
But we're going to do that later.
All right.
So I'm going to go right here and we're going to start doing the you know the pushing.
So firebase D.B DA that ref and we can enter matchups for Slash and the ID that we get on on inside
the state.
So this that state that match ID.
That's why whenever we populate all this information right here the update feels we are storing the
match ID right there.
All right.
Everything's cool.
So we are accessing the majority of course then we're going to get something and what we need to do
after ref is to use the update method.
They wouldn't give us update just like this.
We cannot go to them already.
We're going to be updating everything with whatever we get from data to submit an update data to submit
and then we will get our promise back.
All right.
And then of course we will get a response whatever response it doesn't matter right now.
And we will run something.
All right.
And of course if you get an error you can do the catch.
It's completely up to you.
And on the catch we get a no say form error success success for our troop just same thing are doing
right here at bottom from error.
It's equal to true.
So we can say do something it's wrong.
All right.
Now if we are OK I want to run a success form function so I GOING TO THE I'm going to do this.
That success.
Sess and then form they're going to be passing a message dated.
Correct.
All right.
Make sense.
So we don't have the success form function.
Going to add it.
Real quick right now.
It's a pretty pretty dumb function.
You're not going to do a lot of things on this access forum.
So the only thing we do here is just update state.
Right.
So this dot set state opening close and open again to save form.
Success is equal to updated correctly which is actually the same thing we are passing right here.
So I'm going to say message and form success is going to be equal to whatever we get from the message.
Now the thing is that after we get this message you know that everything was updated.
I want to clear that message.
So I'm going to add a set time out.
We kind of already did this in the past with a different component.
And I'm going to say this that state same thing we are doing here from success.
We set it back to nothing and I'm going to do it after two seconds.
All right.
So all of this looks nice.
This is pretty dumb but everything looks nice.
OK.
So I'm going to reload the application and I'm going to be changing.
I don't know maybe
the this one whatever Matthias blue I don't know an arena arena so we can actually see the change team
result was not played.
I'm going to say yes whatever doesn't matter.
They won and they're going to change that date to something else.
I don't know maybe yesterday doesn't matter.
Maybe a couple days ago.
Going to edit the match and let's see what happens.
We get updated correctly.
And if I go to the database the game was Manchester City and I gazed out of town or something like that.
So we get arena arena so that change was plied.
We get a result of when we didn't change the way we sold the way.
So everything is working we are updating everything correctly and the message goes away after a few
seconds.
So Goodman this works.
So now what happens if I want to add a match.
We're going to go right here.
Clay can match and of course we get nothing.
So we need to add a route for this that it's actually going to go to the same place in this but since
we don't have an I.D. instead of EDID match you're going to get at match.
And we are not going to pre-populated everything.
It's already on the functions and at the end when we want to you know submit submit something.
We're going to do something else right here because we are adding a match.
And remember as well that we want to change this a little bit because we don't want to populate everything
so we don't really have a match.
So if you want you can do it by yourself.
I'm going to put the code of everything on this section this resource so you can try to do it yourself.
It's not that complicated.
Right.
So if you want to do it good if not on the next section are going to tell you how to do it.
It's going to be really really small really short because we pretty much have everything we need.
All right.
So let's go to the next section.