All right so what is the first thing we need to add.
We need to add a route.
Right now we are going to the act we are specifying right here specifying that we want an ID whenever
we go to EDID match.
So in this case if we only go to private route and then of course just Ed match no I.D. We want to render
the match which is pretty much symp component.
So OK so right now we are just passing outmatch at a match.
And it's the same component.
We don't need to create a new component for this.
All right.
So I got to go to add.
Imagine going to reload the application.
And if I go to outmatch Well I'm try again.
Going to go to match and you know we can it get it like this.
Of course we need to do some more things right here.
I'm going to go to at match and remember that whenever we do the component that Mount we are running
some things we are getting the matches and everything else.
But the thing the thing that gets the matches and everything else in all the time all the time and everything
else is this and we are doing it right here.
But we are not doing it right there you know.
So we need to do it we need to trigger this get teams functions but maybe with different arguments.
Right.
So what we would do we would grab this get match get teams and I'm going to run it.
But this is going to be false just like this.
False and that type instead of added It's going to be Utt match.
Right.
So now we're going to go to this function and this function will do whatever it needs to do and it will
be passing this type and the you know and match.
And this is false and the type is going to be at match at match.
And if we go to update fields same thing you know we just update the state whatever we need to update
and from now does it.
Of course relo the application we get at match Nothing gets you know pre-populated.
The only thing we get is just teams.
And the other option is of course as well and we get the match as a button.
Right.
So now the only thing we need to do is to do the firebase request right here.
Or we go right here.
So if the form type it's at match we of course do this if not begin to push a match We're going to store
a new match on firebase.
All right.
So we're going to delete this.
We don't need it and we can use the firebase matches.
We have at the top of firebase and then matches that and to push new elements to kind of an array of
objects between coats I'm going to say push and what we push is whatever we get from data to submit.
And then of course we get a promise this when it's going to be real simple then.
And of course we do something.
And of course if there is an error we catch something.
So e open close if we have a there's that said State Farm.
True.
If everything is OK what are we going to do.
I'm going to say this that props that history that push open and close and we're going to go to forward
slash at matches men underscore matches so we can redirect the user back to the matches.
Remember the mattress is going to be this one.
All right so let's try and let's let's let's see what happens.
OK.
I'm going to select the date.
It's going to be today's date.
So it's going to be Brighton against Manchester City Of course.
So Brighton 0 Manchester City to the referee or whatever.
Marcus fried the stadium Shark Tank arena whatever the team were sold.
They won and the game played well.
Yes they played it already.
All right.
So remember Brighton Manchester City to nil and at a match.
We go back to the to this and we get Manchester City right on to new and it's a final it's final game
is final.
It's a very good man.
Everything works.
All right.
So there's no really really simple.
It took us a long time to do the at the edit match but you know it since is the same component and we
use the same logic.
Why not doing everything in one place and not creating two different files with pretty much the same
logic kind of make sense.
All right so now we have the matches.
The next thing we're going to be doing.
It's going to be the players you know add players and you know it's pretty much the same thing than
this one let me show you on this.
So we have players who have a list of all the players.
And then of course we add the players.
So the the impetus for this one the form can be real simple.
You know the name last name number and a position which is defense midfield or striker.
The interesting thing about this one which might interest you is the ADD file to store the file We're
going to upload a file to image the actual image to the hosting.
None of the storage inside firebase and that's going to be interesting.
So let's go to the next section and start doing the players section first and then we will go and add
players.