All right so let's keep moving forward.
Right now we only have matches and at match so we need to do pretty much the same process with players.
And then of course at players now add players it's a little bit special because we haven't done a lot
of inputs but we have an input you know upload image and we're going to be uploading images to firebase
distortion there for free.
But first we need to get the players.
So just like here we have a list of all the players and this comes from the database from the right
here database.
We have a place where we have all the players of me just show you of course you can go to your database
and check it out.
So inside teams we help players.
All right.
So OK so going to go back.
I'm going to go back to our project and of course we don't have a players and pointone going to go back
to our project inside admin to save players and this one just like the mattress will have an index that
Jay is going to create re-act class based component and the other one was at mismatches.
This one would be at player's right makes sense.
I mean players.
All right.
So now we need to import this round.
We don't we didn't have this round.
So we need to declare that.
So inside of routes we're going to go import at main players from that for Slash components at men and
then you know players since it's an index we don't need to bring anything.
Now we already have an index for Aben matches so I'm going to copy this route.
The closest I going to pasted right here are the top and I'm going to say are we going to use Disk admin
players component whenever we go to admin players.
Right.
So in theory if I reload the application and I go to players we get up pretty much nothing but you know
it is there.
Let me just show you just to make sure I'm going to remove the hair and get the players spoke out.
So I'm going to open this and I'm going to bring the index matches because you know what we're going
to be do around we're doing right here.
It's pretty much similar of what we did right here.
So I'm going to copy all of this because we are going to need the same same thing.
They're going to paste it right here at the top.
So again we're not going to be learning anything you write doing this right here so we're going to you
know just copy some things are going to copy this one as well.
The fire base and we're going to change something inside of there.
But we're going to change it in the nick of minutes and just like the mattress we see we have a state
and it's loading.
Sorry for that sorry.
I got a copy of the state and I'm going to do the same thing just paste it here.
All right.
What else.
We have a component did mount.
I'm going to copy the component mount and I'm going to put it right here.
We are now going to use this.
I'm going to delete it and do it again.
So.
OK.
So the first thing we need to do if we think about this is that we need to fetch the list of players
right here fetch fetched matches.
So right here we will be fetching the players.
Now we don't have a of fire based players.
We have a firebase matches.
So if you go to firebase we have firebase D-B matches promotion teams.
We don't have a reference to players.
So first we want to add it.
I'm going to do this and say Konst firebase.
And then players it calls to fire firebase TV dot ref opening close and I'm going to call it players.
Right now I'm going to export this so we can add it from different file.
All right.
I'm going to copy the name.
I'm going to go back to players.
So now instead of matches we're going to bring players real simple.
Now we need to pretty much do what we did on the other one.
So first we make a reference to firebase players than we do with the ones and we bring the value.
And of course then we begin to get a promise back.
So we open and close and we run something on this Colback you know this then we will receive a snapshot.
Right.
All right.
Snapshot just like with before we're going to get the information.
In a weird way from from firebase so I'm going to say Konst players and I'm going to use the firebase
Luper.
We had the top at this point at all this at least like I don't know three four times.
So this one should be very clear.
So we're not going to do this that said state opening close and we're going to say it's loading we're
going to change to it's loading we're going to add it in a couple of minutes.
We're going to set it to false.
And then of course since we have a list of players we're going to say I want a list of players just
like this.
And if we want it is completely up to you.
You can do the reverse array just like with that before you know there's no need to do this because
there is no date related.
But again we're just going to put everything Canfor backwards.
All right.
So I'm going to go right here and say console log is that state.
So if I loaded and I go to the console so we get OK so we get the loading.
Maybe the mattress does not right.
Made a mistake right here.
It's not mattress it's players.
Let me do it again.
And that's what you get.
You know my copy pasting.
So OK.
Players and we get the players know inside of the players on each player.
We have a Nimptsch going to see this why we're going to change this in a little while and then we have
the ID when they have the last name then the name the number and everything else.
All right.
OK.
You know that.
Let's get.
So am I going to close it for now and I'm going to go back here.
So we need to pretty much.
We need to pretty much create all the same layout with it with matchups.
Right.
We need first the admin layout so I'm going to copy of layout and no I'm going to do simple.
I'm going to copy this going to copy pretty much the whole thing.
Copy and paste it.
I told you we were not going to do a lot of things right here.
Nothing new.
So I'm going to copy and paste it right.
Of course we need to change some some things.
The properties are not the same.
We need to change the properties.
And of course the same thing with right here at the table head.
So first we get a first name.
Let me add it.
It's first and then name right.
Then we have a last name.
So last name and then we have a number what else.
We have a position.
All right.
So OK.
So if we go to the table body we're not going to be looping matches this this doesn't exist.
So we say players right here.
Does that state that players and we're going to map over the players and on each iteration we will be
getting getting a player right.
All right.
So what else we need to do quite a few things right here.
So on the table cell the first thing is going to be the first name.
So we don't really want a date right here so I'm going to do this and we're going to do it pretty much
all the other things because we are not going to use them to do something new here.
So inside a table cell.
What I want to do when you make a reference to the name and of course I went to add a link so we can
go to Edit the player.
So link to equals.
Open and close and they're going to close the link and I don't know why against knocking me out cause
you know to complete tag.
So link of course we can to beat up putting the player that name and the two and this one is actually
that we don't have so far.
It's going to be forward slash Ming underscore players players then for Slash.
It's going to be ad underscore players for Slash and we need to pass the ID.
So then on this component we can fetch the ID and you know make the changes so player Donte ID.
All right.
So I'm going to I'm going to copy this and same thing right here.
But it's going to be a player last name last name.
All right.
What else.
We have the player number.
All right.
This one is real simple.
Nothing special in this one.
We're going to say.
Player number and the last one is the position again nothing special.
Player and then position and that is it.
We're still getting the signal the progress is loading and everything else is just the same.
So if I save it I can reload the application.
And if we go to admin players and we are already at big players let me close the console.
We get it you know we get all of the list of players.
So the zent if I go to Sergio Aguayo admin at players and of course we're still getting the ID.
So now we're going to create this end point.
All right.
So let's go to the next one and start with the players.