OK so now we're going to create this now on the pre's one of the matches we did the at the edit match
because it was a little bit easier you know which is have some texts but if we go to players inside
players we have the last name the name the number the position and then we have an image and this image
this ID it's referring to whatever we have inside storage we will upload images inside storage.
But this doesn't exist in your storage.
I gave you a copy of this database which is a different database different firebase project they have
my computer where I have all the images inside.
And I cannot just give you the images you know like I meant just to give you a file so you can upload
images.
So we're going to create the file upload directly and then we will update all the players.
But first to do that we need a way of course to have all this functionality and to add a new player.
All right.
OK.
So we're going to do it.
We're going to do it in a kind of a backwards.
First the player and then the add and then the edit player.
All right.
So of course we need to do a lot of things right here.
A lot of things are going to be very similar to to EDID edit match pretty much similar.
But of course with some new things.
All right.
So first first thing first of course we need to create an endpoint where we can grab all this code so
that and then edit just like we did before at edit.
But this one is going to be players and going into the capital P makes more sense at a player's Dungey.
Yes.
All right.
We need to go to routes and the route to here.
So I'm going to import then add edit and then players from that forward slash components forward slash
admen forward slash players and then at added players.
Right.
So we need two main routes for this.
You know the players with the ID and the players without the ID just like with it and match.
So I'm going to copy this route and it closes and then paste this at the top.
Of course now the round it's not admin at mattress it's going to be players.
And instead of here we will do instead of added match we could do players.
Why not.
No again you can name this whatever you want.
Just going to name it at players the round on both could be added players in an edit match.
So this is kind of my mistake.
But don't don't worry.
It's pretty much the same thing.
So add players and the players with the needy and whenever we get this we will we will render the players
or of course nothing is going to happen because inside added players we don't have anything.
So we need to create a Riak class based component of course and it will be called at added players.
All right should be with a capital A.
My mistake again.
All right.
Inside players.
Going to do pretty much at the beginning.
What we did with added mench So we're going to go to and match pretty much copy all of this imports
right here just to save time and I'm going to paste it down here.
All right.
So we are still needing the lay layout.
We fill in the form fields we need to validate.
So that's you know Stace.
And then of course we're going to do something right here.
We will maybe need the Firebrace Luper maybe not.
I don't think we're going to use it.
And right here we are making reference to find the steam's.
We don't have teams right here.
It's just players.
So I'm going to bring bring the firebase them players you know the the export we created on the preview
section.
So players just like this we will use firebase TV and find mismatches.
And we are not going to use it.
I'm going to bring firebase just firebase because again we're going to do some weird stuff right now.
So if you go to add a mattress the first thing we have is this state the big state.
So we are not going to use a lot of this.
We're going to use a set of course but it's going to be pretty much it's going to be much shorter than
the other one you know the one we haven't at a match so I'm going to say first of course state we're
going to go here and I'm going to copy the first ones not the form data.
We're going to create this kind of a manually.
So we're still in need and Id remember this one.
This endpoint surfs the edit and the app.
So instead of match player id the form type you're still going to use the form type the form error the
form success and later right now makes no sense.
But later we're going to have a place where we can store the default images.
Remember that this one service kind of an edit and edit player.
So when the application loads it will try to fetch the image so it will be it will be stored inside
of default image.
And of course we're going to see this later.
Don't worry.
So teams will have teams.
All right.
So what we do have.
A form then data open and closed.
And then of course we need to create our you know list of inputs.
So I'm going to go to add and match and the first one was to date.
I'm going to copy this and I'm going to go back to many players and I'm going to copy the date.
We don't have a date right here.
We have a name a last name a number and a position.
Right.
So we're going to start with name name.
The element is an input the config is going to be player name.
I wish there could be kind of a short way to do this but there's not.
So player name the date no name impaired.
And there's one type of chess text.
It is still required bounded false validation message nothing and show label is going to be true.
I want to show the label on this one so I'm going to copy this one pasted at the bottom and same thing
last name.
In this case and then player last and then name just like this.
Right.
And then of course last name impled last name impot still a type of text.
And we want to show the label.
Then of course we have the number pretty much the same thing.
So open close an input player number we can do number.
Right.
And then of course number employed.
And don't forget to change it right here number.
And what else is still in in pre-text we could change it to number.
Doesn't matter right now.
We can do that no problem.
So instead of text you can put numbers just going to leave it in text right now.
So we have a show labeled of true everything else just pretty much the same.
So I'm going to copy this one and instead of couple thinks this one I'm going to go to add it to match.
I'm going to search for the local because this is when he says Select and now we're going to be using
a select on the player.
So instead of local I'm going to put position.
The element is to select and select a and then position then instead of select locals select position.
Right.
Still as elect and again just like we did before this one is show level 2.
We could fetch a list of options from the server just like we did with teams but right here we just
have four different options.
So I'm going to make a space and I'm going to add them manually.
Remember that we have a key of something and then a value of something.
So coma and then value.
This is the way it works our you know reusable components for selects.
So for the key we have four positions.
So the first one is when he is going to be the keeper and to keep it simple I'm just going to use the
same.
So koma paste paste and then paste and never forget the comb.
So we have keeper then we have defense maybe you know nothing about soccer or football or whatever you
want to call it in your country.
So we have keeper defense midfield and I'm doing I'm being very short because inside you know the football
or soccer world you have a lot of different positions.
So midfield so inside of the same you know midfield you have different types of Midvale and different
types of defense.
So now I'm just cutting to the chase right here.
So we have a keeper defense midfield.
And then you know striker Vergon.
So this is the decisions later are we going to have we can add one more maybe in the next section which
is the image remember that we're going to be using just right here.
So we need a place where we can validate that we have the image and you know everything else.
All right.
So for now I'm going to delete this one.
The coma last coma.
Of course we need to add all of this to our hour render.
Right.
So again just like on the match let me just go right here.
We need the admin lay out.
Right.
So I'm going to go back to our end point and say I mean lay out.
So I got to wrap everything inside of a div and div the class name for this class name because to edit
players could be added players you know I just wanted to keep it simple not use a very long string dialogue
because of course you need to type more.
Just trying to type less.
So edit players dialogue dialogue and rapper.
All right.
So age to open and close and we say this not state that form type.
All right of course at the beginning we don't have a form type.
We're not going to get a form type.
But then of course we were going to get it after we make a request to check.
We have an ID.
So form and form right.
Whenever we submit the form Remember we want to call the on submit event handler on met and with this
unsafe meant we will catch the event just like this event.
And then of course we will run a function called this dot of Mitt and then form.
And of course I'm going to be passing the event for now maybe we're going to change it later.
But for now it's just as good as it gets.
So again instead of here we could just start adding the the form feels good to go back to edit match
and I'm going to copy this one and paste it down here.
So the first form field I remember is going to be the name so form data and then this that state that
form data that name.
And we're still updating the form.
We're going to add this functions in a couple of seconds.
So you know what is kind of weird it's that I'm not getting anything because we should get something
at least.
So OK let me just Dolton why I'm not getting anything because I we should be getting something.
One sec.
All right sorry.
Sorry for this.
I know what the promise right here.
We're going to at being an ad player and the route it's at players.
If I go to the Napp of admen nav I'm pretty sure I made a mistake right here.
So players should be players.
That is the problem.
That it is getting weird.
So our players get what we get at least the name that is get.
All right.
Sorry for this.
So let me just go back.
So at edit players or it's going to go back here and we're going to keep doing this.
So first we added the name.
Now we need to add everything else.
We have a last name.
We have a position and a number right.
So copy paste and of course the first one it's the second one it's last name form data last name and
there we go get it.
All right.
Next one is going to be the numbers so Number of course number and then number kind of reloaded.
OK.
So now in the next one is going to be the position.
So copy paste.
And of course this one is going to be a case of select.
So we so you say position just like this and then form data position.
The application will reload and we get to select a position and all the positions.
So far so good.
I get to go back to an edit match and we're going to get all of this at the bottom so I'm going to copy
and paste it right here because it's pretty much the same code.
It's the exact same card.
All right.
So we reload and of course we have the button but we don't have anything because right now we don't
know what kind of form type Do we have.
All right.
OK so let's keep doing this right.
We know which forms that we have pretty much two main functions which is to submit form and the update
form.
Ryan this is pretty much standard so I'm going to go to match and I'm going to copy the one that says
update form.
This one it's pretty much similar.
So I'm going to copy this.
I'm going to paste the function right here and there we go we have it like it will be for the next project
you're going to do this in a different way so there's not going to be a lot of copy pasting because
you know copy pasting.
It's not always good.
All right.
So what else.
We have the submit form so we don't have that function.
I'm going to copy the serpent form and well there's a bit for me is something that we pretty much have
on all all the forms we use through all the occasion.
It could be much smaller or not.
So I'm going to delete whatever we have inside for me is valid here later.
No soup made for it.
All right.
Now all of this right now we are not going to need this.
We're going to delete this one and we're just going to keep this one which is where we add things to
the to the submit the data to submit.
That is when you need it.
And then of course we have the the marbles right here.
So again we're going to do this a million times.
We use this what else we have to submit for now.
And we have the update form.
So now whenever the application loads what I want to know I want to know what kind of form type do we
get.
No what we're going to do and this we do it by getting the ID so we don't have an ID that is an employer.
If we do have an ID is an edit player.
Right.
All right.
So let's do that right now.
First we need to do to of course to do it on the component at Mt..
So I'm going to go right here the top could be at the bottom doesn't matter.
So a component that mounts opening close.
So first we need to get to try to get the the player id so Konst player id player id is going to be
equal to this.
That props that match that per rams that idea.
All right.
Now of course on this one we are not going to get it.
So we ask we check if we do have a player id.
So if we don't then that player if not as a player are going to do all the logic for EDID play or later
right here you know the request to firebase and everything else.
All right.
So of course right now the only thing we get is this that said state opening close and we are going
to say that the form type it's equal to player.
So the application will reload and we're going to get at player.
So that is good of course if I do something we fail but if we type something at least it's updating
the form.
So so far so good.
We have four.
And later if everything is OK and we submit the form we should be getting a console log or something
with the data to submit.
But of course we need to do much more.
Now on the next section and this is maybe it is going to be this is what interest you is to me the player
image we're going to connect to the database and there's an image to the storage of your database project
your firebase project and you're going to use a third party library.
Don't worry it's already installed around.
So again we're going to do this and after we do this everything else you know the player name the last
name number and position it's going to be pretty much the same because we already did it on the other
forums.
So again we're going to do this maybe you want to learn you want to know how to do this.
And after you do this you can just go go to the final part maybe copy the code because you will need
to have the same code and that's it you know.
So after this we are not going to learn anything new.
We just need to do the standard work we do as a developer you know just doing a lot of that.
We do a lot of things many many times.
You know maybe the same thing.
All right.
So let's go to the next section and do the player image.