OK so let's create the file uploader of course this could be something you can every used throughout
the your whole application that's going to happen in this project.
Maybe in real life this is going to be the case.
So we're going to use a reusable components are going to go to you and create a file loader dodginess.
Again you can call this whenever you want.
So this one is going to be a re-act class based component.
Right.
And I'm going to give you the name of you know file uploader but with a capital F that's it just that.
Or of course I'm going to leave this pretty much empty and we're going to do this later.
But first we need to do some things inside at the player's going to close the match for them.
All right.
So we need to import it right here on the top.
So of course we need to go and say import and then file uploader then from dot dot for Slash.
One more time.
You I.
And then file uploader.
Now after we fuck up after we upload an image and everything else we can to store the image location
and everything else we can and need inside the form data right.
Because when we submit something we need to store not just the data but the image inside storage but
the body of the image inside the database.
Now let me go to storage.
I'm going to get I'm going to get this.
Maybe you're going to get some different message something like get started.
And they're going to get you going to get a pop up saying that the default.
It's like everyone can read and then everyone can ride that is OK.
Then we will change them some rules.
But for now that is OK.
So just click.
Got it and it's going to take you to the screen.
OK.
Going to go back to our project and go back here.
So we need to add a state of image.
And remember that inside form data before we submit something we need to check the validations.
So I'm going to go right here at the bottom and I will add to state for the image.
Now the state it's not going to be like this once it's going to be pretty much small.
So I'm going to say image just like this image opening close.
And we will have an element just like the other one element open and it's going to be image than coma.
And we do have a banlieue chest like the other ones.
Remember that this one's the important thing is the value and the validation.
Right.
OK so value for now starts at nothing.
Then we have a validation just like here validation.
And it's going to be equal to.
And we can make it required so we can do symbolization right here and at the beginning is going to start.
It's valid.
True because of course maybe at the beginning we want to you know the image is going to try to blow
something so we don't really want to change it.
We will get this we'll get there in a few minutes.
All right so now we are we have a state we have an image inside the state and we are importing file
uploader.
So we need to bring this component to the actual form.
Right.
All right.
So I'm going to go right here and I'm going to open and close now this file uploader needs to be mixed
to receive a lot of configuration from the parent component.
So the first one and I'm going explain this and then explain what are the probs.
Right now as we type them.
So first I'm going to say dead there and then.
Player or players.
Makes more sense.
So what is this there now after we upload something to firebase we need to store it inside of our directory.
If I don't pass it there is going to store them here on the route.
But I went to store them inside a directory called players you know a little bit better.
So when we abduct something and whenever we do an upload it will go to the player's directory.
That's why we use it.
And this is something we of our own.
OK.
This is not something from the file uploader Ryan nothing at all.
All right.
So next prop is going to be takk.
Now let me show you the final one.
I'm going to go to players the players and show you this one.
This one is the final one.
So whenever we load the page we get the image.
So this is a div with a background image a little bit broken window because it's a small image.
When to use this low small images and the back in the background we have the image so we can render
this background and the remove and everything else from with.
Then the file uploader.
So what we need to do we need to pass some properties like the tag may maybe the you or l of that image
and some other properties.
All right.
So going to go to tag and I'm going to say player player image right.
Makes sense.
So what does attack.
Is this.
We as this tag player name or play last night.
Does it attack.
Nothing really special.
Now again we will be using this to the add edit function i.v.
So we need to have a default image if the if we do have an ID and you know we have an actual image already.
So we're going to set a default image.
And if you remember inside the state right here at the top we have the default image.
So this is what we're going to be using.
It's going to go right here say default MGE and this one it's going to be equal to this that state that
default EMG.
Now we do have a name.
And again right now makes no sense but we will use it later.
So I can say that I want a default image just like the other one but this one is going to be named.
And later we're going to use this.
And this one instead of being equal to the default image it's going to be equal to whatever we have
inside the form data.
So there's that state that form data that image doesn't value.
Again we will go back to this.
Don't worry.
Now what happens if we upload an image just like this and we say no I don't like the image you know
is drawing.
I went to remove it.
So we clicked remove.
We will need a way or maybe a function or something that removes the image and give us back the the.
Let me go at players the file you know the file impot.
So our So we can create a function called Reset image.
Open and close and we don't have this function we created right now reset image opening close.
I'm going to copy the name of the image and image a mistake.
I'm putting this inside the form.
Feel so sorry for that right here.
So we don't have this function going to create it.
And of course leave it empty right now.
Doesn't matter.
Could be a fine art function or just a function because we are using a class.
OK.
So we have a we said Image function.
So then just let's stop for one second and think what is going to happen after we upload the image.
So this component this player will not do any any uploading.
We will do it from the file uploader.
So once they file the image gets uploaded from this component the server which is Firebrace will return
a set of names properties and everything else from the server.
And we kind of need that because inside of there we will have the name and the location of the image
and we need to grab the name and store it on the database on the player's document.
So this firebase uploader will be returning some data we need to use right here so we can update the
state.
Right.
OK.
So this is what this function is going to do.
I'm going to call it file name because the only thing we need it's the file name.
So again this file name will be passing up a prompt you know an argument called file name and then we
will we will use a function called store and then file name something like that store file late and
we will pass that file name.
We will get from the file upload or component.
We don't have this function.
I'm going to go right here.
Say this when it's equal to blah and there we go.
All right.
That is it.
We didn't have more props for now.
This is cool.
So now we need to go to File uploader and start creating the actual uploader.
Right.
So let's do that right now.
All right so let's start to build on this.
First we will need to use firebase because we're going to do an upload right here so we will need to
use firebase and it's from dot dot for slashed that thought forward slash and then firebase right.
OK.
So now just like I told before we will use a third party library for this.
And if we go to the package that Jason we have it right here re-act firebase file uploader.
OK.
So if I go to File uploader we need to import it so it's import and then file and then Kapilow you uploader
That's why we can use this one as it is.
So file uploader from that re-act firebase file.
Uploader all right what else are we going to use a circular or progress from a mature UI.
We have it right here at the top.
I guess not.
We don't like it.
We're going to do it.
So import.
And then it's called circular it's like this circular.
And then progress just like this and then from and if you remember it's not material you core we need
to add to the slash.
And then of course as the name progress right circle or progress Burguet.
So now on this file uploader we will have state again.
So the state is going to be very very simple we're going to have a name which is the image name if we
do have one the beginning and if we add the player we don't have anything.
Then we have a new problem calls a new volume called up.
It's uploading.
So if we are uploading that image to the server we will change this to true.
And we will show that circular progress of course since this is when this starts it's going to be false
because we are not uploading anything.
And then at the end we will get the u r l of the file you know the file you are.
And again we don't have this at the beginning.
It's going to show empty.
Now before creating the contents right here we want to get you know the default image.
If you remember right here right here we are passing a default image and a default image name.
Of course since we are adding players this ones are going to be empty but if we added player we want
to know if we do have a default image right.
OK.
So we're going to use something that we didn't use before.
I'm going to say it's static and it calls Gedor of state from prop's derived state from props.
So this is actually something new from re-act 16 X or 16 6 or 5 or something like that.
So this one is going to you know it is going to load before everything gets loaded.
And when we see new props we want we want to change the state.
So the everything will be right we rendered with a new state.
All right.
So in this one we we see a problem which is going to be the next props and then the next take.
So if opening close and I'm going to do a simpler and one more thing with this with this get derived
state from.
You always need to return something.
Right now I want it to return.
No but if something else this happens happens I want to return something else right.
Something else.
So what I want to check right here is if we have default images.
So if props which are the next props default just like this and I get a copy just to avoid mistakes.
Default image prompts.
If we do have a default image we want to start with a different state because now we do have a name
and we will have a file you are l.
Now the name is going to be whatever we have in default image.
And the other one defiled your.
Oh sorry it's going to be the default image name and the file you are l is going to be whatever we pass
to the false image.
So if I think about this just for a second we could use just one property with an object but you know
right.
You can you can do it if you want.
So OK.
So return and then state open and close and we will get expunged.
Right now we will return a name we will change the name on the state and the file you are Elb.
And again the default image name comes from Propst default image and then name because it's the name
and defile your L comes from props and default image just like this.
So whenever you use you use this they get derived state from prompts.
You always need to return something and whenever you return it's going to be applied you know to the
actual class or the actual class because we always use a class with this.
So in this case if this is not true we will return nothing but right here since this is true if we do
have an image it will return the new state.
So with this what it does is going to replace this state.
This one for this one right is going to remove this one and this will be the new state of course with
it is uploading.
All right.
So everything's good.
So I'm going to save it and find now we are good to go.
I'm going to go to our application and of course nothing happens and we get a lot of warnings but don't
worry.
So no.
I'm going to go right here at the bottom.
For now this part is done.
We need to add a lot of functions right here but we're going to need this first.
So inside of a div I want to add that file uploader know the input.
But the thing is that if we do have default images I don't want to add it since we have the device state
from prop's that it's managing this.
I could say opening close if we don't have it is that state that files you are l we want to do something
we want to play something.
If not we are going to display null for now.
All right.
So make sense makes sense.
So first if we do if we don't have a find you are all I want to show the file uploader.
So I'm going to start with Def opening cause now instead of inside of the div we will have a div with
the class name of a label and then input just like this.
And inside of here we can add the tack.
Remember we are using a tag.
So there's that Propst attack.
All right.
Very low the application our application you know we get player image.
So at least it works.
It's working.
So it's level impetus.
Sorry for that see it again and we get the player image stack so at least this is working this logic
and this is working or it could and we could do this on a different way of course but I wanted to use
a derived state from props.
Never used it before on this project so I want to use it.
All right.
So then we need the actual file uploader.
And when talking about file a bloater is the re-act firebase file uploader that component.
So we have again a lot of props and this this ones are not props on our own this are default props.
You know we need to use from this developer right.
So first the first one we need to do we need to use it except.
So on this one we will specify what kind of images we want to accept if not of course it will return
an error.
So we and say image for Slash and I want to accept all for now again you can check the documentation.
If you go to rehab firebase uploader and very simple you know get have there you go re-act firebase
uploader.
So you get all the configuration right here start fresh file name so you get all the documentation and
you can check this out later.
All right let's go back.
So first we get the except then we have a name which name again we need to present it as the default
doesn't care much.
Right now it's just a default name.
So I'm going to say image we can do something else either way.
So what we can do when we have a property and we could not use it.
But I'm going to use it cause I run two miles just like this randomise and then file name.
So what it does it creates a random file name.
And this one will be stored inside firebase.
All right.
We have value for this.
If you put this is going to do the run.
If we don't put as the put this is not going to do it do anything.
All right.
So then we need to specify define uploader where we want to store images.
We spoke about this previously and we said that we want to store everything inside the player's directory.
All right.
So I'm going to say storage just like this storage and then ref.
And this is equal to something we are going to use.
Firebase DOD we access the storage.
And this is the way we accessed firebase is torture by using this.
And just like we did with the databases we pass a ref remember just like we did with firebase right
here at the bottom right here database.
And then we pass a ref.
Now the only difference is that now we are using storage.
All right.
So file a bloater and BRAF and do we have a ref for this.
Well yes we have it.
We have this inside the door you know the directory of where we want to store it.
So we say this that prompts that there are right now we have three more things and right now this one
went too long the section and we are going to put it right now and then we're going to go and do it
do this create disfunctions.
So by default would file uploader you have a lot of functions.
A lot of callbacks but I'm going to use just three.
So we have the first one because just because it's an upload which name it's upload starred and that's
when of course it's we need to do something with this.
So whenever the upload starts with this method will kick in and you know whenever you get this method
kyndes you can do whatever you want right here.
You can just trigger your own function.
We have the same idea on upload and then error.
So if we if you do have an error we do have an error.
We will just do something right here and then we have of course an upload.
Same thing but instead of air it's going to be success.
So after you upload the images and everything goes OK this upload success is going to trigger whatever
you put right here.
So I'm going to do.
And we didn't have this functions.
We to create this in a minute.
We're going to do this.
Handle handle and then upload and are going to copy this because it's the keyboard word and I'm going
to say start and then this DOD handle upload error and then does this that handle upload and success
of course.
All right.
So pretty much don't we don't have these functions.
So let's go to the next section and start creating the functions to do the actual uploading.