All right so let's grade this functions the handle upload start.
This is the error and then the success.
Going to go right here after the state and gets a handle upload start.
Equals to a function.
So what is going to happen whenever we start uploading.
We're going to change the uploading to true so there is that set state opening close and is uploading
to true.
You can do much much more depends on you know what you're building right now which just changed it's
uploading.
Then we have the error the handle upload error.
If we do have an error we want to do something now in this case I want to again keep it simple because
we still need to do a lot of things.
And this project kind of went too long already and we need to do a lot of things.
So it went a little bit long because then the next one next project is going to be really really long
and much more complicated in this.
So I'm not going to add an error if.
Of course in real life if you do get an error from the server you want to display an error message so
you can do that right.
So we're going to change that it's uploading just to false.
All right.
Just we are going to cancel that.
It's uploading.
All right.
Then of course we want to show this loader the circular progress we're using at the top.
So I'm going to go right here.
I'm going to make some space and we need to add that logic.
We're going to do.
It's going to be pretty simple.
So open it close.
And if this state that is uploading it's equal to true.
We want to do something if not we are not going to do anything.
All right.
Very good.
So it's out of here of course.
We just at a dip and I call that class name and then progress whatever.
And I'm going to add some inline stylings.
This is something I added after wards.
So opening close text a line and going to do some text on line and they're going to do Center coma and
center.
Sorry coma.
And again at a margin margin of 30 pixels in zero from the sides.
All right.
So inside of here we need to add the circular progress.
And as you remember we can pass some props to see modified default behavior.
So I want to change the color to something else and it's going to be 9 8 C 6 9.
Now again we can change the thickness so I want to change thickness so thick and this equals two and
I want to use the 7.
It's going to be pretty thick.
All right.
So we go right here and beginner Sulmasy white firebase a storage.
It's not a function.
And so if we go to firebase at the top we are bringing up database.
Oh but we don't have storage.
So again we need to do pretty much the same thing.
I'm going to copy the import firebase forward slash and then storage.
Always forget to do this.
But you know the error message pretty clear.
So when we do the upload of course we're going to get the circular progress.
I'm not going to test it because the upload is going to work.
I'm pretty sure it's going to work.
So we will be uploading something you know a dummy image and I want to do the handle upload success
first.
All right.
So let's do the handle.
Upload success.
This is the one we care so I'm going to open and close.
Just going to be a function.
Now the upload success rate the job of this one is just going to it's going to let us know what is what
happened after the image was.
Upload it.
And if you if you're thinking where are we uploading images.
Well right here storage ref we are saying that we want to access storage and upload here so the file
uploader will take this and it will do all the job for us.
Resample OK so upload success whenever this is done this process this unravel of task success is going
to go back to this this to handle Oblak says our function and it will be passing some arguments and
arguments its actual file upload information.
What happened after the file was uploaded.
So we're going to say file name.
So on firebase after everything gets uploaded it will return the information about that upload.
And if you think about it we're going to need the name and the you are out because we need to store
them inside of our eyes our comp component to show the actual image.
And this is going to be a little bit weird.
So first what I want to do I want to do this.
That said state open close and I to say I want to bring the name and the name is going to be equal to
file name that Acoma and I want to change it is uploading to false.
And of course right now at the bottom we're going to do some more things.
But first I want to see the file name.
I went to cancel the filename so cancel law and then filing went to see why.
But what we get.
So OK.
So let's do the uploading and see what happens.
So of course I have a lot of things.
So my course Riak practice and I believe it's AM city and I'm going to go and make this bigger.
I'm going to go to source I leave and then resources and are going to go to the directory.
So right here inside images inside resources you have all the images off the players right here.
You have them images and players to upload defense keeper midfield and striker.
So you pretty much have all the images right there players and right here player to upload are going
to upload this one.
Doesn't matter right now.
So we got the progress and then at the end we get dis.
So this is good.
You know it works.
Now if we think about this we can have a problem because we are.
The firebase does.
It's just going to give us back just the file name of the of the upload.
You know the file name of image and this is just the name the name and then Tarpeian G.
If we wanted to include this on a div maybe to get a Bactrim image how are we going to get it.
Because the location of this image should be something like I don't know firebase HTP as firebase that
come forward slash the idea of our you know our project right here inside firebase then forward slash
storage forward slash images and then the name.
So we didn't have a real l which is have the name.
So we need a way to go to firebase and say Dude I want to fetch the actual Eurail the public your l
of this image.
And by default we don't get it.
We need to do something else.
So what do we do.
We use a method that you know firebase is going to give us.
So we do firebase that storage again DOD then we say ref we want to enter the ref and we do the same
thing.
This the problem that there we enter entering our directory inside storage and then going to say okay
inside this directory We want to find a child and now the child is going to be whatever we have inside
the family.
So this one is going to go and find whatever image you have inside storage with this name.
All right.
So after after that happens it's going to find the you know the file.
So what you want to get it's to get to download your else so you can use it.
And then of course we receive a promise so open and close.
Now we're going to get that you are back.
And then we will run a function.
You know the callback function so what we want to do we want to store that you are l inside of file
your L makes sense and everything is start starting to make sense.
So there's that said state and we say file you are l it's equal to whatever we get from our cell.
And just for fun I'm going to do a console console that log that open and you are just to see what we
get.
So we can upload again and just for fun again.
I'm going to reload firebase and right now we have uploaded one image just one image.
You know that odd item in the image and we get the we should be getting the players directory and it's
a little bit slow.
And inside the directory we get the PNB of this right and the preview.
Very good.
So let's upload again and see what we get right here.
I'm going to upload Starling.
Very good player.
The upload starts.
And I notice that after the upload starts the element the component right here of upload gets removed.
And this is because we are updating the state and right here we said that if we do have a failure or
an L we don't want to show this.
So you know that's why it's been removed.
Oh Amerikay I mean I'm saved.
I made a mistake.
Let me upload it again.
So for that company and other good player that's why they were champions this year.
So we get of course the Emmets you are ill because we are doing the console log right here at the top
and then inside Council argue your else.
So this is the you are l and it's a pretty long your l.
There's no way you can guess.
You can guess this you can not just copy.
You know maybe this you are l and don't and don't do this.
Maybe you want to make a reference to your image and you paste the actual urinal without the name of
your image and you use this as an h a normal h f tack or maybe a source tagging to your image.
It's not going to work because you get a token so you don't know the token.
This is why you will need to do this.
There's no way around this.
But we do get to your L and if I click at
Burgerman.
All right.
So now we have a file name and we have to download your l.
So now what we need to do we need to return back to the parent component.
Now before I want to do this before we do this maybe we are going to finish you know with this component
after we upload the image your l the image we do have a u r l so we can show the uploaded file right
here.
So let's do that right now.
Or it's going to open and I'm going to say if this that state and pretty much the opposite of filed
your L we can do it right here.
No but I'm going to put in a different place so it could be a little bit clearer clearer.
OK.
So if not no.
All right so now we need to show the image and it could be pretty simple.
I've already did this you know in the final projects up class name opening close image then upload then
container.
All right.
So then we do have an image and I'm going to add some styles.
I'm going to make it style of.
And let me first close the tag.
There we go.
So the style.
It's Webware with a whit of 100 percent.
So it's style.
It's equal to some props with of 100 percent.
Right now with image we get a source and the source.
It's this that state that file you are l now the Alt.
I don't know maybe in the name of the image doesn't matter right now.
So there's that state that name doesn't matter.
All right.
And later going to add remove Dave class name equals remove.
And then when we click going to add and and click listener on click Begin to run a function called this
dot upload again and we are not upload it again.
We're just setting a resetting everything inside of this component to do the upload again.
We're going to do this later because it's real simple.
You're not going to do anything special on this one.
All right.
So let me go again.
So this should be ready.
So if I add a player company again we do the upload.
And when it returns we get we get it right.
So we get the image of the player now impaired.
And then of course we're going to do the remove by click and nothing happens.
We will get an error because we didn't have this upload again function.
Right.
But now know we are uploading image and getting it right here.
So now since inside of this component the file upload or component we have all the data we need to go
back to the parent component which is the player with all the information we need the name of the file
and the location and everything else we need to catch it inside of this function.
We need to go to the update form and update the form because we have a state of image right.
So let's let's do that right now.
Let's go to the next section because again this one went a little bit long.
So let's go to the next one and do all of this.