Right.
So now we do have a image name and of course a download image.
So OK so now we will grab this name and we will go back to this function.
Remember we were using the file uploader and whenever we get uploaded right here we need to make a reference
to the file name store file name right here.
So I'm going to go back to the file uploader and after you know we upload everything and we get the
image name and everything else we're gonna make a reference to this that prompts that file name.
We open file name and they're going to be passing the file on the file name is not dead.
Download your mail it's just a file on the right just the name the ID and then PAGG that that is it.
So now this file name will be receiving the name of the file.
So can it go back to store file the right here on a store file name.
We will be receiving a file on name and this is going to be a little bit weird at the beginning.
Now whenever we get this file name the name of the name of the file what we want to do is we want to
update the form because right here at the top we have a state of image.
So I want to enter the update form function we have right here at the bottom and I want to update the
value of this which is going to be the image name and we going to set the valid to true right now could
be false.
OK.
So we're going to do that.
We're going to go right here at the bottom to store filing and we're going to do.
I'm going to say does that update form just like this.
And this is going to be weird passing an object.
It's going to be an I.D. off image.
Why I'm using the image keyword.
It's because in the state on the form data we have image that this would be picture.
I would need to use picture on that on that you know that call right here at the bottom.
There's one good picture but we are using image.
So it's going to be image.
All right.
And then as the second argument.
And that is again the weird part.
I'm going to pass the file name now if I go to this update form the update form function.
It's not the way you know it's not the way it works.
The update form what it does it grabs that element then access the element through the ID and then adds
the event target that value.
So if I go right here on the top and do console log and then element just like this and I type something
we get the event and then the ID but we get one single object.
Right now on our you know file name update or whatever you want to call it right here we are passing
two arguments an object with the ID and a file name.
So what we will need to do we will need to Krafty ID from the first argument because right here we have
an ID but we don't have an event.
We have just the file name which is just a string.
So we don't have an event.
So what we can do if we go to update form right here the top can do this and make it right.
I'm going to say that this update update form is going to be receiving two arguments.
The first one is the element which is the new one we know and the second one.
And then we call it content.
Now the content it's equal to nothing.
Now if we don't end this is default arguments this is something from ESX if we don't have this argument
whenever this function gets called the content this Marvel is going to be equal to nothing if we do
have an argument for this one this content it's going to be equal to whatever.
You know we are passing to this function.
So for all of this input no player name last name and number and position the content is going to be
empty.
Right but for file name we will have the name of the file.
You know the id and the PMG.
So what we can do right here instead of saying Dude just enter the element even the target value when
I can do it say if opening close and if content it's equal to you know triple equal to nothing.
Then of course we go to the default scenario and we entered the target the value if not of course we
know that it's an image so we grab the new elements that are new and we say that we want to store inside
value whatever we have inside content which is the name of the image.
Of course that is it.
That's it.
Of course is it.
So now when we go to the render console log opening close does not state that for data we're going to
try again.
We're going to go to choose player Vincent Kompany opening close we're going to upload the image and
at the end we will get new state.
And if I go to image we will have inside image validation.
True because we are running a validation on the update form right here we are running this and we do
have a valid true and you know the value it's the actual image.
So whenever we push this to the database now we upload the new player.
We will have the image as a valid value.
Right.
No this is good.
So we are pretty much done with the file upload.
The only thing that's missing right now is going to be the you know the reset image the remove image
and we can do something very very very simple.
We're not going to delete it from the database because what we can do we can remove maybe cache the
file name go to storage and remove it directly from storage.
But we're not going to do that.
I'm just going to reset the state so we can delete the image from image right here from this and from
the State of the file.
Uploader So we're going to do that.
All right.
So of course we don't have that logic right here.
We're going at it right now.
So at the bottom we have this upload again function.
So the only thing that this upload again is going to reset the state of this back to nothing.
So going to create the function right here or the bottom are going to call it again upload again he
calls open it closed just to function and back in bed can do this.
That set stayed open and close and they're going to say that everything is back to zero so I'm going
to copy the state and store it.
That is that of course we are setting all the props inside a file of bloater.
We also need to clear the state on at players.
We need to go to here and reset back to zero.
So this file our bloater if you remember if I go here to the file uploader we have a reset image function
so we could trigger this to you know do the resetting.
So at the end of this I'm going to call this Probst does that and then reset image.
I believe I called this this way reset image.
I'll just double check.
Reset image.
Finger.
Now again this function.
So far it does nothing.
So what we need to do we need to do pretty much custom update form.
So first I got to make a copy of new form data.
I'm going to do that really quick because we kind of did this a million times.
It's going to be a copy of this that state that form data and he's out of here.
So I have a new form data.
Let me correct it from data.
What I'm going to do I'm going to access new form data I can access image.
I'm going to do value just like this equals to nothing.
And again new form data.
We do image and they're valid.
We're going to reset it back to false.
And of course then we need to do this that sets stayed open and close and we do default image remember
that we do have a default image is back to nothing.
And then we sent the form data with the updated new form data.
Really simple.
We did this a million times.
So now we try again and I've saved it forgot to save it.
If we try it again I'm going to upload company.
It's going to take a second and we get the image I'm going to do remove and notice that we have a console
I have a lock in this state that form data.
I'm going to remove it.
I get the new state and inside image it's valid false and value.
It's back to nothing.
So we are ready to upload again like it's all before right here.
When you reset an image what you can do.
You can go to firebase and unset the image from the storage.
And I'm not going to do it just to save time and it's as simple as doing you know firebase storage and
then ref and unset.
That is it.
So very good.
We have pretty much everything we need for the file uploader right.
So OK so now what's next is doing everything else.
You know the player name player last name you just posting the form to submitting the form with the
real data.
So let's do that right now.
So let's go to the submit form and instead of the form is valid I want to check what I get from the
console log and data to submit as usual.
You know we did this.
So data meant and I will now delete it already.
So you know let's start the whole process again.
So play M.H. company the name it's company.
It's actually been sent so I don't know.
Vincent never then company.
It's a very good player one of the best defenders in the world.
Maybe you don't like football and maybe you don't care.
OK.
So we select defense in the deposition defense of player and the data.
We do have an image last name name number and position.
Very good.
So we are ready to do the uploading.
So OK so I'm going to go here.
And if you remember you're using the same file to do two types of operations.
So if open close and of course then we go to the else.
So if the does that state that form type it's equal to added player.
We are not going to enter this scenario because we are not adding editing a player we are adding a player.
So we're going to go here.
And the way you add things with push just like we did with teams.
So firebase then players that push opening close when we can be pushing is the data to submit after
we do this we go to then and are going to or of course.
Right now we could know that we couldn't pass anything.
We didn't need actually to pass anything after we get the data to submit there's no snapshot nothing.
After we get it they submit that they of course the promise we'll get resolved.
So we need to do something.
In this case this Probst that history can access history I'm going to push and I'm going to go back
to the end point of players so men and then players right here you can do whatever you want.
Doesn't matter.
So then I'm going to do catch just like this catch open and close.
And if we do have another I want to do something else.
I'm going to say this.
That said state that said state opening close and then for him are it's equal to true.
All right.
So let's try it again.
So I will add the image of Sterling.
Doesn't matter.
And for the name I'm going to type whatever.
You know maybe I don't know.
Robert penny because if I add the real name we've already have the real names inside players.
So I'm going to add a new name.
So the play number 77 doesn't matter and he's a midfielder.
So going to add the player and we go back to the main point and we have it right here Robert Penney
77 midfield.
And of course we get this inside the database.
Let's just double check.
So it can take a second close matches.
And this is a new player.
We get the image up.
No this is not a new player.
This is it.
So we get the image.
Penny Robert 6:53 and mid-fielder.
Everything works as expected so far.
All right.
Of course if I answer this everything breaks because we didn't have the logic to pre-load the information
from the from the Id and we will need to do the storage to get the image from the you know the actual
name and we will need to complete it right here.
So again we still need to do a few things but the player logic done we are done with the player.
All right.
So let's go to the next one.
Start doing the player and we are almost done.
If you really if you've reached this section we did it a lot.
It's like you know seven hours of coding.
So it's a lot of time.
And you know we did a lot of things and covering all of this no uploading files uploading images and
all the other things with the routes and everything else.
Man you you're ready to do whatever you want.
At least with firebase because that said even though you have more sections to maybe categories or something
else.
Everything else has the same logic inputs you know file and form and that's it.
And then you just grab it from the server and you render everything from your component.
So we're going to go to the next one and do the edit player.