OK so let's create the edit play or logic.
It's going to be very very simple.
Because we kind of already did this.
So we're going to use this.
Robert Penney the one I've just entered.
Why.
Because the other ones if you go to the database we can have a reference to you know the image of that
player and the image in your database.
And in my database as well doesn't exist.
No it's on a different Feinberg's project.
All right.
So we're going to use just the first one the Roberd penny whatever.
So if I go to from a penny we do enter the edit player logic but nothing happens.
OK.
So on the component that mount this is where we start this one.
If we don't have an ID goes to a player.
But if we do have an ID because this is the case we're going to do something else.
So first we need to fetch the player data with this ID.
So first we make a reference to firebase and D-B that we use the ref opening close and we entered again
to use tempera strings.
We entered the players section.
Then of course we need to pass the player id.
So player id after this we use ones we use value just like before.
And then of course we go to then what we get back is going to be a snapshot after we get the snapshot
we can run a function.
Now again inside the snapshot we don't have anything we need to access vowel.
So first I'm going to create a viable called player and then data and inside of here I'm going to store
whatever we have inside snapshot dot and then bow.
Right now there is one thing we at this point we do have.
We get the player information you know the player data but we just have the image the image name we
don't have the download.
You're out.
You know the actual image.
And we will need it.
So I'm going to enter firebase again dot and your storage Dot are going to enter the ref.
Remember we are using the players directory players.
And then just like we did before we access the child and we have this information inside player that
image.
And this of course is on the database player image.
All right.
Once we pass that the child information the data is going to come back with the get download you are
l and of course then we get a promise after we get a promise we will get a u r l back.
And then of course we can do whatever we want.
So what are we going to do we going to create a function to update fields.
So we don't have this function we can create it right now.
So we're going to do this update just like this and then fields just like we did with Update matches.
So we need a few things.
First we need to play your data something copy player data and put it as an argument.
The second argument is going to be the player IDs are going to put Player D.
That's the third thing is going to be what kind of form we are using and which type which form type.
In this case it's not going to be a player.
It's going to be added and then player.
And again this is going to be the title of the form and then going to do coma are going to be passing
the u r l for that image.
Now we didn't have this update fields.
If you go to our application could break you know and of course is breaking right.
So I'm going to go to our big fields right here on top of the component at Mt..
And you know create the function real simple.
So because of something open it close that's good.
So we get the player as the first argument the second one is the player id player id the third one is
the type of the form type and the fourth one is the default M G and notice that this default EMG is
the same.
We are using on the this is not the same model just the same name but this is where we are going to
be storing that value inside of default EMG.
All right.
OK.
I could use a different name but you know.
OK so what do we need to do first.
Just like always we need a copy of new of the form data so form and then data equals open and close
added.
This that state that form that data right.
So now we have a copy.
Now what we need to do we need to call the new form data and you know change the values change to valid
to true and change the value to whatever we get from player which is all the player information.
So for opening close and let key in New form data I'm going to call this one right.
And going by what we do is we enter form data we enter that key and we assign a new value and the value
is going to be whatever value we get inside player with the same key.
All right we need to change the balance so you form data they're going to copy this one because I'm
lazy and then valid and this one will be ballot too.
True because now we do have a value.
And at the end what we do is we set a new state with a lot of properties the player I.D. We change at
the top we have a player I.D..
So now we will have it a form type and the default image.
Right.
So can we go back here for Pori ID equals two player id.
And remember I am using is 6.
This could be if we are not using a 6 something like this.
But since the key and the value are the same.
I can do this and each will do it for us.
Then we have the default image and that's why I'm using the same name.
Then we have the form type so form type it's equal to.
And you know I could do the same thing form type form type.
There we go.
Magic of ESX.
So then we have the form data.
So form data is going to be equal to new form data.
All right.
That is it.
If I reload the application we are already on that player.
It's going to take a second and we get the image we get the name and everything else so everything works
very good.
So now the next step would be going to submit form.
Right now we are adding a new player but we are not editing a new player.
So this could work if we push some data with the same ID and same everything on firebase is going to
get updated.
But you know I would like to run you know a proper update on the under-fire base.
OK.
So inside form time are going to go right here and I'm going to say OK I want to access firebase to
be.
I want to enter the ref.
I want to use a template strings.
Going to enter players for Slash and I'm going to be using whatever I have inside this state that player
id.
That's why we stored the ID there.
And then I got to go and perform an update opening close and would what we are going to be updating
it with data to submit.
All right.
Then of course we get a problem is back and we run something something very simple and they're going
to run a function called this success form or from success not going are going to call it success form
success and form.
Right.
And the success form and going to be passing on a message.
So it's pretty much the same thing with it.
With the update match same same idea and of course if we get a catch we catch the error.
We run a function and then this that said state and we pass that form error for error equals to true.
So we are pretty much doing the same thing with that with APNIC matches.
This is the same same logic.
Right.
So we didn't have this function this access form so I'm going to copy success for to go right here the
top opening close and it was successful and it's really really simple.
I'm going to say message right here because we are passing a message and on this which is this that
said state opening closed and we say that they form success.
It's equal to whenever we get from the message.
We will see the you know that display the message because we have it right here on the right here.
Something is wrong.
Success label this state from success so we're going to get that message there.
Now of course after two seconds I want to clear this out.
So set time out open it close.
We run a function and this function will run after.
I don't know two seconds.
Sounds good.
I'm going to say this.
That said State Farm success back to nothing.
And that is it.
So I'm going to reload the application.
We're still inside the penny won the rubber penny.
So Penny Wise just like the like the clown they're going to edit player updated correctly and then it
goes away.
Now if I go out to a different route and we go to the index we have an updated Pennywise if of course
if we enter again we can do.
I don't know 69 because it's funny added player.
And we go to players and everything works.
Now if you ask me now I'm taking a look at this.
I could add is downloading maybe a state saying that it's downloading and not show anything until we
have everything from the component that mound right here.
After all the server and everything it's done so we can do this.
I'm not good at it right now because it's something very simple you can do it on your own time no problem.
OK so now what's going to happen next.
We need to create the team and the matches end point because now we have a database for teams you know
database with matches and with players.
So we're going to go.
Let me just show you.
If you go to the team we get the animation with all the teams going to get the images of the players
and we review remember every ball already have this card.
So this is going to be pretty pretty simple.
Now then we have the mattress.
So inside of the mattress we will load the matches and of course we're going to apply some filtering
right here we have the plate.
We're going to show the play or maybe all of the games.
What do they actually won.
Lose draw.
And this table is kind of a hardcoded table.
Did this just to complete lay out.
You're not going to really do it.
But I'm going to explain you why we are not doing league table.
When we reached this section.
Now if we go back to our application we have one tiny problem.
All of this works this you know the final project I did works because on a different instance of a database
of firebase I've uploaded each images I created you know an entry for each player.
I did all that work you know the data entry job.
But on our project we didn't do that.
So if I go for example to one of the players that were already on the database when I give you this
all ready on the Jason if I go for example this one it's going to fail.
We're going to get an error message because on the database we do have an image for this guy you know
for a Whero we do have an image an image name.
Let me see if I can find it.
There we go.
We do have a name for the image but this one of course in our firebase doesn't exist.
So it's not finding it.
And of course it breaks.
Now how to fix it.
I'm going to show you just a quick quick fix and then I'm going to go I'm going to give you two different
options of what you can do.
And this is completely up to you.
So I'm going to open it close and can it just open it close to catch.
So if you get an error begin to catch it.
Now instead of doing this it feels and all of this when I'm going to do I get to say this uptick feels.
But instead of passing the player data just like it is I can use some destructuring.
I'm going to toss inside of that object whatever we have inside player data.
But at the end I'm going to grab the image property and I'm going to set it back to nothing.
So this is not going to fill our application is not going to fail.
We are still unable to find the image.
We are going to get the message but not this will not break.
And this your elf course doesn't exist so we can you know pass nothing.
And if I reload the application the app loads all the rest of the information Sakyo the name and everything
else but not the image.
So we are right to add an image if we want it to sell and we just tried.
I don't know.
So we add the image and we get it.
So maybe later we could you know edit player and add this.
So what you can do.
There are two things right.
You can go to each player on the list because we need them to go to each player and say OK on this one
I know that I don't have an image.
So you can go select Choose file and if you noticed inside resources of the file this folder I gave
you inside images you have players players to upload and you have the strikers midfielder's keep and
everything else.
So you can load this Sergio Aguero image from there and of course you will be floating this from here
players to upload striker Sergio Aguero I do it just like this we added the player and you know you're
ready to go because now this image is in your database.
So if I enter again everything is cool.
So what you can do is this.
You can go on each player and you notice that right here you have the position and the name.
And of course upload the image from this end point to your database.
That's one thing.
Now if you don't want to do this because of course it's some data entry job and it takes a while you
can.
Whenever we reach to the section you can load a fake image.
We can load a fake image on the component and load the same image for all the carts for all the players.
We could do that right.
OK.
That's a quick fix.
If you don't want to do the data entry job you can do that no problem Okay so what going to have now
on the next section I'm going to give you of course a sip of everything we did right here for the players
and we're going to move forward and we can start with with a team.
Why not going to go to the team section.
Right.
Let's go to the next one.