OK so let's start with the first project.
So the first project is going to be called the venue.
We've already seen this on the previews of the preview project.
So it's going to be called the venue.
I've opened the virus code and navigated to that directory called the venue.
You can call this whatever you want.
Doesn't really matter.
And then in the batch and the command or if you're in Windows.
Same thing command you can navigate to the same directory.
So the first thing we need to do to start.
It's to create a re-act application right here to bring a template.
So I'm going to be using the see if you didn't solve ACL I just go back a couple of question a couple
sections and you can find the instructions in how to install the globally.
So we're going to start with create then react and then app.
And since I'm already inside the directory I want are going to do a blank space and a dot and it will
install everything inside of this directory.
Maybe if you're in a different directory and you want to create a directory and store everything inside
you will call it or maybe the venue or you know my app or something like that and it will create a directory
for you and install everything inside.
So since I'm already inside the directory the venue I'm going to put into place just dot.
Bryce Precentor and this is of course it's going to take a couple minutes maybe a few seconds and when
it's done I'll be right back.
OK so everything was installed for me.
Maybe if you're using NPM you're going to get NPM start instead of yorn.
I'm using yarned and it's computer Yorn it's kind of a something like NPM.
They are pretty much the same thing.
I like to use yarn and NPM comes with a note.
So if you wouldn't Yorn you will need to go and install yarn in your computer.
If you don't want to there is no no me.
The only thing you need to know is that instead of using yarn you need to use and PM ride and I will
tell you when we need to use it.
OK don't worry.
So first I'm going to check if everything was installed successfully.
So I'm going to do and Yorn start in your case.
NPM start.
I'm going to press enter and this will begin with the development server of this project.
It's going to take a second a few seconds.
OK so after everything you know after this you to get a window just like this with localhost 3000.
So if you're getting this means that everything is OK.
So for now I'm just going to leave it here and I'm going to go back to the terminal and kill the terminal
kill the command to clear.
And now would we need to do we need to install all the dependencies we need to use in our project.
So if you remember in the previous section I gave you a text with an ad and a bunch of commands and
same thing for NPM install.
So I'm going to use I can copy the Yorn one because I'm using yarn.
If you're using NPM copy the NPM one I'm going to paste it right here.
So we will be using materail UI for to create some things than re-act reveal re-act scroll and re-act
slick.
So these are these are third party libraries.
We're going to be using the word whenever we read your section where we use re-act reveal.
I will show you the get have page and everything else.
So for now just going to press enter.
And this is going to take a minute.
We'll be right back.
Whenever this is done OK so everything was installed.
And before we start coding like it tool before if there is something we are not going to do is to see
assess.
And of course we are responsive.
Right.
So attached to the section on the resources I've added a directory called you know resources you need
to download that sip and incipit inside of the source begin to drop a resources folder right here.
Going to do that right now.
OK so I've added this directory is going to be called resources.
Again you can call this whatever you want but later of course remember you changed the name right here.
So on this directory you have the images and some icons maybe the sliders.
The images were going to be using on the slider with this woman.
And then of course you get the styles that CSSA.
And this is the all the styles of the web page is not a long web page.
So again we are not going to do styles right here.
We're going to focus everything in that javascript section of the of the project.
So OK.
So remember to put it inside of the source.
OK.
So to begin first I'm going to go to the app that is going to leave that one I'm going to go to APS-C
assess I'm going to delete this one.
We are not really going to use it are going to go to the app tests.
Not going to use it.
So delete this.
Then we have an index CSSA.
I'm going to delete this as well.
What else.
We have the index Dangi as I'm going to leave that one and then logo SPG goodbye logo as Weegee and
then register service worker.
Delete it.
All right so we get we only get the index.
And the app digests.
So on the index dodgiest I'm going to delete this lines because we didn't have those files anymore.
And we're going to get an error.
So I'm going to delete everything and just leave this this and then of course I'm going to go to Abdin
Jesus I'm going to delete the import for the logo and the APS-C SS and then the return just leave one
day of saying I don't know.
Hello.
All right so now I'm going to go right here and do your start.
We're going to begin with our development server.
Get going to take a second
look at we get hello.
So that is OK.
So we're going to go to the next section if we're going to start building the website.
We're going to build.
We're going to start with the hetter.