OK so let's begin doing this.
So I've created this you know I've changed the color of the terminal you know a little bit better.
So we have this screen and then on another tab I have the other you know the finished project so this
is what we're going to be doing right now.
Of course before I buy record this course this practice course I have all the projects finished so you
know I could have a reference.
So OK.
So this is what we're going to do and we're going to start with Hetter.
So whenever the pitch loads we get Hetter and it's transparent.
And whenever we scroll down we get a caller.
And of course it disappears when we reach the top.
And then of course we have the side drawer.
And if we click on an item going to go to a new section so we're going to start with Hetter OK.
So let's go back to our project.
So first the index which is the first to file and we're going to leave it just like it is.
We don't need to change anything here but we're going to change the app that jazz which is the other
entry point the main entry point of our application in this case.
We're going to be using the CSSA we have in we sources and we get it injected right here.
So I'm going to say import open and close that force slash resources for Slash and then styles.
So the styles will be injected in our application so whenever we use a class name we will get it right.
So right now we didn't have Hetter.
So we can create a directory inside the source which is going to be called components components and
inside components.
Of course we need to create the header.
So okay.
So I'm going to go to component's new folder and I'm going to store the header header dash and then
footer.
So I'm going to store the header and footer on the same place.
So for the header I'm just going to create a new file call called header dodginess and the header dodgiest
is going to be a class based component.
Now and this is I will tell you this and if you're using VBA code it's going to be really helpful helpful
for you.
I'm going to be using some snippets for example I'm going to say re-act class based component and if
I press enter it will give me all the lay out for this.
So this is a plug in.
I have installed and he will recommend for you to install it.
It's going to be called re-acclimate search for this re-act native.
No not this one.
Let me find it.
Because they have a lot of you know installed plug ins so all me find it.
You have the material team which is which is the one I'm using right here with all the icons on me see
reac native No react to you as coach snippet.
So this is the one so whenever we type something R-S.C. we get a class based component and same thing
with statelets component.
So if you're not using this you know this there's when it's really really great.
That's the first thing.
OK.
So first we create a class based component and this one is going to be called header.
And let me change this header.
Come and I'm going to change the name of the file with a capital H.
OK.
So OK so we have the header.
We have a class based component.
And for now I'm going to just return Hetter.
So we need to import Hetter from from the app dodginess.
So I going to go right here and say import Hetter then it's going to be from.
And that for Slash components for Slash header and footer and it's going to be header.
OK.
I'm going to make a reference and that's it.
If the page is going to reload and we get Hetter which is the text we have right here really really
simple.
So to start we need to bring things from material UI.
So I'm going to go right here and say import and then app bar just like this app bar end with a capital
B and then from and then it's going to be at and then material you eye core and then for Slash and then
app bar we need to bring a few things we are going to go right now to mature UI and show you what this
is all about.
That import and then toolbar just like this toolbar and toolbar There we go from.
And same thing add material.
Core and same tack toolbar when we copy and paste.
All right.
So then we have to import menu icon.
So import menu icon.
There we go from at mature UI core for Slash.
And this one instead of menu icons is going to be menu.
So it's like a dependency.
And the last one is going to be I combine an import icon button from opening close at Mattioli or ice
core for Slash and same name.
All right so this is what we're going to be using at first.
Solutio you first something about virtual UI OK.
So if I go to the if I go to Google and Google material you I can get this really the world most popular
re-act UI framework.
So we get to go and enter there and mature you I would it this is pretty much like I don't know Jake
Querrey but for react so we're going to get a lot of components right from the you know from the start
and we can use them in our applications.
So I'm sure you're right here if we go to the the options you can have you can get the components demos
go to component demo and go to a bar which is the one we're importing right here at the top.
I'm going to go to a bar and this is what you get.
You get some examples of what you can do with this bar and this is what actually are going to be doing
if we go to the final project.
We have an icon.
We have a button and then you know we have the app bar so we can use it as a header.
So if I open the show resource showed a show source of this right.
We're importing the same things on bar then the toolbar button.
So I'm sorry I can button so we can click on this on this button.
And of course menu icon so we need to install this as you know bring it on the on the on our component
so we can use it.
So again Marjorie until you die it's really really cool.
And we can be using it a lot for a lot of things.
All right.
So can it cause us and we're going to go back to our application.
So right now we're not doing anything.
First we need to create an app bar so I'm going to delete this.
I'm going to do.
Up up and then bar open it close.
Now this bar meets some specifications and this is actually comes from Riyadh UI.
I'm sorry from material UI and the bar which is the header we can set it you know in the relative position
where we can use it as a position fixed.
So if I say position equal to fixed and then let me put something right here.
Header is going to start as a position fixed right.
Right from start to get the background.
And of course right now I cannot test it because the height of the web page it's not long enough so.
But you know don't worry we can begin to simulate this later.
So what else.
I want to change the background color because that's when it's really really ugly.
And if you remember we have kind of a transparent or black kind of color.
So for now how can we change the styles.
I'm going to go right here.
Say style opening close and we can get past the styles right here.
First we need a background color so background and then color just like this.
And I'm going to use that grayish color.
So it's to f f f then coma I'm going to change the box shadow.
And then going to change it to none because I don't like the box shadows shadows then panning and 10
pixels some pixels from the top and nothing from the side.
OK.
So of course we just can't see the color and the padding.
But that is OK.
Now inside of this so we can put things inside we need to use this toolbar.
So inside of the toolbar we can put buttons icons and other things.
So we need to make a reference to toolbar.
So again toolbar open and close.
Now inside of toolbar we will get to thinks the header I'm sorry the logo and then of course later we
can add the button.
So the first thing is going to be adding the logo.
And remember that I gave you the CSSA and we are not going to do CSSA.
So I'm just going to write a component in this case is going to be just a div and I'm going to be adding
just a class name and make sure you're typing the same name the class name is me.
Because if you're not type in the same class as me of course the application will not find that class
on the resources and styles around.
So in this case you can do whatever you want.
If you make you change it right here you want it to go and change it on the styles.
That's the essence.
All right.
So head on Logo.
That's it.
Now I'm going to go right here and say Dave and I are going to be adding the venue.
We have two lines right here.
The venue with a different kind of font and then musical events with a different you know type of font
or you know different size and everything else.
So going to create two dips first one with a class name.
Going to leave it empty and then are going to create in pretty much the same thing.
So I'm going to copy this one and paste it at the bottom.
So the class name we're going to use something that calls font and righteous something like this.
And this is a font that we need to install from.
From Google fonts so it's all right.
And then just like this and then hetter logo Benue and then the text for this one is going to be the
venue.
All right.
And with a capital B There you go.
Now the other one is going to be Hetter logo and then title and musical events when they make it on
the right spot.
The call.
There we go.
Sorry for that.
Musical events.
OK.
So if I of course really love this we kind of get something but the font it's you know something else.
And this is because we don't have the font on our project so I'm going to go open a new tab.
I'm going to say Google fonts and inside Google fonts We will search the font that we eat in this case
it's going to be righteous and I'm going to click the plus button and we're going to use another one.
It's called robo dough.
You know very very popular so on the font family are going to go to customize light for Roboto and then
medium and the other one is the only one we get which is regular and then are just going to copy this
go to the public directory index and paste it just like a regular font.
And of course the app will reload and we get you know the venue and musical events.
So the next step would be adding the combine and said let's go to the next section and add the button.