Write so now we'll be we will add the button right here so we can cook it and whenever we click it we
will create a side drawer.
So first is the button.
OK.
So going to go back to our project and if you remember right here we've imported a menu icon and I made
a mistake.
This one it's not from core is from icons.
It's kind of a different dependency.
If we go to you know the package to Jason we have material you like core and then icons so it's a different
library.
OK.
So sort of for that are going to go at the bottom and first we need to bring that Bunim now to use buttons
inside the toolbar and actually inside the module.
We need to use the Eye button.
So we're going to open and say icon button.
OK.
And remember we are importing Eichenbaum button right here at the top.
So now from within I can button we can put an icon and in this case I'm using a Nikon from you know
material.
And you can use whatever you want.
It doesn't really matter.
Right here we can see the icons can have a black eye we've going to change that.
And again if you put your own your own icon is going to work as well.
But you know this one comes already ready to go.
OK.
So the I can button needs some configurations so I'm going to do Area Leavell area labeled just like
this.
And this one is going to be a menu.
The color.
And you know the color we will inherit because the color by default it's white.
So we can get it in a white collar and of course if we cook it nothing happens.
So in real life what it needs to happen is that whenever we click it we open the side door.
We didn't have a side drawer but are going to add and click event listener opening close.
And in this one whenever we click it we will write a function.
In this case I'm just going to say conc lock open.
All right.
So let's see if this works.
So inspect and I'm going to go to console.
I'm going to cook it and we get open or whenever I typed it open.
OK.
You know you're going to get it.
Let's get.
OK so now what we need to do is we need to add a side door just like this.
So let's do it right now.
All right so let's add this side door first let's go to the documentation.
So if you go to drawers right here you're going to get.
Of course all the documentation all the this is actually the demo section so you can open it left or
you can open right.
You can open.
Actually you can open tops of this is really really cool.
So we can use the open write option.
Now if I show the resource right here of course we need to import drawer and you know set some state
and everything you know like that we go to the door option.
So which each drawer you can set an encore which is going to be where you're going to open it from the
left or the right.
And in this case we're going to be passing an open state.
So whenever the page loads if this is the state top it's actually true.
This you know this value it's true the page will load with the side door open so we can meet to mind
that.
And then we have a third prop which is going to be the on close whenever we want to close it.
We need to trigger a function to close it so we can change the state of this state that top in this
case.
That's fine.
Don't worry.
We're going to do it right now.
So I'm going to go back to our project and I'm going to host the side door on a different file so I'm
going to create a new file and this one is going to be called side and then drawer that jacks so the
side door is going to be just a stateless function.
So I'm going to use the the in red react state those components going to press center and it will create
a side door for me.
So I'm in a mistake made changed I always make this mistake.
I don't know why something you know so side drawer with a capital S and then side door with a capital
S..
So this side drawer will be receiving some props which are all the configurations we need to use you
know the ancor maybe or maybe the open this top and everything else.
In this case we're going to be passing the open and the close props.
All right.
So first we need to import the drawer from the top so I have it right here.
So we have it right here drawer.
So I'm going to copy this one and paste it right here at the top import drawer from multi-role you I
court's always the same thing.
And then drawer them are going to be using list and then list item.
I have the list right here so I'm a little bit lazy so i going to copy and paste it's import list from
then material the core and then just list and we're going to be using one more thing I'm going to import
right here.
It's called a list item.
We're going to talk about this in a couple minutes.
So again is from matyr you ice core and then you know same name list item.
Right.
So we have there's three things we can be using.
Now this component will just return the drawer.
So I'm going to delete this step to open and close tag and say door open and close and inside of here
we will get you know our door.
So we're right now I'm going into say door.
That's good.
So the door just like we spoke briefly.
It receives a Natcore which is going to be where are we going to be opening it in the right or the left.
In this case is going to be that right now we have an open prop which is required.
We need to pass it and then we have a nun close which is what's going to happen whenever the we want
to close this.
And this one it's a function in this case.
So we didn't have that function right now.
So we're going to be passing it from the parents which is Hetter now from within.
Within Hetter we need to include the side door so I'm going to import.
Right.
OK I'm going to go at the bottom import then side door.
Just like this drawer from.
And then that for Slash and then side door.
So I'm going to copy this and I'm going to go at the bottom and include the side door on the on the
actual header.
So right that's the only thing we need to do right now.
Let me make it at self-closing tack.
So if you remember we need to be passing from parents to child.
The Open and the unclose property.
So right here we will get an open equals to you know something we're going to be adding right now and
then and close.
All right.
Open and close the open is going to be true or false if we want the door open whenever the app starts
it's going to be true or false so I'm going to store this inside this state and then door and that open.
We don't have the state going to create right now.
So we're going to go right here at the top and again going to say state open and close and we will be
adding the of course the state.
So in this case is door open.
And whenever the application starts I want it closed.
So it's going to be false.
All right so now we are we are passing this that state jor.
So the this when will we be receiving a prop called Open.
So we need to pass probes and then oh sorry props that open.
All right.
And remember this is a stateless component.
We don't need to use this that props.
It's not a class.
All right.
So now we need to create a function that it will tackling that this state door open whenever we want
to close it.
Now we didn't have this function or could it create right now it's real simple.
So I can run a function.
And whenever we run this function we're going to be passing a value in this case.
And then this is going to be does that toggle and then door open and close and then value.
Now maybe there is no need to pass a value we can just you know use a turnaround but the time for now
is just going to be passing the value.
I want to show you something else.
So inside side drawer whenever we click whenever the drawer wants to close we will fire this around.
OK.
So inside side drawer are going to be making a reference to the props we are passing which is probs
on close and then false.
So and this is why I want to show you because maybe you didn't know it.
Right here we are passing a prop called on close.
Right.
OK.
So this one is just a function.
We don't have this function.
You're going to create it right now.
So this function is going to be running this with the with an argument which in this case is going to
be false.
So from within here will trigger the this function called unclose on close makes a reference to this
the Tuggle and this unclose we see if that falls.
So grab false run this function and it's kind of a passing this to this.
So this pretty much are the same thing.
If I don't do this this value this double door will never receive that false.
I need to pass it from no child to parent.
That's why I want to show you this.
So we don't have this function is a really dumb function going to go with the top and say Tuggle dollar
equals you know just a function opening close and this will we will be setting the.
This nut said state opening close and it's going to be door open and then banlieue.
All right.
So we are receiving a value which is the actual prop which is just false.
We could just say you know false or something like that.
But in this case I wanted to show you this OK.
Right so let's try to open the talk of the sidebar so I'm going to refresh the web page.
I'm going to open and nothing happens because when I click it we are getting this Cancellara.
So whenever we are clicking it we are not really opening anything because the unclick it's just cancel
luck.
So we need to change it of course.
And we're going to be using the toggle drawer as why we are doing this like this.
So whenever we click the disk that toggle the drawer the value it's going to be true.
Right because we want that to change the state of the drawer open to true.
All right.
Right now it's false.
So if I reload the application I click it and we get the jar or I can remember if you change the default
defaults to true and you reload the application is going to you know start as open but we don't want
that.
In this case.
All right.
So everything works fine right now.
So of course in real life we're going to get something like this.
So notice when I hoover it can it get kind of this but in effect.
And if I click it we will of course go to a different section on the page.
But you're not going to do that right now.
So on the side door we need to add something called List and list items to show you right here.
So material you go to lists at the bottom you can get something like this nested list so you can get
this effect with lists.
And of course you can nest lists and everything else.
So we will be using this inside of that now.
All right.
So on the side drawer are going to go and create a list just like this year.
Remember we are importing this at the top so this list meets what kind of component we're going to be
using.
And in this case it's going to be a nav because we're using it inside of a navigation.
So inside of here we need to add each button.
We're going to be using right here and for this one we use the list item.
So I'm going to open and close that and this list item needs some configuration.
And in this case what is this list item is going to be.
And in this case I'm going to say button and all this is on the documentation.
So whenever we use button it will do that.
You know how we're in fact and everything else.
If you don't use it it's going to do something else.
So whenever we we click this button we need to do something.
So I will attach an on click with a function and for now we are just going to do console log.
And in this case the first button is going to be featured it's just going to say featured.
All right.
So this one will be the option.
Event Starts in which Actually it's you know when the event starts the main section of our Web page.
OK.
So.
Right.
Are going to write it.
Event starts and if I reload the application Mikko's that's going to open and we get you know that same
effect event starts in.
And if I click it and go to inspect we get the console feature.
All right.
So now pretty much we need to do the same thing for all the other options when you impose highlights
pricing and location and later we going to be creating a different function so we can scroll to a section
but it's a little bit more complicated than it is than it sounds.
So a list item.
The second one is going to be Benue info.
I mean do with capital and f o going to copy paste.
Sorry for that.
The mike is maybe too close.
So list item.
The next one is going to be highlights.
So he's going to write highlights.
There you go.
Sorry high lights.
There we go.
Copy paste.
Then we have the prising.
So let me remove this prising now we're almost done.
I'm going to copy one more and this one is going to be location location.
So I'm going to reload it.
And if we open we get all the options.
Now there's one more thing I want to do before we finish with the header and everything else.
So right now on the final one if I scroll to the top we get kind of a you know transparent effect.
And if you scroll down you know it shows with the background color.
So first to do this and to to check if everything is working with a fixed position.
I need to add more height to the you know to our application.
So I'm going to go to the app then yes.
And I'm just going to hard code some styling so we can you know simulate that we have actual real content
in our web page.
So I'm going to add height.
There we go a height of I don't know something big 100.
Yeah that's good pixels.
Very good.
And I'm going to change the background because I want to see that you know transparency.
So I'm going to ride corn flower blue.
You can put red or whatever doesn't matter.
So OK so we get this.
And if I scroll down the header it's in a position fixed.
So this this proposition fixed works.
Now when I when I am at the top of the screen when I want to do I want to give Does this transparency.
Right.
And when I scroll I went to show the color so we can do that.
And the next action.
Let's go to the next one.