All right so now we're going to be creating this transparency effect we get.
So when whenever the page loads and the head are it's on the top we want a transparent background not
a black.
So I'm going to create a new state right here and I'm going to say I don't know.
Hetter show some like that at her show and at the beginning whenever the page loads it's going to be
false.
OK.
So now right here instead of just hard coding the color I could ask the application for head or Joe
show.
It's false.
So if it's false We're going to show Transparent.
But if it's true we can show a color.
OK.
So it's going to be this dot state DOT show drawer.
Sorry had her show and I'm going to use a ternary.
So if it is true we can it show this color.
But if it's not we're going to do transparent.
Just like this transparent the application right now loads.
And this is false.
So it's going to go to this scenario.
So if I go to our application the application starts and we have a transparent color.
So now whenever we scroll we need to ask the application OK the user scrolled from the top.
Yeah.
OK.
Just change the color so we're going to do it through state.
Because whenever we change the states the application we renders and this state is going to be true.
So it's going to go to this scenario instead of this one.
Let me remove it.
There you go.
So what can we do.
So on the component did mount attached to the window an event listener and this listener is going to
listen for this cruel event.
No this is just a vanilla javascript not not react so at event just like this.
Sorry.
Let me do something else I forgot to do something.
I'm going to first go to the component mount so component at Mt..
Open and Close.
Now I'm going to make a reference to window Dodd then at event listener opening Krogh close and the
listener is going to be scroll and remember again this is vanilla Javascript.
So whenever you use a scroll to run a function.
So I'm going to say this that handle scroll we didn't we didn't have this function we can create it
right now.
This hander's call.
So I'm going to go right here at the bottom and create the function handle scroll.
Open and Close.
Let me just do it like this.
There's no difference anyways.
In this case because we are using a class.
So right you're just going to do console log user scrolling or something like that user.
Let me make it right.
All right.
So whenever the application loads the application after its mount it bounces.
It will add and even listener office scroll to our components.
So if I scroll I run we run our function.
This one handles Krull.
So on this one what we can do we can check the window scroll position and if it's greater than zero
then you know we don't show the caller but if it's greater than zero it means that the user scrolled
from the top.
So we changed a color.
All right.
So I got to into this for now I'm going to say F just a good old F and then of course an else.
So right here I get to be checking the window dot scroll and the why.
Because we only need to check the y axis not the horizontal axis.
So if this one it's greater than zero right we will do something.
If not we will do something else.
So what do we do we toggle the state of Hetter show.
So I'm going to say this that set stayed open and close and the draw were show for this one is going
to be true because it's greater than zero so we want to show the color.
And if it's not we're going to say false.
Right.
So false.
So if I were the application we and you know the application loads and you know this crawl is try here.
So we get the caliber you scroll up you know we are at the top.
So it goes to the Falls condition to the outs so we don't get the car.
And if we scroll down we get it.
And if not we don't get it.
So that you know the recall.
So this one works OK because this is a single page it's a landing page.
So we don't have a route because maybe if you're doing and you're adding an event listener on this page
and maybe on don't know and your application you have a different route where you didn't use this effect
would be a good idea to remove the add even listener instead of at it's going to be removed event listener
and you're going to be doing this on the component will unmount.
Always remember to remove the event listeners whenever you go to a different component where you're
not really using this.
OK.
So goes so everything works as expected for now.
All right so now we're going to be creating the you know the slider and the countdown on this one.
I made a mistake.
Let me just give me a second let me just fix it one second.
So this site you're sorry the event starts and this is the final one.
But I did this this project you know a few weeks ago and I have a date right here we calculate the date
and let me just give me one second let me find this one right here.
OK.
I modified this on the original you know file on the original project.
So the end starts in what does.
We pass a date in this case is going to be December 16th of this year.
So we have one 166 days and what it does it's going to calculate how many days minutes hours and seconds
until you know the event starts.
So this is what we're going to be doing.
And whenever the the application loads we'll use the transition and we will do this you know this slide
or this carousel.
OK.
So let's go to the next section and we'll start with the carousel and then with the the event starts
in and I'm going to skip this version of the project with all of this I'm going to upload it to this
section so you can get the code we have so far.