OK so let's create the slider for this.
So we have three different parts on this slider.
We have you know the actual slider.
We have this text with the name of the singer.
I've never listened to a singer before.
It's not my style.
I just choose someone that maybe you know someone popular.
I don't really like this music but that's OK with you I am much more like a jackass fashion that kind
of music you know really old.
So this div with the name of the singer is going to be on top of the slider and then on top and have
this event start.
And this one it's an obsession absolutely sticked to the bottom of the container.
Look up first before we do anything we need to create a place where we will be hosting the files.
So we're going to create a new folder and I'm going to call the section featured.
Now this feature will will contain an index dodgiest with all the other components.
So the index digests of this one is going to be just that re-act stateless component and are going to
change the name to featured in something like that.
All right.
Copy and paste.
Now again the container needs to be positioned relative so we can float this right here the bottom and
float this in the middle.
So I'm going to change the style.
Style equals to open and close position and then relative Vergon first thing.
Right here we're going up with the carousel in a minute.
But first I'm going to put div..
And then you know I'm going to put the container where we where we put this in the middle of the screen
and the class name for this one is going to be artist and then name and instead of this just a div with
a class name of wrap her.
Right.
And then of course the name of the artist.
I've never listened to this girl before the singer a more kind of a jazz fashion rock kind of guy but
you know I picked this singer because she's popular and everyone knows her.
And that's good.
So now of course if I reload the application nothing happens because we're not including this featured
component inside of the app.
All right.
So first we need to import so import featured from forward slash components for Slash featured and that
is that because we have an index so there's no need to put index right here.
So I'm going to make a reference to a featured opening close and if we reload the application we get
it.
Now the problem is that the div that contains this ariana grande and everything else is not big enough
to put this in the center.
And this is because the device that it's going to be expanding this container is going to be the slider
and we're going to be using re-act slick.
So let me go to react slick and get to the Get Help page.
So this is one reacts licked react carousel component.
So again this is a third party library where we can but we can use to create that kind of slide you
know behavior and right here we need it we can do this or you can add the CD and link in your H Tim
L which is the slick CSSA and the theme.
And we will meet the CSSA for the sliders.
So I'm going to copy this.
I'm going to go to I'm going to save this.
I'm going to go to that e-mail and I'm going to pace the styles because we are going to need it.
It's not you know it's going to look really really ugly.
Now if we go to the example we need to import slider from Riak slick and you know inside of a class
we need to pass the settings to the actual Slider.
It's a really really simple to use.
Right.
So we don't have a component that hosts this carousel.
So inside of feature I would create a new file called Carrousel.
Let me make it right.
All right.
Yes.
Now this one is going to be a classmate component or it could be a stateless component.
Going to create a stateless component react to stateless component.
So instead of carrousel we need to bring this import slider so we can import the slick slider and instead
of this of course we need to start passing the settings and creating the slider before we do that.
I going to go to the index and require this image carrousel or this carousel.
So import then carrousel from Carrousel.
There we go.
I'm going to copy and paste it down here.
OK.
So of course nothing is going to really happen right now.
So inside of the carousel we need to first do the settings.
If you go to the documentation we need to create a maybe a concert or let where we host the settings
of the actual slider.
So I'm going to do that since we have a stateless component.
I can just create a viral load right here called settings equals to open and close.
So I want to remove the dots and of course for this you can remove it check the documentation on this
so we can remove the dots and the dots are the you know the little dots we get at the bottom of the
slider.
So we can change positions.
I don't really want it got to say infinite just like this and true.
So it's going to start looping in an infinite way.
So then I would play.
So true.
And the speed is going to be 500 of course you can modify this into whenever you want doesn't matter.
Now the carousel are going to put this on on a container right.
And you can see why in a minute.
So this container and I'm going to put this on the bottom we'll have a class name of carousel and then
wrapper.
Now if you're wondering why I'm using you know custom CSSA and not using something like bootstrap or
something else it's because how boring would be to do call dash em asked 12 call dash em as Tony call
dash M-S And you know that would be really really boring.
So I did my own classes which has all the you know the properties right there.
So this class theme is going to be the actual wrapper.
And then I will do something I'm going to add a style I can change some styles and I'm going to add
an overflow.
It's going to be hidden just like this and I'm going to do something else.
Now if you notice whenever the application load this is the final one the height of the slider is the
height of the actual you know actual window.
If I scroll down the next component begins.
So if I make this smaller.
Make it a little bit smaller and reload the application the application.
Our component is going to calculate the height of the window and make it as big as that.
So scroll down the next component begins.
So we're going to do that.
Let me go back and if I reload again full with full height.
So how can we do this really simple.
Whenever the application loads or the components you know renders I want to calculate the height of
the screen and I'm going to be using template strings.
And then I can calculate the window.
And this is vanilla javascript not react windowed.
And I'm going to calculate the inner height and then of course I'm going to be passing pixels.
So whenever the application starts you know the height of the component is the height of the you know
the up the window.
So let me put a background so we can clearly see it.
So it's going to be red.
There we go.
So we get to read and if I go down you know that ends let us get let me remove this.
So what else we need to start adding the slider and the slider.
We just need to use the component we've imported the top pass the settings and inside put whatever we
want.
OK.
So right here I'm going to make a reference to this slider.
We are importing the top slider open close.
OK.
So we need to pass the settings so open and close.
Dot dot dot and then settings.
So if you are not really sure with your sex whenever we do dot dot dot instead of this we are putting
all the props everything we have inside this object because it is an object inside of the slider and
we pass it as props.
So it's going to be at the end you know be behind scenes.
It's going to be like dots equal to then infinite a call to something like that.
But you know it's much much much easier to do that than that and then pass the settings.
OK.
So right here we need to start adding the images Songun to say DIVX and image 1 something like that
then Divx image too.
And I believe we have three images for this singer.
So Image three.
OK.
So if I go here right here image one any fight.
Move it.
Image.
And same thing if I move it emits three.
OK.
So now we need to bring the images if we go to resources inside images we have slide one slide three
and slide two.
So we are going to import the images right here at the top so we can use it.
So import that is slide one.
You can call this again whatever you want.
As a matter right now.
And it's from that that forward slash that forward slash resources images and then slide one right and
all the other ones are going to be pretty much the same song going to copy paste and change this one
to two.
And this one today.
All right.
And the next one image slide three and this one slide three.
So now inside of this I'm going to delete this one I'm going to say Dave can create a new div with a
class name of carrousel image image Breguet and inside of here I will add style let me make it just
like this so you know a little bit nicer.
So instead of here you know I'll be adding a style and I'll be passing the background image as a prop.
Right.
So background equals opening close templates strings.
I'm going to say you are opening close and we need to pass the.
In this case the slide number one.
And then of course the height is going to be the full height of the window just like with it before.
So I'm going to copy from here.
So I'm going to copy paste.
So instead of adding the the node can have an EMG with source and passing a div with the background
so we can use that position cover or position contain.
We can use to make use of that.
Let me go right here now if I copy this one and you can see it right here I'm going to copy that image
number two.
And of course change the name because it's going to be image number two.
We could create a loop and loop it from function.
But this is really easy guys.
There's no way to do this.
We're going to do a lot of a lot of that in the next few projects.
OK.
So I'm going to reload it and we get it.
And if I move it we get the second slide and then we get the third slide and we start again.
If you scroll down everything else it's so good you know thing works really really really simple.
So the next step will be adding the event starts in.
So let's go to the next section and finish the featured component.