OK so let's create this component.
So we have a few things we are going to be adding a transition whenever the comput and LOTES and all
this logic.
But first we're going to create this component and you know some dumb some with some hard coded numbers.
OK.
So first we need a component where are we going to be hosting this so inside a feature I'm going to
call it time until could call.
You could call it countdown or something like that it doesn't matter.
So of course I need to import it from here.
So import.
I called it time until from 4:00 slash time until I get and I'm going to make a reference to this at
the bottom of this.
Or at time time until there we go.
Sorry for that.
So inside time until it's going to be real simple it's a class based component because we will have
a state that will manage all the numbers all the logic right here.
So I'm going to create a react class based component.
OK.
So there you go and it's going to be called time until we will have a state of something we will be
completing this later.
First we're going to create this you know the the layout for this.
So at the bottom are going to go right here to the render and the class name which is the container
of this section is going to be called Count down underscore and then wrap her count down.
All right count on wrapper and I'm going to call the and copy the keyword count down because we're going
to use it a lot.
So inside of here we have two different sections.
This event starts in and then you know the bottom part.
OK.
So first I'm going to create a div and the class name for this is going to be counted down underscore
and then top.
And this when it's going to say event starts in.
And if we check it you know we can it get it.
OK.
So then we have the bottom part of this which is you know a container.
We can create a div with a class name off of course the opposite of the other one which is bottom.
So inside of here we have four different items.
You have this one which is the one with the days the hours the minute and the seconds.
So we need four different dips with different values.
So it's kind of a template.
It's always the same one.
So I'm going to create a div with a class name of Countdown underscore item.
Now instead of here we have two different things.
We have the number and we have days or hours or minutes or seconds.
So I'm going to create a div with a class name.
There we go.
Class name.
And it's going to be Count town town and time sort of here in this case will be the days.
So I'm going to put them to 23 and then at the bottom I'm going to say div opening close.
And this one is going to be called two days and they're going to be adding a class to this one as well.
So class name and I call that countdown task.
All right.
So overload we have 23 days.
So we pretty much we need to repeat all of this and again we could create a function to loop all of
this but we will only to create an array with no different strings and everything else.
There's no need to do that.
So this one is going to be I don't know two and there's one.
It's ours going to copy and then paste it at the bottom and the next one is going to be 20 and then
minute.
So something like this.
Let me make this capital H.
Yes.
All right.
I'm going to copy this one in it's the last one and it copy paste and this one is going to be the seconds
and I don't know 40.
OK.
Can I reload it.
And we get it right.
So everything's good.
So now if you notice on the original one whenever we reload we are getting this transition.
So this transition comes from a third party library called re-act revealed.
Let me find it right here.
Re-act reveal and then get have
so there go re-act reveal.
So this is the get have of react with Bill.
It's really really simple to use and it's really really great.
So we have a number of different type of effects for different components Faid flip rotate bounce and
roll.
So you can check the documentation's.
You even have examples so if I go to one example you can get it right here with an example code with
what you need to import and what you need to use to fade it.
You know to the left and same thing for the ride top or bottom and you can even rotate and you can bounce
roll you know really really really simple to use.
So we're going to use this one and I'm going to be using the gate effect right now.
So I'm going to go at the top and since we have this re-active installed we have it right here and we
find it re-act reveal we can use it.
So inside instead of the time until I going to import then slide from oh sorry I'm using slide this
one slide and slide it from left to right.
OK.
So the slide from then react then reveal four slash.
And we need to bring it just like material.
So we agree with you.
OK.
There's no way to do this.
I just you know used to do this to put this in my column.
So now how can we use it.
Real simple.
We need to wrap whatever component whatever div or container we want to animate within this.
No this component does slide component.
So I'm going to create a slight opening close and I'm going to chop everything from here and I'm going
to paste it inside of a slide going to select all and then format selection you know just to make it
nice.
Now this slide meets to know where from where is going to be sliding from left or right or everything.
By default I believe it's left.
But anyways I just left.
All right.
So of course you have a lot of other properties inside the documentation.
You can use props right here customize the SS or component props so you can select a duration delay
which means how long it's going to wait after these component appears to you know create the transition
or the animation.
So you know left right we really know about this one.
What.
What else.
You have the distance.
The time out.
The mount on enter.
Maybe you can unmount an exit.
You can destroy that whenever the components goes out.
And again you have a lot of options.
No.
OK.
So let's go back right here.
And I want to slide to the left but I don't want to slide at this as soon as the page renders.
I want to wait a little bit before it shows.
So I'm going to use a delay property.
So the lay equals opening close.
They're going to wait one second after the component it's completely rendered.
So there you go.
Let me reload it.
All right.
You know looks nice.
OK.
So what is it.
So now what we need to do we need to read all the logic to populate the numbers right here.
So let's go to the next section and do this.