So let's see the logic for this.
So what I want to do what we want to do is that whenever the component loads we want to trigger a function
that is going to get the deadline.
You know where this event is going to start and the date right now and we're going to compare both.
And of course if the event already passed we're going to display zero or maybe something else.
But if not we're going to do some math operations and calculate how many days until that date.
So whenever the component load we need to trigger that function and remember that we're going to be
animating the numbers right here so the display how much left.
So we need to run the same function after one second so after each second we need to run it again and
get the numbers again.
So first we're going to go right here at the bottom and say component that Mount opening close.
So we're going to create and trigger function.
Now this function are going to call it gain get don't get get.
Sorry did not get get time until opening close.
All right.
So this component mount will be triggering this function on a loop after each after one second.
So for this we can use a set interval.
So after one second begin to be running a function.
So it's going to be after one second.
Now of course we need to do this not get time until and begin to run this function.
Of course nothing happened so far.
Now we need to know where or when actually the deadline of this show is going to be.
You know when it's going to be a singer doing the show so we're going to host this inside of the state.
The state is going to go right here and say deadline sounds like that.
So the date is going to be first the month in this format than coma space then the day coma space and
the year.
So this is the formal beginning to be using.
So then coma and right here we're going to be storing how many days how many hours how many minutes
and how many seconds.
And this is going to come it's going to go from the time until.
So first we have days.
Not that eight days.
OK.
Sorry.
So then we have zero days.
Right.
The application starts with zero.
So then coma we have hours then we have zero then coma.
We have minutes.
All right.
Same thing.
We have zero and then seconds and then again zero.
All right.
So we have a deadline right now.
So whenever we run this function I want to pass to the function.
You know the the deadline is going to be and then when this is going to end.
So winter is going and it's going to be the deadline.
So we passed this that state that that line.
So instead of doing this you can just leave this to empty.
Set of game time game time until you can get get it from this that state that deadline this doesn't
change when the application loads.
You know I'm pretty much doing the same thing.
So OK so here's the thing.
Here's the important part.
I'm going to create a barbell called time.
Now time is going to get that line and it's going to get to today's state and it's going to get it.
Get them both and it's going to arrest this deadline.
Minus the current date.
So if you get a negative number it means that the date of the event already passed that's what's going
to happen.
So if it didn't pass it's going to be a positive number.
So I'm going to go.
I'm going to go right here I'm going to say date dot pars opening close and are going to make a reference
to the the argument we are passing which is deadline and deadline.
All right.
So it's going to be minus date same thing Date dot parse open it close and we calculate the new date.
So I'm going to bring today's date.
Right.
So if I cancel law I'm going to do cancel law and I can look.
Time with me reload the application.
We're going to get you know the current time after 1 second.
Now if I change this to January and let me change it first Jan. And we are on break here on July.
So of course the date or so we should be getting a negative number.
And we do.
All right.
So now what is simple.
What we can do we can create a conditional if time.
It's less than zero of course.
We can do some.
Do something else.
I'm not going to really do it right now.
Maybe saying date past something like that.
You know something simple we could hide.
You know this component.
I'm not going to do it.
Begin to do a lot of things a lot more difficult than this and fun than this.
So now what do we need to do we need to calculate each second date hour and minute.
OK.
So I'm going to create our Marvel and let me go.
So I'm going to do Kunst And first I'm going to get the seconds so the seconds you're going to use a
math dot then floor opening close.
Now to get the seconds what do we need to do is to bring the time divided by 1000 and then get it from
60.
So opening close one more time.
So each time that one falls for Slash 1000 and then by 60.
So if I do a console log for the seconds I'll just show you
console.
So of course to date pass.
Let me change to December.
All right.
So we get 16 15 14 until the of course the next minute.
So I'm going to copy this one and I'm going to do the minutes so minutes and the math it's kind of a
pretty much the same but not really after the 1000 fours.
And then 60.
That is it with numbers.
Now with the hours is going to be a little bit different.
So I'm going to copy this one for now and say hours and I I'm going to delete this one right here.
What floor.
So for the hours we do again our parentheses and then time and then forward slash and we need to open
a new Burnand to see.
So all of this is of course vanilla Javascript.
So we need to do 1000 then star than 60 star and then 60 and everything is going to be by 24.
So this is how we get the hours.
Of course you can get us get this from Stack Overflow.
So then four instead of hours we can calculate the dates.
So four days is going to be the time this is going to be the same for us.
Instead of Birnam see 1000 by 60 by 60 by 24.
And then of course I'm going to remove this 24.
That's it.
And ok.
I have one more.
Me.
Just make sure of this dropping everything in one Princie.
So there we go.
This is what we need to do.
Time than 1066.
And then 24.
And this is how we get the dates.
So now we have the seconds minutes hours and days.
So what do we need to do.
We just need to set the stage so this that said state opening close and then days.
And OK since we are using the same names for the same values we can use some six magic so we can use
days hours just like this.
Then we have minutes and then we have seconds.
So this if you don't know if you don't know ESX that much this is going to be translated as days equals
equals equals days.
It's a key value pair.
So if the key and the value are the same name we can do it like this.
And U-6 will translate this for us.
So if we love the application of course nothing really happens right now because everything happens
on the state and right here we have kind of a hard coded values right here on the bottom of with this.
OK so first we need to calculate the days so open and close.
And this one is going to be equal to this state that takes.
All right we're going to do the same thing for hours instead of days.
It's going to be hours copy then go to minutes and there we go.
And the last thing it's seconds so seconds.
Right.
Let's see if this works.
All right.
So we get two seconds and the minute changes and everything starts again.
Right.
So everything works.
OK so now I'm going to sip this.
This said I'm going to skip the project so you can get the files until this section and we're going
to be moving forward to the next one to this one and it's going to be with simple.