OK so now we're going to be creating this module this component the venue info and then highlights are
going to be real simple which is do transitions and animations with the same re.
Right here same Briac reveal we've been using that really hard to use.
So like I told before this the first project it's really simple is just to warm up the next one next
once you know the second and the third are not going to be that simple.
They're going to be very long and we're going to do a lot of things.
All right.
So let's start with this one.
This one this component.
I'm going to call it the venue info.
So I'm going to go to component's create a new folder called Benue info.
Now inside of your index dodginess and instead of index dodgiest this info is going to be a re-act stimulus
component so reactive stateless components and again to change name to venue info or something like
that.
All right.
If you notice on the original on the final one you have a calendar icon and a location icon and they
are inside the resources icons you have location and Kandar.
OK.
So we need to kind of bring it.
So import let me do it right.
Import and I'm going to call it icon and then calendars like that from opening close that that for Slashdot
that for Slash resources we have it inside images.
We have it inside icons and then forward slash.
And I believe it's a calendar.
There we go.
All right.
So then we do the same thing.
But the other one instead of Candar is going to be location.
So can location.
And of course same thing here.
Can I delete it for Slash and location P and G.
Right.
OK.
So first we need to create this wrapper.
So it's going to be this step.
So class name opening close and I added a class called back black because the bad container for this
one is kind of black.
So whenever we add something right here I don't know whatever.
And we can put in LOTES.
We should because something of course we need to include this inside the V right here.
The actual page.
So let me go there.
One second me component's index app.
Yeah.
So import import Benue info from that for Slash components and then venue info.
Right.
So I'm going to make a reference to Benue info.
Open and close self-closing stack.
And if the compound reloads we get back with you.
Hahaha.
All right.
So I going to go back to Benue info now.
We need to we have kind of a centered container right here.
So again we're going to create a div inside a div a class name of center center and then wrap her right
now inside of the center wrapper.
I created a different wrapper.
This is something you know I would like to do sometimes depending on what I'm going to doing or going
to do.
So I'm going to just wrap everything inside of a new wrapper.
That's OK.
So we have three different properties now.
Then inside of this A B and rubber We have two different parts we have the last left box in the right
box.
And since this one uses flex we just can make a reference to a div and this one go to the left and the
other one goes to the right.
Just like this.
Find out which is going to create the first one.
So the first one has a class name of V and and then item.
All right then the end item has a div and I'm going the the inside of the B B and item.
I am going to get a class name of B and outer you know see why in a minute.
And inside a different wrapper with dvn.
And in this in this case is going to be inner.
OK.
So class name be an inner or so outer and inner.
Now of course this square is kind of an in a position absolute.
So it's kind of floating.
So this is where the where this icon is going to go on at a different place of course.
So the time doesn't matter.
So inside of that we an inner eye are going to say div and I'm going to add a class name off and it's
going to be an icon.
So this is actually the I can be a guinea Using going to use right here and the icon.
I give it a name of a square now b c k Red is going to be for the background red and then the other
one for the background of yellow.
But the first one is red.
So we're going to make just a reference to the first one.
Now if I go back.
OK.
We have the box and we have the actual you know box right here.
Now instead of here I'm going to say Dave I'm going to create a class name of B an icon and inside of
the ME AN ICON are going to be adding more classes.
And what I'm going to be wanting.
It's the icon.
So it's a div with a red square and on top floating on top of the main container we have the actual
icon.
So what I'm doing here is just adding the icon directly from the component and not through CSSA.
So background open and close.
We use templates strings you are l and we make a reference to the calendar icon.
We've imported the top right.
OK.
So OK.
So this is it if I reload it we get you know the Red Square and the calendar icon.
Then of course if you go to the final we have a date and we have a time.
OK.
So after the see and icon are going to go and create a new div called div and actually adding a class
name of B and title and this one will be the title which is event date and time sign and copy paste
it and then have the description.
So I'm going to create a div with a class name of B an desk of description and begin to copy this which
is $7.
You can you can put whatever you want right here.
Doesn't really matter.
So the application.
That's it.
We get it.
So I'm going to copy to be an item going to put it right here at the bottom and it just duplicate the
contents.
So since we are we are using on the container opposition flexed.
It's going to put it on the correct position.
But the changes and the color of this and the text of course changes as well.
So on the second one instead of B C K red it's going to be b c k yellow and the icon is going to be
location and the data inside is going to change.
So the title is going to be event location.
You can put again whatever you want.
And on the address you can put whatever you want and it's up to you.
Then again this is just for practice.
So if you're below the application we get it and then your review is simple to do.
I'm not teaching you anything new right here.
But the only thing is that the difference is that what whenever the application loads and we load the
component you're going to do that same transition.
And this comes from re-act reveal so at the top we don't have it.
So we need to import it.
And what we can to be using is the soome option inside re-act reveal.
So I'm going to copy this from here and paste it right here at the top.
So we are importing soome from re-act reveal for Slash suit.
So how to use it.
OK.
So first I'm going to go right here on the to the first item and I'm going to say soome Oh sorry soome.
Open and Close.
Now organic.
Copy this.
Just chop it and put it right here OK so soon.
If you remember any of the all this this options inside react we'll.
We have some configuration we can use.
So in this case I want to set a duration so I'm going to say duration and this is how long the animation
is going to last.
So whenever we load the component we should be getting the duration.
So let me save it and go again.
So we go.
We have that soome and it last 500 milliseconds.
Now I want to do I want to do the same thing with the other one but I want to you know DeLay give you
a kind of delay.
I want to load this one first sumed this one first and then this one after this one it's done.
So I will do pretty much the same thing.
I will wrap everything.
I mean the second item inside of assume opening close.
And then I can copy the contents put it inside of the second soome And in this case we will give a do
ration again of 500.
Of course five hundred and decide just like with it before just going to do a delay delay of five hundred.
So when the application reloads
the application reloads first the first we have left and then we have the second one and that isn't
good.
We have the second component totally was it going to be really simple.
So the next one is going to be the highlights.
And we do pretty much the same thing but we do three different.
We have three different components.
The top the left the ride.
And we have different transitions on this ones.
So let's go to the next section and do the highlights.