All right.
So let's do the highlights.
So when are you of course girl.
We have highlights this gets animated.
And this is one component and then we have the other component which is going to be animating the number
right here.
And then of course we have a different part where are we going to be sliding towards left.
All right.
Well let's start reading this.
Going to go back to our project and inside of our project I'm going to create a new directory where
we're going to be hosting the files and I'm going to call it highlights again.
Call this whatever you want.
So inside highlights I will have an index that is and this index that Diaz of course will be will be
rendering the components inside of here.
OK.
So I'm going to create a re-act stateless components and I'm going to call this highlights.
All right.
So inside of here I can add a class name for the wrapper and it can be called high lights and then highlight
wrapper.
All right.
So instead of here going to create two different components one for the description which is the first
thing we're going to do.
And then you know for the actual discount.
So OK so we don't have this component.
I'm going to go right here and create a new file and I'm going to call it description.
This is the first one we're going to be creating.
So the description is really simple.
So we just need a yakked stateless component.
And I made a mistake called the descriptions and it's description and the fix it right now.
All right.
So instead of description's is going to be description.
So on this one we're going to reveal this this that top part with a fade transition.
So straight ahead I'm just going to import fade fade from re-act reveal for Slash.
And then of course fate.
All right now the.
Right here on their return since we need to wrap everything inside of a fade.
I'm just going to say fate and the content is going to be a Dave with a class name of center wrapper.
The title is going to be in H-2 and I'm going to call the highlights.
There you go.
Highlights.
And then of course the text is going to be inside of a div with the class name of highlights or highlight
description as a recession.
And of course I'm going to copy some lorem ipsum.
You can go to law ipsum and copy some dumb some text.
So I'm going to save it.
And of course if you reload the application we are not getting anything because I'm not including the
highlight index and I'm not bringing that description here.
All right.
We're going to do that right now.
So first we need to import it so import.
And notice how how easy was this.
You know to add the transmission so import this corruption from open forces close description.
All right.
And then I make a reference to the description component right here inside.
And then of course on the app we need to bring the highlights component on the app.
So import highlight from dot dot for Slash components for Slash highlights could be highlight instead
of highlights and that's fine.
And then of course since we want to bring the index there is no need to make reference to that.
And then instead of here opening close.
All right we'll see what happens next.
You know it's fine.
So I scroll down and we get the fate of highlights and notice that right now the via's code.
It's kind of a boring is doing a great out on this components be a code.
Actually it has.
It has a few bucks.
I've updated the operation and it fails by fails doing this.
So I don't know what it is have never read and of course we have it right here.
But you know if I close it and open it let me do this.
Well sometimes it clears the air.
I don't know what the obvious code or mismatch error.
Right is a bug.
All right so let's do the second part of the highlights.
So I'm going to go to highlights.
Create a new file and this one is going to be called Discount dot J Yes.
So this discount is not going to be that simple.
We're going to do a few things right here.
So I'm going to create a re-act class based component and called discount.
All right.
And we use a phase transition and a slight transition from Briac we veal.
So I will do import fade from re-act reveal again and then we can get a B calling it.
We can call the same thing fade and we do the same same thing with a slide.
So Slide copy and paste slide bigot.
OK.
So now if we take a look at the final one we have two different parts the left and the right.
So instead of here I'm going to say div add a class name off and center wrapper.
These are you know the wrapper classes instead of here are going to wrap everything inside of a class
name of a discount wrapper.
All right.
So pretty much this one is the one that is adding the color.
You know and this one is one that it's centering everything doesn't matter.
OK.
So instead of here we have two different sides.
We have the left side which is going to be a div with a class name of discount.
We always use pretty much the same thing.
And then poor centage percentage we get.
So me just copy the discount so I didn't have to type it.
And then inside of here we have two pens.
So going to say is pen.
And then another is Pam.
Now the original has the spine and top with the number.
And this one at the bottom.
So the first one will have the number and we will be getting the number from state.
And then we will be adding the percentage something like that we find a percentage that we go.
All right.
And the other one is going to say chest off.
So if I reload the application of course we need to include it sorry for that.
Imported.
So I'm going to go I'm going to the index of highlights and in port we call it discount.
There's count from four slash and discount.
Sorry for that I forgot to do this happens sometimes.
So inside discount we should be getting that.
Twenty three percent.
And then the off of course we're going to be animating element this and we're going to do it through
state.
You know we could do it with just with javascript but begin to do it through state or not.
So the next component they want in the right is going to be just active and with a class name of this
count with not a capital D discount.
And then this question.
All right.
And on top we have an H3 and I know this is the boring part.
We are almost done and we can focus more on Javascript.
So the title is purchase tickets before.
Again this is just practice you can type whenever you want.
Doesn't matter.
So then we have a paragraph and again I'm going to copy these.
Lauren ipsum then have a p.
And then we have a button right here we have this button.
But later in the application we will have the same button.
So it makes no sense for us to copy to create a button right here and this component and then do the
same code right here.
So we're going to be creating reusable component for this but we're going to do.
We're going to leave this to the last.
All right.
So after this you know after these discount description I'm sorry after the paragraph we're going to
go make some space after the paragraph.
Well adding a day of just a div with Button.
We know that the button goes though it goes there.
So if I scroll down everything looks nice.
So now let's add the transitions first because it's the easy part.
So I'm going to go right here.
I'm going to bring Faid opening close and I'm going to put everything inside by default live it's left
then we're going to be adding slide on the other components.
So I'm going to put slide chop everything put it inside.
And then of course I can say I want our right transition so OK.
We had we kept the fate.
And then we get the right.
So you know looks looks nice.
So now what we need to do I need to animate this number and we can do this through state not just maybe
Javascript.
So I'm going to go right here and create a state state.
Equals opening close and I need to say when does this count starts.
And when the discount is going to end you know it's going to animate from zero to I don't know 30 percent.
So the first stage is going to be this count and then start and it starts at zero then pretty much the
same thing but it's going to say discount and it's going to start up and so it's going to stop at 30.
So when I want to do.
And if you notice whenever the application loads this Faid transmission's takes some time.
This transition of the fade takes time.
So what happens if it triggers the animation of the zero to 30 when the component starts and not when
this you know this component this part of code starts fading in.
So where are the tablets.
You know try to simulate this.
If I reload the application this of course will trigger and it will start.
Does this count.
You know that animation with a number and by the time we reached this part we've already have the authority
you know makes no sense.
So what we need to do we need a way to trigger that animation that function only when we have the component
rebuild already.
So again just like before the library it's really really good.
They give us a call back.
So after everything it's revealed or this component this element gets revealed we can run a callback
function.
And there's this calls on reveal just like this.
So on reveal we can trigger whatever function we want.
So we can to just trigger a function called this percentage again call this whatever you want percentage.
No port centage.
All right.
So we didn't have this function going to go right here.
Again to say percentage open and close.
So the main This function is going to do me make it like this.
What this function is going to do is going to check is going to check if that didn't this count start
equal to the discount end and we're going to be updating that discount start and this is what we're
going to be rendering right here.
This is what we're going to be doing.
And seems like I to another this percentage it's because I never saved it.
Now if you save it you go.
So what I can do I'm going to go right here am I going to show you with code simpler.
So first we're going to check if the discounts start it's greater than the discount end.
If it's not an update to state with this count start plus one.
Pretty simple.
So OK so I'm going to say this that state that this count start it's less than this that state that
this count and all right.
And if it's of course if this condition goes through we're going to go right here and said the state
of the new value on this count start.
So this can start equals this state that this can start plus one.
All right.
I could do this a lot smaller but I'm going slow on the first project and I'm going just easy.
So of course whenever the Faid gets real that the element gets revealed we will run the function the
function will go true because zero it's not greater than 30 and we will be updating the states with
one.
So on the next render discounts start it's going to be equal to one.
All right.
So I'm going to save this and I'm going to go right here.
I'm going to say this that oops that state discount sorry discount start.
So we should be getting zero in after the render.
We're going to be counting of course we're going to be getting one because we are adding one to the
mix.
So if I go Faid we have one.
And I'm going to add the percentage.
So help page reloads we get the fade in and we do the callback and we are just getting one.
But the thing is that we need to get 30 so we need to run this function right as many times we need
to reach the number 30.
And of course when we do this when we do said state when we said state we're updating the state.
So the application gets re rendered or gets updated so we can grab the component that update and run
this function again if we actually we really need to so.
So it's going to be set at a set time out because I need to kind of wait a little bit of time before
we can update the number so we can you know see the transition.
So it's going to be really small.
I'm going to show you why in a second.
So if I do this that percentage whenever the component APS-C updates the first time we're going to run
it again.
Now it's going to be two then we're going to run it again.
It's going to be three four and five and so we'll reach 30 and we are not updating the state any more
so this component did update will not run any more.
So I'm going to save it reload the application and get it now this Thursday it's the amount of time
the flow from that that's going to take for the animation from number two number would actually not
an animation.
But you know looks like an animation.
So if I put 300.
The transition is going to be real slow.
Look.
That is it.
That's why.
So that's why we use third and that is it.
So this component it's pretty much done.
So the next one is going to be the pricing.
And this one we have a few interesting things.
But before we start doing this are going to do the buttons and this button we will be using this on
this one.
So we will create every usable component with the button right here.
So let's go to the next section and just do that.