All right so let's create that re-useable button.
So from time to time you will need to use some code that of course you can if you're going to you're
going to be using the whole time in this case it's just a button because of course this is a single
simple simple application.
But on the next to the next project you begin to do a lot of reusable code because we have tons of sections.
So it kind of makes sense for us to reuse some code.
So OK so we added first going to go to components and create a directory folder werent going to be hosting
this reusable code.
I'm going to call it right now.
But sometimes I call it.
I know it's completely up to you.
So inside you tell us I will create a new component called my button.
Yes.
So this one is just a button we're going to do something very simple right here.
OK.
So this my button is going to be chose to react statelets component.
So it's going to be called my button.
So this component will be getting some props and pretty much what we need to do we need to use a button
from material real material UI material UI.
So let me just show you the button first.
So right here a component demos and then buttons.
So this is what we can be doing.
We're going to get a button and we will be adding an icon to the button just like this.
All right.
So we're going to go back to our project and he out of here I need to import than Bunin from AD material
core.
And then of course button.
OK.
Button up.
All right.
OK.
So now on the if you go to the original we have kind of an icon for a ticket and that this comes from
resources.
So we have right here at the ticket icon.
So we need to import it as well so import ticket icon from opening close that that forward slash that
that for Slash resources for Slash images lash and icons and ticket.
There we go.
OK.
So instead of here the only thing that this component will return is the material you buy button just
like this button open and close and this button will have the image and the text.
But we're going to be passing the text.
What we have inside the button through prompts and a lot of other properties properties through prompts.
So first we're going to just create the button EMG.
We have a source and the source is going to be ticket icon just like this.
Me make it like this so we can you know it's a little bit nicer.
And then I get to close the stack.
So instead it's going to be adding a class a class name of icon and then image and I will add an alt.
If not you're going to get a warning.
So icon buttons something very very simple.
So then we're going to have a text of button whatever.
Doesn't matter right now.
And this button needs some configuration.
This material component needs some configuration if you want to make the button a link just because
it is a link.
We need to add an H ref property.
So right now I'm just going to be adding Google that come.
But BKB passing the ref through prompts.
So then we need a variant.
And this is one of the props of you know of button and we have several options in this case.
I'm going to use contained the size the size is going to be small and we could pass all of this as props
but you're not really going to.
So then style open and close and then background going to change the background too.
And I'm going to be passing the background color through props so props that b c k.
Actually we didn't have it so far ascending it with just maybe red.
And then the caller is going to be I don't know what are we going to get kind of a template right now.
So now instead of discount we need to include this Bonnin and use it.
So I'm going to go to this account and we go at the top and import the Bunin from you Tilse.
So import my button.
There you go.
My button from that that forward slash utilities for slash my button and I get a copy in my bottom and
included of course we're going to get a dumb button but a dummy button but doesn't matter right now.
All right.
Let's see what we get.
So I'm going to go to the our product.
You know we get the button if I click it is going to take us to Google that come.
All right.
So you know we get the Bunim.
So no if you are maybe on a different component and we bring a button and then of course we put the
component my blood and right here you get to get the button doesn't matter if we are in highlights or
featured or whatever.
So this is a reusable component.
Now.
My button needs to be sending some props because maybe you want to change the color or maybe we went
into the link to be on a different to do different location.
So we need to pass the props as props.
We are getting it right here.
So I'm going to go right here and again to say that text is going to be equal to.
I don't know in this K purchased tickets let me do a capital P purchase and then tickets next the b
c k which is the background I'm going to use the yellow color f f 8 I'm sorry f f A then 8 0 0 0.
Then the color is going to be equal to white color.
One two three.
And then the ref or I'm going to call it like better.
So I don't know.
And so this one is going to be maybe the same thing we were using right here.
Google's outcome doesn't matter.
OK so now this my but in this use of component will be receiving all these prompts so we can use the
props right here.
We can access prompts when say say Propst that text and we can get the purchase tickets so we are rendering
the reusable component with the props of whatever we are you know including my button.
Then we have the basic K which is the background.
So I'm going to say props that b c k we have the color I believe I called it.
Caller Yeah.
So props dot color I can to save it.
And we get the yellow and the white collar so next one it's going to be the link.
So on the property kind of opening close and we say props that link I believe I called that link.
Yes.
All right.
So if I look it we go to Google you know that works right.
So this reusable component.
This button we will be using the button right here.
So now there is no need to redo this code again.
We just import it call it pass the prompts.
And that is it.
Right.
How easy is that.
OK.
So I'm going to of course skip the project.
The code we have so far which is this one.
And you can download it and maybe inspect if something is not working in your project.
And of course we're going to be moving forward to prizing and then you know the location and the footer
which is they are going to be really really simple.
And then of course we're going to be passing to the next project which is going to be you know pretty
not pretty hard but you know hard enough.
OK.
So let's go to the next section and do the pricing.