Right.
So we're going to build the next component which is the pricing component.
So OK so I'm going to.
This is the final one.
You know the local host 3 0 0 2.
And if I reload the application we get this transition.
So first we get the one in the middle and then we get the other two.
So this is what we're going to be doing is going to be really really simple right.
So first when I'm going to do to close everything right here because I have a lot of files open I don't
really want that.
So the first one is the app that I guess which is you know we are going to require import the next component
and this one is going to be the prizing so I'm going to go to components create a new directory called
prising makes sense.
Prising up message.
So an inside prizing of course we just need one file.
I'm not going to divide this on maybe two different places.
So prizing and it's going to be Index index that Jap's.
Right.
OK.
So this one is going to be a class based component.
I'm going to feed the boxes from the state so re-act class based component and instead of index this
one is going to be prizing.
All right.
Going to change the name.
Now I'm going to go to abdicates and include this imported import prizing from.
And same thing DOD for Slash components than for Slash and pricing.
Oregon says we have an index.
There's no need to put in x.
And then of course I will include it right here.
Now we're going to go back to our project and of course we get nothing because we pretty much have nothing.
OK.
So first are going to be adding you know the structure for this the container def is going to be a class
name of B C K and then black.
Remember we've already used this rather than inside.
We will have a div just like this.
And with the class name off and I'm going to use the center wrapper we use before center and then wrapper.
And this one is going to be the prising section.
All right.
So on top we get an age to tag with the prising prizing.
And then of course we get the you know the container that will contain the three boxes.
So I'm going to say Dev and the class name for this one is going to be prising wrapper prizing and then
wrapper.
All right.
And of course right here we get the boxes.
So if I reload the application we get prizing and then we get boxes so we are on track.
So right here when I want to do I want to run a function trigger function whenever the component renders
and that get from state whatever is that we need to output to show.
OK.
So first to do this before calling the function we need to state where we can get the information.
So I'm going to say state open and close and we will have several things we have the price.
You know the category the description and the link where is where this is going to go.
So OK so first I'm going to start with prizing.
So I'm going to say prices prices and since we have three and we need to loop an array I'm going to
just loop this charade prizes.
So the first box is going to be 100.
The second one is going to be 150.
And the last one is going to be to 50.
You know this one is the expensive one.
Then we have the positions you know balcony medium star whatever.
So positions you can call again this you can call this whenever you want.
So the first one is balcony.
The second one I call that medium and the next one is going to be you know the star just in front of
the time.
Then we have the scription and for this one for now it's going to be an array.
We three lines of descriptions so you can do this.
You can put whatever you want inside.
I got a copy of some I have right here.
You can go to learn tips and you know get the text from there that doesn't matter.
So I'm going to put koma going to go to the next line.
Let me get this one.
I'm going to copy the other one.
So if there's been you know it's when I I need to do it again at your home you can skip this and the
next one is going to be the last line.
LMC I got a mistake.
See why this is why forget coma.
And that's it.
We have the description coma description.
OK.
And then of course we have the link.
So I'm going to put a coma on this and then link to I'm going to call that link to.
And again we we've got an array.
So the first one is I know it's GTP call for Slash and then don't know sales forward slash B for balcony
and then pretty much we do the same thing.
You can put whatever you want right here.
Now on this Web sites most of times when they you know you have you create a page on the page where
they sell something.
Most of the times the link will take will take the user to a different place where they can complete
the purchase.
That's the way it works.
So I'm going to do the same thing so this one is going to be.
There's one is going to be this for medium and the other one is going to be star.
Everything is in order.
Right.
The first one its balcony the first always the same position on the right.
So this one is done.
So right now we have the stage so we can loop this and generate the content right right here right.
So we can add it.
So I'm going to create a function called show Buxus.
So it's going to be show and then Buxus it's going to be equal to a function and that function will
return some GSX.
That's why I'm using the parentheses and not this whenever we use parentheses we can return some div
and that will be rendered whenever we call the function.
For example if I put.
And now I go right here and make call to this that shoeboxes.
And you know the function I'm going to reload the application and begin to get.
Hello.
All right.
And there's no need to do this.
If we do a bracket just like this one will not work and all top this is not going to work.
We need to do a return and do this and put to death inside.
I'm telling you this because maybe you didn't know you know and you're wondering why are you using brackets
or parentheses instead of brackets.
So that's fine.
But in this case we can use the premises.
All right.
So now what do we need to do.
We need to loop at least the prices because we have always three positions on each array.
So we can loop this and then get all the other positions with the iteration number right.
So with the index number.
So for now I'm going to do this.
I don't need it.
So I'm going to say this that state that they're going to use prizes.
That map going to loop over it.
And in each iteration I'm going to be passing something and running something again since we want to
return some GSX from this map if we use brackets this one will not work if we use parenthesis it will
return some GSX.
So if I do dev and now right here are going to say a box makes sense.
And then the iteration.
So the box is going to be each item on each iteration.
The first iteration which is the one the first is going to be 100.
Balcony the first description and the first link.
So the first div which is the container will have a class name of prizing and then item right.
Prising item.
Then inside of here we get a different wrapper.
Which class can it be.
Prising per izing enter.
And then we leave it.
I call that rubber and I'm going to call.
I'm going to copy the prizing keyboard and look at instead of here we have pretty much three different
things.
We have the title which is that the top part actually.
Then the description and then the button.
OK.
So the first day of going to college and the class name is going to be prising underscore title.
And of course right here we're going to get the title.
All right the next one is going to be the description.
So I'm going to do Dave create just a div with the class name of prizing.
And of course the scription and right here we're going to get the description or whatever.
OK.
So then Dave and the next one the class name and prising buttons.
So prizing and then buttons and right here we get a button at the bottom.
So in theory I reload this we should be getting three different boxes and we do title this kitchen and
then button.
OK.
So seems we are looping something we can get the values from the loop.
The price we can get it from the box or we can call this state the price and then the number of the
iteration.
We can do that.
So for the title we can get two different pens.
So the first pen it's the actual prize.
So again a dollar sign or currency sign.
And I could use box or I could use this that state the price to use.
Does that state that prizes.
And then of course the position of the iteration and it's going to be of course 0 1 and 2.
So we get 1 100 and 200.
So that is good.
So next one is going to be next the next responder which is the position.
So we do the same the same thing.
There's that state that positions and again the iteration number the net and the next one is going to
be the description.
So there's that state that the desk called the desk and then the iteration number.
All right all right that is good.
So next one is going to be the Bunin if you remember we have a component a reusable component.
So what we can do we can include the component at the top and make use of it.
So it's going to be import my button from that dot for Slash us that's why we have you Telles.
And then my button.
All right.
So now I'm going to go at the bottom and instead of this are going to be passing the button.
Right.
So OK.
Let me make it right my button.
And instead of my brain I could make this a you know self closing.
Right.
So if you remember we need to pass some configurations.
So first it's a text we need to add.
In this case I'm going to say I don't know just something simple.
The next one is going to be the background color so B C K and B are the property for this same yellow
f a 8 zero zero.
The next one is going to be the color of the text which in this case it's going to be white because
it makes sense.
And the next one I don't remember the name I believe was called a link.
Yes.
Like.
All right it's going to go back and the link is going to be.
And if you remember we have the link right here.
So the property for this is going to be this that state that link or actually link to and then of course
the iteration.
All right.
And so we get it.
So if I open this sales B and the next one is going to be I really am.
And that works.
Everything works.
So now the thing is that if we take a look at the original let me just reload the application.
We have a transition and first the one that it's appearing at first.
It's the middle one.
It's going to be this one.
So we cannot add a transition in order.
What we need to do is to do something else so how can we do this.
How can we make this for the second one appear first and then the other ones.
All right if you want to do it on your own you can you can do it no problem.
I'm going to show you now I'm going to use a state so I can store it inside of the state a delay.
Right.
Because it makes sense.
So OK so I'm going to say delay.
So the first iteration on the delay is going to be 500.
So the first element before you to Pierce is going to wait a half second.
Now the middle one needs to appear first.
So there's one it's zero.
It's just going to show.
Right.
Right away.
And the third one is going to show with the first one.
OK.
So now we need to use that transition from re-act reveal.
So I'm going to go right here.
Import soome from.
And then of course re-act reveal four slash and then the name of what we are bringing in right here
which is suit.
All right.
So now what do we need to do.
We need to wrap this component and instead of returning just a div we need to return.
Assume component.
OK.
I'm going to copy paste it.
And there we go.
So now this soon needs some configuration.
First we will need a key.
Remember that when we act whenever we loop something we need to add a key so key open and close and
the key could be the iteration number.
And then of course we need to add delay.
So delay opening close.
And is this that state that delay and iteration number.
Right.
So let me reload the application and we get it and we try again.
OK so let's get this done.
So let's move forward to the next component which is going to be real simple.
It's going to be the I believe it's going to be the the the location one.
So we're going to do that right now.