All right so now we can read the location and the footer and there are going to be real simple so it's
going to take it's going to take a couple minutes.
So I'm going to go to Google Maps and you know a chosen Magnolia Dallas downtown whatever just to get
the address of.
Go to Google Maps and get get one link.
Going to use it in a minute.
But first we need to create a component right here.
So I'm going to go to a new folder and I'm going to call this one location.
And inside of location index that day is that yes.
All right we go.
OK.
So again this one is just going to show a map.
So there's no need to create a class based component so react stalest component and the name its location.
Now with the wrapper for this one special class.
So location and then underscore robber Breguet again.
The only thing we need right here is just indifferent.
So I'm going to go and click and share I'm sorry.
Mine has since Panish can change this.
So I'm going to copy the HVM L and let me open it again.
Because it was NOT GIVE ME SOMETIMES up the the Google Maps fails.
So once I go let me get the address again.
Can I click on this.
The Dallas aquarium because I should be getting this.
You know that after PV I should be getting this.
I was not getting it.
So I got a copy and I'm going to pay the I-frame right here and make it a little bit nicer after you
know all the settings.
Sorry for this.
So we have the long string.
Well when we do it like this why not.
Then at the bottom like this almost done
and there we go.
So there's nothing else right.
So OK so we have an I-frame we have the actual link with the word and the word I want to change it to
100 percent.
Then the height is going to be 500 pixels around and then three more there is going to be zero.
And if you run just like this re-act is going to give you an error message that frame border should
be frame border.
Remember that this is not an actual It's not an actual I-frame.
This is J.
It's just some code which actually which is GSX and it's going to be translated to HVM else so we need
to use their tax.
Now style I don't need style go back goodbye and allow Fultz full screen.
It's the same idea allow capital F and then S and that is that.
Then we have the location here at bottom this tack.
So I'm going to go and create a div with a class name of location tag right and on the bottom just Dave
and then location.
Me write it correctly location.
OK so now of course we need to include this components.
And one thing before we move forward.
If you run the application and go to go to the console you're going to get an error message from the
buttons.
It's because of a mistake and I know I should be use soon using small.
And that's it.
Sorry for that.
OK.
Let's include the location right here on the top.
So import location.
When they make it ride location from.
And you know same thing from components that for Slash components for Slash prizing sorry location location
where you get it.
OK.
So now let's include this after prising location.
And we should be good.
So we are done with this.
So now the next thing is going to be the footer and we are this one is going to be real simple.
And then the next section we're going to create this remember that whenever we click in this we need
to do a scroll and we will use a third party library for this.
Our on our project the one we are doing right now this one of course does not work.
So let's do the footer.
OK so I'm going to go right here.
And if you remember we have a or fritter component.
So the only thing I need to do is just create a new file with the name footer.
Yes.
So inside footer we need to create a stateless component.
There's no need to create a class based so re-act stateless component and of course it calls footer.
Now inside of the footer are going to change this four footer and the class name it's a b c k.
Red instead of black.
Well this one is just red.
Now if you notice on the original one whenever we go to the footer reloaded again we get to feeling
that effect from re-act reveal.
So I'm going to do import then Faid opening close reac reveal for Slash and then fade up fate.
There you go.
OK.
So forget the From.
So now I'm going to bring Faid just like here and I'm going to do.
I'm going to select going to put a delay of hundred.
At this point of this you know should be easy for you with this a few times already.
So 500 dead inside of here.
We have the name of the place.
So I'm going to say dev with a class name of.
And again we are using that word font which is fonde righteous.
I have it right here let me copy and paste it and then footer.
Then Logo and then venue and right here says the venue.
OK so the next thing is going to be the copyright.
I know this is boring but this is something actually we we need we always need to do.
If you ask me what is the deal part of a web page or an app.
I hate creating it it's the footer.
I just hate the footer.
I don't know why I just hate them so I don't know electrum.
Maybe not electrum the venue or something like that the venue to 18.
All rights reserved.
I hate them because most of the times the client will always ask absurd things sweet things on footer.
I don't know.
It's just the way it is.
So I'm going to save it and I'm going to go to app and in poor footer from that for Slash and we we
are almost done and we're going to go to the next one.
The next project and the next one is going to be really really fun.
So footer for her.
All right.
So let's go to our project and if we go the bottom up we are not getting it.
Maybe I didn't say something footer from of course for her.
That was a problem.
Cannot solve for footer.
So again I made a mistake components and it's inside header footer and then fruiterer.
That's my mistake.
OK.
So if I go down we get the footer.
So we are pretty much done.
Let's go to the next section and do the scroll to that.
That's interesting.
So let's go to the next one and do this.