All right so now we're going to do the scroll thing.
So what do we need to do.
In theory is just open the side door and click on a section and the page will scroll to that section.
So what do we need to do pretty much is to connect this side door right here.
Remember we have a list item where we can click on a console log we click on the link for example venue
info and then here we can a can it trigger function or tell the application to scroll to you know a
different component.
So we can a need to to bind to connect this unclick with one of the sections.
This is what we need to do.
So I'm going to be using a third party library calls re-act scrawl the documentation and this one it's
not really great but it works very very good.
So right here you get all the documentation for this.
Now you have all of this options.
This is the kind of the usage or the demo.
And in real life if you're you don't need all this they just put everything right here.
You know it's not a very clear demonstration right here you have all the prompts begin to use some of
them.
So do not read the documentation just yet.
I'm going to show you how to do this and you can see that it's much much simpler than doing all of this.
OK so I'm going to go to the side drawer and first on the side drawer we need to called in to bring
this third party library.
This is the way they tell you to do it now instead of importing all the stars means all we don't need
all we just need one thing and we don't need all of this we just need this crawler property.
So I going to go right here.
Import opening close and I'm going to say scroller and this is the only thing we need right here.
So from re-act scrawl.
All right.
And if you remember of course we already have an install and we just make sure we scroll.
Very good.
So on the side drawer we have the scroller Burguet.
So now whenever we click on something we want to trigger a function.
Ok so I'm going to create a function I'm going to go right here at the bottom and I'm going to call
it I don't know.
Scroll to element makes sense.
Scroll to elements something like that.
This Curle 2 element is going to be just a function.
Open and close.
And this one will be receiving an element.
So this is the argument we're going to be getting.
And the element is where we're going to go.
We're going to go to Benue to highlights prizing or location.
So now to use it first we need to make use of the thing we imported at the top.
So scroller now dot and this is cruller has a method called scroll to.
Now the scroll to is just a function right.
And this function needs two things needs two properties.
It needs the elements where are we going to be you know going to which is element and then a callback
function.
I'm sorry then the configuration of this squaller.
So right here in this is simple it's just the props we have right here at the bottom.
So we can set the duration.
How much is it going to last this transition.
So I'm going to add one and a half second delay.
How much is going to wait before it starts transition.
So the delay is just one hundred.
Now then you have a smooth you know you get that fancy transition which is going to be true and that
is going to show you maybe a couple more but for now this is this is good.
So now whenever we click on one an element for example the highlights we want to go to highlight So
instead of doing a console log are going to make a reference to scroll to elements.
So I'm going to delete the console log in highlights for example and I'm going to say OK this time I
want to run a function that does scroll to elements and then the name of where we want to go.
In this case I'm going to say high lights something like that.
So now whenever we click this this is going to trigger the function and the scroller the main mistake
right here is scroll to.
This is scroller.
We'll try to find an element on our project on our No.
Our app calls highlights.
And the thing is we didn't have that.
We just have components.
So this scroller gives you a different a different part inside the library where we can wrap a component
with a scroll too with which what does it as a reference to that components that meet let the show you
are going to go for example.
Here we are clicking on highlights.
So we need to go to the highlight component.
Where do we have the highlight component inside up.
Yes right here right here we have the highlight so you know we need kind of a a way to say OK scroll
to this one which is the name is going to be high light.
So the scroller will know that the name of this one is highlight.
So to do this we need to bring on elements you know a component from reactive scroll.
So we're going to go right here after the styles maybe and import.
And this one scrolls element.
So it's going to be from and then react react scroll.
So now what we do we need to grab this element and drop the highlight just like you're going to say
elements and inside can put highlights.
Let me make this a little bit better.
So now this element needs to know this element.
It's actually from reac scroll so the scroller knows that we have an element but we still need to pass
the name so we add the property name.
In the case of highlight we said that we want to go to the name of highlights.
So again to say highlights and that is that they're going to reload the application are going to go
are here and if I click on highlights Oh I made a mistake or scroll to element is not a function.
OK.
Let me just double check.
I made a mistake on this one.
Now it happens.
Oh I know why.
I know why.
And using I'm not like I'm not in a class and I'm making a reference to this.
So it's not this is just called two elements.
Let's try again.
So highlights and if I do it.
OK.
You know it's kind of like going to highlights the thing is that we have a floating a header a fixed
header so it's going to the right spot but the header.
It's kind of in the way now with a yes called to we can set an offset.
So we're going to say coma and then off and then set and I get to say minus 150 whatever.
Ok let's try again.
Going to go right here.
The top click it highlights and OK now is good.
But the problem is that the the side drawer it's not closing.
OK.
So what we can do we can enter props if you remember the the the props on close.
We get this function that closes the side drawer.
We have it inside props on close so I can copy this and say OK whenever you go to do whatever it is
that you want to do just close the sides or try again to reload it going to go to the top go to highlights
and that is that.
All right.
So now we need to do the same thing with the other ones.
So we're going to do pretty much the same thing right here I'm just going to delete this and just delete
the names I'm going to complete this in a second.
So it's called two elements and location and highlights.
Of course it's already done.
So the first one I'm going to call it featured the second one.
It's Benue info like that the this one is surprising.
And the last one.
It's location right location.
OK.
And I'm going to I'm going to make this a little bit bigger and I'm going to buy this so I can get you
know the names right here.
So it's feature info highlights and prizing.
So we need to repeat the same steps.
So we're going to copy this paste it over here at the bottom and close the elements.
Elements or go there we go.
We're almost done.
And the name is going to be featured.
We're going to repeat the same the same process with Benue evil.
I'm not going to make it a little bit faster.
Call the venue info remove it replace it and then just replace the name highlights.
It's already done so I'm going to copy this one.
Paste that copy the prizing remove the highlights and just change the name.
And one more to go location.
So copy the location remove prizing and then location.
OK so in theory this should work.
Let me just close this.
OK so let me go back to the Rhine so I get to go to the top so I'm going to start from location to location.
We get it all right if I go to events starts in.
Which is feature all right we get it.
I mean your info then highlights and then prizing.
So OK so everything works correctly and this is the last thing we're going to do for this project right.
Right now it's done so we can see if we can see how to upload how to put it inside of inside of a production
environments.
Of course remember that old code of this was going to give you a sip of the Aghan attaches a resource
a sip.
For this project if not of course you can you can find it in get have are going to upload everything
to get have.