All right so now our project is finished.
So we need to put it inside of production or host the project some place so we can to use search for
the yes.
For the first proper project because this is you know a static web project.
You know we don't have a no day as going in the background we didn't have a server we didn't have anything
after we create a building.
This is just some L with some J.S. so search it's really really simple simple to use.
And if of course you want to use greater features the prising.
It's really small.
So if you're a front end developer there's no need to go to Heroku or go to Amazon do you.
The only thing you need to do is search.
You just push and it's really simple to push the project into production.
Really really simple.
I can assure you right now.
So I going to go to the terminal our terminal you know and I'm going to come and this are going to clear
now the venue is inside the venue.
Inside our project now what we push to search is search is going to be our build.
You know the build of this project not all the directories with sores and everything else.
So we push a modified version of our project.
So if you go to Pakistan Jason and we go to scripts we have right here the built so we can run NPM run
build or Yorn run build and it will create a bundle for production.
So I'm going to go right here and I'm using yarned remember.
So I'm going to say yarn run built and of course if you're using NPM it's an end run built.
So I'm going to press Enter.
This is going to take a couple minutes and I'll be right back.
OK.
Everything was done.
So now what we need to do is to install search so we can you know upload the project to build directory
we need to upload this one.
Not everything else just built into Sorge.
So if we go to help Of course we get all the instructions of how to do it and it's real simple.
I'm going to show you right now.
First we need to install first which you installed search in our computer we install it globally.
So I'm going to say clear right now and I'm going to do.
And of course if you're using NPM you need to do and PM install mine is because we installed globally
and then search.
This is what you need to do in my case.
I'm using Joern.
So it's yarn global.
And then of course search just like this.
So I'm going to present or will already have it.
So I'm going to Precentor of course is going to do it.
I'm going to pause and be right back.
Maybe it's going to be done let's give it a minute.
OK.
Everything was installed.
So now I have surge in my computer so I can use the search command.
First I'm going to clear.
So now how to upload it.
Really simple.
We'd say search just like this.
We said mine is P and we are using minus P because I want to put inside of search I when to upload a
very specific directory which is the build directory to build we have right here.
If I remove the P and I press Enter it's going to try to upload the whole directory all the contents
inside the venue directory and we don't want that.
We just want to upload to build.
So by doing mynahs P I can specify which directory I want to upload.
In our case it's going to be built.
So I'm going to say minus the build going to press center and it's going to do something in the background
and you're going to get something like this.
Now I'm getting the e-mail and the token because I'm already registered.
I've pushed a few projects into search in the past so it's already my computer.
If it's your first time it's going to ask you for your e-mail.
And you know to add a passport and after that it's going to give you some information how many files.
No the main buy in the first time because it is going to give you kind of a dummy domain and right here
you're going to get this square this you know this rectangle and it looks like frozen but it's not it's
a waiting for you to press enter.
So I'm going to press enter is going to do something is going to start uploading.
It's going to take seconds.
And that is it.
So after it's done it's been a success project.
It's published and running at and this domain.
So if I copied the domain and I go right here and paste it there you go.
We get our re-act app of course we didn't modify this and we get everything else so everything works
very very good.
You know it's really really really simple to use this is kind of my favorite for chest front and applications.
And of course you can do a lot more.
You can add a custom domain Maybe your client has already owns a domain so you can of course add that
domain and you have kind of a free service.
Of course we're not a lot of features.
And of course if you pay $3000 a month which is not a lot you get all of the other you know the more
professional features.
So again everything is on help.
All the topics you will need to find you know adding a 4 or 4 or maybe testing or whatever you have
it right here.
So it's very very cool.
And that is it.
So remember to go to get help you have the project inside get have you can get the link.
So now we're going to move forward to the next project and it's not going to be this easy.
This is really easy for us.
It took us a few hours maybe two or three hours really really simple but of course this is kind of a
warm up project we're going to do.
The first one.
The next one we will be doing with indication we will using Abebe we will be using a little bit more
complex animations.
And of course a lot more.
So let's go to the next one.