Right.
So this couple of sections we're going to discuss in how to use get and how to use GET have now get
and get have are not the same thing.
This one is get have.
And the other one if I go to get just like this or in-style get the first option is going to be this
one so get and get help but are not related.
And why are we using.
Are we going to be using this once.
It's because you always need to have a copy of repository of all your project.
What happens if the computer is going of you know Dites dies on you and you know you pretty much lose
all your work you know very real dangers.
Of course I have a different copy on a different you know instance of get of this project I have everything
saved saved on different places but of course on this one I've deleted everything.
This project this is our project you know waves it's not really related to get or get help right.
OK.
So what I'm going to do I'm going to install get I'm going to show you how to use it.
And then we're going to link get with get have going to generate S.H. keys and everything else are going
to tell you how to do it first.
We do it to start with get right this is the first step.
So we need to download.
Of course if you're in Windows you're going to get the download for Windows.
But it's pretty much the same installer.
So first I'm going to download and now we're going to get this screen.
Sometimes you don't get the you know the out magic download.
So click here to download manually.
And it's going to take you to so two to Source Forge and you just you know you're going to get it of
course.
I've already have an install and it is going to download it anyways.
Can take a second right.
I can open it all right to get the download I'm going to install it I'm going to click right click and
open because maybe you don't double click it on unmask at least it's not going to let you move move
forward.
So I'm going to click an open select Open and then you know are you sure.
Yeah.
We are sure open.
All right so you're going to get the screen instructions.
So we need to click Continue then you know the location that's ok install.
And of course if it's asking for the password install software and everything else.
All right.
So the installation was successful that that's OK.
So I'm going to close it and move to trash.
All right.
So I'll close it again.
Now how can you know.
How can we test in our computer if we you know we have a get installed right.
Because that's the first step checking.
If you get insulted me go back to the previous version.
So this is the version maybe you know upgrade in mind because they have the 2 0 something.
OK.
So first I'm going to go here.
We're going to go to our project.
I'm going to kill the server.
I'm going to do it clear right.
So how can we check we get.
Well first we start with the command get and then minus minus and then version.
Now if you press enter you notice that this is the same one.
So if you're getting this it's because of course you have get in your computer if you're not getting
this it's because you need to restart the computer.
Right.
That's the first step and I believe that with Windows you will need to restart the computer.
And if you're just that you're asking yourself why most of developers they want to work with the Mac
or Linux based computers.
It's because of the terminal that is that's pretty much it.
I have both both things that have a Windows computer.
I use it for different things for music production.
And you know all of the things gaming and everything else.
But for Koning I just use the Mac.
I don't use anything else.
All right.
So now we have everything installed LEDs.
You know let's create a repository right here.
Right.
So I'm back in the project.
Let me make this a little bit smaller so so I'm back in the project k I'm going to do clear.
And now what we need to do we need to create and this is the keyboard a local repository inside our
computer.
Whenever we use good we are not storing anything in the cloud you're just creating a copy of our project
inside the same directory.
Notice I am inside waifs.
All right.
So how can we you know start a repository right here.
So far we don't have anything.
So the way we start a repository we do get because now we have it installed and then we do that now.
The Enter is going to say initialize empted get repository and it's going to give you the location and
then a directory called Dot get.
Now in this folder we don't get that get.
And of course if you navigate to this folder you might not be getting or seeing this folder.
This is a hidden folder and this directory contains all the data of your project.
After of course you store it right.
If you delete this folder locally in your computer you know this directory.
You can delete all the you know all the stored repository all the repository in your in your computer.
So you know don't do that unless of course you want to delete everything.
Right.
OK.
Now if I get in it again it's going to turn me reinitialized existing get reported repository.
So I of course didn't do anything because we already get it.
Now if I do ls notice that I'm getting all the directories in all the files inside my inside this directory.
But I'm not getting anything else.
Now if I do ls minus a and this is for Mac minus a it's going to give me all the directories including
the you know the hidden ones.
In this case the does get or I'm going to do.
Clear.
How can we you know start things.
Well the first command you use with get it's get status.
So let me do it right here get status.
OK.
So the branch master it's you always the main branch.
What were you going to be storing all the files.
Like the main repository in the main part of use to your store right here.
Now when you do get status you're pretty much asking OK what is the status of my repository.
And it's going to give you two things.
First the untracked files and then later we're going to get something else saying no commits yet.
And this means that you know all these files are not store inside get.
So far we didn't get anything right.
So how can we you know start adding things inside get you know storing creating our repository with
the files we want.
Well the next command will be good.
And then at.
Now before we do it I'm going to tell you something else.
Remember that we have this get ignored.
And we pretty much get to get ignore whenever we create our you know project with the CLID.
Now the good ignore it's actually we use it with good to recognize old files or directories.
We don't want to store it.
Let me just do the following.
I'm going to just go back and of course we do get status and it's still looming.
OK.
So in your project Julians you'd have stored the ignore defined good ignore you don't have the client
for Slash because the client files Jason's you know the Jasons package server and you're in luck so
it's making a reference to everything but not the note modules right.
It's not telling me that I'm not getting the node modules and it's because we don't store the node modules
inside inside get.
You know it's are inside a repository or get help.
And it's because the node modules has a lot of files so there's no need to do this because whenever
we create a repository or actually we bring to a project from the server or move from Get have we've
already have the package adjacent.
So we do NPM or yarn in it and it will install all dependencies for us.
So we don't never never ever store the node modules and a good repository.
Right.
We never do that.
And the way we do that it's by specifying on the ignore what we want to skip.
So this is just a script file.
So we are saying that we don't want to store the Noj modules the node modules inside the client.
Remember we have node modules inside client and you know that that M-B the one we use for the server
and a bunch of stuff.
Now if I delete the node modules just like this and save the file and run that get started again we
get the node modules right.
So you always need to be aware of what you get inside to get ignored.
All right.
So going to a clear and going to go back with the node modules and again to do get started again and
now that getting the node modules that is okay.
So how can we add things.
Well there's two ways you have to get the ad than space and you can specify whatever is that you want
to store inside of the repository.
So I got to say Jason's.
And then for Slash I'm making a reference to this directory.
If I press Enter You know we go back to the branch and that is OK.
Now if I do get status it selling goes OK this one are inside the repository and the other ones you
know they are not.
So this would this way get Add in the name of what we want to add.
You're just adding things manually one by one.
Right.
OK.
Now the thing is that you know maybe you want to store everything that it's in your project and do it
by one by one.
Takes a lot of time.
So the way to do that it's to do get ad space and you put a dot and this will add everything that it's
not untracked.
Of course the all the untracked files in that local repository now and do clear if I do get status we're
going to get you know a list of all the files that you know were stored inside the local repository.
Now there is a difference between adding and committing you know there are different actions whenever
you add something.
It means that you're kind of adding to a to do list of get something right.
You're telling.
Ok I'm ready to store this files.
They are not stored inside and you and repository.
Right.
So it's kind of the get at creates a list of what you want to add right now.
Now to do really create a repository and add all these files into a local repo.
What you will need to do is just to run a different command and that one is commit.
So there is a difference between adding and committing.
So the way we commit we need to do get then commit space minus M and then we need to pass a message.
We need to tell to attach a message to this specific comment.
So on this one I'm going to say first commit and then we press enter.
It's going to do all of this in the middle clear.
And now if I do get status just like this you know we get nothing to commit.
Everything is good.
You know everything was set and inside a good store you know that get folder we get you know all everything
that we just committed which is pretty much the whole project.
That's why we don't get anything get status.
So what happens if I go to I don't know to the index I'm going to just modify one space save the file.
So now we made changes.
This index it's a little bit different than what with what we get inside the repository.
Right.
We have one more space.
Now of course we need to grab this file and store it again.
We need to update version.
So if I do get status it says OK.
So this file was modified it was modified and it's not inside your repository.
So you have a different portion of what we have in our repository.
So we just follow the same steps over and over again.
Good.
And you can pass the name of the file or you just do everything.
Then did you get the status and noticed that right here.
Now it's green.
Now we do get commit minus m minus M and then we pass the message which is under no changes on the index.
You always need to put a message that you know reflects the changes as they're going to press enter
and one file change.
Everything was good.
And if I do get started again we go back to nothing to commit you know everything it's up to date.
So this is a way how we use get right with our computer.
But again we are screeding to get the repository inside our computer if our computer just kind of breaks
or something happens with your computer.
You're going to lose everything because the repository it's local.
It's not on the cloud.
So the next step would be creating a get have account linking this good repository we have right here
in our computer with a get have account and upload files.
Right.
It's it's very simple let's do it right now.
OK so I am it and get help.
Of course you need to create an account then log in and of course you know the usual process when you
register or some planner form.
So inside get have you have two ways of doing things right.
One the first one it's free.
Right.
That's the first one.
And of course you can store repotted you can create repositories inside to get have and they are public
whenever you use a free account.
They are all public.
You can not create private repositories.
So once you upload this anyone has access to your files that's the first thing you need to know.
Of course if you want to of course have private repositories just like I do you know this ones are private.
You need to you know pay.
It's like five bucks a month maybe six or seven bucks.
It's real cheap.
Right.
And you can use it the whole time.
So once you have your account create it you can go to Home and click new repository or if you go to
your profile right here and you go to repositories you can create a new one right here.
So whenever you create new of course you're the owner and then you need to put the repository name right.
You can added scription.
And if it's a free account it's public or if it's your you have a pay account paid account.
You can go private.
That's OK.
So I'm going to select public and I'm going to create a repository.
All right.
Once you create the repository it's going to give you some instructions and it's going to say right
here the first one let's go to this one is going to say OK first you need to do get in it.
We kind of overdid this.
We need to add a re me.
So this is kind of a file where we can get instructions.
We didn't have a read me.
We just had get me inside the client but don't worry it's just a file with some instructions.
Then you need to do commed we kind of already did this and that get.
And this one is the one we need to do now.
You need to prompt a command to link the get repository we have right here in sideways with the you
know the location inside get.
So I'm going to copy this in a copy and you need to do the same thing and you need to paste it get remote
at origin.
And this one it's going to link whatever repository getting waves with this project.
All right.
So I'm going to press enter.
And that is that.
Now I'm going to say get push and this is the way we can have a push to files or push our repository
which is the master to get have by doing the get remote and or Genk we are just linking our repository
would get have.
So get push pushes all the files to the cloud.
So I'm going to press enter.
It's going to take a little while.
So we will fast just files and we are not including the node modules.
So it's going to be really fast.
And that is it.
Now if I go to get get have and reload the application we get our you know our project all the files
inside.
Inside our project without of course all the Noach modules because you know we don't need them and that
is it.
So now you have you get your get get help now on the next couple of suctions you're going to be adding
S-sh keys right can meet need them.
And then we're going to go to Heroku link again the S-sh keys and then deploy everything to production.
So let's go to the next one and start with the S-sh keys.