Right.
So now that everything is inside you know get and get have what we will do will do.
It's at S-sh keys.
So again if we think about this we are kind of sending things to you know our files our rent maybe maybe
very private files to the cloud.
And it's you know a good idea to add some kind of authentication or maybe some security in what we are
doing and this.
It's through S-sh case.
So if you go to your profile and you go to S-sh keys you can generate an SH key.
Now the problem is that we need to create these keys in our computer.
We create the keys locally.
Right.
OK.
So we're willing to do is we need to follow a series of steps right.
To generate the keys first in our computer and then associate associate the keys to get help Brian.
OK.
So the starting point is going to be this go to Google and type checking for existing S-sh keys.
This is the first thing we need to do.
So once you're here you're going to get different options.
Mac Windows and Linux.
Now if you're a Windows computer go to the other BDO have another video for the same action.
That of course is related to windows because we need to do some other stuff we do in a different way
for Mac.
So go to the windows.
Right.
If you're on a Mac computer use Mac of course and going to do both.
So right here if you're not getting anything nothing is associated to your search.
So we need to do this.
Copy this this code and go right here and paste it right.
Doesn't matter I am inside waves because I'm using the tiller.
So if we press Enter you're going to get some kind of information just like this.
Now if you're getting something that says Id something perve or ID areas are s a.
It means that you already have A.H. keys so you will need to go to add your S-sh key to the SSA agent
to begin to do this later.
So first we need to generate a key if you don't have a key and this is what we're going to do now.
So we're not going to you know make this up I'm going to just show you the steps are going to follow
the steps and get help.
So generate a new message key.
All right.
So first we're going to go here and we need to generate the key.
So I'm going to copy this line of code I'm going to do clear.
It's actually actually is a command.
And we do sh t minus T whatever whatever.
And then you need to provide it need mail and e-mail.
It's the e-mail you're using for get have are going to delete this one and going to put my e-mail.
So right.
Yeah.
And Gmail that com.
OK.
So I'm going to press enter and generate a public key and then it's going to say Enter file in which
you want to save the key so you have the option to store the key in a different place than you know
the usual.
But but the one way or we're going to be storing by default I'm going to store it on the default place
I'm going to press enter.
Now you have the ability to pad to enter passphrase for this I'm not going to do this I'm just going
to go default.
I'm going to press enter.
And then of course you need to confirm the passphrase.
Now if you're getting this it's because the key was already in it get it's generated in your computer.
So now if I do this.
LS And you know we check for the S.H. keys.
We get the ID say and the pup.
So we have keys now.
Right.
Very good.
Let's go to the next step is going to be adding your sh key to the SSA agent.
Now I'm going to do clear just like this.
I'm going to copy this line of code.
This command actually.
And paste it.
Evil.
And then everything else.
So I'm going to press enter and it's going to say Agent P ID 4:7.
So if you're getting this good track I'm going to copy this one again as well and again paste it down
here.
I'm going to press enter and we get the identity added right.
So we're kind of linking this computer to the SSA to key.
Right.
So the next step it's adding the S-sh key to get help.
All right.
So I'm going to go to that one.
How can we do it really is simple so we can accomplish this.
And again pasted right here.
Now I'm going to press enter and it seems like nothing happened.
And it's because the PV copy it's a command that it's entering this file copying all the constants and
everything you know got copied on the memory of the computer.
So now of course if I do a command and B to paste it.
Are going to be pasting the contents of this file.
So now what we need to do.
You need to follow these steps.
Don't worry you're going to do it right here.
So we need to go to to get help and go to the section inside the profile S-sh and deep keys and click
on new S-sh key.
You need to add a name.
For example if you're in your Mac computer you know that you're going to a Mac for example or maybe
you can you know give a name but of course this name needs to be related of where you're you know you're
storing.
You get this sh he's And this is my Mac computer.
Later I'm going to get a windows.
So I'm going to paste the contents control the end you're pasting all the contents of the same key.
Now I'm going to click Add a search key and we are pretty much done now of course we can and need a
way to validate the S-sh key we get right here in our computer with the one that it's linked and get
help.
So I'm going to go back to the command.
I'm going to do clear and I'm going to do as a sage just like that.
Mynahs capital-T space and then get at get have dot com of course.
All right.
So going to press Enter it's going to take a while and it is going to give you your username.
This is my username you know successfully authenticated but get have does not provide shared access.
Ok that is good.
You know if you're getting this everything work now if we go back here to get have a reload get a green
now.
So everything was validated.
Now the S.H. key is related to get have and we have a more secure way to send the files.
Of course this works just like before.
If I modify the file and go to get status we can get it.
So I'm going to get to get at that get commit minus them and then you know changes on index.
I'm going to press enter and then you push it again.
You know to push the files.
Usually we did get pushed master and this one since we already did this.
We can do get push because the Master is already there.
So I'm going to do get pushed
and we are done.
Everything is good.
So again once you get the keys you get get get get have and everything else you're ready to go to get
to Heroku link.
The same etch Etch a Sketch key but it can be much much easier.
And then we will be able to deploy to production.
All right.
So let's go to the next one and do that.