OK so now we're going to be doing is adding S-sh keys to our computer.
So if you're asking yourself why we could we need to add a set of keys.
Well if you think about this you're sending files to the cloud.
So it's always a good idea to have kind of an indication or something in between that you know it's
a little bit more secure.
All right.
So this is what we're going to be doing now.
If you go to your profile I'm going to go to the profile and just let me show you right here instead
of the profile going to go to settings actually settings.
You get a bunch of options.
And if I go to S-sh keys right here to answer say and GBG you're going to get a list of a set of keys.
I get the Mac because I did the Mac Berio first and I've added the S-sh key right here.
But now of course we're going to do the windows and for this we need a bunch of stuff we need to do
a few stuff.
Now first I need you to go to the to the browser and type adding a new SH key to get have a count.
Actually not this one.
I'm going to go to the other one.
Let me go back.
Type checking for an existing S-sh key.
If you check that on the browser and you get to get HAVE result go to go to get help.
We're going to need this right.
This is the first STARTING POINT.
Now before we can move forward I'm going to tell you something after whenever you installed get by default
you get this option but whenever you can naggy says Windows Explorer integration get back here.
And we need to get Bash.
We need it.
If you unclick that when you install this you will need to click it because we will need the bash.
We cannot do it without the bash.
So this bash story is kind of a simulation of a terminal that actually works for Linux because it would
be really complicated for us to do it with the normal command prompt to close it.
And I'm going to say exit set up.
Yes and I have the right to it right here.
I get the the command prompt.
Let me see if I can make it bigger maybe a little bit.
There you go.
OK.
So we're going to be using this in a minute.
So there we go.
Sorry for this.
All right.
So if we go to the checking for existing SH keys right here we need to start.
So I'm going to copy this.
And again you cannot do copy paste because again is a simulation of a terminal.
So I got a copy going to go back here and they're going to paste it.
So by doing this you can go to the default place where we store S.H. keys and we're going to check if
we do have a case.
So I'm going to press enter and you going to get something like this.
If you get something saying have an ID RSA or something like that is because you already have keys.
So if that is the case you want need to go to this one and your sh key to the SH agent.
If not you just move forward to generate a new S-sh key.
And this is what we are going to be doing.
OK.
So this is the first step.
I'm going to copy this just like we did before.
Can it command copy are going to go here and I'm going to I'm going to paste it with paste so we are
going to be you know adding creating an SH key and you need to put the password or your email and this
isn't going to be using of course the e-mail.
What I'm using for the Get Help account.
So it's just like this.
I was done that come.
All right.
So I'm going to press enter and the Keys are you know kind of already done but it's going to ask you
Do you want to save it in the default place.
Or maybe a different place.
Well default place so I'm going to press press enter and that's it.
You have the ability to enter passphrase for this.
I'm not going to carry the passphrase.
I'm just going to press enter and then it's going to go to default.
Now if you're getting this it's because the data key was generated.
Now if I go to the previous command and pressing the up arrow and do ls to check if I have keys can
press enter.
And now we get it we have to get the ID say an ID pup.
So you know this is this part it's kind of ready.
We have the keys right here.
Now what we need to do we need to add the SH key to the estate agent.
So I'm going to copy this in a copy.
I can go back to the bash and paste it right in a press center.
And if you're getting this done then we need to go to the other command.
This one I'm going to copy paste and enter an identity at it.
So it's kind of I'm making a link between the key and you know your computer.
All right.
So the next step and the key to your get have account and this one is pretty pretty simple.
So I'm going to copy this line and are going to paste it right here Paiste are going to press enter
it.
So whenever the press center seems like nothing happened.
So basically with clip and side windows you know we are just copying all the contents of this file right.
We are just copying all of this.
So now we need to go to get help.
So we're going to go new S-sh key just like this and I'm going to say Windows right here because I mean
my windows computer and I get to go here and I'm going to do a command and paste all the cum all the
contents which is copied from the command and it's pasting pretty much spacing all the contents we have
on that file.
And that is that I'm going to add as a search key.
And we're pretty much done.
Now I'm going to try to validate this so I'm going to do.
I'm going to go to the command.
There is no copying pasting right here.
So I'm going to do.
S S H that minus capital T space.
Get at get have that come just like that.
I'm going to press enter.
And is going to say hi your username you're successfully authenticated.
So pretty much of this command what it's doing is just validating all your your kids ride with get have.
So now if I go here and reload the application it's not in black anymore it's going to be in green.
It means that everything was validated.
So you're ready to use using SH keys.
All right.
So that is good if you are at this point.
Everything going OK.
So we can move forward to the next thing.
So the next thing it's going to be go into Heroku installing everything and kind of a link.
This is a key again.
But with Heroku.
And if you're maybe you are thinking oh we need to do all this commands again.
Well not really.
We're getting with the Heroku.
It's really real simple.
It's pretty much.
We just installed and that's it.
So let's go to the next one and go to Hiroko.