OK so now we need to create or to actually to do the Heroku side of things.
We did it would get have.
So now we need to do it with Heroku we need to grab that SH and link it to Hoku.
Right.
OK.
So the first thing you will need to do is to go to Heroku of course and create an account.
Right.
Of course.
So after you create your account and please remember your username which is the email and the password
because we can use it right here it's going to take you to go to the dashboard and you get to get something
like this.
You're right.
This is OK.
This is actually starting point.
So now in order to use or to actually send our project or deploy the project from here from our terminal
to Heroku you will need to install the Heroku CLIA of course go go to the browser and do Heroku.
I like that.
And the first option you get is this one right.
So enter there's this one.
So if you go to download and install you get to you can get a bunch of options to install.
You can do it from a homebrew or whatever of course but you will need to download the installer so download
the installer for Mac OSX or do it with homebrew.
If you know how to and if you're a Windows computer download the installer are going to of course and
you get Ubuntu of course are going to download the installer right now and i've already have it installed
in my computer.
Got it but again installed anyways so I'm going to download and I'll be right back.
All right so I'm going to open it and install it again.
So of course resemble continue then continue.
That of course continue.
And then again with the password of course maybe for Windows you going to get the run as administrator.
Some like that but that is OK.
So almost done right.
After everything is installed of course we need to we need a way to check that Heroku was installed
so we're going to do Heroku minus minus help.
So when you do this is going to give you all the you know all the commands we get Bogdanovic we have
all of it we get.
Available with the Heroku Seelye.
Right of course we are not going to use all of this are going to be clear.
Of course if you're getting this this help it's because it was installed.
If you're not getting this you need to restart the computer.
All right so now we have left Heroku in our computer so we need to log in or there to deploy our project.
So how we log in Heroku and then log in are going to press center is going to ask you for your username
so gonna do.
I'm going to put mine it was done.
It's one of my email accounts I have a lot.
And then of course the password I can log in and of course logged in as your username.
Right.
I'm going to do a clip just like that would get have.
We need to grab that S-sh key remember and associate that key with Heroku.
And remember that would get have was you know we when we needed to do a lot of things well with Hiroko
it's really really simple.
So Heroku going to say keys Cohen and then at going to press enter and I would magically is going to
go to the public folder where we get the you know we store the S.H. keys and you know tells us that
I've found one tree and use that one.
Well we're going to say yes and that's it.
That's pretty much the only thing we need to do.
The last step would be associating this.
So we do S-sh just like we did before.
S-sh minus the space we do get at Heroku dot com.
I'm going to press enter.
It's going to do a bunch of stuff and then it's going to say authentication and right here and we find
it offensive cations succeeded.
And that is it.
This is the only thing we need to do to link Heroku with you know our project and our computer.
So on the next section we're going to now do configuration.
But before we deploy we need to make a few changes in our project.
First we need to deploy a project then we need to go to the Heroku dashboard add the database we need
to do some configuration right here.
And of course we need to change something inside our project because this one if you remember when teachers
go to the package that owns this one works on a development environment.
If we send this to production nothing is going to really happen is not really work.
So we need to make a few changes on the package that J-Zone we need to make a few changes on the server.
We need to instruct server that you know it needs to use the index of this build.
Remember we're going to create a build well in it.
We need to actually let the server know that that's the file we want to use and not this one.
All right.
OK.
So let's go to the next section and start with all the configuration.