Rights and we got everything we need.
So the first thing is going to be going and making some changes right here.
So I'm going to go to the package to Jason of our whole project.
You know the main one and are going to go here now before creating an application inside Heroku for
sending everything to Heroku.
We just pass it by Heroku which version of note we are using.
We're going to go to the terminal and I'm going to say node minus minus B node minus v sorry and this
is going to tell me that I'm using the version 8 1 3.
So we need to specify on the Jasen on the package to Jason is going to go to Heroku.
Which version of node we are using.
And we do this by specifying the engines.
So I'm going to say engines then we use an object and here we say that we are using node and then we
just pass the version that is at.
Now of course now we have a change in our file now in our product.
So we need to do good.
And then we add on this case then get commed minus m and you know pad changes in Jaison Arite are going
to press center and then we do get pushed again to send everything to get have Burguet very very simple.
Now we pretty much have everything set of course we need to do a lot more.
But you know at least we can create an application inside Heroku.
This is the only thing we need.
So how can we do it.
OK so I'm going to declare I'm going to use that Heroku command and I'm going to say create a press
center.
It's going to take a minute and that's it.
That is then.
This is the only thing we need to do is going to give your L right where this where we can actually
see our application.
And of course we get this you know get it done something else.
But if I go here are going to go and put it right here.
I'm going to press enter and you know Heroku welcome to your new app.
Of course nothing is kind of really happening so far.
So if I go to Heroku in a reload the application at least we are creating an application.
This one it's not really related to what's happening here right.
We just create an application.
Now what we need to do is we need to grab all our contents and send to this application right here.
So what I'm going to do I'm going to do.
Clear again.
All right going to declare and this time we do get push Heroku.
So we're gonna grab everything that we have them get up of this repository and send it to that application
inside Heroku.
So I'm going to press center.
It's going to take a while.
Right so it's fetching it's Lincoln dependencies and it's doing all the stuff it needs to do.
And it's almost done building succeeded it's compressing.
And at the end of course you're going to get something like this deployed to Heroku and they know everything
was done.
Now again this is the year of our application so it's too much doing it's grabbing whatever we have
right here.
It's building it.
And then of course it gives you the your L where it's doing this deploy Ryan.
Of course if we go right here I reload the application.
We get some errors.
If you remember when we were creating the server we were getting cannot get.
Well this is pretty much the same thing.
We need to change some of the things right here inside the server and everything else.
In order for this to work.
All right.
But the first part.
It's done all right.
At least we get something and it's showing something that's related to our application.
OK.
So the first thing we need to do is to link Mungo.
Right.
Because so far we're using in our computer Mongo from our computer not from this one is it is a different
instance.
So if I enter the application you need to do the same thing and go to resources.
You're going to see this but an add ons and we need to find more add ons.
So Mongo right.
SURFACE.
You actually you cannot use it by default without Heroku application or actually any server.
You need to add it.
And this is of course a different save service is a paid service.
So yeah you need to pay for it.
So I'm going to go to MBLAQ and Mongul TV.
This is the service we get and I'm going to scroll at the bottom and it says plans and pricing.
So this is these are the plans.
You know what we can use.
So by default we get a sandbox you know testing a sandbox for free.
And of course that's what we need to link that one to our project and of course right now we are going
to use free.
Now how can we tell the application our application and the server that we want to use a sandbox we
want to use a database among OTV database.
Right.
Are going to go to the two.
You know the terminal are going to clear.
OK.
So first we need to do Heroku.
You know access that and then we say Anand's.
Now with this add ons and then Collen and we pass the name of whatever on you want to add.
In this case we're going to do Mongo but you have much more you just pass the name of whatever you want
to add and then you know the what what would the configuration that the library or the the deep the
service tells you.
In this case we need to say add ons create we are going to create a new one and then we specify which
on which is Mongo laugh CONAN And what type of plan.
In this case it's sandbox.
And for now right now for me it's not going to happen but maybe it's going to happen for you and I'm
going to tell you why in a minute I'm going to press center and it's going to say creating sandbox takes
a few a few seconds.
And that is it.
So if you're getting this you're good to go now.
Maybe you're going to get a message saying that you need to you need to link Mongul laugh or at least
your Heroku account to a credit card and you will need to do it.
Sorry for that.
So let me go right here.
I'm going to go to the profile.
We're going to go to account settings and on the billing.
I have a credit card linked and current usage zero.
So you will need to link a credit card in the past.
Actually we didn't didn't have to do this.
It was you know free to use with no credit card but a lot of people you know they were misusing this
sandbox account.
So you know they said OK you need to have a credit card because if you really use it for production
you're going to charge you.
So you really need to use a credit card or for that.
There's no way around this.
All right.
Well that's great.
So once you add the credit card to your account and everything else and I assure you there are now going
to charge you.
I don't I don't use this account for production or use just for testing and I've been using it for like
I don't know three years maybe more.
Never a penny.
Nothing.
So don't worry about that.
OK.
So I'm going to go back to the dashboard right here dashboard and go back to our application.
Now if you go right here to the overview is going to say install add ons and you get the Mongul laugh.
And of course if you have more add ons they're going to show up there.
OK.
That is good.
So now we have Mongo in our computer in our project right.
We need to do a lot of things because we fight deploy to Heroku again this is still going to fail.
Now I'm going to go right here and it says Create a Mongul laugh as Mongo DVH you are.
I if you remember in our project we were using the dot E-M B and this virals contain the location of
where your you know Bongo DVDs are going to work.
Your database is going to work.
And this is the name of the database not this one anymore.
So we cannot use that Deedat be.
And that maybe is just for testing in our computer.
What we will need to do is answer to the to our project to the server add all of this virals manually
and whenever the application loads inside of the Heroku server is going to take.
Oh OK.
I need to access to process that maybe we'll just inside the server and the cloud name and everything
else.
Now I made a mistake right here and I'm going to change it right now.
It's Mongo divi you or I.
And I'm going to change the dot EFB instead of database.
Mongo HD-TV you or I.
And same thing on the server.
This is actually my mistake.
So instead of a database is going to be process that M-B Mongo DVH you or I.
So whenever we send this application to the server and on the server we'll do this by our rules whenever
the application starts and says oh I need to use process that maybe this virals are going to exist right
now they does not exist.
Now how can we check it out.
We access Heroku and we say config.
So by using config the this command will show all the variables the dot process that M-B bbls we have
on the server.
So if I press it we get only one which is the Mongo divi you or I.
So whenever we specify process dot EFB and then Mongo gives you your are you are I.
Our application is going to be using this instead of whatever we have on the dot and B you know the
Daddums again is a simulation.
So now what we need to do we need to add the secret the cloud name the API key and the API secret.
OK.
That's good.
So how can we add it real simple.
Did Heroku then config just like this.
And we do Collon and we need to do set you have more options like unset you know to delete a viable.
I believe you have one for update if you wish.
So yeah you can check the Hoku documentation.
It's pretty pretty clear.
So we can set several bbls on the same command.
So first I'm going to do the secret.
Can I say secret equals and just copy.
Same thing.
All right.
What else can it do space.
We have the cloud clout name so cloud name equals and I'm just going to copy all club name space then
we have the cloud API key going to copy and paste.
Now we have this one.
The cloud API is secret right.
Going to make some space and paste it.
Now I'm going to press enter.
It's going to take a second.
And that is it.
So now again if I do Heroku confect
we get all the you know environment variables.
So now this Marble's we have on the server whenever this is working on the server they're going to work.
You know they will have values.
All right.
So this is the first thing we need to do we need to do more things.
But I believe know I know that that's why in 11 minutes it's OK.
OK.
So I'm going to give you a kind of a simulated scenario.
After we push this to production I'm not going to do it right now because it takes time and it's not
going to work if I push it right now to production every time you know you create up a project in this
case most of the times the server actually pretty much always what it renders in your screen in the
browser is going to be the build of your single page app.
Right.
Actually we kind of did this previously.
You make you run NPM or Yorn crumbled.
You will get a build directory and what you've sent to the server is that built right and that and that
Jason with that index it's what's going to be rendered on the screen.
So while this is pretty much the same thing if we create a build right now every time we make a change
in our application we need to run the build manually again and then send it to the server.
Now there is an we've got an easier way to do this.
I'm going to go to the package that Jason just like here and inside of the package adjacent Jason we
of course need to make some changes.
Now here we have we get the def and that one stays the same.
This one is going to work in our computer right.
Every time we need to run the development server we just leave that one there.
But we need to add one more one one more.
And this one is going to be Heroku dash and post built just like this.
So whenever we deploy our project Heroku Hiroko will read our package that Jason and it's going to say
Oh OK.
So this dude has a parochial post Bill.
So what this is going to do.
The application Heroku is going to try to do the builds are going to send everything to the server is
going to download everything for the server all the dependencies and then is going to say okay I get
a post Bill so I need to enter the client run a built in all of this is going to happen on the server
for us it's going to run the build and at the end what we will be rendering it's the build right here
the top that it's going to be on the server.
So it's pretty much we are just automating everything.
So we need to write a few few things right here.
A few set of instructions.
So what we do it's capitol NPM underscore that config underscore production.
So what we say you know this one it's not production but there's ok that way.
So then of course we need to pretty much did do what we did here which concurrently don't thing is that
this is going to happen on the server.
So in this case we do NPM install space space and when need specified the clients let me make this smaller
go when you specify the client just like we did right here minus minus prefix and then client well this
is the same same thing prefix and then we do client.
All right then I'm going to do and percent and I can do one more thing.
I'm going to do NPM run build.
So we are pretty much passing.
You know what we're going to be doing what we're going to be doing in this case whenever we go to the
client.
We go and we install all the dependencies we get in the node module that that's what can happen first.
Once everything is installed it's going to go and run this one which is to build.
So we say NPM run build the Riego make smaller and we do pretty much the same thing.
And this is going to happen on the client.
All right.
And that is it.
So whenever we send this to production Heroku will recognize there's an after building whenever it needs
to build for the server is going to go to the client and build build that as well.
All right.
So that is the first thing going to save this.
Of course we need to go to get her to push everything to get and get help.
But we have more changes and we're going to go to the next one because you know it's a little bit long
and we need to do it on the server.
So let's go to the next one.
Do the server.
And then we are pretty much ready to send this to production.