OK so now what we need to do we need to make some changes to the server.
Just so you know we can make it work and it can make sense.
For example whenever we pushed as to Heroku Heroku will you know create that post build and everything
else but the server needs to know how to render that indexed that HD mail that we get inside of built
after we of course create a build.
So we need to give instructions to the server in how to render.
So we're going to do just that.
I'm going to go right here at the bottom and this should be the last route because this Froude it's
going to be like a default case something like that default.
So why it's a default.
Well we have other routes right here.
So whenever we make a request to our server which is Heroku and the our server it's in our application
no whole application.
It's not finding the route is going to go to a default because if it's not finding the route it's you
know the symbol or the single page application react.
Right.
That is pretty much the whole logic.
Now of course this only works and in production right inside Heroku whenever we run development server
this actually you know does not does not apply.
So we need to create kind of a rule something something to rule that the server or the development server
out.
So how can we do it first are going to access the process that are going to say EMV dot and then node
underscore EMV.
So this pretty much whenever we make a reference to the node environment this is going to be production
or something else.
So if it's triple equal to production just like this.
Let me make it right.
Production let me do it like this production.
It means that of course we are inside Heroku.
So of course it will record next recognize this of Orvil is going to pass.
It's true.
And this girl code right here will run.
All right.
So first I'm going to import path.
This is something from note J.S. so require.
And then it's gone.
It's going to be called Path.
Right.
So this is what we need to do we need to create a route that accepts any kind of requests and it can
and it kind of prompts.
So I'm going to say app that get opening close I'm going to open this I'm going to save slash.
I'm going to accept.
All right.
The Istar right here means all.
And then of course we do the response.
You know we function with the request and the response.
All right.
So we're going to send our response back to the client and this case is going to be response and we're
going to send the files I'm going to say sent file and the file is going to be our index that HVM out.
Of course we need to pass the path of where this file is located inside our directory inside Heroku
and inside the client or inside the building.
All right.
So going to say underscore underscore name Oh sorry forgot to do something.
We need to do path.
The right thing including right here at the top.
So resaw opening close instead of here we need to pass some arguments.
First one is going to be Dirnt than coma.
I'm going to say OK it's dot dot dot dot for Slash and then client.
All right the next one is going to be where we can we find the index that HVM L..
Well inside the build and then they're going to say coma and what do we need to render.
So the index that H team L and that is it.
Of course none of this routes right here.
There is no match within the routes is going to go to the fallback scenario.
And of course whenever we get this it's a request for a route of you know inside our application inside
the re-act single page down.
All right.
So far so good.
The problem is that sometimes we need to render.
We need to you know provide to the browser or whatever some static files just like javascript.
Right.
This indicates that it's Jamail cannot work without this without the bundle with bundled edges.
So we need to tell the server how to handle this kind of request.
You know the static files.
So again we pretty much do the same thing before.
Let me just go here.
I'm going to go right here at the bottom now I'm even with all the middleware.
That's OK.
And I'll go right here and I'm going to say of course and I am going to register a middleware So app
that Jews open and close and we say Xpress DOD and we say static.
Now we need to pass an instruction of you know where to find static files.
So they're going to be inside client and inside built.
All right.
And that is it I'm going to save it.
And now we can have it ready of course to go to Heroku again.
But first I'm going to do get status and begin to get you know just a server in this case because I
just did it.
But I can say at DOD then get command minus am and you know as server changes I'm going to press enter
and then get push
OK.
So now I'm going to clear since everything is up to date.
Inside get help and get I'm going to clear and we're going to do the get push Heroku.
Now of course we are going to get pretty much the same build than before but this time the build is
going to stop or actually it's going to do something before it stops and it's going to be that post
Bill.
We added right here Rick opposed Bill.
All right.
So let's try it.
We're going to press enter.
It's going to take a couple seconds.
Of course we're going to get a pause and be right back whenever we get the post Bill.
All right so now it starts stop the everything stopped with the post Bill.
Right.
And this command we added to the package to Jason and this is going to take a while because imagine
that it needs to download the dependencies it needs to you know run the build for react and everything
else.
So let's give it a minute.
OK so after everything was built we get you know the your L back.
So let's go to the your L and check it out.
I'm going to go right here.
And of course we get something but it fails.
But at least it's flashing something you know the header.
Let's see if we get again we can get it again.
Maybe we don't that's fine it doesn't matter of course I know why this is happening.
So if I go in to inspect something it's happening and we can add property overdressed.
So we get some errors but they are related to main dot and you know this is the jast This is the bundle.
So it's actually creating the bundle and trying to re-enter the re-act application but everything fails.
So why is it failing.
Well the thing is that if we go to the database the data is pretty much empty.
So it's trying to work with data we fetch from the database right from the start.
Real simple data and it's failing to get it.
So right here whenever the application starts it creates some of the you know some of the documents
collections right here.
But they are empty.
So it kind of fails.
All right.
So we have two choices and this is going to take a couple of minutes and it's going to be a little bit
weird.
So we have two choices.
You can manually go to Roble 3D just copy the contents of waves.
In this case whatever you can add manually the collections you can do that or you can try to grab whatever
you have in your computer and export it and then import it from here.
And this is on the cloud.
Notice that we are inside Mongul lab.
So we're going to do that right now.
OK.
So inside the on the left and right here we have some options.
And if we go to tools they you know they give us import and export Export helper.
So we cannot just you know run an imported or maybe export them from Mungo's from rubble through the
export files and then imported right here we can do that.
We need to do it through here and you get several.
You have several ways to do this.
And they are all weird and complicated.
So so we're going to be doing is this one the binary.
So what we're going to do we're going to go to our you know our instance of Mongo in our computer and
we're going to export to collection once we get that then we're going to import that database with Mungo's
store.
So right from the start in our computer whenever we installed Mungo you have access to these commands
now.
All right let's go.
Here are going to do clear and I'm going to just show you that you just cannot run these commands for
example right here we have Mongo dump.
So if I paste that command not found.
The thing is that we get we get this commands but they are inside the Mongo bin.
So just like with it right here to start a connection.
Let me see if I can find the first command we ran me one second.
Let me try to find this.
We have a lot of things of course could be real long I believe.
I mean.
Almost there.
There we go.
OK.
So to start Mongo we do dot for Slash Mongo d pad and everything else.
So this Mongo is just like the Mongo Dom and Mongo we store is pretty much the same thing.
So what we need to do we need to go to Ben.
And again if you're in windows you need to of course do the same thing.
Open a new shell a new command prompt and navigate to the bin of Mongo.
Just like with it to start we do start a mongo server.
And then what we do we just use dot for Slash to access that commands.
If I do that for Slash and Mongo dump something that's going to happen.
But of course it's not going to really work.
We need to type a lot of things.
All right.
So first I'm going to open a new tab right here.
Going to make a click and new tab with the Mongo bin.
Notice I'm inside the bend already.
So first we need to do we need to run a command.
And this is going to go to the robot 380 database and it's going to grab all the files and put it you
know can convert into binary you know kind of be Jason.
That's OK.
And it will store all the files inside a directory.
I've already created a directory I have here documents inside documents my example.
I call this dump it's empty directory.
That's OK.
It's going to show you in a minute.
So let's go back to the batch and what we need to do inside of the pen.
We do dot for Slash then Mongo then dump just like that Mongo dump the next one.
It's going to be the source the source of whatever we want to do.
You know the Mongo instance in our computer so we do minus H to make a reference to the location of
Mongo instance.
So what is the Mongo instance localhost.
2:7 Collon and you need the port 2 7 0 1 7 just like this.
Then we do a space and we need to specify the D.V. name right.
The database name.
So we do minus and then D.
It's kind of the shortcut for database and then we type the divi name our device name its waves.
So I'm going to say waves the next one.
We have the ability to do mine as you put the username and then minus P and then do the passport but
we don't have a user and a password.
Of course with databases you can add users and passport passports and they can only access through there.
So instead of our Mongul instance we don't have any users so we don't specify a user or a password.
That's OK.
It's going to work then we do minus 0 and 0.
It's going to be the director where are we going to be dumping all the files that dump directory.
And and this one what we need to do we just pacify the location.
If you're a Windows machine you will need to do see Collen or whatever.
You know it's the local drive then forward slash maybe users and documents you will need to you know
go to the location in our computer and of course if we are Mac we just do that.
Tilda just like this then for Slash and I'm going to go to documents for Slash documents for Slash and
then that dump directory.
I'm going to press enter and after you get this if I go to that directory we get the waves inside dump.
So creating a directory for us.
And if I enter we get all the you know all the data.
So what we need to do now is run a different command.
But instead of exporting this we need to import I'm sorry.
Importing Karena export from our our instance of Mongo.
We need to run a command to import it from the Mongo divi on the cloud.
Right.
So let's begin with that right.
So now we need to do pretty much the same thing but the opposite side we need to grab whatever we get
inside the directory and put it inside Mongolia laugh.
And again we go to Tools right here.
You get the command.
It's Mongul restore than the name of this instance of Mongo TV and you get all the information right
here.
The database user and everything else.
Then you will need a username password.
And I'm a little bit curious right here.
I never tried this without a user and without a password I always you know create a used in a password.
Of course if there's we're going to try it and if it doesn't if it's not working then we will at the
user password.
How can you add users.
You go to the users tap out a database user username and password resemble.
All right.
So let's try this one.
I'm going to copy Mongul restore go to the bin.
And remember that we need to do that for in case Mongul we store the space and I need to specify the
place.
And remember if you don't windows see column and everything else.
If not if you're a Mac just like me that for Slash documents for Slash I believe it was a dump dump
for Slash and then waves and for Slash.
OK let's see what happens.
Enter And
well it should be all much longer.
I believe that maybe something is wrong.
Maybe we need to add the user and password.
Let me go to collection's reload of course.
The process right here whenever we do this actually goes ok.
It's much much much longer not outcries so yeah.
OK.
That is good.
Let's try it again.
I'm going to call and go to Tools.
I got a copy pretty much all.
And I'm going to just stop and password.
We're going to do that forward slash then Mongo restore.
Right.
And then you know pretty much the same thing of course.
This one is for import database.
Make sure of that.
And we are importing a database not a collection collection is just a single part.
So you have the user password.
Let's create a user in a password and see what happens.
So I read mine and then password one two three.
Let me do it again password.
One two three.
One more time.
Passport.
One two three.
Of course in real life you need to be a little bit more creative than this.
So create.
All right so now we have get a user.
So we're going to go to user and say f my last name which in English means Wolf kind of weird.
So then password one two three.
And then of course and don't say same thing for Slash then documents.
Then of course for Slash and it's dump for Slash and then waves.
Just make sure waves and then dump and then cut and then are going to do four slash press center.
And it works.
Told you this is much much bigger.
All right.
So you need to use the password now we know.
So I going to go to collections.
If you just go to collections nothing really happens.
So I'm going to reload the application.
And now we get all the documents.
So the migration is done.
Of course we didn't have a lot of things but this could be much bigger.
So including one by one.
You know I'm not a good idea.
All right.
So I have one more problem I want to fix.
I never tested this before and realized that I have a problem in my code.
If I go to Minsk on the server routes I have API for class users and nothing.
And the same thing with site voice site.
So this works and that this one has a four slash.
So on the development server this works but on production this will not work is going to give us an
error message.
So I'm going to change that and I'm going to do it again.
You know push everything again.
Get as you can get this part if you wish it and then get push ups or get commit minors.
Am I the Sam then the message which is change routes server whatever.
Then go get push.
And then I'm going to go to Heroku again like I told you you can skip this because you know you know
this kind of boring.
So get push and then Heroku going to try one more time going to pause the video so it can be a little
bit faster.
For you at least OK so everything was done.
I'm going to copy and check it out.
Let's see what happens.
Hopefully no mistakes so I can go to the route and
we are good to go to everything works.
So if you scroll down you know the Lanc you're getting you're getting the images from you know college
Narey and everything goes OK.
Now if I go to this beautiful sir.
It works.
All right.
So everything works for now.
Now of course if I do this that we will get an end and we are not going to get any message.
Yeah I remember we get it on the council but I'm not going to do it.
Everything works as expected.
Right.
So I get to go to home back home.
I'm going to try to log in.
So Frances password one two three law again and we are able to log in and we of course maintain the
information about the user.
Let's try to go to home if I at a Navan is a gem.
It is a deep bass guitar.
Can add it.
We get the cart and you know we get my guitar and then the jam.
So everything works man very good.
OK.
So this is the last thing we're going to do are going to skip everything.
I'm going to put everything inside this project this waste repository so you can get the final code
and I'm going to be adding some more sections at first going to add more to WIPs because you know this
is the more complete one and most of the notes students or people want to know about this one.
So I'm going to add some more which adds some more functionality to this one.
And of course on each section I get to add tiny sections as long as the discourse is pretty much done
with waste project.
It's not.
But you know just for fun I'm going to add and I have a list right here.
Maybe you can.
Of course maybe make some comments in what you want to add or maybe what you're interested in.
You know I'm going to generate an ID whenever a user buys something.
Remember whenever we buy something we get the idea from pay pal.
Well this time we're going to generate again to do a hash.
Our own custom hash and I'm going to return that one again inside of the you know the database and then
of course I'm going to add here maybe an end point where we can see all the purchases with the ID and
everything else and on the mike my account on user history I can add the ID that ID of purchase.
So we can make a reference to that ID on the database.
That's one thing.
Know maybe not that simple but the point right here is just it's going to be very simple just like my
account just like this.
A simple simple table what else are going to do a reset password.
Right now we cannot password.
If I go to log in you know forgot my password we didn't get that.
So I'm going to do it.
What else.
I'm going to give you maybe a couple of options with sending e-mails maybe when the users log in you
want to have a service or something.
Or you can send an e-mail whenever they log in.
Or maybe when they reset the passport maybe send the hash you know to the e-mail.
Do the user e-mail and they didn't then they can enter to a different route with that hash.
And we said the passport you know the usual usual stuff what else I was going to show you how to upload
images with multi-hour.
That's when it's very very simple.
No not that hard.
But maybe I'm not going to do it on this end point to this project I'm going to maybe create a tiny
tiny tiny form with a server with no Jair server are going to show you how to use motter it's very very
simple because if I if I tried to do this on beaches go here Francis passport one two three if I had
to show you how to link can to do everything inside of our products.
I'll have to you know kind of kill the logic right here and mortified.
I don't want to I don't want to do that.
I just want to leave this like this.
And maybe in a different component.
Just show you how to do it with Mulder just with a couple of images maybe a couple of images and nothing
else.
Maybe with files.
That's OK.
And then I have some minor improvements maybe I really didn't do the job.
No it didn't.
The 4:4.
OK.
I'm going to add it to the list.
We didn't do a for a four.
So I'm going to do it for four.
That what should be really really really simple.
We did it on the second project and after and done adding things to waves I'm going to add a few things
to the second project.
They are more firebase related stuff.
But that said and of course as time goes goes by if something comes up I'm going to just create a component
or maybe a tiny widget and show you how to do it.
All right.
OK.
So I hope you enjoyed the project and catch you maybe on the next course.