Write so before using Mongo D-B we need to install it.
So I'm going to go to the browser and I'm going to say Mongo D-B just like that.
And of course it's going to be pretty much the same there.
The first result Maunganui to be for giant ideas.
We're going to go there and OK you're going to have a bunch of data right here a bunch of options.
We're going to go right here to the one that says download on top and we're going to go to download
and we need to select.
And again you can have a lot of options but begin to use the one that says community server.
Because of course it's free.
So if you're you need to select the person that you're going to use.
In this case we are a Mac so I'm going to use OSX 10 64 bits with S as well.
We're going to use that one.
And then of course we need to download.
So I'm going to click and download OK it's going to start downloading it just one second and I'm going
to save it into downloads.
So it's it's going to be like 90 megabytes.
It's going to take a few minutes.
So I'm going to parse the BDO and be right back.
OK so now everything is downloaded.
So what we need to do we need to go to downloads and we need to extract the the folder.
Gays can take a few seconds.
OK.
It's going to give you a folder you know this folder Mongul divi OSX and then the version.
And what we do now is to grab this folder and drop it inside the boot directory or your user directory.
In my case it's going to be Apple.
OK I'm just going to drop it here and it's going to get it's going to be right here if you don't have
this option on the favorites.
What you can do on the finder right here you can go to go and you can have an option that's going to
say home.
So you know same directory.
So now what we need to do this folder.
We need to change the name.
We need to rename it.
So we're going to rename it to Monga.
Now the next thing is going to be to create a new folder.
It's going to be Mongo hyphen data.
So this Mongul data folder is going to host all the information about the database that you're going
to create inside this folder.
So this one is going to be the one that is going to host all that data.
So now what we need to do we need to start the server and connect to Mongo.
So I'm going to go right here and we need to navigate to this Mongo folder.
I am at home root.
So what we can do is say CD Mungo for Slash and we can go to the bin folder to the bin directory.
Now if I do is going to get a lot of directories and there is two that begin to use begin to use the
Mongo and the Mongo D.
So Mongo D is the one that is going is going to start to server so we can make no rescue operations
and Mogo is going to be the one that is going to connect with Mongul D.
So these two are the ones that we're going to use.
OK.
So now before doing anything we need to start to server and to let Mongo d what is going to be the location
of the database which in this case is going to be Mongo data right here.
So first we're going to do that for I-Slash and we're going to use Mongo D then we do minus minus D.B
and then path and then we need to make a space and we need to specify the location for Mongo data.
We're going to use the tiller and then for Slash and then Mongo hyphen data.
Now if you press enter it's going to start doing some weird thing
OK almost on an alley and you're going to get a message that's going to say waiting for connections
on port 2 7 0 1 7.
This means that the server is running and it's ready to go.
So now the right side on the terminal going to make a right click and I'm going to open a new tab.
So this new tab notice that I am I am already the Ben location inside Mungo So this tap with this tab
we you're going to connect to this server that we have running right here.
So we're beginning to do it's really really simple.
We need to do that for flash and then Mongo.
So he's going to give you a lot of information and notice that you don't have the command.
You have just the ride ponding pointing arrow.
So this is just like note.
This means that you are running and then you can run Mongo divi commands right here.
You can use the database and if you go to the Mongo the right here you can have some information that's
going to say received climate data from localhost.
And you know who's going to give you some bunch of information Mongo shell and then the type of computer
that received this connection which is going to be Darwin and Mac OS which is my computer you know local
host.
That's good.
You know so your ready to go.
So I'm going to go to right here to Mungo and I'm going to just run some tests I'm going to say D.B
and this is the way we connect with the database going to create a dummy record inside Mongo DB.
So I got to say D-B they're going to say test and this is going to be the name of our database.
We don't have a database right here.
But since it's not there is going to create it.
I believe that by default.
Not really sure that by default with Mongo D-B you get a test D-B by default.
Now it doesn't matter if it's not there it's going to create us it's going to create this database for
us.
So we're going to say insert and with this we will insert new data.
And I'm just going to do curly braces and just going to add name and of course Francis.
Now I'm going to press enter.
I was going to say.
Right.
We sold and inserted one.
So this means that it's good you know.
We have one record when went day two month old baby went to the database and inserted one record.
So how can we check if this record exist.
So we're going to say again same thing D.B than we do test and we do find now the find method is going
to show you all the records in that database.
So going to press enter and it's going to give me this as a return.
We have an ID and we're going to talk about this I.D. later.
And then name and Francis this I.D. It's unique.
It's something that Mungo TV it's doing by default is going to provide you with the default I.D. but
this is this comes from Mongo D-B you know everything is working.
We are running the show the database you're connecting and we are just adding some records.
OK that's good.
But you know if you if we need to create a project and we need to do a lot of operations with the databases
you know just checking everything from the terminal it's just like a pain in the butt.
You know we can be typing the whole time.
It's going to be really really long.
So we have some tools that can help us to inspect the information you know in a little bit more Rafic
way.
We have something that is going to be called rubber Mongo.
So just get ready to install rebloom on go in just one second.