So let's install Mongo.
I'm going to go right here to the browser.
I'm going to say Mongo D-B.
So OK.
So we going to have this option here.
Mulga would you be for giant ideas.
It is going to be Mongo D-B dot com.
So I'm going to click on it and it's going take us here.
So on the top right hand corner you can have a button that it's going to say downloads so we click download.
And again we can have several options.
The one we care is going to be the community server.
That one is free.
You know the word community.
So again we can have several options.
The one we need is going to be Windows Server 64 bit and later with S S L support Sevigny so that selected
that one they're going to click download and you know it's quite large it's going to wait it's going
to wait like I don't know 150 megabytes So that's going to take a while.
So I'm going to pass the Berio coffee and be right back.
OK so everything is ready.
So I'm going to click the installer is going to give me the run and just click click and run.
OK.
We're going to do next and accept terms.
Now it's going to give you two choices to complete.
And the custom of going to choose the complete and then of course we will click install is going to
ask me if I'm I'm sure just wait for it.
And yeah I'm sure go.
OK.
So it's installing.
It's going to take a few seconds.
There we go.
Almost done.
And I get it finished so I'm going to call it unfinished.
So now what we need to do we need to do two things.
First we need to start the Mongo divi server and then we need to connect to the Mongo divi server.
So to do this we can open a new command and open ACMD it right here and go into navigate to the root
folder to see so I'm going to say CD for Slash is going to take me just right to it.
Now I'm going to open the explore.
I'm going to go to a local disk program files right here inside program files.
We can have mango DV and then server and then the version which is the 3.4.
So we need to navigate to this location.
So we're going to do cd than Program Files.
My mistake.
Let's go again.
CD program files.
Oh sorry my mistake again.
Let's go back.
So again see the server that program then files and it's going to be for Slash.
We need to go to Mongo Mungo D-B for Slash and then server forward slash go again server for Slash.
And the person is going to be the three that for that.
Fortunately again and when he entered the bin folder.
Good.
So now right here.
I'm going to say there is going to give me a lot of options right here.
A lot of executables.
And there is of all the options.
This two are the ones we care the Mongo that the SC and the Mongo D that exist.
So the Mongo D is going to start the server and the Mongo that he is going to connect to that server.
So now with Mac or Linux what we can do we can go to the local disk and enter users and create a folder
where we're going to install all this all the same I'm sorry we're we going to store all the databases
so I could do it right here under my user.
But with windows that my cats cause some problems.
So the Mogo divi by default uses the default folder inside the local disks.
So for windows we can do the local disk.
See that's going to be the difference.
So we need to create a folder that is going to be data and inside the data folder we're going to do
a new file folder folder that is going to be the be.
Right.
So now I'm going to go right here and I'm going to execute this Mongo D that easy.
It's going to go right here and say Mongo D that e x c and then just enter.
It's going to do a bunch of stuff you know it's going to take a second.
And at the end you can negate you're going out waiting for connections on port 2 7 0 1 7.
That's cut.
So if you get this it means that it's working.
So we can open a new and I'm going to do reichlich and then command prompt going to do pretty much the
same thing that before.
Going to do CD4 slash is going to take us back.
And we need to re-enter to the same location again.
CD program files for I-Slash Mongo D-B for Slash server for Slash 3.4 for slash and burn.
So now here we're going to start instead of the Mago de Mongo that you see.
So this Mongo that easy is going to do something and then it's going to connect with with the with the
Mongo the instance that we have right here.
If it's not connecting go back to the Mongo D and do Control-C that is actually an error that is happening
with Mongo that DXi.
But you know it's going to work.
So you're going to get something like a connection except that one connection open it is going to give
you information about your operating system.
In this case it's going to be Windows Microsoft and whatever.
So this means that you're connected.
You know this instance is connected and right here you're going to get the you're going to get a right
pointing arrow just like we'd get with node.
Whenever we start node with the rebel.
Well this is the same idea.
Now we are inside Mongo and we can run Mongo commands.
So.
OK.
What I'm going to do I'm going to go right here.
I'm not going to say the B and begin to start a database.
I'm going to say divi that test that's going to be the name of the database and I'm just going to insert
some data.
So we're going to do dot and we're going to do insert now insert we do open and close parenthesis and
right here.
I'm going to pass an object so the object of course is going to be some Jason data.
So we're going to do.
Name and of course you guessed it Francis.
There we go.
So when I press Enter it's going to try to insert this record into Mongo Mongul D-B folder.
It's taken a while so maybe it's frozen will be do with the control see again.
Nothing happens.
Let's see what happens.
OK.
So I press enter.
Sorry for that.
And this right result and we get and inserted and then just one.
This means of course that everything went OK.
And this record was stored inside our Mongo folder.
So to check it we're I'm going to do is D-B dot test which is the name of the database and then don't
find this find method is going to bring all the information we have on our database.
So going to press center is going to give me or resolve an ID which is a unique ID that Margot DV is
going to is going to assign to this document and then we have the name Francis So you know Mongo DB
is working now.
We're going to we're going to work with servers and we're going to be inserting data into the Mongo
DVH database and doing it from the command prompt.
And this is kind of a pain in the butt.
So we're not going to do that.
We're going to use a different tool.
We can of course use knode but to inspect everything going to do it on a different way we can use rebel
Mongo.
Now it has a different name.
It was rumormonger in the past.
Now it's going to be called robo or something like robo that treaty or something like that.
But it's the same thing it's the the old the old Rebel Mongo.
That's fine if it's working.
That's good.
If you had any problems just just sent the chat right here to put it on the Q&amp;A.
And I will answer as soon as I can.
Let's go to the next section and install rebel Mongo.