OK so let's install Reber Mongo.
I'm going to go right here to the browser.
I'm going to say rather Mogo.
So you're going to have some results right here and you can have robo 3D formerly Rovell Mongo.
So back in the day when this project started started as Rovell Mongo not rubble.
380.
I believe they had some problems some license's problems problems because it was using the word Mongo
Mavie Mongo divi ass.
Ask them for money or maybe to change the name so they change it to robo 3.
I liked them more but that's fine.
I'm going to click and download is going to start to download of course.
So I'm going to say download and you know I have it for Mac so we download it.
So it's going to take a few minutes.
I'm going to save it and downloads.
OK so it's going to go.
I can possibly deal and be right back.
OK so now everything is ready so I'm going to go to documents and you can have the.
I'm sorry to download.
And you can have the file just right there are going to double click it.
If it's not old and you open it you need to do control click.
Of course we're going to go to devices and inside devices you can have it right there.
If not you're going to get it inside applications.
If it's not inside applications just like we were going to go to robo 380 and just drop it inside applications.
So if we search it right here we're going to have it right here.
Robo 380.
So I'm going to DoubleClick it.
It's going to take a few seconds.
As I say robo it's not an application downloaded.
Yeah.
That's.
We are.
Sure.
So that is going to open the application.
You might have some things right here.
I'm going to remove it.
Going to do it.
Everything from the start.
So you can have this panel.
Mongo DB connections.
So right here we need to go to create inside the create.
You can have some options and we're going to use the connection for now.
So we need to give a name to this connection.
So I'm going to call it local local and then MZB for Mongo divi you know local for this computer.
And the address is going to be again just local host and the default port 2:07 is your 1:07.
Then going to click save.
And with this highlighted we're going to do connect.
So in the left you're going to get this you know the system and the test and this is the actual database
that we were we were with did right here you know this record if I double click and test is going to
give you give us this panel with the actual information that we have on this database you know named
Francis and the ID.
This is really really great.
The other choice would be to do it right here from the terminal which is kind of a pain in the ass.
So right here we can do the information whenever we inserted.
It's going to just out magically appear right here and we can even inspect like this.
We have we have different types of abuse or we can just add data manually.
You know that's really really great.
OK.
So now we are ready to start with Mongo D-B.
So let's go to the next section and start with this.