OK so let's insolvable Mungo.
I'm going to go right here.
I'm going to say rubber Mongo.
OK so now right here you can have the rubber Mungo dot org which is Robo 330 formerly of Mongo.
That's the one we need.
So right here we can have two choices.
This is the one we want to download robo 3-G so we can click and download and of course we want it for
Mac and my case is going to be the installer 64 bit.
You have the option for a portable version.
Now just going to go in to install it.
So I'm going to put it in downloads and it's going to take just a few seconds.
It's 11 megabytes.
It's really small so it should be done in a second.
Everything done.
So I'm just going to click on it and open it and you get a click yes.
And then just next then I agree then next and then then install.
We just need to keep clicking next.
So OK I'm going to run the reboot 3 T.
Just real simple.
So of you will do and we and then just next we don't want to do this.
So I'm going to click and finish and.
OK.
So the main screen you can have this tiny window and we can have just two choices are going to delete
and remove all of them maybe because I have them from a previous version.
So I'm just going to delete them.
Now what do we need to do with it to click uncreate.
Right here we have four choices create edit remove and done and clone and then click and create.
Right here we going to create a new connection.
You can assign whatever name I'm going to put mine.
Local then Robo.
I'm sorry for Mongo.
And then we get.
So again it's going to be local host and 27 0 1 7.
Remember that we have right here Domingo the running on the 2 7 0 1 7.
So I'm going to do save right here.
We're going to have this instance the local MTV.
Again you could use whatever name you want.
Going to connect.
It's going to take one second and right here on the top left you're going to have local MTV system and
then test.
Now if we open this test and if we go to collections and we will talk.
What collections is and document are you going can have the test.
Now if I double click on the on the test you can get right here the information that we've entered previously.
You have the D and the name Francis.
So right here you could have whatever view you can have the table view you can have the Jason view and
we can edit or add some documents some data and modified Vihear directly from this interface.
So this is much much much much easier than doing it from here.
Right.
So everything went OK that's good.
This is just a simple application just a simple interface.
So let's move forward and go to the next section and start using Mongo D-B.