OK so this is going to be the first bonus section of the third project and what are we going to do now.
We're going to send e-mail so whenever we can send an email whenever the user registers right here or
create an account we will send an email from within the server they're just saying you know welcome.
Or something like that.
That's what we need to do now.
We're doing this as the first bonus section because.
And of course this is a bonus section because maybe you don't care about e-mails.
You know we sent e-mails so there's no need to add it to the no original flow of the application.
But we're going to do it now.
Now we have many many ways of sending e-mails.
We're going to use the most default one which is not mailer this one.
So this one is a third party library.
We can install.
We can hook it up with our account our G-mail or maybe e-mail account works with any e-mail and this
one 3L is a testing.
I'm not going to use this one.
I just created two fake accounts for Gmail and just to get it a little bit more real.
And we're going to send an e-mail to you know the from the Francis I'm sorry Francis let me find it
here.
FRANCES JONES Oh it locked me out.
Let me just do the log in.
I create an account called waves that guitarist that Rabbe.
So this is the this is the shop and this one it's the user that's going to be registering.
So I'm going to log in I create of course a fake account.
I'm going to give you the passport everything else.
But of course you shouldn't use this one.
So
all right so what are we going to be doing.
Of course we're going to install this module and we're going to send an e-mail to something like this.
Of course you have and you get all the documentation you get a lot of configuration right here.
Ours is going to be real simple but you know right here you get all the examples and if you want to
use thermal is a testing environment for males.
Right now on the web for development you got a lot of ways of sending e-mails.
Now this is one one one way.
Right.
You have other ways like using Amerson services.
You can even use a sales force.
And you know and they work just like the cloud denarii they give you a service they give you the connector
the token everything else.
You set it up on the server and then you just you know send that to the to their servers.
For example when they bring this one.
This one called Melgen and this one is very very popular popular and works really really well.
So this one it's just like clock Kloeden Harry.
They give you an API.
They give you a token.
You just hook it up right here send email through them and they will send you our response and that
is that works really really great.
Use this one in the past never had a problem and has tons of support.
You can even send 10000 e-mails free every month.
And of course if you need to send more e-mails you can upgrade and the prices you know are really really
good.
Not bad prices.
So I'm going to close this because we're not going to use it.
We're going to use this one.
So first we need to install it.
It's going to go here and say I'm going to kill the server then do clear and we do your own install.
So you're sorry your odd and then node mailer.
Right.
I'm going to use a very specific version.
You should do the same.
So it's the four six seven going to presenter.
It's going to take one minutes very very fast and now it's done because i've already have it installed.
So I'm going to clear.
And then you run your own run dev to start everything again.
So like before we have we get the waves that guitarist that ref which is the main account the shop account
and then the user right.
This is the new user you could use the same one you know the same sender and the same receiver with
your Gmail account.
You can do that.
It's going to work.
Now there's one more thing.
For example this wave that Guitard that Rev we need to pass some passport and configuration so we need
to put the passport right here.
So we need to change the configurations on the on the one that it's going to be sending the e-mail.
Ride the shop.
So right here if you look at when you're logged in with your account if you give access to my account
that Google dot com less secure apps and if you look at this on the web it's going to give you the configuration
you need to allow less secure apps on to you know send emails with your account through third party
service.
In this case our application if you of course don't do this.
Nothing's going to be sent so you need to do this if you want to test with Gmail.
Maybe you want to test with something else.
And that is cool.
It's going to work anyways.
All right.
So let's begin.
We install everything everything is running so now we're going to go to the server and require of course
the node mailer.
So going to say Konst Konst node Aghan called Meilleur equals require opening close.
And we say node Meyler real simple right now.
What are we going to do.
So we can learn how node Meilleur works are going to do all the logic right here.
So whenever the service starts we will send an e-mail.
Right.
And then we're going to of course begin to grab this.
Put it on a different place and make a more elaborated call code for this.
We're going to create some templates and everything else.
But for now just going to give you an example of how this works.
So first just to send to e-mail.
You need to create a transport.
So I'm going to say Konst as MCP and then transport you know this is just the name of the Birol you
can call wherever you like.
Then we make a reference to that third party library which is no way Meyler sorry.
And then we bring the Create transport so they create transport.
It's the connector is the thing that it's going to connect with the shop account.
In this case wave's not guitars that Rev.
So of course we need to pass an object and the object is the configuration you know how are we going
to use it.
So we need to specify a service.
And in this case it's going to be G-mail right than coma.
And we need of course to pass the indication of this not nothing's going to work.
So I went to a user and a passport so the user in my case it's waves that that RAM so waves that get
tars.
I believe I did plural guitars.
Yes that waves waves and guitars that Rev at gmail dot com.
And then of course coma and we need to Pat we need to give the password to this.
So the password it's full tone 1985.
So Fulton is a brand for you know guitar pedals.
I'm a guitar fan.
What are we going to do.
OK.
So now we are whenever we send the email discreet transport will connect with this and send email at
the end.
Now the next thing is going to be setting everything that has to do with the receiver.
Someone is going to be receiving e-mails from this account.
So we need to create a viable where we can store this and call it email and everything is on the documentation.
I'm using pretty much the same example then we have from we have two we have a subject just like this.
We have a text you can skip text and then an h t m l which is you know the code it's going to go to
the e-mail.
So the from is going to be from where you know from which you know service or user or whatever.
In this case it's going to be the waits which is the shop.
So this is going to be waves or something like that.
And then we need to pass the e-mail just like this now too.
And the two it's going to be that Jones that rep.
FRANCES JONES That rev at gmail that come then we need to pass the subject what is the subject.
So I'm going to send send test e-mail right.
That Acoma the text.
And again it's just a text testing our waves mails whatever that is coma and we need to pass the mail
that it's going to be rendered on the on the actual mail.
So in this case I'm going to put a bold of.
Hello guys.
This works something like that.
And that is it.
So whenever we create the transport that's going to connect this account and it will send an e-mail
with all this data in this configuration.
Then at the end do you get a third thing which is the the S T S M A T P transport and a callback.
So we do m s r s m t p and transport than dot and we send the email.
So we are doing that action and this one of course will need the mail that we want to send just like
here and the S.M. GP transport it's survival.
So is connected to this sending this email.
And then of course Colma you get a function back you can use our functions.
I'm using pretty much same example.
They give us so of course you get an error and you get a response.
Now of course if you get an error or something like this I'm going to cancel on the console log the
error are very good.
And then else opening close and we do console log.
I don't know email sent now.
Every time you open this it's going to go and perform this action.
So you need to close it so.
And as transport.
And then we do close.
All right.
And that is it.
So in theory if I restart the server noticed I did a safe right here and not want it's restarting my
server.
And we get the e-mail sent.
So we get this callback everything worked.
So now if I go to Frances Jones again we get two e-mails.
You know really works really easy.
Waves sent us e-mail and hello guys this works and we are sending of course from this.
Now this is not working is because something of this is wrong but most likely is the less secure apps.
Make sure you set this on for the this account.
The way waves not guitar you know whatever account you're using.
All right.
So this works.
So what we're going to be doing now we're going to create a function actually you can create a place
where we can store our emails logic because we don't want to do this every time we send an e-mail.
Right.
So we're going to create a function and that function makes a reference to a file that hosts this function
and we will be passing the sender the name some extra data we will need later and which template we
can create templates.
Right.
Well let's go to the next one and create all the logic to create that function.