All right so let's begin with this.
I'm going to come in this out because we're not going to really use it right now lived here because
I'm going to copy paste later in a minute.
So now what we can do we can create a place where we can host all this logic and just like we did with
a client.
I'm going to create a new directory called you Tilse just you tell us.
And instead of if you're going to add the email you know all the logic for mail could be mails but I'm
going to call it mails.
So we're going to create a folder called mail at one minute.
Let me fix it lit and details and then I'll do the same thing.
Let me do with the directory.
So I'm going to clog mail and this mail will get an index Dunja Yes you can call it whatever you want.
I'm just going to call it an X..
So on inside of this and this will create a function that you know does all this logic and then we just
Later here we'll just make a reference to that function and we sent the email very simple.
So let's begin with the function real simple just a function going to create a concept called Send email.
Write the send email.
It's going to be equal to a function and later of course we need to export dysfunction.
So we can include it inside server.
And you know use it.
So we're going to do module Dionte exports equals send email just like we did before.
So we're going to copy and paste up copy and paste right.
So now this function it's available from within other components or files.
So on the send email we will be passing many many things.
First I'm going to send it to you know where are we going to be sending e-mail.
Then coma begin to pass.
The name of the user of where we are going to be sending is them I'm going to add a token we are not
going to really use it right now but I'm just going at it.
And then a type and again the type we will use it in a couple of minutes.
So pretty much on the sent e-mail what we need to do we need to create transport.
So we got it right here.
Going to copy and paste and going on come with this.
So we are creating an empty as empty transport with Meyler and kwi transport.
So the problem is that now we may correct.
We are making a reference to Meyler but Meyler it's inside of the server.
So I'm going to copy the mailer and remove it save it and I'm going to bring it right here.
So now we do have access to Maler.
Is this still going to be G-mail and the same Wavves that guitars all the males are going to go through
this.
Now the thing is that we are adding the password right here and we maybe maybe we don't want to do that
because this is going to go to get have.
And if you make it public everyone knows your password.
So I'm going to copy this.
I'm going to go to dot ENP And you know add a passport for this added to the environment variables.
Later of course when you go to production you will need to add it you know just like with it before.
So I'm going to call it e-mail underscore.
Pass it calls.
And then the password.
Now remember that to use this we need to include the EMV right here.
So now whenever we make a reference to that no process that EMV e-mail past we should be getting you
know the password.
So I'm going to delete this and say Process me make me get right process that and the DOD and we call
that email pass that is dead right.
Imma pass going to this one for now.
Close it OK.
So now we have your creating the sim to transport everything.
OK.
Now the problem is that we need to kind of choose what template are we going to be using.
Because if we send a welcome email that the right here the DML is going to look a little bit different
than the reset passport email.
So we need to create some logic so we can pass that type of what are we going to be doing whenever we
trigger this function and send the correct template of course we know.
We don't have this function going to create it right now I'm going to say Konst mail just like we did
before and I'm going to create a function called get e-mail data or you could call it again choose email
template or something like that.
And I'm going to be passing all the same probs getting from the you know the function and then of course
at the end going to save go to server and we do the S.M. GP transport only uncomment and that is it.
So of course we do the A.P. transport we use this one and then we send whatever we get from the mail
and whatever we get back from this function.
So this function is just really really simple.
It's like creating a reusable component in re-act are going to create the function and then we just
use a switch.
So Konst get e-mail data again open and close and it's just a function.
We will be getting pretty much the same thing right here.
So instead of type for example you could call it template.
It's completely up to you the type it's the type of template to be using.
So at the top we can ascend we can to create a viable called data could be called email or template
again no.
And it starts us.
Of course.
And then at the end what we return return is the data we return this viral.
So in between what we do we use a switch opening close and we say that we want to evaluate the template.
So if we have a template of welcome then we will return the welcome configuration.
So in this case we're going to create a case and if the case is welcome we're going to do something.
And then of course we always need to do break.
Of course we get a default scenario default opening close and we just return just data that is that
the data equals data.
You can do the return right here doesn't matter right now.
OK.
So what are we going to do if the case is that we get up.
I'm going to I'm sorry we get a request for this e-mail and then get e-mail data and we need to check
the template.
If the case is welcome we can to change the data.
So data it's equal to an object.
Remember just like with it right here on the server right here and I going a copy of this and paste
it right here.
All right I'll comment and make it a little bit better.
So the from.
It's going to be always wave guitars that wrap.
Right.
OK.
Then the two it's going to change.
And remember that you're going to be receiving this as an argument and this is an object.
So what I can do I can do just this and that's it because we are using ESX now the subject in this case
for the welcome we need to kind of a hard code.
This right here.
So it's going to be welcome to waves and we are passing the name so I can make a reference to the name
of the user right here.
And of course we need to use templates strings or not we don't read the text.
If you want you can delete it just like this.
And then of course we say OK we want to send this team out.
Right.
OK.
The thing is that we don't have a template.
You're just sending some hard coded data right here.
So now we need to create a template to send a welcome and we're going to do that right now.
I'm going to add if you check his resources you have a file.
It's a welcome template that H Tim L and that one we have all the code for.
You know a welcome template.
Of course you can use your own if you wish.
Just possibly though I did right here Tomales.
Right.
And then I to show you what we're going to be doing.
All right so if I have added the welcome that template now if I double click it this is what we get.
I don't know if something is simple welcome to waves and syntax and then a GIF with a.
You know doing the super rock position.
OK.
So this is what we will we will be sending to Francis that John Jones that.
Right now if we open this right here is just an h m l template.
I'm adding this and giving you this because what are we going to do on the screen.
Everything manually is just the table is just a table that does it.
So what are we going to do since we want to include this right here we can.
We cannot just include a template of an h t m l template we can and need to do it with template strings
just like we are doing right here and Javascript.
So I'm going to go to mail going to create a new file and this one will be called the same name.
Welcome underscore template dot Javascript.
So there's this one the only things going to do it's return some strings.
You know some HDMI counted inside templates strings.
So Konst welcome.
Let me do it right here.
Konst welcome equals to a function and that function will be returning return some template strings.
Right of course with node we need to make this welcome a bail when it's exported.
So we do module that exports equals and then welcome.
All right.
Of course what we need to do we need to put inside of here all this template that's why I'm giving this
to you.
So you don't need to type it.
So I'm going to copy paste and make it a little bit better.
Well that's OK.
So now what do we need to do instead of index this index of mail.
We need to include this function that returns a template and then make a reference of the welcome template
right here.
Brian will a simple act of a make sense.
So I'm going to go and say Konst welcome equals require.
And it's inside that forward slash.
And then welcome template that jazz.
So now we just say welcome.
All right.
So whenever we make a request on site we make a reference to this send email function within the server
send email will receive a to a name a token that we can do this later and a type which is the type of
template write the type of e-mail we want sent.
It will create the transport.
It will get the data from the function that gets the template and then we just send it and we get a
look at is it a very very simple not that hard.
OK.
So we pretty much have everything we need.
Hopefully hopefully no mistakes.
So we need to export.
And so we are already exporting.
We need to import this sent email from within the server so we can use it inside around Ryan.
OK.
So I'm going to go here and say that I want to you know bring something from you tills.
All right.
So of course we need to include it.
So just like with it right here Konst cons opening close in and we call this function sent e-mail right.
Yeah send sent e-mail copy.
I'm going to paste some space equals and then we do the require opening close and it's not for Slash
you tails for Slash mail always lash and then index.
All right.
So now we have a function right here.
So we need to use it.
So we're going to be using this inside of the user whenever we register a user.
We're going to send this.
We can send this e-mail right now and right here you can choose to do this whatever you want.
Remember that whenever we do a save on the user we do the preset save.
Let me just go so I can refresh your memory whenever we save.
We are doing a presale.
So you can include that function right here and whenever you you do the pre-sale and everything is done
you can trigger that function right there.
I'm going to do something simple so everything it's you know kind of clear right here.
So after we save the user and we are ready to send the response back to the client I'm going to send
the e-mail first.
Let me do a return right here.
OK.
So I'm going to send an e-mail opening close.
Now we need to pass that to the name a token if we have one and then type.
Right.
Very simple.
So I'm going to go to server.
I'm going to pass it to.
So if we are using our we are storing as a user we get the response of that user you know the date of
that user inside doc.
So the name is going to be on sort of the e-mail it's going to be inside doc.
That e-mail Ryan the first property.
It's that too.
All right.
Now in a coma.
The second argument is going to be the name.
So again doc.
And the name of the user.
We don't have a token.
So in this case we pass no and then coma and we just pacify what is a template.
We can never using in this case the index.
We say that it's called Welcome.
So I'm going to copy and say welcome and that is it.
So before we return this we are going to send in e-mail.
And there's one more thing you can do.
I'm not going to do it right here but you could do it so you can pass the last argument.
Could be the last which is going to be a callback.
So this callback.
It's pretty much a function.
Right you can make this a function.
So if we're never we send an e-mail right here.
You bring the call back from the arguments and you say OK whenever it's sent I want to trigger that
callback.
Right.
And that callback you can execute that call back after you send the e-mail and that call that we'll
be executing this code.
So you're kind of a changing actions in this case we just send the e-mail and we go straight to generate
success.
True right.
You can do that if you wish.
OK so now we are ready to test.
Let's see what happens.
OK so I'm going to go here to our application and bring my my user.
It's Francis Jones that rep.
OK.
So name Francis last name.
Jones let me make it right.
Francis
All right.
The e-mail Francis that Jones died ran at gmail dot com and the passport.
The good old passport one two three passport one two three if you're carrying a user remember the passport
because we can change the begin to reset the password of these user later.
So again to create an account.
Congratulations again.
It's Francis that Rav and then passport one two three and we are still able to log in and if we go to
our you know Gmail waves welcome to waves Francis and we get the welcome to waves and the you know the
get.
Good man.
So everything works.
Everything works.
Remember to check the documentation because sometimes whenever you're using maybe you're using more
much more complex servers for e-mails you need to specify port and you need to do a lot of things.
So you need to check the documentation for this.
But right out of the box is real simple.
Create a transport passee.
You know the data of the work.
Which one we know which user is going to be receiving the e-mail and then you just send the mail.
And that is it.
OK.
So this is pretty much done.
I'm going to skip the the project so far I'm going to give you the code anyways.
It's going to everything is going to be at get help a get help.
And let's go to the next bonus section.