All right so we don't have not found section.
So I'm going to add it right now should be really simple for you at this point.
We kind of did it many many many times.
So I'm going to store the the not found component inside of you tells.
I'm going to create and you filed cold.
Page Not Found done jazz.
So this one will be a re-act statelets components of course.
And I'm going to call it again.
Page not found not found because it can add an icon.
You can you can do it if you wish.
So I'm going to bring import import font.
Awesome.
And then I called my hands are a little bit cold.
We are mid winter right now and in my country winter home in really cold.
So if you remember it's Fort Austin and then react for it awesome then import.
And then the icon calls F A exclamation and then circle no real long keyboard.
So from at that we're awesome.
And then Fortt awesome free and we copy a exclamation right.
Whoops there we go.
OK.
So pretty simple.
I'm just going to be returning the container the class name with the container right.
Then I going to go here and say OK I want to create a div with a class name of not found container.
And again don't take the CSSA reference.
And then I get to make reference to that font.
Awesome icon.
So font awesome opening close and we need to pass the icon and the icon f a exclamation mark.
All right.
And then I get to it you know just say something maybe whoops coma and then Page Not Found.
Right.
Page Not Found.
Very very simple.
So now of course we need to include this within routes so I'm going to go to routes and I'm going to
import it right here the top maybe at the bottom because this is not a very common route.
So import then.
Page not found from that forward slash components forward slash U tails and then a page not found.
Right now we need to put it always at the end.
It's the last route on the list.
So I'm going to copy the home just like it is and I'm going to paste it right here.
Now we need to remove the path.
So by default is going to go to this component.
If we if it's not finding the route we don't really need to know.
So I'm going to say Page not found for a component and we are done.
Really really simple.
Of course the app reloads this one should fail and we get oops.
Page Not Found.
And if we go I don't know two guitars and then forward slash and whatever.
Oops.
Page Not Found.
Very good.
You can put it read direkt right here.
Maybe go to home or whatever.
It's completely up to you at this point.
This should be piece of cake.
Piece of cake.
OK.
So we are we're going to again sip the big project and let's move forward to the next component.