OK so now what are we going to be doing.
We're going to be adding purchase or there's an after we do that we will send an email to the user.
So far just to refresh your memory.
If I go to a user and I go to the history we check the history and we get the date of purchase and everything
else and the payment I.D. which is the payment we get from Paypal but maybe we want to create create
our own custom ID for this transaction and not use the one for paypal you know.
So that's what we're going to do.
We're going to create a hash with an I.D. a purchase or ID with hash and everything else.
And then we will store that purchase or their ID inside of the history of the user after they make a
purchase.
And of course we will store that inside the payments document as well.
Right.
OK.
So we can to use a dependency called crypto non-jazz.
If you look for cryptologic as you can find the NPM or the get help.
So we will need to install this dependency to create a hash so we can use the user id to hash something
and it's really simple to use and descriptor Nudgee as it's very very popular.
Real simple right here you have you get some examples in how to use it.
And for example you do you bring the the description you wish and then you just encrypt that is it real
simple.
You get a lot of the types of encryptions right here.
So you can use one you know whenever you want doesn't matter.
OK.
So let's first begin with this.
I'm going to go to the terminal.
Everything was closed the I killed the server and everything else.
So we need to do you.
Yawn.
And of course if you're using NPM NPM installed mine is mine safe at and then it's called crypto jazz
jazz and I'm going to install the version 3 1 9 and then this is the latest version so far.
So going to press center it's going to take a minute and OK everything was installed.
So I'm going to go and double check on the package to Jason.
We've already got it.
Very good.
OK.
So I'm going to close the package adjacent and close everything.
You know we don't need this right now and I'm just going to open the server that is going to go right
here at the top and the first thing we need to do is to include it.
So on the documentation you have the instructions.
So whenever you want to use a type of encryption you need to include just that you don't include everything.
So in this case I'm going to use the Shaw one because it's a very simple encoding.
You can again choose whatever you want.
So Konst going to bring Shaw one equals require open and close and then it's from crypto that jacks
for Slash and that Shaw one.
OK.
So how can how are we going to use it.
How are we going to be creating this purchase or they're going to do it first.
Whenever the service starts I'm going to create revivals right here you know creed the purchase order.
So first I'm going to be using a date.
Of course then we're going to use it on a different place.
Right.
For now just going to just teach you how to use it later.
It will do this correctly.
So first I'm going to bring the date right.
So then what I want to do I went to Crete to purchase or there is going to be equal and I'm going to
use template strings.
So my purchase orders they will start with P O and then dash and then of course I will attach the date
which is you know hash is going to be kind of hash.
It's a set of numbers that you know they are to date.
So we're going to make a reference to date date dot and I'm going to get the seconds.
Remember that this is just kind of an idea.
So then of course first attach the seconds and are going to be attaching date dot and yet get milliseconds.
All right.
This is the only thing I'm going to do.
You can choose whatever you want right here.
You can create your own encryption and then get to the dash open and close and going to use that Shaw
one.
So I'm going to make a reference to Shaw one opening close.
So what I want to use is the idea of the user in this case of course right now we don't have the I.D.
but whenever we make the purchase we will have access to the ID of the user within the route.
So for now I'm just going to do I don't know.
Whatever doesn't matter.
This is going to be the idea of the user will be his word wrap this then what I want to do I want to
of course convert this to strings.
I'm going to say to string open and close and then of course this.
SHAW it.
You know it's going to create like 10 I believe it's more than 10 characters and it's a little bit long.
I don't need more than 10 it's actually much more than 10.
I don't want to attach more than 10 characters right here on this encryption.
So I'm going to do.
I'm just going to do.
Substring and bring the first eight.
So 0 8 and of course when we do Konst.
All right.
So whenever this service starts I want to output this o.
And let's see what we get.
So I'm going to save it.
Of course we need to Yorn Ron dev.
And we should be getting this in a second and right here.
We get it.
So it's P.O. the seconds and the milliseconds you know really really small right here.
Again you can choose whenever you want to create the number or date or you can even get it you know
can be kind of a time stamp but it's going to be much much bigger.
And didn't want that.
And then of course we get Hosh with Shaw one just the first eight characters.
If I don't do this let me just show you.
Going to save it.
The hash is no.
3 to Preter Bik much more than 10 characters.
All right.
So this is what we're going to be using.
So I'm going to I'm going to kind of a calm in this because we need to create this logic within the
correct route whenever we make a purchase.
We will create a purchase order with the user information and then you know pass it to the stored inside
Mongo.
So we're going to be doing this.
Well I got a copy of this.
You know use it in the second is going to copy.
I'm going to go to the correct route and it's at the card.
No it's success mine.
So whenever we make a success by we will generate the correct number right.
So I'm going to go right here.
I'm going to pretty much do the same logic logic going to attach everything create the deck get the
date and then get the O.
Now remember we are using the mouse middleware.
So instead of here we have access to request that user ID.
So instead of just passing this I'm going to say request that user that underscore ID.
So this will create a hash with the date and the user ID.
Very good.
All right.
So now we need to attach this purchase order inside of the history of the user whenever they make a
purchase and then we need to add it to transaction data so we can store for it in site payments.
Right because it's same purchase order number.
So we're going to go right here to say p order you can call this whatever you want.
And there's one it's going to be equal to PTO to this viable.
Right now we pretty much need to do the same thing with different section data with this one is going
to go right here.
So I want to include this inside of the payment data.
So we're going to bring object notation.
Okay instead of this object I want to add everything that side requires that body the payment data which
is you know pay pal information and then coma.
And I also want the pre order and the P or there it's equal to.
Oh.
All right.
Looks nice.
And that's pretty much it.
Whenever we stored the information inside our database they will get the pre order the purchase or inside
of the user with the history and inside of the transaction data.
All right.
And later much later we're going to send an e-mail.
But first let's see if this works.
All right.
I'm going to go here.
Reload the application.
We already have an item right here.
So I'm going to go to pay pal.
I'm going to use my testing account buyer and I don't remember the past where a thing was testing one
two three.
I'm not sure.
Yeah.
Get our.
All right.
So I'm going to complete the purchase.
I'm going to pay now.
And everything is OK.
So now of course if you go to account we have this history and this is something that we need to change.
I went to change the date.
Date of purchase for the P or they're going to do this in a second but first I want to check on our
project to check if everything it's ok inside users.
So I'm going to France is the Joan JONES We have this history and we get the order and same thing with
payments.
You have a new payment with the data and the Order of you know same ID.
So good.
So now what I need to do I need to change the date of purchase for the PPI or other.
Oh let's go to our application inside client.
Remember we have this dashboard inside user and then index and we have the history block.
So we're going to open a history block does it cause us and insight of the history block.
Very simple.
Instead of using moment and date of purchase and everything else are just going to output the product
or they're so closet product that P or other.
Now there is no reason to use moment.
I'm going to I'm going to do this because again this this will go to you.
So we're going to I'm going to copy this code because maybe you don't remember how to use movement and
this one you know will be in light you are going to delete this and then product per adult dot and then.
Or their P or other.
All right.
And that is it of course we need to change this with the I don't know or there are a number make sense
or there or there are a number.
Very good.
Let me delete the last.
Th.
All right.
So now of course you reload the application can it get it or the number and then the P.
Very good.
I'm deleting the date because if not begin to get a lot of things here let's get it get really crowded
and I don't want that but again you wanted to keep the date.
You can do it.
No problem.
All right.
So everything is good here.
So we are pretty much done with this.
We're going to go to the next section of this bonus and we will send in e-mail.
And we already have the logic for sending e-mails.
We just need to call that function.
We've included Now the tab.
But the problem is that right now we just get one template.
This is the only thing we get.
So we're going to add a new template with all the logic to showing that the order.