Right.
So now after after they complete a transaction I want to send that email to the user saying OK thanks.
Thank you for purchasing.
You know for buying wheedles or shopping with us something like that.
And here here you get the order number.
That's what we want to do.
Of course we can already have this would send the e-mail and it's going to be really simple but we get
just one tiny problem right now.
Of course we are storing everything in our Mogo instance and everything is OK.
All right.
So right here just like we did before we will you know send the mail.
Now we need to instruct the mail what needs to be rendered you know what are the purchase orders or
the purchase order and a little bit more detail and what they are or what they bought when we why they
are buying.
Maybe one guitar maybe two guitars or whatever.
So we can a need to run that function to send email function but we need to pass some arguments.
All the information about the purchase.
Right now if we go to the mail function right here you have to have the name we have the token the template.
So we don't have.
So far we don't have anything that you know passes some information to the actual template.
So we will need to add it.
All right.
So we're going to go to the server going to start doing this right here.
So on the server we need to of course go to this function.
And if you remember it sent e-mail open and close.
Now we need to pass the user e-mail and right here at the top.
Just want to show you because it's a little bit confusing on the first one the first find one update
whenever we find a user we get the user back.
So I'm going to make reference to this user.
Right.
So send e-mail.
We make reference to user and then e-mail that we need the name.
So it's user up user dot name than a coma.
The second argument on our function was a token we are not using a token.
So we say no then it coma.
What is the name of the template.
We didn't have the template template but we're going to create it in a minute.
So this one is going to be called purchase.
You can call this whatever you want.
So the last argument is going to be the transduction data or the actual information about the you know
the purchase.
So if I scroll right here to the top we get the transaction data.
And this is what we are storing instead of the payment model.
Right.
So I got a copy transduction data and I'm going to be passing pretty much all of course later.
We're going to we're going to get out of here.
The only things we need.
OK.
So transduction data.
So now this function this sent e-mail will be expecting a new argument right here.
So of course we need to specify what we are expecting.
All right.
So on the sent email going to do coma I'm going to say act transaction data could be action date.
I get called Action data right here and this one of course by default sometimes you're not going to
get this at all.
So I'm going to say by default it's not just in case you can do this with the access Isak's.
So I'm going to go right here at the top of the bottom and whenever we make of reference to the function
to get the template we're going to say transaction data or sexually action data and begin to be you
know passing the argument to this function at the top.
Now the function of the top of course will be getting that actual data.
And now we need to create a new template.
Ryan I'm going to copy this one because it looks pretty much the same.
So the case it's purchase.
All right.
Portus still from waves and you know ways the two we got the two.
The subject could be.
Thanks for shopping with us something like that.
Thanks for shopping with us.
And then the name why not.
Now we need to make a reference to a new template we cannot use the welcome.
So I'm going to call this purchase and inside of the purchase will be passing.
We will be passing whatever we get from the actual data.
So make it right to get a copy and then paste it.
We don't have the template it created right now.
So of course we're going to parse the BDO bring the purchase template that each team will get it from
resources.
Right.
And they begin to create Deeya jazz for that template.
OK.
So this is the purchased template This is how it looks.
It's pretty much like the other one pretty much you know same welcome to waves or same Hetter we're
going to changes of course.
And it's your purchase information.
I've added a T row and each side of the information outside the purchase information.
You know after the H2 tag we get with you know all the products we get from the data.
Right.
Real simple.
So we're going to use this one.
OK.
So what are we going to do there.
So we need to create the jails for this.
So it's going to be a new file and then purchase underscore template.
Yes real simple.
So just like the welcome this is just a function that we get exported.
So it's Konst purchase equals and then we run a function.
Remember that this one will be getting some data back.
Right.
And then of course we need to export this.
So I'm going to go and say module dad exports equal and then purchase you know same name purchase.
Right.
So now of course we need to include this template from within the mail.
So I'm going to go with the mail and say Konst opening close then purchased and we acquired this from
the correct place.
So require that forward slash and then purchase template.
Yes.
All right.
So now purchase of course exists and we are passing the data.
So let's go to the purchase template.
Now of course we will get a tiny tiny tiny proem not whenever we for example if we make a transaction
right here we could be buying just one guitar but we could buy many guitars.
So you need to tell specify right here what are we buying when we go to the purchase template.
So right here we get one.
But what happens if you get two.
So you will need to go one than two than three.
And you know all the products they purchase or there it's going to be the same because we get only one
purchase or purchase section.
But in this case what we will need to do is to create a loop through that data and show everything right
here.
So for now just going to go back to the way it was.
All right.
There we go.
So I'm going to pretty much copy the whole template and I'm going to go back to our purchase template.
Remember that at the end of this function we always return a template string.
So inside of the template string I'm going to copy paste and format this a little bit better.
All right.
Now what are we going to be doing is that after the H2 tag going to this and make a reference to a function.
Right.
Because we want to loop something and we cannot really do it from here.
So I'm going to say get items.
This is going to be the name of my function you can call this whatever you want.
All right.
So I'm going to go at the top before the return and we will create a function that takes the data and
loops everything.
So cons get items is just a function that returns something are going to create a template that for
now it's equal to nothing.
It could be equal to no.
If you wish and that of course we need to loop.
And at the very end return we return the template.
Right now let's create the loop.
Really really simple.
OK.
So first we enter data the data right here the top.
Then if you remember that data on whenever we store it.
Let me just show you right here whenever we store something we get a user a data in a product.
So the one we need right now it's the product all the products that the user it's buying.
Right.
OK.
So we do data that product dot for each.
I'm just going to run for each if you want to do a for loop that is OK.
So on each iteration we get an item and then we just loop it.
What are we going to do.
We can grab the template and we can concatenate everything to that template.
And what we do which is you use template strings and the code we're going to be using.
It's pretty much really the one we have on the template that's one.
So we could attach this dev.
And let me make sure maybe I did it incorrectly.
Let me go to purchase H2.
Okay that's good.
So we attach a depth each guitar for example if you get two guitars we can get two deps with the information
inside.
So I going to copy the div go right here at the top and paste it inside and I'm going to make it a little
bit better because it's really ugly.
Well you know sometimes the format not that nice.
All right.
Let me correct this a little bit better.
Just a little bit.
OK.
So we have a name.
We have a price and we have the purchase order.
Now if you remember we need to access the item I'm going to say item.
Paste.
And then space and again to add the name.
So first it's the brand and then the name so item dot name.
So the brand of the guitar and the model of the guitar.
Then we need the price.
So again pretty much the same thing price.
And then the R&amp;D and the order the purchase order and then item item that P or other.
Okay that is good.
So if we get I don't know maybe 10 articles this will loop the 10 articles it will attach to this template.
You know concatenate this code and that it's going to go right here and the user will get the email
with the correct information.
That is the idea.
So I'm going to save it.
I'm going to go.
Let me just make sure everything is OK looks nice and index that G-mail index sorry action data.
And then we send the data.
So everything look looks really good.
Well let's test it out.
I'm going to go to here.
Can a reload just in case go to home.
I'm going to buy one guitar and maybe a guitar like I like Ivan has his guitar.
I don't know what with Stratocaster you know that they get that particular sound with you Charvel a
real life Charvel.
This one I love this one.
All right.
So now we get a cart sort of server that I can go to the Pay-Pal check out you know the whole process.
It's buyer and then testing one two three Lagann I get to complete the purchase.
So pay now
and then your order is complete.
Let's see if we get an e-mail.
And we do.
Thanks for shopping with us.
Oh and forgot to change this.
Welcome to waves and your purchase information.
Going to check why we are getting nil.
I'm guessing I know why.
And then we get a Fender wrote Kaster price paid and the purchase order and everything else.
So let me let me change the welcome to waves and the no and first thing going to you know possibly Neo
and check why we are getting mil.
I'm pretty sure I know why but I'm going to just going to check it anyways.
Yeah it was this because the first time we are doing this and we don't want it.
All right.
So and then I'm going to change this.
Welcome to waves.
Let me do the word wrap.
And if you're a Mac and used in the via's code the alt not the command the alt and the set or C gets
you the word wrap.
So welcome to waves.
No.
Could be.
Thank you.
Thank you for buying whenever.
Right.
Of course I'm not going to do it again of course because you know we get the information we wanted so
you could attach whatever information you want right here.
Maybe just show one purchase or there because the are all the same and then show all the products again.
It's completely up to you.
OK so just like before.
I'm going to snip everything gave you the code.
And remember that everything is at get have.