All right so net would be going to do on this bonus section we're going to be adding a file upload.
I'm logged in as an administrator so if I go to add products the only way we can add a file it's an
image and it's going to be declared denarii.
So on this section we're going to add a new route where we can send a different kind of file but we
will be storing this inside of the main directory right here on the upload directory.
We don't get it right now but it created.
So we're going to do that going to show you a different way of uploading files.
Right.
So to do this we need to install this middleware call.
It's going to be called Mulder.
So that's the name.
And with this middleware we can use it on our node server.
And of course to now load to a directory right here.
Very simple.
Of course you get all the documentation.
It's pretty simple to use.
I'm going to show you right now.
But first of course we need to install this.
So I'm going to go to the terminal to clear.
And I'm going to do yarn at mulcher and the Bertran.
It's I believe one of three that one going to press center and I'll be right back whenever this is done
everything is done.
So the first thing we need it's a route where we can you know upload a file so we can read the route
right now that's the first thing we need to do before we can even begin.
So I'm going to go to the server.
I'm going to go to the client.
I'm going to close off this.
All right.
So first I'm going to store this inside user because this is an admin action so I'm going to go to user
and store the file inside of mine.
Right.
OK.
So I'm going to call this at file.
Right.
Makes sense.
It's going to be called.
Underscore that file doesn't last.
Of course this one is going to be re-act class based component so Riak class based component.
All right.
So again a galat file.
So on this one again just like with it before we will we will use that re-act drop zone.
Remember we were used for it with the cloud Narey to store the image.
We will use the same thing for now is just going to create the component going to add the user out so
import that the user will lay out from dot dot for Slash one more time one more time and then for Slash
and I'm not getting the 0 to complete.
I don't know why that force last a chose C for Slash and then user.
All right.
I going to wrap everything inside the user layout and then say upload upload or something like that
whatever.
OK.
So now we have the component we need to add this to the routes.
So I'm going to go two routes.
Right.
So this one of course is an apin route.
So I'm going to put it right here.
So import import.
And then it's at file from DOT for Slash components for Slash user for Slash at man and then add file
and the route just like this one's going to copy and paste it at the bottom.
So the route for this it's going to be at file very simple on file and it comes with the component and
we are kind of good to go.
OK.
So of course if we reload the application we didn't have a way to ruin the restart server.
We didn't have a way to enter that route because we didn't have an option on the part.
So we need to add it.
We have this inside show c and the user right here we have the links.
So this one is going to be a user anatman route.
So I'm going to copy the first one the last one and then paste in at the bottom and we can call this
upload file and it's inside outman and the route is going to be at file.
All right let's see what happens.
All right.
So we get the route if I go to upload find a file.
We get this upload all right.
Good you know kind of weird.
So what we need to do.
I made a mistake right here.
It's upload backwards Breguet.
So now of course this file will use that drop zone and we're going to use a few things more.
So I'm going to go to the Eutelsat form and file upload.
Alot of things are going to be the same.
So I'm gonna copy and paste a few a couple of things.
So the file we will use the dropzone and we are going to use ASIO's.
So go to the file and load copy the dropzone and then copy the axes Begay use the link.
So I need to import link furrow on and then of course react and react then router and then Dom good
again we will use the same icons.
It's pretty much the same.
Of course we're going to make a lot of changes but you know they don't.
Now the constructor again we're going to need this.
So I'm going to copy and paste.
Now we could have created maybe a file app load more default because this way it's kind of a working
only for the images.
You know I was not going to add this I'm just adding this as a bonus.
So I cannot we use this component and I don't want to you know just break this or undo this because
we can already do this but that's OK.
We're going to create a new component just to add files with Mulder.
All right so can constructor we get the super and the state.
Now what I want to do I want to add a couple more things.
And for now I'm going to delete the upload files I'm going to just delete it.
I'm going to be adding form success.
And remember it's equal to false.
Then we have the form error.
Just like with the forms form error.
And again equal to false.
Then we get the uploading false and then we store the files right here.
So I'm going to save files and then akong Breguet.
OK.
If you remember we we use that on job function where we can catch the files and then do something.
So this on drop is going to take some files and then it's going to do something first.
We're going to build everything else.
So now if we go to final upload and scroll down right here on the actual you know layout we pretty much
need you know pretty much the same thing.
So I'm going to go back to that file going to go to the user.
Leo I'm going to say H-1 each one.
Well each one and I'm going to call this what do we call it upload file.
I mean upload file.
I don't know upload file.
All right.
That's good.
So I'm going to create a diff and inside of the division to put that dropsonde.
So this one we can just copy paste and then copy this one and I'm going to paste it inside everything
else.
You know this inside dropsonde THOMPSON It's pretty much the same.
Same thing.
Let me just clear this a little bit.
OK.
So we get the drop zone whenever we drop something.
We run the drop with the file multiple.
It's false.
And the class name still drop drop drop zone box and we get the you know the plus circle so everything
else is just OK.
Now if I go to upload we get this one we are not going to use this function.
We're going to do something else going to explain you why later.
And then I'm going to copy the disk that state that uploading are going to go right here and paste it.
All right.
Everything else is just pretty much the same.
Now the thing is that of course we need a button to actually not a button we need to form success and
a form you know error because on this one when we include it on the form we don't get the state you
know we get a directory from the form but the form in this case is going to be this one.
So we need to add a couple more things.
All right.
So I'm going to add a div and I can add style and clear both.
I know that this is boring but you know it can and need to do it.
So clear both and east out of here we will put all the messages after we do one now upload.
You know the forms access and the form errors.
So I'm going to open close this state.
You can catch that form success and of course if we get it we're going to do something.
If not we do know.
All right.
And inside of here are going to return a div with a class name of forms success nothing you so far form
success and saying success or something like that.
Then of course if you get a foreign power and then open and close and say this that state that form
are open and we say Divx me make it like this now a little bit better than we do know.
And of course the class name for this one it's error level or OK.
And this one could say please check your data or whatever you say that you know you want to use.
If not we could return just an empty string.
You can do that now.
Later after we create all the logic for uploading a file and everything else below this we can ill render
the whole list of files inside the upload directory.
So later right here we are going to be doing the uploads just like that.
All right let's see what we get.
We get the uploads and you know the upload file.
If I click it at least we get we are getting that window.
So everything is cool now.
OK.
So whenever we do a non-job if you remember we need to go to files in this case and say this that sets
date and we change the loading to true.
So uploading to true.
That's the first thing.
Then we pretty much do the same thing before some going to code go to file upload.
Not going to you know.
All of this again because I want to save some time.
Got it.
Copy this one from date config and form append.
And I'm going to paste it right here.
All right.
OK.
You know that's the first thing.
Now of course we need to create a request and we don't have a route for this going to create it.
Right now in a second.
OK so let's keep going.
We pretty much have everything we need whenever we drop something we want to upload the file and that's
it.
So we need to create the route that it's going to be listening for this files.
So right now we need to go to the server.
Can we go to the server then yes and OK I'm going to do it right here just at the beginning.
Now of course we need to use mulcher ride.
So I'm going to do Konst then mulcher equals require and then milter the usage of maltol it's real simple.
But first it's a little bit weird.
OK.
So with monitor you have many ways to do uploads right to handle uploads.
The most common one is going to be using the disk storage.
So I'm going to create a revival just a contest could be a lead calls storage going to call it storage
equals.
And then we use that multa we are importing the top and noticed that you can import mulcher before the
code.
Doesn't matter if you know we do it at the end of the file or at the top just like we are doing right
here right here doesn't matter.
OK.
So we get the matter and then we make use of a property called disk storage.
So inside of this this is storage we need to pass all the previous configuration and then on the actual
route master will grab all the logic and the files and everything else and it will use this configuration
we are going to do right here.
So we have many many options inside this torch disk search and the first one which is the most you know
the most important one.
This case is going to be the destination where are we going to be storing the files now for this one
you get a request because again the this is a middleware is going to be listening for that request response.
And then we get something that calls it that it's a callback stickleback function.
So whenever we process everything everything you know the request and response is going to do this.
What we need to do we need to return a callback so we grabbed that callback.
And what we do we need to pass some set of things.
The first one we are not going to really use it is going to be NULL if you want to read more can go
to the documentation and get it.
But for us right now is just no.
All right.
So I'm going to open and close the second argument and the destination and each property you know meets
some particular kind of information its Where are you going to be putting this are going to create an
upload directory.
We didn't have it but whenever we upload something is going to create the directory for us if it doesn't
access of course then going to coma and I can add a new one.
This one calls file me.
So the file name it's equal to you know the name of the file and we pretty much do the same thing.
Oh not a response.
The second argument is file.
So whenever we upload something mulcher middleware is going to grab this.
The request is going to give you a file which is a set of information about the files and something
like that.
You know we can access file and get information of what we are uploading and the same thing with filename
and we are going to need it.
For example we get the request the actual file we are uploading and the Colback.
So what I want to do I want to return a callback.
The first one is no.
And the second one is going to be the file name.
What am I going to use for filenames.
All right.
So I'm going to open and close.
So what I want to do I want to grab the original name of the file and add the date.
So I'm going to use template strings.
Real simple.
And first I'm going to put the date so I'm going to say date now.
Right.
OK.
And then when I want to do I want to do an underscore and attach the file original name like a tool
before you have access to the file.
So you can grab the file and say OK I want the or original name and the file will be uploaded to the
uploads with the date and the original name of this properties are under documentation.
You can check it out.
OK.
So let's you know kind of keep going on this.
So right now we have the mulcher instance the storage and what we will need to do.
It's an app load.
So upload.
So this instance equals to the monitor.
So I'm going to say mulcher opening close.
So whenever we upload something this all the uploads are going to go through this I'll upload.
So this upload can emerge.
They require motor and the disk storage into one instance.
So we say monitor and then we pass.
OK.
So for storage what I'm going to use for storage for storage I'm going to use storage now another way
to do it instead of passing this barbel right here we could copy all of this and put it right here.
Pretty much just same thing just creating a different Barville to host all this logic because you know
it's a little bit better.
And then we have a different option.
We can attach.
We can tell instruct Walter in what we want to do we want to upload a single file or multiple files.
So I'm going to say single file.
And now what is the name of this file.
Remember then when we upload things we are passing the name.
In this case in this case file could be images or whatever.
In this case it's just files so we're going to say file right.
If you want to do multiple You need to know go to the documentation and check it out.
It's pretty simple it just tell a select multiple.
But note remember that whenever you have multiple You have multiple Fink's inside of here you have file
maybe name last name and something like that.
So you will need to pass an array of all the names that this upload instance should be expecting.
All right.
Now this is really simple.
So first I'm going to create the route I'm going to create in an AP.
I then forced slash then users then upload file upload file.
Right now only our users and admin users can do this.
So then I'm going to do coma and you know the request and the response
if you're not getting this don't work you're going to get it right now.
So no I'm going to grab this upload instance to say upload and then open and close this upload needs
the request the response and a function.
And we could do it just like this.
All right.
Now this function just contains an error.
Now of course what we're doing we are making a reference to this upload upload.
We'll take all the information from the actual route request and response is going to go to this storage.
Read the request and the files and everything else.
It will process with the options you know with settings we pass right here and then it's going to of
course do the bloat and come back to this whenever we come back.
It come back comes back.
It will run the callback function.
If there was an error is going to tell us.
And of course if everything went OK we're just going to return a response to the client.
Real simple.
So if open and close are you going to say if we get an error I'm going to return a response with a Saun
of don't no success falls.
And then I'm going to be attaching the error.
And of course if everything goes OK we go.
Return responds.
Jason and this case begin to say chest success truce.
I'm going to copy and paste right true.
So again we are just making use of this applet.
We are uploading with the with it you know the settings and then we just get our callback right.
So we can you know kind of try this.
Of course we need to go back to the client and you know make a of this maybe the this went too long
went too long already.
So on the next one we're going to go to the next one.
And you know make the actual request with ASIO's.