All right.
So let's keep it going.
We need to create the route this and I mean I'm a cigarette here with this method.
We cannot you know create the directory so we can and need to do this manually.
I'm going to go to new folder not insites ever made a mistake and go outside the server and create a
new directory called uploads.
And of course if we are not creating this nothing is going to happen so are going to go back to ad file
and we need to create the request.
Very very simple ASIO's then post.
We pass the name.
You know the route copy the name of the route going to paste it right here.
And of course then we need to pass the form data that coma and we passed that config right.
Then of course we get a response back so response response.
And then you know we need to do a few things.
Now the server up after we upload the image is going to send success.
True or false.
So inside of they're of here going to say OK if we get a response that data DOD success then of course
we're going to set some state.
So there's that set stayed open and close.
And what we're going to do.
I'm going to grab the form success change it to the form error.
Leave it to false.
And the upload back to false.
Remember that whenever we start this episode we are sending it to true.
All right.
So the former success.
It's true and everything else is just back to false.
Now we want to do I want to delete the form success after two seconds.
So we just ran a callback and we do set timeout.
I'm not teaching anything you right now we can know this is old code.
So there's that said state opening close and we changed it form success back to true.
And we can do it after two seconds.
Right.
OK.
Virga So this looks nice.
Let's give it a try.
I'm going to go here again at blowed something.
I'm going to open.
And then we get the success on the server.
And if we go here and we go to uploads we get the upload image.
Very good man.
So you know it works it's really really easy to use release to use.
Of course you can go to the documentation and check this a little bit you know further.
Now before we move on to the next thing of course if you once again check the documentation I'm going
to give you a scenario what happens if we want to you know FELTER what we are uploading and what is
this.
No.
OK.
So I'm going to do coma.
I'm going to I'm going to put some code here I have it ready right here I'm going to put it and then
I can explain you we are not going to do this.
I'm just putting the code so I can explain you.
So you have another property called File Filcher.
So with a file filter you can inspect some of the properties that the file has and then you can decide
if you want to lead the file move forward.
You upload the file inside the uploads to stored there or not.
So for example right here I'm entering the path and this is actually something from.
From no jazz.
We need to require path we're going to do it in a couple of minutes for something else.
Then we enter the extension name and we check the extension then the original file name.
Yes.
Remember we have access to file and then we just check.
Is this AJP G or PNB.
So if it's not again we are not going to let the user move forward.
So what do we do we return that same callback.
But now instead of No this is going to be the response.
And this is actually the response we sent back.
Before we go to this instance.
Right.
So we did this we say OK you are not allowed to go in.
So the first callback is going to be that rejection.
And of course the second one is false.
Now if Gore this of course passes this then we're going to go to the you know our regular Colback saying
no forever and then true.
And in this case if we get true it means move forward.
The next thing which in this case is doing the upload.
So this is one way you know this is what they what the know.
The first argument means and how can we filter you know the files.
I'm not going to use it right here.
Not that important to you know deleted or maybe media just going to leave and come this out because
of course this file is going to go to you.
So now what we can do we can upload the things right here and it's not doing that some time out time
out this state for success back to false.
All right.
So after we upload a file what I would like to do I would like to go.
I'm sorry.
After upload a file no after I load this screen the file I would like to get like to get a list of all
the files inside the uploads directory right.
I want to go to this location get all the names of files and put them right here.
And later what I want to do I went to click maybe one file open in new window and download the file
and all of this of course is going to happen on the admin side of things.
So let's do that right now just trying to fetch all the list of files.
Right to fetch the list of files that we're going to need a new route that can handle this kind of request
is going to be a get out and it will answer to the uploads.
And we turn all the results inside of here.
So for this we need to require a few things from note.
So we need to bring the file reader so require at fast so we can read what's inside the directory.
Right then we need the path because we need the location of that.
So we do require open and close and we require PAF and node modules.
They come with no jast.
That's why we are not installing them.
All right.
Then we need to create a route app that get and it's for Slash API users for Slash and admin files.
All right then coma.
And of course this happens only if the user is authenticated and it's an administrator.
And then of course we run our callback.
So I get so request and response.
So what do we need to do now.
We need to go to the directory to this directory.
And you know kind of get the location of that directory.
So I'm going to say Konst and then they're equals and we're going to use that path and we're going to
use resolve.
So whenever we do we just go you know to the main directory to the main route.
So we use dot.
And then I'm going to do plus and I'm going to be adding the uploads.
You get several ways of handling this.
Inside No just this is one way.
So we just pretty much we are creating a viral host hosts the location of that uploads.
And then what we do we use the FS and if FS will enter to that directory and read the files inside the
directory and we use it read Durr that FS will provide us.
So the first one the first argument of this reader is going to be the directory We want to read and
then you know the Colback.
So all right.
So the Colback contains an error if we are not doing anything we get an error.
And the second one is going to be the items inside the directory.
So what we want to do we just want to return the items.
So I'm going to say return response status off to 100 and I'm going to send the items just like that.
No really simple.
So whenever we make a request to this location we will get a response.
We have an array of all the items inside uploads.
I'm going to do one more upload so we can get you know maybe at least two files maybe three files and
two seconds goes away.
And then this.
All right.
So now we have three outlets.
Very good.
So let's go to the you know the front end and make a request OK.
So on the front and we will fetch the files and we will store the files inside the files state.
Right.
OK.
When do we want to do this.
As soon as the component will mount.
So that component will mount.
Sorry comput dismount.
Open and close and then we say X-ers dot get we passed the route and then we catch the response from
here.
So dot then and we do response.
We've run the callback and on the callback we want to do this that said state opening close and I'm
going to say that files equals to whatever we get back from the response that data noted.
Notice that not doing redux right here and I'm doing this just to save time because you've already know
how to use redux at this point.
So you know I just want to save some time from your time of course.
All right.
So before I do this I want to get the council Council lock and then responds that data.
And you know just check that we're getting something at least.
So inspect and let's see the con..
Hopefully we get something.
OK.
You know we get an rate with three different files.
Right.
We'll it is simple.
So now on this component we kind of have to have a state with an array of files.
So the only thing we need to do is just you know show the files.
So I'm going to go right here to bloats.
I can create a order list and then do.
Does that show file list opening close.
All right.
So this is going to be a function.
We don't have this function.
We need to create it.
So we're going to go at the top and say okay show file list open and close.
All right.
So this one is going to be returning some GSX.
And what we need to do first we need to check that we do have files.
So there's that state that files.
And if we don't have anything we don't do anything if we do have something this state that files then
we do a map open and close up map and at each iteration I want to get the item and the it again the
data transfer item What is that item coma.
Well the iteration right.
To deleted Oh forget.
And then of course we run something and we return some GSX right.
All right.
So what I want to do since we have an order list and when to return return a list item right now.
Later much later we are going to click on that list item and whenever we click it we can go to a link
to a new location and in that location it's pretty much a new route and that route will be listening
for the name of the file.
So whenever we catch name of the file on that route we're going to do that later.
We're going to download the file.
So we're going to leave this right.
I'm going to do I then key and the key is going to be equal to you know the iteration.
So he or I.
And then of course we pass the link.
Right.
So false.
And then like so of course with the link we need a name so the name itself is the actual item.
We get right here.
And on the link we need to pass it to.
So to open it close and the location and they're going to do it right now.
AP I don't use Sir's for Flash download for Flash.
And then we pass the name of the item the name of the image.
And I want to do it when it create this as a target black.
Nothing you it just right here is just a blank blank.
Right.
OK.
So why save it.
Now we are getting the images.
Of course if I click it we go to a target blank but we don't have that route right.
OK.
We're going to need to kind of create or do something with that.
All right.
API is downlow API user download.
All right everything is cool.
So now what do we need to do we need to create a route that is going to be listening for this and whenever
listens is going to grab the name of the file.
Right.
It's going to search it and give you the download.
Let's do that on the next lecture because again this one went to larm.