OK so now we need to create around with API users download and a D to you know get the download really
simple right.
So I'm going to copy this and I'm going to go back to the server now on the server.
We need to create a route that is going to be getting something.
So get then of course we passed the API users and download.
So this one the contents after download.
It's dynamic.
So again just like the like we did with rehang Browder of course this is different but pretty much same
thing.
We passed Collen and the ID and this is a dynamic value on this one.
Of course we need both and we need admin as well.
And then we just run a function with request and response request and response.
Right.
How can we you know send the file or tell the client or send back a request sent down something sent
to the client the actual file.
Well with a node you get the download property method it it's really really simple.
So first we need to tell the application what download We want to send back to the client.
So we do Konst file I'm going to host it here.
So we do that path the same thing we did before Pat.
Then we go to resolve opening close and we pass the you know this location than we do plus and we do
OK.
We want to enter the uploads for Slash bloats just like this forward slash and the name of the file
and the name of the file since we are passing this as you know a dynamic value.
We get it inside to request that pair of rams Dodd and then Id if we put a I don't know something like
the something here.
Like I don't know file name.
This should be filing of course.
All right.
How can we send the response with a download file.
We send the response and we used to download it.
No real simple.
And then we say file OK we want to send the response with this file.
So now when we make a request to this one we should be getting you know something to download.
So I'm going to go to this one and we get it in the fight when we do it right here in documents and
if I go here we get it.
If I open this
right here's the file.
You know Reader It is simple.
Go to another one.
We get it.
Very good.
So of course we're going to close it and this lay out it's pretty pretty basic.
You can and you should.
You know do something much better with this.
But remember all the information it's inside the items and you just need the actual name.
That's the only thing we need.
Maybe if you want more detailed information and this maybe you will need to go to the database.
You know the data uploaded.
And you know all the other information.
So in that case yeah you need to go to Mongo.
But in this case it's just a simple example in how to upload a file.
OK.
So just like before.
I'm going to skip all of this content I can to make it a little bit better.
I'm going to change maybe the place where I'm requiring multo and everything else but I'm going to make
it a little bit better and I'm going to upload everything so you can download it and of course you can
get it from get help.
And I believe it the next module and check the next bonus section.
Oh the next bonus is the reset passport.
That's when it's very useful.
So I need to log on.
What happens if I want to log in I want to log in and I forgot my password so he can go to a forgat
passport.
We will put in the e-mail and we will send an e-mail to the user with the token.
And whenever we access to the token we can check on the server if the token is valid and everything
else.
And we're going to let the user change the password.
You know the usual stuff when we forget a password.
So that's the next bonus section.