Or write.
So now we're going to do the reset passport.
Right.
So if the user of course I'm now logged in as Frances Jones and ref.
OK.
So for example I log out and I want to log in.
And I just you know forget my password.
So we can add a burden right here where we can go to a new route where we can send an email and the
user will get an email with the token so they can go to a new link and reset the user and the password.
And of course we need to validate that token and everything everything else.
So we need to do quite a few things right here.
You know a lot of things so go.
So let's begin with the first part which is going to be creating a route where the user can send an
e-mail.
Right.
OK.
So I'm going to go to component's going to create a new directory because we need two routes.
The route that the user is going to be entering the email and the other one when they come back with
the token and they put the passwords.
So I'm going to create a new folder and I'm going to call that reset reset underscore and user.
Makes sense.
Yeah.
Now the index is going to index.
You can call this whatever you want.
This case the index is going to be worthy users going to send the mail and then again to create a new
route which is going to be when the user comes back from the e-mail.
Right.
So file a file and then reset past that that's going to do this later of course.
Now the index this one is going to be class based components.
So re-act class based components.
And I'm going to call it reset and then user.
All right.
Going to save it.
Now of course we need to put a few things but for now I'm just going to say reset user and of course
we need to add it to ramps.
So let's go to route and I'm going to import it right here at the top.
So important then reset user from that forward slash components for Slash reset user.
And we don't need to bring anything else because this is an index.
OK.
So the next thing putting the round right here.
So I'm gonna put it right here on the bottom.
Let me copy one.
This one's this.
Now if we think about this this reset user is just like the log in I'm sorry the register or the log
in because the user if it's logged in should be able to enter to that route.
Right.
So going to enter to there we are going to copy the one that says register because it's pretty much
just the same thing.
And I'm going to say that the user needs to go to reset the user.
And of course we will use the correct component right here.
Reset user.
Right.
So it's false.
Arayan not know.
All right.
So let's see what happens if I go to reset user.
We get we said user.
All right.
So we are kind of good to go to the component and start bringing all the things we need to bring.
So we need to bring the form actions.
Now I don't want to tie all of this again so I'm going to go to the we just have a log in can go to
register and I get a copy the form actions right here and I'm going to paste it.
All right.
So we have the update general data and the form ballot.
That's what that's what we need right now.
All right.
We need the form feels so I'm going to copy form field and paste it down here and that's it for now.
Good.
Now I'm going to bring ASIO's again just like sorry and just like we did before.
I'm not going to go to redux and just going to do it from here just to save time.
All right.
So then of course which if this is going to be a forum right.
Just one single and put so you know the form it's simple but we also need the state.
So I'm going to copy this one right here at the top.
I'm going to paste it and then close and then close the state.
Now aside from data we have an e-mail so I'm going to copy the e-mail and I'm going to paste it right
here and that's it.
You know that's the only thing we need to do.
Of course if you want to do everything by hand you can still do it.
Now we need the update form and the submit form.
So I'm going to go again a copy update form update form.
And then again to change the tack for this.
So reset email email and I'm going to do the submit form.
So copy the submit form.
I'm not going to use all that content.
Don't worry.
And I'm going to paste it right now I'm going to change the attack.
Did this many many times before and it inside a format that just delete everything and say console console
that log and then data to submit real simple.
All right.
We are pretty much done.
So now of course we need to add all the way up for this.
So look at what's happened right now.
So I'm going to go to the main div and say class name of container I can add a to a title to this one
and reset the password.
I know that this is boring but you know it can be.
Can I need to do it.
If not we cannot do anything.
I can just show you with no real environment.
So form.
So now we get a form.
All right.
So instead of here we will add the form field.
Right.
Real simple.
I'm going to copy the form field for email and I'm going to paste it right here.
And now we have an e-mail and we make it better.
All right.
So after the form field the only thing we need is the forms access the form error and the on click.
And they believe we do have this on the on this on this one on the register.
So we don't have the success don't worry to create it.
But I'm going to copy the form error and the button.
Right.
So I'm going to go at the bottom you have a form error.
Please check your data.
Or it could be you know something else and then the button with the submit form which is going to be
sent e-mail e-mail to reset password or whatever.
You know that is completely up to you and the designer that the company hired to do.
Of course all the UXO and everything else.
So now I'm going to do this to form success because we can if needed right here we cannot escape this.
So there's that state that forms success then we're going to show something.
If not you're not going to do anything.
So what we do is just give it just like this one.
So I'm going to copy and I'm going to change instead of our label is going to be form success right.
Just like with it before form success.
All right.
So this one is going to say Don check your e-mail of course in real life you will need to do John.
Check your e-mail.
Never forget.
Never forget to check the spam or the trash directory and you know all that that kind of things.
So OK.
So right now we get this.
Of course if we do something nothing is going to happen.
But you know everything is going to work and we get the validation and everything else.
And if I do an e-mail we should be getting the council log of data to submit.
Right.
And we do Frances and Gmail.
So all right.
So now what we need to do the next step is going to be going to the right here to the form is valid
and we going to make a request to the server.
The server is going to grab the data to submit with the email and it's going to try and find the user
Ryan.
And if it finds a user is going to generate a token generated hash and send the email to a new link
with that hash you know usual stuff of course you already know how this works because this is the way
we do things on web.
So we are going to do that right now.
We need to go to the server and create a run for this and this one is going to be a little bit heavy.
OK so let's go to the user part admin uploads and then I believe we have right here words users are
going to do it right here at the top.
So first we need to relicensed Ellison for this route.
So its app that post and then open and close.
So we are posting because we need to catch an email so API users for Slash and reset user not password
we are resetting the user.
So reset user are then coma open and close.
We don't need to use the middleware of mouth because you know they are not authenticated and that that
that is the whole point.
So response a request and response.
Right.
So instead of here we need to fine the user by email.
So we you go to a user we could do dot then find one opening close and right here we need to tell Mungo
what are we looking for in this case.
We are finding by e-mail.
Right.
And then where is the email inside of the request.
The body dot and then e-mail.
All right.
And then of course we run the callback so Im going to put coma and do the callback.
Now we could get an error or we could get a user.
All right.
So now what do we need to do.
Because we actually this route is getting an email since we are finding an e-mail.
What we need to do we need to go to that user.
You know the owner of that e-mail on that database and create the hash.
We don't have this logic we need to add to the models the new and new parts and you know do all of this.
So are going to do it right now I'm going to go to models and I'm going to go to the user schema.
Now we need to add two more things.
Right now we have the token and the token of course works after we log in or register but now we are
resetting the token we want to reset the password.
So I'm going to put a coma and I'm going to create two new fields reset token and this one is going
to be a type of string just like the token.
And then I'm going to be adding one more.
I could you know skip this.
But again real life you will need to use it.
I'm going to copy this one pasted right here and XP for exploration.
We're going to create a number.
This one has a number and you could use dates.
There are many many ways to do this.
It is going to show you want.
So whenever we create a reset token we need to set that token to expire at one point.
So by doing this and we pass the time stamp whenever we get the request to change the actual past password
even if the token is correct.
We're going to check if it it's expired.
If it is of course we're not going to let the user do anything or get.
So this is good.
Now we have this now what we need to do we need to go.
For example if I go to the server right here we need to you know create the token and store it instead
of the user that we are finding right here.
Now I'm going to create a method just like we did with the reset password.
I'm sorry the general token.
Remember we're going to do very much the same thing right here.
Since we do have a user we are inside of a user begin to enter that user and we to create a new method.
So generate reset and then tokin and this one is going to be a method.
Right.
We can add it in a second.
And of course after we are done we run the request we get the request and we get the you know the I'm
sorry the request the error the error and the user back.
Now we don't have this method.
We're going to add it right now.
Let's go to users and I'm going to go maybe right here at the top.
Why.
Why not.
So just like with it the generate token.
We just need to create a method that is going to created reset tokens just like this is pretty much
the same example.
So user schema methods dot and then generate reset token.
Right.
So again this is going to be a function opening close and at the end we will get a callback.
All right.
So just like with it for I'm going to create var user that is going to be this because of course we
need to modify the user.
Now at the top we're going to go right here at the top and we need to include crypto because we will
generate a hash just like we did with big crypt with WTS.
We need to generate a hash.
And of course put it inside of the users whenever we request that we set token right.
So I to import crypto.
So Konst than crypto that equals require open and closed.
And we bring crypto.
All right.
So I'm going to go copy this.
And if you remember we've already used crypto bringing in the Shah one you know to generate that coding.
So with crypto of course you get other things you get all the things you can do.
And one of the things you can do is you can of course generate a random byte.
Let me just show you random bytes.
So with this one of course it will generate a random string.
How many 20 how many characters.
20 then it coma.
Then function opening close.
And this one will get will return with an error and the buffer just like this and open and close.
Now this buffer is going to be the random thing.
But I'm going to say bar tokin equals buffer and remember that we store it to a string.
So we're going to do that than to string and we say hex right.
OK.
Now I'm going to do that dates after we store the token because it's a little bit confusing confusing
but you know so.
OK so since we are inside the user X one we get to talk once we get the token to access the user access
method.
We added a reset token of course and a copy.
And I'm going to say OK so now the reset token has a token and it's equal to the token we are generating
with random bytes.
Right just like with it before.
Now once we get the token we need to graph the user we need to save it and then we need to of course
run the callback function.
Now the callback function contains the error and the user with all the changes.
Now again we can already did this.
So I'm going to copy paste if we get an error.
We return that callback.
We are passing right here that function with the error.
If not we are just you know moving forward and passing the user resample.
OK so now we need to go back to the server because this January reset token will be returning a user.
So let's go back to the server.
Right.
On the server.
Let me find a route.
I just moved it.
OK reset user.
All right.
So we going to get back from generate reset token with an error and an actual user.
So are going to say if I open and close if we do have an error we will return something with a response
with a Jaison sign and then success with false and then the actual error.
Same was always.
Now then we get to send in e-mail.
But first I wouldn't want to check if we are getting a token before doing anything else.
So I'm going to send a J.
Jason responds and say return responds not Jaison.
That opening close and it's pretty much the same thing than this but the opposite of course going to
delete the error.
And then of course change it to true.
All right.
So everything is good.
So now of course we make a request we pass the e-mail.
If we are finding the e-mail we go to the method we store the token.
And when we get the we save the we save the user we go back and we send that response pretty clear right.
So let's let's just add and maybe the you know the selector.
Yeah I went to a little bit long.
So let's go to the next one and we're going to test it of course.
And how can we test it.
OK.
Well we need to go to the index and create you know make that request from Pierre.