Right.
So back on the index I'm going to get this and going to make a request to X-post.
I believe we've imported this at the top.
X-posts kind of don't remember.
So we went with it.
Then of course this is going to be a POST request.
Open it close get it copy the route API user I make it.
Users just like the other ones recent user right.
And then of course we put the location right here.
Koma we pass the data to see if made with the email.
And then of course we do something right.
The den open and close we send the response with something else very good.
Now remember that the server will be returning success.
True or no success false.
So of course if we get a response response that data does success of true then I can do this.
That said state this that set stayed open and close and save form success.
True.
So we can you know get the message right here.
Former success right here at the bottom we get the from success.
I'm not going to do the form.
You can do it if you wish.
If you get of course a different response you can attach the.
You know please you know the email isn't correct or this e-mail is not a database just going to skip
it to save some time because it's pretty simple.
So now of course we're going to make a request and we can set the token.
Let's see if this works the application and I'm using the Franz's that Jones that rep.
So Francis Jones that BRAF are going to send the email and done check your e-mail.
All right.
So I'm going to go to users going to Frances and we get the research token so that it's working.
So now we have one more thing we need said the you know the date for that token the expiration date.
All right.
So let's go back to user.
Are we going to do it right here.
Can it create a date and store it.
Now the thing is that we need a couple of things.
So we need to day stay.
And again to set it for to morrow.
So my token is going to last one day.
Now what I'm going to do I'm going to send the token to the beginning of the date and the end of that
token when it will expire it's the end of the date.
So if we are you know we are entering we are requesting the password right now is going to be the whole
day of today.
Right.
And going to do it like this like this.
You can do whatever you want.
You can create a time stamp that starts right now and it will expire in two hours.
Depends on your logic.
Just going to do it just like that.
You know it starts today and ends today.
So I'm going to create a viable call today equals and we need to use moment.
I'm not sure we have it at the top.
No we don't.
I'm going to include it.
So I'm going to do it right here.
So Konst moment calls require that open close.
And you know moment now we do have this installed we installed this moment I'm using the to that 22
that to see if you didn't install this version.
All right let's go back to user.
So woman's right.
So now I'm going to go right here and say OK so what I want to do I want to get today's date.
But the starting of today's date is going to say moments dot and we have a method called Start off.
And when we say we start off this date and now if you do it like this we can get the date like a more
readable date.
But I want to get just the numbers.
You know just like a timestamp timestamp so we get the value off and we get that number.
Now I need to get you know the date of to morrow because to date this do it today it's not going to
be setting on the receipt token we set the expiration date so the expiration date.
It's to morrow I'm bringing this so I can create that to morrow Barville you can see it right now.
So tomorrow equals pretty much the same thing than this.
You know the same thing.
But I'm going to be passing that today instead of moment.
So we will calculate the end of this date starting from today and then instead of say start off we say
and off and this will give us the end of today.
Right.
I told you it was going to weird but you know it makes sense.
So now whenever we get the to morrow date with the value of we say user and I believe it was a token
XP.
So this one it's equal to tomorrow.
All right.
So now on the server we don't need to do anything else.
We need to try and check if we get that the data are going to read the application are going to go to
Francis reset password and check it on the database.
And now we get you know tomorrows data actually today at the end of today.
And the reset token.
So we pretty much have everything we need now the next step is going to be sending an e-mail to the
user.
Of course.
So they can you know get the token and the like.
All right.
So let's kind of do it right now so I can go right here and say All right.
So if everything goes OK I'm going to send an e-mail if you remember we need the e-mail.
The user name the token which in this case is going to be no again the type of the template and then
the data we want to send.
All right.
So send e-mail.
First one is the user not e-mail.
Right.
The second one its user name.
And now I'm doing this all arguments.
You can do is just create one and send that Jason.
Right.
You can do that pretty much the same thing.
Then I'm going to say no than a coma and I get to create a template.
We didn't have this template.
It's a reset password.
We're going to create it right in a couple minutes and then I'm going to be passing more information
because whenever we send e-mail we need to get the token that we are generating right here.
So we need to pass this on.
All this is inside the user document which is more modified.
So if you remember the last argument could be an object with a lot of things.
So this case is going to be just the user data.
All right.
So let's go to the send email function.
Right so I'm going to go to you Tilse male male and the main index.
We do have the welcome and the purchase and everything else stays the same because you know at this
point we pretty much everything we need.
All right.
OK.
So we get a case with welcome purchase.
So we need to add a new case Ryan.
So case opening close and we called this case reset password.
So the case is reset passport go and say data data equals an object and then never forget to do the
break.
All right.
So the data is pretty much just like this one.
Of course we're going to change things.
It's from waves the two still the two and we need to change something here.
We're going to say I don't know.
Hey.
And the name of the user that reset just some like like here your pass whatever.
Now of course we cannot use this template.
We need to create one on a new one.
So I'm going to call it reset pass and we're going to still pass the actual data which contains the
token of course the user with the token.
All right.
So we're going to read the template right here.
We're going to parse the BDO bring the HVM else so we can take a look at that and then it come back.
OK.
So this is how it's going to look.
Remember I've gave us a resource that we use the past template to map.
So click the link to reset a password.
And whenever we click it we go to our application with the token.
Right.
OK.
So let's do it right now.
Are going to go to mail and creating new file and call it the same way we said past underscore.
Sorry.
Yeah.
Pass.
And then template that javascript.
Right.
Of course this one just like the other ones is going to be just a function.
So Konst reset pass equals opening close and we run some things and at the end we will return some templates.
Right.
So of course we need to export it.
So a module that exports equals and then reset pass reset pass.
All right.
Not give me the option.
So we said pass.
All right.
I'm going to make it a capital P Ryan a little bit better.
OK.
So we do have a function.
And remember that this function will be we will be getting some data.
So what we need to be we turning inside of here it's the templates Angelico copy the whole template
and paste it.
All right.
And I'm going to order this a little bit.
So now if you if you notice maybe you noticed already we have a tiny tiny problem.
What we need to do we need to pass a link right here reset the passport arrived.
So for example I'm going to enter here I'm going to say all right.
So what we need to do on the Tref we need to pass.
We need to go to local host whatever whatever.
Right host.
Eighty three thousand actually.
And then for Slash and we're going to go to a route called Reset passport.
We don't have this route when we do this.
The word wrap we're going to go to reset password for Slash and we're going to be passing the token
we get from data and then reset and then tokin right to pretty up is the problem right here is the local
host.
How can we tell the application that we need to go to local host or wherever you are.
All we have inside production right.
Because you know this is what can happen if I go and put local host.
The user will get an email going to localhost.
All right.
So we're going to go at the top right here.
Going to go and just create a function that Barville that's going to be deciding where are we going
to be going.
So Konst you r l e course.
Now what I want to check it's to check the process if the process and can did this on under a different
section.
If the process equals to note underscore EMV and it's equal to production we can do something.
Let me do it right.
Production we're going to do something if not we're going to do something else.
So that's something else.
If it's not equal to production if you're not inside production you're going to say OK so this is development.
So we're going to do the DTP HGT pecan for Slash for Slash local host three thousand whatever your environment
your testing environment is.
If not we need to pass the u r l of the production.
Well we're in the testing mode.
You will need to do something else.
But you know at the end when the application goes live you can have your your out your final your elf
horse so we can store this inside the embarkment virals.
So I'm going to say process dot D-NV dot and I'm going to college route you are l.
We don't have this in a copy and go to the environment virals going to say that they're route you are
l is going to know it's going to be I don't know HTP for Slash forward slash and then waves dot com
whatever.
Now remember that if you're adding this to the environment virals on the development place of the development
environment you will need whenever you go to production go to the configuration of Heroku and you know
add them if not of course nothing is going to work.
So now we have the route you are l.
But what we need to do is to include that dot and beaches like that with a server.
So I'm going to copy this and I'm going to go right here at the top and paste it.
All right.
So now inside of this file we have access to this Eurail which is going to be equal to whatever we get
inside the rural with that M-B or is going to be equal to localhost three thousand.
This one.
All right.
So instead of putting the address you know the domain just like this I'm going to say just you are Apple
and it's going to go to whatever you are you are you are using recent passport and it will attach that
data token.
All right.
So this looks nice.
No mistakes hopefully no mistakes.
So now what we need to do right here we need we are making a reference to recent past.
But we are not including this at the top so Konst opening close recent past re Choire that forward slash
and reset pass template so now it's going to work.
OK.
So we are ready to try it and see what happens.
I'm going to go and reset the Jones wrap.
Can it reset the passport.
Done.
Check your e-mail.
And if we check the e-mails.
Hey Francis.
Reset your pass get the link.
And if I go here we go to a local host reset password and a token.
Now of course we are getting page not found because we need to create this route.
This is the next step.
And on this route we will have two different things.
And you know the two different inputs the password and the you know confirm password if the passwords
are good that we're going to go back to the server check if this token it's correct and it's not expired.
And if everything is OK we're going to reset the password right and let the user move forward.
So that is what we need to do right now.
Let's go to the next section and complete this.