All right so now let's create the layout for this.
You know the route and the component and everything else.
So inside the we said user and recent past edgiest So react re-act class based components.
Right.
And I'm going to call this reset pass because the other one was we said user right now I'm going to
be using a lot of things from you reset user.
So not this one.
Let me bring it right here.
I'm going to put it all right.
So I'm going to go at the top.
We are still going to use actio.
We are still going to use you know this one the form action so I'm going to copy and paste.
All right now we're going to use one more thing but I'm going to add it at the end or maybe I did right
now I'm going to go to the register file and at the top we can see that we have a dialog so we can do
pretty much the same thing if we are able to reset the pass successfully.
We will see us show a dialog to the user asking the user to log in.
OK.
So now we have the recent past I'm going to say we said pass and we're going to go two routes.
So I'm going to go to routes and include this at the top so I'm going to bring it import reset pass
from that forward slash components forward slash reset user and this one it's not an index.
So we need just pacify this.
Of course I'm going to go right here at the bottom.
Let me do this.
So we're going to copy paste.
Now this route it's a little bit different than the user because the reset passport has a token.
Remember we need to catch the I.D..
So first I'm going to say that we're going to use the recent pass component and this one instead of
user is going to be passport and then always lash Collen and then tokin.
So this is an I.D. right just like the product detail and the I.D. you get the token.
And we pass it to that component.
Right.
OK.
So in theory we should be getting something so we get reset pass.
Very good.
Let's go back to the reset pass component.
Now we need to do a lot of things just like we did with the index of the recent user I'm going to go
to register.
I'm going to do this pretty much same thing we did before.
We're back to the boring part.
All right.
So form data now.
We will use the use the passport and the Confirm passport and on the register component we we have this
we have the passport and the confirmed confirmed passports are going to copy this state right and paste
it.
That's it.
Everything else just the same right.
So OK so I'm going to go at the bottom.
Save it.
We do need again the update form and the submit form.
So I'm going to copy and of course modify this up.
I mean a mistake when we copy again there we go update form going to go to reset pass pasted.
And I'm going to call this a reset pass.
Why not reset pass.
Same thing for the other room for the submit form submit form.
Of course we delete everything inside data is met and then console log data is made.
Right.
OK.
So right so we get to go now.
One more thing right here we get the reset passport and the token.
So we need a way to catch the token.
So we could do this inside the component that Mount for example can it open and close.
Now how can we get the token Konst reset token.
And we have access of course to this that prompts that match that Rams programs dot and we call this
token.
So we need to make a reference to whatever we are using the word token matches the word token right
here.
All right so now what you want to do I want to store it inside of the stage so I'm going to go at the
top.
I'm going to say reset and then token.
All right.
So we have a token a form error a form a success and it can add one more.
It's going to be form error and then message.
And this one is going to be empty.
You could do this at the end.
All right.
Now the form success instead of false I'm going to change it to an empty string.
All right let's look at we we're going to get good to go.
All right.
So we pretty much have everything we need now whenever we get the token.
I want to set the new state of this so I'm going to go right here at the bottom and say this state said
stayed open and close and we do reset token we are pretty much using the same.
So it will pass.
Right.
So now let's bring the you know the container for this class name.
It's going to be container so we can center everything container and I'm going to add on page one right
here outside of this.
I'm going to just copy the form and then bring in H2 just like we are doing on the register.
So I get a copy going to close the form.
Right.
And the H-2 will be you know reset password reset password.
All right.
Now if you remember on the register we were using the reset password in the left and to confirm the
password in the left and in the right.
The confirmed password.
So we do have this in the register.
And again it's just to save time I'm going to copy that.
BLOCK Foreign block to verify password.
All right.
Get a copy and paste again.
We are saving a lot of time.
All right.
So enter password and confer password.
We need the buttons and the errors and everything else.
So I'm going to go to register again and copy this and paste it at the bottom right and ugly put the
copy copy the it did as well.
All right I know it looks ugly.
I'm going to format.
All right.
So form our label please check your data.
Now what I want to do if something goes bad I want to show the message I get back from the server.
That's why I'm adding a form error message.
So I'm going to say if something goes back does that state that form error message whatever message
we attach we're going to show it.
If not we're going to show an empty stream.
All right.
Now instead of creating an account it's going to be reset password.
So it looks good.
Right.
So now what do we need to do.
Whenever we add passport and let's see if this works I'm going to say for a password password again
password 1 2 3 and then password 1 2 3 I'm going to check the cons. remember we are doing a console
log for the data to submit and we get passport 1 2 3.
All right so now we know we get a passport when we need to do whenever we send a request to a magical
place.
We need to send the new password that the user is entering and the token.
And at this point we don't have information about the user.
We don't have a user ID or e-mail or anything.
We just have a token.
So what we do we just go to the database and we find the user by that token they are providing right
here.
That of course comes from the e-mail.
All right.
So let's do that right now.
So I'm going to go to the server to same spot.
Then the you know the reset user right here and I'm going to say app.
I'm going to post open clocks.
Right.
All right.
So there you are Elford this begin to say that it's for slashed API for Slash users forward slash and
then reset password makes sense.
OK.
So again we don't have the middle where the off nor the admin.
So it's request and response we get so what.
What do we need to do right now.
First we need to find the user by that token.
Right.
So I'm going to say user dot and then we do find one same thing we did before.
Find one now.
Next it's going to be the arguments what are we going to be finding.
So we need to find a user by their reset token.
Remember this token.
Now the.
Right here.
Me just copy because I don't remember it's reset token.
All right.
So we're going to say that the reset token should be equal.
Let me copied it right.
There we go.
So that the reset token should be equal to whatever we get from the request that body and that reset
token that the user is passing.
Right.
That one we are getting right here from the programs.
All right of course we're going to be passing this right.
OK.
So I'm going to close it of course I'm going to put a coma right now.
I'm going to say OK.
So we want to find a user that contains this token and we want to find it.
We want to return something.
Only if the date it's not greater than the you know the thing we did right here the end of the day.
All right.
So we can it did this with a greater number.
So I'm going to say that the recent token and then the XP expiration should not be greater.
So GTP greater or equal than today.
Now I'm going to create a viral today of course as rivals doesn't exist.
So I'm going to say var today equals going to bring moment again opening close.
I'm not sure I've imported this at the top.
So it's moments that dot start.
I didn't.
That's why I'm not giving me anything.
So it's going to be start.
Then off and this is when you know when the autocomplete get to gets really useful.
So day and then we get the value and then off.
All right.
So I don't have a moment at the top.
I'm going to import it and I get a copy from here so I'm going to go.
I guess I don't we don't yeah we don't.
There we go.
In to go back to the user.
So for that.
So now we're going to get the value of today.
Right.
The start of today.
Now of course if the start of the day it's greater than the values we have right here nothing is going
to be returned and everything is going to fail.
Right.
OK.
So then we do coma opening close and we return our response on this response we will have an error and
a user right now of course if we have no user it's because the token it's incorrect or it's you know
expired.
It expired.
So you're going to say if no user begin a return our response and let me make this bigger because it's
going to get bigger.
So we're going to send a response a Jason opening close so we send that Gudel success false coma and
again to be attaching a message.
So message and it could say Sorry token bad generate a new one.
All right.
Let's get.
Of course if everything goes OK.
There are a couple of things we need to do.
We need to reset the password.
I'm sorry.
We need to of course reset the password and we need to reset the token.
Back to nothing.
Right.
We could of course also reset the date.
Why not.
So remember that whenever you go to a user right here you go inside user and you make some changes on
the pre save.
Right here we have a presale.
So whenever we do something we save we change something it's going to do the user that we're going to
do that you start that safe ride remember.
So right here we get the modified passport says we are modifying the old password with the new passport
is going to go and enter here.
Of course it's not going to not do anything.
All right.
I just wanted to you know mind we Firfir for this so user dot password.
So the user password entering the user we get back from find one entering the passport and say that
now the passport it's changed.
It's equal to request that body that passport.
I'm going to say OK so now of course we have a new passport and set that token.
So I'm going to go to the reset token and now say it's equal to nothing.
And we could do the same thing with the date.
Why not user dot reset token XP.
It's equal to nothing.
All right.
Now we need to save the save of course the new state of the user.
So I'm going to go to user go to save open and close.
We will get an error and a document if everything goes OK of course or if go goes back goes back.
So if opening close if we do get an hour we can send a different kind of response.
So we turn you know same old same old thing response that Jaison when me do that returned correctly
returned Jaison.
We do success then false and then we send the error back.
All right.
Right of course if everything goes OK we will return our response with the status status of 200.
And Jason now I just added I just realized I'm adding this status.
But you know pretty much the same thing if I do this.
I should be doing something like that like 400 or something like that.
That's OK.
All right.
So success then it's going to be true.
Right.
So let's go over this again.
We're going to get this route and we're going to get the token and the passport.
Right.
So we're going to find a user by the token they have on the you're out and if the token expired we will
not return any users because it will not find one if it's finding a user which is which means that the
token is correct and it is still active.
The token we can go to the user and of course if no user we send the message if not of course we said
the new passport is going to go to that Preece safe inside the model and we're going to reset the token
and the expiration the expiration date of the token.
And then of course we just save it and then it's going to go of course to the presale.
All right.
If everything goes OK we send the success true if not success false.
So now the next thing is going to be testing the route.