Right.
So back in the recent past whenever we submit the form.
Of course we're going to do this and we're going to do a big expose expose no X hosts post opening close.
Right.
So we need the route.
It's API users and reset passport.
And of course maybe maybe thinking well we spend a lot of time doing this.
Well not really if you know what to do because after a while you will you will know what to do.
It's going to take you maybe half an hour maybe a little bit more but that's that's it.
So of course what we need to do we need to send the data we want to submit.
So I need to put the data to submit which contains the password.
Just one password right now.
They Ballie date revalidate passed with confirm password just this one but we also need the reset token
remember that the server looks by token.
So we need to pass the password and the token.
So again data Sabet and doing some destructuring some putting inside of here whatever we have inside
data to submit and then I'm doing that reset token equals to does that state that reset token remember
we are setting the value of this right here.
All right so now the server will be receiving this.
And I I was telling you after a while this is going to be easy for you because you going to do it several
times.
So response.
And now of course it takes more time video because in talking at the same time that's why.
But in real life this is going to be much faster.
So OK so now of course on the year when the promise gets solved we get a response.
And we have two possible scenarios we have.
If everything goes ok of everything goes bad which means that the token it's not valid.
So if the response and I'm going to do it right here if the response that data that success remember
we are setting sending a success just like this.
It's of course falls then what we would do with it.
So show the error so this that set state opening close and we're going to set the form are to true coma.
And then they form an error message.
Remember here.
All right.
The form error message.
It's going to be equal to the message we are sending right here.
The sorry token bed and everything else.
So this one is going to be inside responds that data and then message.
Right.
So if everything goes OK we want to do of course.
Something else we want to set the time out and you know set the state a form error back to false.
But in this time again a form error.
Let me do it first form error.
Back to false.
Go back to false.
And then we have the form success.
So it's going to be koma.
Sorry.
Come on.
For him success.
And it's going to be equal to true.
Now after a while and we can do pretty much the same thing with it with the register whenever everything
is OK.
I want to show a dialogue and this dialogue will be of course shown to the screen whenever we change
to form success to.
And then after a while I want to do the set timeout to kick the user back to the log in you know so
they can enter with a new password.
And this is going to pass.
It's going to go up two or three seconds.
And of course this that props that history history that push.
And then we push it back to register log in.
All right.
Looks nice.
Hopefully again no errors if not of course any possible deal.
Chuck what's wrong.
All right.
So OK.
So everything looks correct so let's give it a try and then go here.
And of course I need to do the whole process again because we have the.
But we could be wrong so I'm going to go back to logon right back to home and I'm going to use the account
of this dude.
This guy Frances Jones Oh I'm sorry.
Before we do that we are not going to get a form that we are not going to see anything on the screen
if everything goes OK.
We need to add that dialogue.
So I'm going to copy go to register and copy the dialogue.
I forgot to do it.
So I'm going to go to the bottom and maybe after the form Yeah that's OK we could say congratulations
or no.
All right.
Something like that doesn't matter.
And password.
I don't know your password.
I don't know why we said.
And you will be directed.
You know something real simple.
Now remember that we are listening for the forms access so whenever we change it if everything goes
OK to true this dialog will show.
Ryan.
That's the idea.
Same thing like that before.
All right so now we are ready to try again.
So in.
Of course we bet we failed to remember the password.
So log in.
I believe it was we said user sorry we're going to add one and the minute reset user.
All right.
So now I want to reset.
FRANCES JONES done.
All right.
I'm going to go back to waves and we get the reset passport and reopen it.
Now it's the correct token.
So the default password for this do it's password 1 2 3.
I can change it to password 1 2 3 4 and then password 1 2 3 4.
All right.
Of course reset password and write your passwords was was a we said no errors on the server.
Let's try again.
I'm going to try to enter with the password 2:59 which is the old one.
So passport 2:59 log in it fails.
And if I add a for we are good to go.
It works no errors right man.
So OK.
So what is next.
And it's the last thing we're going to do.
It's to go to the log in and at the bottom.
Let's do that right now.
OK.
So the components of this button it was there were just a log in and it's inside the log in.
So I'm going to go after the log in get the log in right here.
So good copy the button and it's a little bit.
We're going to do it really fast.
Get copied and put this and say for God my passport.
Now I'm not going to be I'm not going to add a link because we will need to change the styles a lot.
So I'm just going to keep that unclick and I'm going to add style to this Bunim because it's not it's
going to look a little bit weird.
So I'm going to do margin and then left you can you can do it if you wish.
Doesn't matter.
It's just a timing thing than 10 pixels.
And the unclick instead of of course submitting the form.
What we want to do is redirect the user to a new place.
So I'm going to get at this and do the events well and whenever we unclick we do this that probs that
history that push.
All right.
And then of course we go to reset and then user.
Looks good.
Now remember at the top you're using with the router.
So that prompts a history push should be working.
So I'm going to reload the application and we get the forget passport and if you look at we go to the
route.
All right.
So everything goes.
Everything works of course.
Snip everything and put it in.
So you can you can get the code and that's it for now.
This is the last of the bonus of course are going to be adding some more but not this week maybe the
next one or maybe in a couple of weeks.