Welcome to the re-act jazz practice boot camp.
My name is Fernando and now we will guide you through this three practice project because maybe the
best way to learn it by practicing.
So this course is for almost everyone.
You need to know a little bit of yes 5 and iOS 6 javascript.
Now if you bought this course and you know nothing about react don't worry.
I attach as a bonus section a very tiny re-act course for beginners.
So with everything you need to know just to get started.
So you're going to create three different projects.
We will start our engines creating a landing page with transmission's carousels and of course all the
other re-act logic and we will deploy the project to search the second project.
It's much more difficult.
It's a soccer or football team web page and this one includes routes animations transitions of authentication
user dashboard firebase storage and upload database and much more of course.
And at the end we will deploy everything to firebase and the third and final project.
It's a monster.
We will create a guitar Web site e-commerce style and we will add carousels filter's detailed pages
use of cart Pay-Pal routes of authentication user admin and dashboard.
And of course with this one we will create our own server with Express and no just and we're going to
use Mongo divi as a database and at the end we will deploy everything to Heroku.
And of course you will get a bonus much more additional re-act blocks for each project as we go and
it's going to be a very long journey.
So grab the beans put the coffee on get a cup and let's begin.