Right.
So before we start with the actual coding are going to give you an overview of the three projects.
This this one this section it's for the first project.
So this is going to be a static web page.
Right.
No database no log in or dictation.
So whenever the application LOTES we get an animation with some javascript loading with the counter
a count down until the event starts.
And of course we get right here a carrousel right now at the top get a header.
And when we scroll down of course everything shows.
Now as we scroll down we get some transitions with the different sections of the web page and again
with apprising you know some kind of different kind of animations.
Then we get the map and the footer You know it's really really simple web page.
And we even get a side drawer and whenever we click it we go to a different section and we scroll to
a different section.
Right so this is what we're going to be building on a natural and at the end of project is going to
look something like this.
So we will create a you know a lot of components.
So again this is the first one and I'm showing you this because maybe this is maybe too easy for you.
So maybe you want to skip it and you just want to go to the second project.
All right.
So this is the first one.
Let's take a look at the second one.