So this is going to be the second project in our course.
So it's a it's the Manchester City web page it's soccer or football team maybe you know it.
And again when the application Lote's you know we get a little bit more complex animation and we will
use a different library than the one we use on the first project.
All right then if we scroll down again we get more transmission's and this piece of information comes
from D.
Comes from a server from the database so we will connect this project to firebase so we can get the
data we need.
And again if we keep scrolling then we have more transitions and right here again we will use that database
to store some information on firebase.
Then of course we get get other sections like the team and the matches.
So if we go to the team of course we can get a list of all the players inside our squad key pers defense.
And again we will do more transitions right here.
Same idea with the mattress we can to create the matches endpoint and whenever LOTES can it get all
the matches of the team and we will do some filtering right here at the top with no wins lose much played
and everything else.
And of course the table right here river is simple and of course since we need a place where we can
store the teams and the players we will need to sign in.
So we will create a sign n end point.
So if I log in with passport 2:59 real simple passport we can answer to the user dashboard and break
your rule at minister the man just the mattress.
You know all the mattress we see on the home the ATM match of course will add a match.
We can edit the players and add new players and of course of course if we log out we go back to the
log in.
So again we will create all the Alphen dictation logic for this one with firebase And if we go to the
we go right here to the project we can see that you know we get a lot more things going on here we have
a lot more going on.
So again we're going to do a lot of work on this project.
All right.
So let's go to take a look at the third and final project.