Write so this is going to be the third practice project in our course it calls wastes and it's a guitar
selling website.
So we are going to sell guitars and when the application loads we get a slider a slider and at this
point it should be really simple for us.
But then of course if we scroll down we can fetch and perform queries to note.
A server using Mongo divi to bring the products we meet right here in this section.
Same thing right here.
That's one it's best selling and this one it's by new arrivals.
Right.
And of course we'll get an end point where we can search guitarists and we will do some filtering with
the database.
We can do load more.
And for example if I go to Fender I just see the get the Fender guitars and fender and Ivan as guitars.
So again we're going to do a lot of filtering logic right here and same thing right here we can change
some some of the layouts.
Now of course if a user wants to buy a guitar they need the ability to log in or to register.
So if I go to Lagann we can create an account.
We don't have an account or we can log in and since I'm I'm already registered customer are going to
do password 2:59 again and after I log in we're going to get the dashboard with the user information
and the history of purchases.
Forget Of course if I want to go to the card.
We get it right here.
But we can access through here and we can access to the card to the user at the items to the card.
I mean we can of course remove the total and everything else.
And at the end of course we need to you know pay the guitar.
In this case.
So we're going to use the Pay-Pal connector to complete the transaction.
Right.
All right.
And of course we get a few more a few more sections like updating the profile of the users.
And if we are an administrator we're going to create an endpoint where we can say we can change some
of the side information we can at TAR's including uploading the image and we can manage some of the
categories.
So again just like a just like it's all before this one it's pretty big.
We're going to do a lot of coal coding all of this files all of these files.
So we're going to spend a lot of time right here.
All right.
OK.
Doing the server and the client.
All right.
So of course we can log back out.
So again this is the final project.
And on the next one we're going to start with the first one.
If you don't want to do the first one because it's really simple for you.
Just go to the second one OK.
So let's begin.