All right so the first step is going to be installing no doubt as if you're you already have no gas
in your system.
There's no need for you to install it again.
Right.
So how do we install it.
First we need to go to know just that Orrick and right here you can have of course the options.
I'm a Mac computer so this is videos for Mac so you will need to download this one.
I have this one I believe.
But you can download this one or this one.
So I'm going to click on this one and I'm going to go and store it inside that downloads.
So it's going to take a minute and a pause to BDO and be right back.
OK so everything was downloaded.
If we go to downloads you're going to get it right here if you click on it.
Of course it's going to give you this window asking you for the installation times.
Now I'm not going to install it because I've already have node in my system.
They have a different version so you need to delete the previous one.
Install the new one but the the one I have is going to work just fine.
So I don't want to updated it.
So we're going to go to continue then continue is going to ask you if you want to agree yes agree.
And of course the installation time.
And then of course go to install and after everything is installed you just exit the installer right.
OK.
Now the problem is how can we check if node is installed in our system.
Since I believe you're using a Mac computer so you will need to do command and space and you know bring
the spotlight search and you do terminal of course you press enter is going to give you the terminal
and B we will be using this terminal.
A lot of this course.
So how can we check if you have node.
So first we say no.
Right.
Just node and then minus V minus V means Berson.
So with this we will be asking the terminal the burden of node we are running in our system.
So if you press enter it will leave you the burden of node I'm using the ADA.
So I'm a little bit behind but that's fine.
So if you're not getting this it's because you will need to restart the computer so restart your computer
and then come back.
All right.
So let's go to the next section.