OK so the first step is going to be installing jazz in our system.
I'm on my Windows computer right now.
So first you will need to go to No.
J.S. dot org.
And then of course it will give you two options for the downloads we need to install this one or whatever
Burreson you're using in the future maybe.
So I'm going to click on this is going to download.
It's going to take a minute.
It's going to the BDO and be right back.
OK so everything was downloaded.
So I will go right here.
I'm going to click an ad and then of course run.
It's going to ask me if I'm sure.
So let me give you and show this you're going to get this tiny tiny window and after a while it's going
to you know it will give me the next option is just kind calculating the requirements in my computer.
I don't have a very fast Windows machine so you know it might take a little while it's a little bit
slow.
Just let's give it get the installer a moment.
Sorry for that.
All right.
After it's done will click next accept the terms then click next.
Of course it's going to be in program files that just click next.
And of course Cuca keep clicking next.
I'm not going not going to install it because I've already have a version on this computer I might need
to upgrade it at but I don't really use know J as in a Windows machine I have the Mac machine.
So I'm going to cancel it of course you will need to move forward.
So after that is done after everything was installed correctly.
So we will need to check that node runs in our system so how can we do that.
So I'm going to go right here to the search and type ACMD and I'm going to bring the command prompt.
Let me bring it right here.
So this is my machine the user's local machine doesn't matter the path where you're going to be.
So how can we check it.
Real simple.
We're going to say node and then minus the minus V means version.
So this will give us the birth of node that runs in our system going to press center.
It's going to take a second and then it will get me that 6 0.
You know I'm a little bit behind in this version.
So OK so if you're getting this it means that everything's cool.
You know you can use no jazz and your computer.
Now if you're not getting this and you're getting some summerlike command not recognized you will need
to restart the computer for sure.
So restarted the computer and then come back.
So on the next section I will talk about about the virus code.
The IDE Iam going to be using if you're a Windows machine I will suggest for you to take a look on to
the next video.
Don't skip it.