OK so we can start simple.
First we will learn the easy way.
And as we advance we are going to move forward to the Pro way.
So re-act provides us a re-act boilerplate.
So with this we have everything set up for us so we can download as I trigger some commands and presto
we have to react.
We get our re-act application.
So of course this is going to be just the minimal template.
But first to do this we need to install the seat eye globally.
So whenever we install a global things in our computer then we can trigger and access this package from
anywhere in our computer we can access and use it for any project inside our computer.
That's why we make it global.
So first we will need to install this.
So I'm going to go right here and I'm going to say and PM and it doesn't I'm navigated to my project
but right now it does matter.
Just open the terminal and then go over here.
If you're on a Windows computer you can type ACMD and it's going to give you the command line.
So I'm going to go right here and say install space and we can say mine is G.
Whenever we use minus g it means global.
And then we're going to do create hyphen re-act hyphen app press center and it's going to take a couple
minutes.
Depends on your connection and your computer are going to pause the BDO and be right back.
OK so everything is installed.
So I'm going to go to the command line.
I'm going to say clear.
And now notice again that I am inside the project.
I've navigated to one re-act basics and this folder is going to be the one that is going to go to you
inside.
Get help so you can.
You're going to be able to download this folder.
And right here inside the Via the Visual Studio code I am already inside that folder.
So now how do we install.
How do we create a boiler plate right here.
So I'm going to go to the terminal and I'm going to say create hyphen re-act hyphen app just like that.
Now if we do space and we type a name to something like my awesome app something like that whatever
this react is going to create a whole boilerplate inside this folder.
So it's going to go right here.
Create a new folder and inside that folder is going to put all the files for the for our project.
I don't want to do that.
I'm already inside the folder inside the command and inside the studio code.
So what I'm going to do I'm going to delete everything and I'm going to say that space and that whenever
you use Dudd is going to install all the files inside that folder.
So OK I'm going to press Enter.
He's going to take again a couple of minutes and I'll be right back.
And for Windows users and for Mac users why not.
If you didn't like to use the terminal this terminal where you can do the visual studio code once you're
inside the project you can you have access to an integrate terminal.
If I click right here it's going to give you the terminal and you're already inside that project so
you don't need to navigate.
You can use this one if you like.
OK.
So I'm going to go right here to the terminal.
I'm going to press enter and it's going to take a few minutes.
So I'll pass the BDO and be right back.
OK so everything is installed.
And be sure that it's giving you some commands.
I'd just clear them up.
Don't worry you're going to be using them later and right here we're going to have all the project structure
the power source and everything else is going to be talking this in a minute.
But how can we test if the application works or not.
So I'm going to go to the terminal and we need to be inside the project always inside the project and
we're going to say NPM start going to press center.
It's going to open the browser but I don't want it right now.
And it says startingly will have been server compile successfully and then is going to give you some
suggestions of an address of a location.
And if I copy this one to local and go right here and pasted of course we're working right here is going
to give us the application the welcome to react and this it's our actual project right here we have
a file that is going to be the index for this and we can modify it and it's going to modify it right
here.
So whenever we use create react.
Everything is ready for us.
You know we can just start changing things and that's it.
There is no need to manually install everything.
Now this course is going to be a full stack of course.
So if we do create re-act app it wouldn't be a very good course.
So there is there are a lot of things happening behind this.
It's using web mail web PAC for example.
And you know we need to learn about web pack and we're going to do it later.
It's going to be going to go from right from the start with web pack and we're going to do all this
process everything that is happening with Create we act up are going to teach you how to do it manually
install everything manually but that's going to happen later.
For now to learn react we're going to be using the Create we act app.
Let's get.
So I hope that everything it's working for you if you have a problem you just can leave a comment on
the Q&amp;A and I will answer as soon as possible.
Let's go to the next section and start with Dr..