So when you work with react or enage single page applications you're going to have a lot of files.
But what the user sees on the screen is going to be something else something different.
So let me bring you a chart right here.
So in one hand you can have your application right here.
So your application of course is going to contain a lot of files a lot of javascript and different files.
Let's get you could have hundreds of files then whenever you need to finish your project and you need
to publish to put it inside production you're going to be using web Pech and vavle and web pack and
battle is going to grab all your project is going to compile everything and then is going to give you
just a couple files.
You can have two or three or maybe a little bit more but just a few files.
So this index is going to be what the browser is going to be using is going to be seeing on the screen
and all your code or your application code is going to be bundled into one.
So battle and well-padded they're going to merge all your code and put it in some inside something that
calls bundle that D.S..
Now the bundle the name.
It's my convention bundle you can use you can use whatever name you want to react and create the app
is going to do this job.
And it's going to stored inside Vandel that has some mean exit right here.
So we have our application.
This one is the one we have right here.
We know that.
So if I do right click and I do inspect is going to give me the console and right here we can have that
actual Dom.
If I go to the header you can have a few tacks the fight the con Condon the styles and whatever.
Now if I scroll down and go to the body you can have a script and notice that right here we have a bundle
that jast.
So all the code for this application it's merge into one.
Let me just do a right click and let me go right here to network and reload the page again and this
Varndell that Jesus is going to be a bunch of files.
A lot of a lot of code bundled into one.
Right here we have all the code and this is going to be a really long coat of course and it's going
to get longer of course.
OK.
Let me close it.
So Noda know that whenever you work with react or single any single page application you're going to
be using just a bundle.
Yes.
And for now we are now going to learn how to do this by hand because we're using create re-act app and
create re-act up is going to do it for us.
But then when we reached the web pack section of the course we're going to do this Vandel manually.
OK.
So let's keep moving forward.
Right.
So let's talk a little bit of what's happening with the project structure.
So on top of the chain let me make this bigger just like here on top of the chain we have the node modules
here are all the dependencies that our project is going to need.
So if our project works is because we have the node modules.
So this is kind of the vendor folder.
If I open this can see a lot of files.
That's why it's taking a lot of time in installing and creating the re-act app.
It's installing all the dependencies for our project.
So OK we can have a bunch of files.
If you do this one nothing is going to work.
So think of this the node modules as the vendor folder.
Every piece of code you use from different developers is going to be right here just like we act and
everything else.
So then at the bottom of the chain we can have the package that Jason.
Let me make this better.
So the package that Jason is going to be the manifest for your project all the information about the
project modules just like nobody else and dependencies you're going to use is going to be listed right
here right here and dependencies.
We have re-act react Domm the name of the project.
It's one reac basics version and everything else.
And then of course you can have the scripts folder.
So this is what we're going to do what node is going to be listening to start the application remember
to start this.
We did NPM start this one.
We are doing NPM.
It's entering here start and it's starting the development server.
Good.
So we're going to be talking more about commands when we reach the notes section of the course but this
file it's really important.
And this is not a re-act file.
It's going to be a node jast file got me close.
Yes.
OK.
So then we have the public folder and the source folder.
So the important part of the public for there is going to be the index.
H Tim L So this index HMO is going to be what it's going to be rendered on the screen it's what we get
right here with the bundle that jazz and everything else.
Now the funny thing about this is that if I scroll down right here let me make it smaller.
We didn't have a bundled digest just like we have right here.
So what is happening why we are getting the bundle jast inside the HDMI out on the browser.
Not right here.
Well whenever you do NPM start re-act they create we act app and we pack are going to build a development's
server.
So the server is going to be something that can happen behind the scenes and what you see right here
is going to be rendered from memory.
It's not using the actual files.
It's building everything storing in memory and then you get this because you are in a development server.
Then whenever you go to production it's going to run web pack is going to create build and you're going
to see that that bundled that J.
So right here you get no development build.
It's not optimized then to create a production build.
We need to use a different command not NPM start but am pm on built and we're going to get this at the
end of this section.
OK.
Then the second folder is going to be the source folder.
We have it right here.
Make it bigger so we can have ab you know with the C Ss the javascript attached and everything else.
We're not going to be using a lot of files right here.
Now one of the files is going to be really important the index that has an inside the source begin to
store all the files for our application.
But the main file.
The one that that starts the application is going to be the index that G-S.
So this file is going to start everything for us inside our application and we're going to be using
this one of course.
OK that's good.
Let's go to the next section and keep moving forward.