OK so all the files we have right here we are not going to use them.
Of course if you want in the future you can keep them.
But for this course for this basic project that you're going to build We're going to build everything
from scratch.
So you know there are just in the way.
So I'm going to delete them pretty much are going to read them all.
So I'm going to go right here to the project that they're going to delete the files from here because
it's easier to link the files from here.
So I'm going to select everything I'm going to unselect the index that I'm going to leave that one I'm
going to delete everything else going to center trash.
OK.
And then I get to go to the source folder and I'm going to select everything and just leave the index
non-jazz out and then I'm going to send everything to the trash.
So I'm going to go back to the project and we just have the indexed h d m l and the index that has and
again we are going to build everything from scratch.
So I'm going to delete everything and then I'm going to save it.
OK.
So now if five of the application.
Of course nothing works.
That is good.
So I got to go back to the project.
And now whenever we write code for react we use components or buse.
So these are the first key words you need to remember.
So this components are going to be these pieces of code we connect so they can work together.
So we write everything in javascript but whenever it's compiled it's going to be rendering javascript
and some H-2 him out.
So again in re-act we create functions and classes we work with functions and classes but some some
functions are going to be returning some DML.
But again just like I told you before everything is javascript so this lookalike HMO is going to be
in reality.
J.S. it's going to be Javascript and this is going to be called J as sex is what right does.
We're going to write some major Gmail that looks like Gmail but then it's going to be compiled and it's
going to be rendering that HD email on the screen but that HD mail is in fact javascript and it's called
GSX.
So let's create our first component you're going to be starting with that are going to create a rival
that is going to be Konst and it's going to be called app and this app is going to be equal to fad Aro
function.
And this one is going to return some code and I'm going to return an H1 tag and inside we can have hello
then world.
Simple as that.
And just exclamation marks.
Now notice that this is just the regular iOS 6 function.
It's a fat arrow function.
So we get we're going to be using ESX and discourse and if you don't know iOS 6 at all.
Don't worry just keep watching and we will learn as we go.
Or you can go to the final section of the course and you will have a bonus content is going to be a
fool iOS course you can start from there learn your sex and then you can come back.
But if you wish you can stay and just learn as we go don't worry.
So this is just the function is going to be equal to function then app then opening close and you know
just a regular function.
This is the same idea.
OK so let me delete this.
OK so now this is our first component if we invoke app is going to return some text some H-1 take some
time out.
Of course if we go right here we get an error.
It's a first error re-act must be in scope when using j as sex.
So OK so let's keep moving forward and see what is missing in our application.
So in order for react to compile our component in a code that the browser can understand we need to
let the script node know that we want to use react because that's what we want to do.
We want to use react.
So we need to bring react to this script.
We need to bring act to the equation.
So how do we do it.
We import things.
So at the beginning of this thread we will bring two main libraries or dependencies and we are going
to be making use of the keyboard import than space.
And we passed the name of the thing that we want to bring in this case.
We're going to be bringing react and then we're going to say from where we want to bring this.
So I'm going to say from now are going to say space and in single quotes I'm going to put the name of
what I want to bring.
It's going to be react.
So what's happening right this is that node is going to say OK this dude wants to bring something that
calls react and it's going to get a wanted from react.
So whenever we don't have an extension just like this for example node knows that we whenever we put
a name just like this knows that we want to bring something from the node modules from the vendor folder.
So it's going to goes to the Bendre folder bring everything and put it right here.
So we need two things.
The first one is react and then we're going to need something else.
We're going to say import and begin to say react.
Damn just like that react and then dorm.
And of course we want to bring it from re-act dawn.
That this our domain of dependencies of libraries that we need to work would react.
And if we go to the package that Jason you can see that you have it as dependencies react and we act
on it.
Let me close this.
So what happens.
So let me save the page and if we go right here we render nothing happens.
But you're not getting this message right here.
Let's go to the inspect and check the console.
OK re-act arm is defined but never used up is designed.
But valy never use.
We're going to get to getting a different message right here.
OK.
So let's go back to the code.
So OK we have our component we have the dependencies.
So now we need to show decode.
So we explicitly need to say react.
Here's my component and this is what I want to render.
So we are going to be making use of Riyadh.
Damn I gotta go.
Right here up bottom and I'm going to call this react dumb.
I have it right here.
So we act dumb.
It's going to be using a method.
So this method is going to call render and this vendor is going to take some arguments.
Now of course we are not there yet.
So this argument that we need to do is our component we'd say dude render our component.
So I'm going to go right here and we're going to say app we need to render this one.
OK.
So if I go right here of course we get a new message target container.
It's not a dom elements.
So whenever we use this just like this we are saying that we want to render a component class are going
to be talking about this later.
So what we should pass.
It's a component instance.
So we need to say we need to explicit say Dude this component this right here at this function.
It's a component so you need to render as a component.
So what we do we enclose everything in attack just like this just like an HDMI attack Walt same idea.
And if I save this and go to the browser it's going to be working.
But we get kind of a kind of a different a different message a different error message.
So I'm going to go back to the project and this render method is going to need this one which is going
to be the component.
But then it's going to need to know where to put it.
Right here we are telling what we will want to render but not where we want to put this.
So the second argument is going to be the where.
Now if I go to the HMO and we take a look right here we have a div that is going to be called rude and
this is a convention you can use whatever name you wish.
But of course you need to specify and index.
By default we called Rule root and it's a convention.
So if I go to the index as the second argument is going to be that rude and right here we're going to
be using Document dot Querrey selector and this is vanilla.
Jazz is going to be crazy selector.
And then of course we pass the name of the ID which is going to be rude.
So I'm going to save it.
Let me make it right.
So the everything should be working.
If I go right here.
OK.
We get.
Hello world.
Everything works.
So what is happening to some.
Everything everything up.
We are importing react.
We are creating a component that returns some DML and this e-mail.
In fact it's going to be Javascript is GSX but re-act is having this converting everything to email
and then we pass the initialiser to the function that returns that code.
And we are saying where we want to put it.
And then of course it's creating the bundle legist and the Vonda that Jesus is putting everything everything
inside this container.
OK.
That's what's happening behind the scenes.
So let's go to the next section and we'll be talking a little bit more about GSX what what this.