So right here we have a component that returns some h h d m l code than just an H one tack Burguet.
So in fact this again looks like HD mail but it's javascript It's j as sex.
So behind the scenes react is kind of doing something else.
I'm going to delete this deleted and I'm going to call react and react has a method that is going to
be called create element and this create element of course is going to create an element.
Is going to take a few arguments.
The first one is going to be which element we want to create can open and close and I'm going to say
H-1.
Now if I save it and go to the browser of course nothing is going to happen right here.
But if I go to elements to the body and right here inside the body inside the route we're going to have
our elements.
So this create element it's creating it and appending it to the body to the root.
So again this screed element is going to take a few arguments we can pass some options.
So the second argument is going to be the options.
So if we pass.
No of course you're not going to put any options.
But what we can do we can pass an object and this object is going to take some arguments.
Now for example let's say that I want to add a class to that.
H-1 are going to be using class and then name just like this class name and this class name is going
to be equal to the class.
So if I save it and go to the browser you're going to get one class of title and something weird is
going on.
Notice that it's put in class but here where you're using class name you get to see why in a minute.
Let me make this bigger.
So OK.
The second thing is going to be the arguments that we're going to put as an attribute to that H1 tag.
You can put whatever you want.
OK.
So the third argument is what's going to be inside the elements.
So we were use in Hello world.
So I'm going to say hello world.
Now if I go to the application we get the whole world.
So the third argument is going to be whatever we have inside the H-1 tag.
Now what happens if I want to put dev.
I want to add an element inside the contents of H-1.
Well we cannot do we cannot do this.
We cannot just say something like this if I do that.
Hello world.
It's not going to worked.
So it's parsing everything and converting everything to text.
So if you want to pass a real elements what we do we just concatenated with the same method I'm going
to go right here and say react react darte create element and I'm going to create a div just a div.
Sorry.
And if we go right here or go to the root.
Oh I made a mistake.
It's not kind react it's going to be react.
There we go.
So we reloaded again of course we get nothing but inside the H-1 tag we have a Deppe So we are concatenating
the same method inside the same method.
So of course this is not really a very fun way to create some major D.M. That's why we use the On the
one it's humanly readable.
So I'm going to go back to the other one whole overreact but know that behind the scenes react is kind
of a doing that re-act create element.
So OK let's keep moving forward.
OK so now we need to talk about about some gotchas that we have with this GSX.
So right here are a component.
It's just returning a single statement.
So whenever we return a single thing it's going to work.
We do it like this and works.
But what happens if I want to add a div that say whatever hey I can reload the application.
And it's of course failed to compile whenever we turn something inside of nothing we can.
We need to pass only a single argument so to fix this I'm going to go round here put everything inside
this.
This the C going to go right here and just paste it.
OK.
Now if I save it and reload the application again we have failed to compile.
It's not going to work.
So he's going to say adjusting GSX elements must be wrapped in an inclosing tack.
Kind of confusing but makes sense whenever we pass something inside we turn whether we have an inside
of a parentheses.
We cannot do it like this.
We need to pass only a single argument.
So we going to put everything inside an element it's going to copy and put it inside diff tag.
So now instead of saying a 10 instead of returning to different elements you're returning one.
And inside we have the children.
So if I save this and go right here to the application we get hello react and hey.
So it's working.
Remember that you need only you need one in closing elements and then inside you can put whatever you
want.
You can have a thousand dips right here.
It doesn't matter as long as you put them inside of a div.
It's going to work.
So the thing that we need to talk about is that the class name and class.
So if I go right here and add a class to the elements it's going to say new elements something like
this going to save it.
And of course it's not it's going to work but it's going to give you an error message.
It says embodied Dom property class.
Did you mean class name.
Well again all the error messages inside re-act are pretty clear.
So class this keyboard does class remember that we are using javascript right here.
This code is javascript not h tim L.
So this class is a reserved word.
We're going to be talking more about classes in the next few lectures but we cannot use class.
That's why we use class name.
So class name is going to be equal to class.
So whenever this GSX gets compiled by re-act is going to be converted converted to class.
So if I reload the page and go to elements we get the class inside the new elements right here.
And of course we are.
We are not getting an error message so everything works.
I know that this is kind of a pain in the butt because now we need to change that class to class name.
We are not going to use class inside OSX.
So again it's kind of a pain.
But but you're going to get used to it don't worry.
OK let's go to the next section.