So when you work with react or any other single page applications such as maybe bew or angular it's
very common to split everything in tiny tiny pieces.
This is VERY come.
And if you come from maybe Wordpress or the APHC world begin to know that you split everything in tiny
tiny tiny parts of it so we can do the same thing right here.
Now the first thing that we need to talk about is going to be about project structure begin to build
on this re-act basics.
S.S. we're going to build a tiny tiny application is going to be in use application and we can have
a header where we can filter some news and inside a different component we can have some news of course.
So first we need to talk about the structure of this.
So I'm going to bring here we can have our application and the first component is going to be the parents
component.
So we always going to get a parent component that it's going to enclose all the other code all the other
components.
So the first component is going to be the header so the header is going to contain the logo and then
we can add some an input text so we can filter some of the news we get at home.
Then we can have a different component which is going to be the news component.
This one is going to hold some other components that are going to be the actual news.
And now inside you can have each news.
Now we can use one component for all the news items that we get at home.
Now this news item is going to dynamically feed the information about that news to the news component.
So to sum everything up we can have four different components.
We have the parent component.
We have the better components to begin the news components.
That's three.
And then the news item we have four components.
Now why are we talking about this.
Why am i just telling you what we are going to do.
Well I'm not making this up but this is the first thing that you're going to need to do.
Whenever you start a new project you need to stop or five minutes before you start coding and think
about your project structure.
And again I'm not making this up you're going to do it because you need to think what are you going
to use and how are you going to structure.
If you start coding and you make something that it's maybe maybe not.
Right.
Are you going to you're going to go back to your code and start splitting everything again.
And of course if you were a freelancer you're going to be doing it.
And if you work in a company the first reunion the first media that you're going to do with maybe other
developers is going to be about the project structure not about your payment and not about the time
that it's going to take you is going to be the project structure.
Good.
OK let's keep moving forward and start with the new component the first component which is going to
be beheader So OK so let's create the structure for this.
I'm going to go right here to the directory I'm going to make this a little bit bigger and I get to
go to source now whenever we again we work with this kind of applications you need to have a folder
that contains all your components and you can call these components.
As I saw some people I know some people that use abuse or MV includes or templates components imbues
are the most popular ones.
So I'm going to go to source and I'm going to create a new folder that says component's just like that.
And now we're going to have three different components.
The paranoid one is going to be indexed.
And inside here you're going to have a header components.
It's going to be Hetter digest.
We're going to have a news item that is going to hold all the news so we can say news underscore and
list and you can name this files whatever you want.
It's essentially up to you again to create a new file that is going to be news on the score list on
their score item dodgy.
Yes everything is genius.
Of course you look at me and make this a little bit smaller.
There we go because this one and I'm now just going to close all the components.
So the first component that we need to create is going to be the head or component.
So first I'm going to just delete this just like this.
And of course right here we can have a header and begin to begin to do it right.
Right now in a minute we're going to say DIVX and right here we can have the header.
Remember that when whenever we turn something we need to return everything wrapped into into it.
Inside one element.
So right here we can have a header of course just really simple.
And if you go get better.
That's good.
So now let's create the component for this.
Now again whenever you work would react since you're going to be using GSX and re-act code you need
to import re-act from react to the same thing we did right here.
So I'm going to go right here and get a say import react just like that with capital are from react.
If you don't do this and you want to use them some re-act code it's not going to work.
You to you can get an error message and that's it for now you're not going to be using the other one.
They react on the react.
It's just to render something on the route says you're not going to do that.
You're just going to create the components and include it right here.
So we're going to create a components can be Konst just like we did with the other one.
This one is going to be called Hetter is going to be equal to is just a function that is going to return
some code so I'm going to say return and begin to return a dev that says Hetter real simple.
Then of course we're going to be changing this.
OK so now we have our component.
Now we we need a way to connect all the components right now to the index which is depende one and the
header.
So we need to tie them together.
Now unless we connect them manually they are not related.
So to connect things to connect components with other components we need to make them available for
other components.
So I'm going to go right here at the bottom and we're going to say export than default.
And then the name of the component that we want to share with other components.
So since our component calls Hetter we're going to say Hetter.
So now this component is going to be available from other pieces of code.
Now I'm going to save this one and we're going to begin to include that component to Hetter component
inside here inside the main components.
So I'm going to go right here I'm going to just add a comment.
I was going to say component's so right here we're going to have a list of all the components that we
need to include inside the main one the parent one.
So no how do we import that coat.
We're going to say import just like with this before import.
And then we need to put the name of what we want to import.
This case is going to be beheader so I'm going to say.
Now we say from now instead of doing Hetter just like with it right here since this is not a note module
is just one component from our application.
We need to specify the path I'm going to say Dot than then for Slash and access the components folder
for I-Slash and bring the header.
Now since Hetter it's already a javascript file there's no need to put the extension if you work with
VSS and we're going to be talking about that in a minute.
We need to use the extension.
But let's get.
So I'm going to save the application and check it right here.
So we going to get Hetter is defined but never used.
So it's whenever you have some code right here that you're not really using it's going to give you a
warning.
So it's considered bad coding having components that you're not really using.
Ok so now how do we include how do we use this Hetter component that we are importing from here.
So what we can do if I just copy this and it's happening right now and I paste it and since this is
a viral is not going to do anything is just outputting text because we are just using some text.
So just like we did before whenever we render the app we need a way to tell react to this component.
It's it's an actual component that we are importing.
So we need to enclose everything just like this.
So now re-act knows that whenever it needs to render this is going to check oh this is this one has
takk.
So this could be a component.
Let me check.
Yeah it is a component because we are importing it right here.
So if we save it we get Hetter just to make sure that we get something else.
We're going to say this is my new header.
And if I save it we get.
This is my new header.
So now we are exporting this component and we are just importing it right here and including the components
inside the parent components.
That's got you know it's working.
We're going to of course make a lot of changes right here to the header.
But for now I want to talk about something else.
So let's move forward to the next section.