So we react we can output inline dynamic content.
I know this sounds a little bit confusing but let me show you with some code.
It's real simple.
Let's say that instead of returning this is my new header I want to show the dates.
So I'm going to say the date is now right here.
I need to pass some dynamic content.
I'm going to get the date in milliseconds from javascript so I'm going to use curly braces and inside
the curly braces we can put some logic right here.
So I'm going to use vanilla Yes if sex is fine.
Sorry my little javascript I'm going to say now this is going to return to date in milliseconds.
So you finally reloaded and check it.
The date is in milliseconds.
So inside curly braces we can do pretty much whatever we want as long as we return a single statement
a single expression.
So let's say I want to print the ear.
So I'm going to just say this I'm going to make it just like this.
So it's a little bit more readable but it's the same idea.
So to return the date for the year first I need to create a variable that is going to be called new
date and this one is going to create an instance of date just like this date.
And then if you wanted to get the ear from from there you need to return the new date just like this
and Dot and get full year.
So this is again it's another Javascript.
So this is one is not going to work is going to give as an error message because you're using two different
expressions.
First we have the verbal and then we are doing the return.
So this one is not going to work.
But what we can do to solve this.
We can create a function that returns that data.
So I'm going to go over here and again to say Konst get your.
Something like that.
And then it's going to be just a fat Aro function and this fat function is going to do this logic and
it cut and paste that and we get your and this function only returns that year.
So now if I say get your just like this and I call to this function is going to give us back the ear.
So it's going to work.
So this is good.
And you can do it right here pretty much whatever you want as long as you return a single expression.
So we can do operations kind of a five plus five.
That's going to work.
We get the data Stan you know it's good we're here to get ears inside but never used.
I'm going to delete it just for now.
So why is this important.
Let's pretend that instead of Hetter we have kind of a user profile so we need we have an object of
the user with all the data inside and what we want to do we want to render the user data.
So I'm going to say Konst then user is going to be called to an object and it's going to have a name
and the name is going to be Frances of course if you if you're it's it's the first time for you in one
of my courses.
This is my main default user name it's Francis.
And the last name.
You guessed it Jones.
And let's say an age of 16.
So this is really important.
We just have an object.
So now if you want to output a card the card to every user are going to just put it just like this and
enclose everything remember everything in Princie just like that.
And now this one this dev is going to be the main container we need to.
We can only output some GSX inside a container.
And right here I can just put Dev and make a reference to that object.
It's going to be user name.
And if I wanted to get the last name.
Same thing.
User Data last name.
So this is going to be the way.
How how can we the way we output output dynamic data inside react and age.
And if we go right here we get Frances Jones and 16.
So you know this is really really simple but we're going to be using that.
Using this the whole the whole time.
So let's pretend let's just pretend that this user is going to be validating if the user is able to
access right here.
So again we can just run a function check if the user it's authorized to enter our our page or web page
our application.
And right here we get it just past True or false.
And this one is going to love the content that the page load are not going to do that later of course.
So OK let's keep moving forward.
We're going to be talking about types of components.
It's going to be really interesting.
So let's go to the next one.