So now we're going to be talking about types of components.
First I'm going to delete this because you're not going to need it.
And right here I'm going to say Hetter.
So whenever you work with re-act you have two main types of components.
You have a functional component where a class base component.
So the difference is what do you want to do with this.
That's the main difference.
And at this point this header is just a function it mind receives and arguments we will do that later.
But for now is the function returning some GSX you know something really basic.
So it's returning some static data.
Let's get.
So this is a functional component.
This component dysfunctional the functional components doesn't care much what happens with the rest
of the components.
It doesn't care what happens with index or what happens with news list or whatever is just returning
some some data some GSX.
It's like saying OK do it my job is just to send some GSX.
That's what I'm doing.
I don't care what happens with the rest of the components.
My job is just to do this so I'm going to go ahead and do it.
And that's what it's doing.
That's the main purpose of a functional component.
So on the other hand you have the class based components.
Those components are a little bit more complex.
They have the ability to know what's happening on the application and they could have a record or maybe
a record of data that could be changing inside our application.
Don't worry we going to do that a lot.
So for example our header is going to be real simple.
We'll have a logo and an input to search and filter the news.
So I'm going to write it right now.
We're going to have instead of a div you can have a header just like that.
Let me change it right here.
Header and this header is going to have logos.
I'm going to say you did and you know just logo whatever.
For now it's just real simple and they can have an impact.
So this input and me type which is going to be text and they see everything is good logo and in text.
So whenever we type something inside this input let me make this bigger whenever we type a keyboard
right here.
This header is going to connect to the news list and it's going to try to search and used a post with
the same keyboard in the title.
So we type M.B.A. right here just M.B.A. we're going to catch disvalue go to the database and rendered
that news inside news list.
So this Hetter needs a way to connect with the rest of the application.
So again this could be we need to do something else right here.
This must be a class based component because it needs to know what happens there.
There are ways to create a functional components and emulate that.
But for now we don't need to change this to a class based component.
How do we do it.
First I'm going to delete this.
You're not going to need it for now and again to leave this just like it is.
So now to create a class based components we can start with the key word class.
So this class is going to need a name so we can use the same name Hetter.
And this is creating a class Hetter is just like doing var header.
If you if you come from the east Fae world it's kind of creating an object of course they're not the
same.
We have we have a lot of more features with classes but it's just like a creating an object.
So we're creating a class with the name of Hetter and we enclose everything inside curly braces.
That's the first part.
OK.
So now the hetter this class Hetter needs to connect with the re-act application.
So what we need to do we need to do extends and then space and we need to invoke react then react.
We have on top and this re-act has a method that is going to be called component so we can say component
so whenever you use a class you need to use the render method just like with that right here with the
render it's kind of different anyways.
So to use the render method we need to again enclose everything inside render so we can say render open
and close and then inside curl the braces going to put the whole content that we want to render.
So again it's first we use the method render then we return something and it's going to be some GSX.
So again if you come from the yes Fae world this is like a lot just like creating a constructor function
and creating a method that is going to be render and then this one is going to be equal to a function
just like that.
That is going to return return some content you know something really dumb.
So this is the same idea than doing this.
Of course we have a lot more extra features with class based components that are going to be talking
about them later.
So get them going to delete this and save it.
And notice that class header and then export default.
We are exporting this class.
We go right here we get the same result.
For now we're not going to have are not going to get any difference from a functional component but
begin to do it in a minute.
So OK.
One is we can make this we can convert this to something a little bit better.
I'm going to be using ESX.
So instead of doing re-act component.
So this means that we're bringing something that calls component that it's inside react and we are importing
we act right here.
So with ESX we can make use of the structuring and we can say coma and then curly braces and I can say
components just like this.
And this is not we act it's ESX.
So with this this is going to be called destructuring and pretty much if I delete re-act component and
save it it's still going to work.
So how is this working.
Well whenever we use destructuring this is pretty much saying okay go to react and bring something that
calls component and created a variable that calls component with a value of reactor components.
So behind the scenes we don't see this this has happened happening in memory.
It's entering to react and it's saying OK graph react that components and create a variable.
So it's doing a rival that calls component some like that.
And this one is going to be equal to react maybe make it ride react that component component.
There we go.
So now whenever we again change the sea to a capital C whenever we use components right here is going
to be called to react that component is going to create an alias for this.
So delicious.
So this destructuring is going to be equal to that Varnell.
That's why we can use component right here and skip that react up components.
Of course everything is working OK.
That's good.
So we're going to be working a little bit more with this.
But first we need to add some style.
This is really really ugly.
It's really really actually going to get we going to go back to this and check which features we get
with classis.
So first begin to add some stop because it's really really ugly.
Let's go to the next one and talk about styling.