So in the re-act world there are many many ways to style our projects.
So we're going to be talking about some different methods going to show you different ways.
So first we have the inline styling with re-act we can do what we can do is create an object that looks
like a C Ss and then pass the properties to the actual element.
I know sounds kind of confusing.
I'm going to do it right now.
And by the way I've added Google fonts to our project is going to be the aunt.
Finally you can choose whatever font you wish.
It's up to you.
So I'm going to go back to the header and I'm going to create a variable that is going to be an object
and noticed that I'm doing it inside the render OK.
So I'm going to say let.
And this is of course 6 is going to create a variable.
This could be Konst.
Thus I'm going to say Konst.
So it's going to be equal to styles.
And this is style.
It's going to be an actual object.
So right here inside styles are going to add a property for the header and for the logo.
Real simple just an object notation.
So it's going to be Hetter and header is going to have several properties.
You can have background just like that and the background is going to be a color and it's going to be
called two hash tag then 0 3 a 9 4.
But now I'm going to add logo and since it's an update I'm going to do a coma and create the logo one
and logo of course it's going to have several properties you can have a color you can do something simple
a color of white.
It's going to be white one two three and then coma and I need to put the font family with standard DSS
what you do is font then style and then family.
But this is not yes that's going to be Javascript.
So we need to keep the hyphens and do it all together family family all the OK.
And that's what is going to be equal to on the phone to Google phone.
I just added.
So we're going to do coma and we can add a new property and I'm going to do text align and remember
this is javascript.
We do in camel case text align and text line is going to be center just like that.
So now how do we pass this styles to reference to this to the sex.
So what we can do we can go right here to the Petar for example and we're going to say style equals
to something since you're going to be passing object data you know javascript.
We cannot use this.
We cannot use the double quotes what are begin going to use curly braces and begin to make a reference
to that object is going to be styles.
Remember we have styles and then pass the property.
That's the one we want.
And if I reload the page you know it's working.
So I'm going to go to logo and do the same thing styles style it called to an object and it's going
to be styles dot logo.
And if you go right here we have the Anton and the logo with the center text.
Let's get you know it works.
So again you know imagine that you have tons of styles right here.
So you know you're going to have a pretty long file.
You can do an import you know of a could you could have this inside of a different javascript and then
include the variables.
Right here you could do that if you wish.
I don't really like this method because everything it's inline it's inside the actual elements.
And you know I like it.
So what we could do.
Let me just delete this.
You're not going to need it for now.
Sorry.
I'm going to leave it so I can copy it.
Remove the heterostyled and then remove the one in the logo.
So what we could do we could do it the old fashioned way we can.
We can put a link inside the index to a real CSSA file.
So I'm going to go to public and I'm going to create a new folder that it's going to be.
Now let's create a new file.
Let me show you why in a minute it's going to be styles going to call it styles not us.
So this stylus is going to have a stylus of course.
So first going out of body to remove the margin the ugly margin that we get by default with with you
now.
OK so I'm going to say margined zero.
Then of course the header and on the head are if you remember we have text a line background.
Sorry.
So I'm going to copy it from here.
That's why I left it.
Background and the background is going to be the color I'm going to do text align and then Center.
What else.
We have the logo so I'm going to create a class with logo and then the logo is going to be color of
white then koma font size font size and the font size is going to be I don't know 40 pixels.
Sounds good.
What else.
We have the really get to do fun family and it's going to be on time.
Very good.
Now we have the input so I'm going to add styles for the impot going to be using this later.
That's why I'm doing it right now.
It's going to be head or input.
And I'm going to add some font size something really simple.
So we don't waste too much time then we could have a margin.
Let's add a margin of 20 pixels and then zero pixels from the side.
Let's get it.
So now how do how do we include this.
You know we are inside the public folder.
So everything you have in public is going to go to the real world is going to go to production.
Let's say so right here what I can do I can just add a reference to that idea.
Yes.
So we say link a draft and then we pastilles that CSSA just like that.
And of course I'm going to do the role just to make things right.
And then we do stylesheet of course style sheet and we load the application.
We are kind of getting it you're not getting the background C-y.
It's because I forgot to remove this.
So you know let's get that's the old fashioned way.
Now there is a different way and a lot of developers like they like to do this.
I don't really like it but you know you could use it.
I'm going to leave this right here the logo we need to add a class.
Remember we add a class right here to logo.
So we are not going to use class but we use class name.
And this one is going to be called to a logo.
And if we reloaded we get the content.
That's good.
So what you can do.
You can import that CSSA right here on the javascript and then whenever you are the web pack it's compiling
all the information it's going it's going to include that javascript.
I'm sorry that CSSA inside the blue.
So how do we import it.
This is real simple.
I'm going to say import just like that import.
The thing is here comes the problem.
You cannot import files from when the public folder the only files that you can import might hear that
pack is going to let you import are going to be you know they need to be inside the source father.
So if I do public it's not kind of let me.
So let me let me just show you.
Going to say we're going to open up right here single quotes and we're not importing Javascript.
So whenever we import CSSA we do import and then we pass the location of that file.
So right here we're inside indexed.
So I'm going to say that that forward slash and are going to go to that that forward slash and go to
public folder and the public is going to bring the styles that CSSA just like that you're getting out
of the index entering the public and bring in CSX.
And right here it's going to say you attempt to import public styles he assess which which falls outside
the project's source directory.
So you know we cannot do this we can bypass and just trying to modify things but we're not going to
do that.
What I'm going to do I'm going to just have to see a just create a new folder inside here that is going
to be called CSX and right here going it just grab the styles and put it inside the source.
So I got to go back to Hetter and instead of doing this we just delete it.
We're going to say that for Slash we're going to go into SS for Slash and we're going to bring this
dials Nazi SS and if we reload this it's going to work.
That's going to work.
Now what is the downside of this if you consider this as a downside of course.
Whenever we do the application LOTES the pack is going to convert everything is going to transpire everything
and it's going to give you that Mandola.
Yes.
But in addition you're passing an import.
So this information this into the C Ss is going to get compiled with the import with the bundle and
the bundle is going to inject the CSSA inside the DOM.
So if we take a look right here we have it inside the header.
Everything gets injected right here.
So let's say you have I don't know three different CSSA style sheets with a lot of code.
A lot of CSSA styles.
They're going to get injected into the DOM.
So again a lot of developers likes like this.
I don't like it that much.
But again it's just up to you.
So we have more things with stylings but we can do a lot of tricks with styles.
But the thing is that this tricks we need to use this tricks along with some options with classes and
with all the things that begin to be using with react.
But we are not there yet.
So I'm not going to show you.
Right now we can wait until we know what else we can do with classes and we'd react and then we to bring
kind of styles sections advanced something like that.
So let's keep moving forward on the next section.
Going to be talking about events and it's going to be really really interesting.