So one of the most important things when we work with applications just like re-act are going to be
events you know when the user clicks on something or maybe they enter some text inside an input or maybe
when they are on something.
So let's say that whenever the user clicks on the logo I want to get something I want to get that event.
And you know do a console log.
So OK first we need to be taught we need to talk about handlers or the events you know just like we
did with vanilla jacks.
We have events that we can listen.
In this case with vanilla it's going to be on and then click just like that.
But with that react it's a little bit different.
It's going to be on an income case click just like that.
This one it's not going to work because it's vanilla jazz but this one is going to work because it's
react now.
If you don't know what vanilla jazz is it's going to be the raw javascript not the ESX but the previous
version.
That's good.
So now I want to add this event to the logo whenever they click the logo.
I went to get something.
So I'm going to go right here make some space so we can read it a little bit better and get it started
with the on camera case because we act and click.
Now this one.
What I want to do.
I want to trigger something.
So I'm going to use the curly braces.
Now I'm going to make use of a fat arrow function.
This is just a function.
That's what it is.
Just a function.
And when the user clicks on something I want to do a console log of I was clicked.
Simple as that.
Now if I go to the browser and click the logo I get I was clicked.
And if I click it again of course I'm going to get it several times.
So ok that works.
So this fat Aro function is just like a reference to the same function we have inside.
It's like writing a function that calls click.
And then of course if we call it we call it in one one point of the application it's going to get triggered
with the consul lock inside.
Now same thing let me go back.
So now what I want to do instead of us just triggering the function right here.
I want to go first I want to show you some magic.
Is this ESX magic.
If you have a fat Aro function and we have only a single expression just like here with one log.
In this case we can get rid of the curly braces and this is still going to work.
He has six magic power.
OK.
So that's fine.
Let's go to the next part what I want to do instead of just triggering this function right here.
I want to pass a reference to a function.
I don't want to trigger it here.
I want to have a different function inside of the class and trigger that function.
Whenever we do the unclick.
OK.
So I'm going to delete all of this.
We're not going to need it.
So what I want to do I want to pass a reference to a function.
So first I'm going to create my function I'm going to say input and then change.
Now then this is a convention.
A lot of people use handler for this whenever they use an event they use handler as a keyword.
And again it's a convention if you want to skip this.
That's good.
I'm just going to leave it.
So whenever we call this function we want to console log console clock and we do.
I was correct.
Simple as that.
So now what we need to do we need to pass a reference inside the unclick to this outside function.
And notice that this function it's inside of the class.
So if I do input handler just like that it's not going to work.
It says impot change handler.
It's not mine.
So the thing is that whenever we use a function we need to invoke a function.
We need to pass the where this function is going to be inside the component inside the class.
So to make a reference to it we need to say this.
This means declasse.
So it's going to say this.
The class and it's going to enter class and try to find the function that calls input and input change
handler.
That's what's what's happening right here.
So I'm going to save it and I'm going to test it.
Now if I click we get I was click.
That's very good.
You know same thing same result.
So now the thing is that we need to do this inside of the of the input not the logo.
So I'm going to delete the on click on the logo and I'm going to just go back what we want to do.
Our goal is to get whatever the user types inside the input.
So OK I'm going to go right here and I'm going to call the imp in the onchange.
It's going to be on change.
It's going to be a different event.
Not unclick but on change.
So now we need a function that is going to be catching the values.
OK.
So instead of input a click could be interchanged just like here.
So we're going to make a reference to this function.
It's going to be this dot and imprint input change handler.
That's good.
And if I say I was changed that makes more sense.
It type something and we get I was changed.
And if I keep typing things every time we enter or we change the input we get the event that's good.
So now what we need to do we need to pass the actual events so we can get the value just like vanilla
jazz.
So whenever we use an event by default we have the event right here.
So if I go around here and say event the first argument it's going to be the actual events event.
Now if I do cancel logged in the event we're going to get a lot of things.
So all of this does an event.
So I'm going to type Panay and we can get an object and this are all the events that we have available
for us to use.
Now the thing is that whenever we type something we need to get the value of what the user is typing.
And this is going to be inside event and target.
You can go right here.
So we have the event and we're going to say Dot target dot and then value just like Nilgiris and I get
to say and we get a f. we get F..
Let me type Francis and you know for each each word each character you're getting a council.
So you know that's working.
That works really nice.
So this aren't events but this are not the usual events.
We know this art called synthetic synthetic events and they are from react Mikko's right here and again
to say re-act than darks and then events and we get it right here synthetic event.
So this events are from react.
React is handling the events for us and not the actual browser just like we did in the past.
So if we go we scroll a little bit down we can have supported events and right here you can have a list
of all the events in this case keyboard events form events whatever events you can think of.
They just have it so you can check the docs and inspect a little bit of this documentation and know
which events you can get and maybe you can play a little bit with these events on the document.
You can do that.
OK.
So I'm going to just possibly DIOSA.
I'm going to go get a coffee.
Come right back and I will I will suggest you do the same thing.
I'm going to be talking about two three or four minutes about something that most people get complicated
with this most of the people get confused with this.
So what possibly deal and be right back.
Right.
So I want to talk about a few things.
I've made some courses not just to you to me but in my country and other places and pretty much all
students have the same question.
And this has got to do with the usage of this right here this so I'm going to start explaining some
Thanks and this are not related to react to this more as five or six related.
So if you're a master of javascript you can move along.
No problem.
If not just please please stay and watch this if not later.
You're going to have some problems.
I'm going to get confused with some things because of course it is.
It is really confusing.
So first I'm going to change the input change handler.
I'm going to give you an example.
Just going to come in the console lock and we're going to say cancel that log and then I went to get
a hey whenever I type something.
So if I go right here to our application I'm going to type something and we get hey several times that
you know that that works.
Now instead of doing that I'm going to go to the project right now and I'm going to add this I to add
parentheses.
So this is pretty much the same thing.
We are just invoking the function Simpang.
So if I go right here let me reload the page.
You know we are not typing anything but we're still getting Hey whenever the page loads.
So a lot is happening now whenever we use it like this we add the parentheses.
We are practically saying to react that whenever you render this this section this piece of code I want
you to immediately run this function.
So that's why whenever we remove this we are just making a reference to this function and not triggering
the onchange it's calling the function for us.
OK.
Now let me go right here and put the parenthesis.
So in theory if we just trigger the function I'm going to say cancel log on come in this one and we
need to cancel the event.
The target that Bhante.
And you know if it's empty we are not passing anything it's empty.
The target the value should be empty but now we're going to get cannot read properly target undefined
The thing is that whenever we don't have the parenthesis the on change it's binding the event to this
function.
So we have the event available because the onchange is doing this for us.
But whenever we trigger the function manually We didn't have any events.
It's the the arguments right here are empty.
So this event doesn't exist.
So you're calling to write here to a property that doesn't exist so we can be get can we property target
of undefined.
You know Diwan use undefined.
So how can we fix this.
So this is going to look really really weird going to put it right here because it's a little bit long
one second ago.
So how can we fix this.
I'm going to put a space and I'm going to pass a fat R-OH function.
This fact our function is going to have the arguments of the event and then when I call the function
I'm going to pass the event right here.
OK so let me come with the console OK let's try again.
I'm going to type Francis and you know it works.
It's still working.
So how can this work.
And the other thing too.
Well this is got to do with with nested functions it's more.
Yes.
Five or six.
Let me give you an example with the S-5.
You can get a real really quick.
First I'm going to have a function that is going to be one function one whatever.
So the one is going to take the argument of a name going to be passing a name to this function then
you're going to have function to add this function to it's going to have the same arguments.
And then what I want to do I want to trigger the function to pass a name.
So this function instead of doing the console log isn't going to call the function one and it's going
to pass.
The name argument which is going to be Frances and now of the function one it's in charge of doing the
console log.
So I'm going to say cancel a log and then just name.
If I reload the page we get Francis so that it's working.
You know real simple this is.
Yes fine.
Very good.
So the same thing is happening right here.
Whenever we call the unchanged disk on change it's calling to a function.
The first function right here and it's passing the event as an argument and this function it's calling
a different function and it's passing the event right here.
You know this is the.
Right here the two it's the this one outside and this one is the function one.
So whenever we call this we pass the end with that we have on the on the function to that we get from
the change.
And this of course works now.
Same thing.
It works really good.
So OK that's the problem.
You know it it's not that hard when you see it like this with the S-5 But just like this.
All trimmed.
It's get a little bit hard to understand.
Let's get up let's get we have a few more weird things with this.
At some point of course you can see something that says bind this but we're not there yet.
We're going to begin to do something else with buying this.
OK.
Whenever we get to that problem I would explain why we're doing by buying this and why we are not doing
bind this.
So let's keep moving forward on the next section.
We're going to be talking about the six constructor.