All right.
So this section is going to be pretty much about the sixth constructor and classes.
That's not strictly related to react.
It's not from re-act it's directly from ESX.
Now if you know E6 classes like the palm of your hand you just can move forward no problem.
So I've created a new file is going to be called Playground digests an included data file inside index
that you mail.
So I'm going to start doing the things I'm going to say class and I'm going to click create a class
of for car.
At first you're not going to get it.
But you know just keep moving forward.
You're going to get it at the end.
Don't worry.
So right here I get to say I'm going to create a method for this.
Is going to say Alert brand whatever.
And this brand is going to just be a function that it's going to be doing a lock for hay.
So now we have a class with a meth inside now what I want to do I need to create an instance of this
car so I can use the method alert brand.
So I'm going to go right here I'm going to say car is going to be equal to new and then car.
This is just like constructor functions in iOS 5.
So if I want to output to trigger that function I'm going to say Alert brand.
And if we go to the browser we get hey.
Good.
So let me change it to Ford so he can make us make a little bit more sense for it.
Very good.
So now what happens if I need a new class and I want to inherit some of the properties we have right
here.
OK.
So I'm going to add that the large brand and now with constructor's constructor function we can add
methods inside of the prototype of this constructor function.
You know that's classic is fine.
So with ESX going to do the things a little bit different.
So we can just say constructor and inside the constructor we can have all the properties of this car
are going to say this because this means the car of course and then wheels something like that and it's
going to be equal to four.
And then we're going to have this dot and then type and this type is going to be a hatchback.
Never had a hatchback.
It's going to do she but you know you can like them good.
So now this car has a constructor inside of the prototype of this class.
You can have this virga.
So now what I want to do I went to create a new class and inherit this options.
So I'm going to go to class and I get to create a class A it.
I'm going to open and close.
Now how can I inherited this inside here.
So we're going to be using the keyword extends just like we did with the constructor with the components.
Well same idea.
I'm going to say extents and then space and then car just like that car.
So now these properties are inside and available of Ford we are inheriting the car inside Ford.
So if I create a new instance of Ford it's going to be equal to new forward.
Of course you know Ford and then I do cons. look for the wheels that we don't have right here.
But since we are inheriting the car we have access to the wheels.
I'm going to say cancel that law and then say Ford Dadds wheels.
And if we go we get four.
OK let's get.
So with extents we are inheriting whatever it's inside the construction of a different class.
OK.
That's good.
Now what happens if I need to add a constructor inside car.
I'm going to say constructor opening close.
And for now I'm going to say this that I don't know Windows something like that and it's going to be
equal to four.
And right here.
Notice that I'm doing Ford wheels and if I go right here to the browser you're getting must call super
constructor endured class.
OK so what is the problem.
We are adding a constructor right here and we're still inheriting all the constants of car.
So the thing is that you're creating a constructor function that it's empty.
So we need a way to instruct the constructor that we did it extents and we want to add whatever options
we have on car and we need to add it to the disk constructor.
So what we do is we use the keyword super.
So I'm going to say super and just super and then Super just like this.
Oh sorry I'm gonna look at this for now.
So we are calling super and then super is going to bring whatever we are bringing from extents and put
it inside of the are over for it.
So if I go right here we get four.
So that's the main purpose of super.
You're bringing whatever you are extending and putting it inside the constructor of this class.
Good.
OK.
You know a lot of logic and you're probably saying Dude what this has to do with re-act this 06 got
nothing to do with that.
Well on the next lecture we're going to be talking about state and a few more things and we're not going
to directly use it but you're going to see it on a lot of places.
So remember that when it where when whenever we were on Hetter we create a class that extends component.
So this component comes from a react and react class.
So right here whenever we create a class for our our project we are extending a lot of properties and
method that the the date re-act class has.
So something like when we go right here this one is going to be called react just like that.
And then inside the constructor we have something that is called props some like that and props is going
to be an object with a lot of things inside.
Whatever MiddleEast this.
So then we begin to create a new begin to create a new class of something for example a new page and
this new page is going to be extending react.
So whenever we call the constructor we get all the properties and method from the parent class which
is react and of course we can do a lot of things just like we are doing right here.
That's the main purpose of the class.
Now classes are really important and but but they're kind of heavy.
So we always need to try to avoid classes.
We will talk about this in the next few lectures for now as soon as you get what we are doing with the
constructor and probs and everything else.
That's good.
A little bit more about classes.
You know we now know a little bit more about classes.
OK that's good.
Let's go to the next section and we're going to be talking about state and state.
It's really really important for us.
So let's keep move forward.