OK so now we going be talking about state and for re-act state it's kind of important.
So there's no easy way to understand this.
And if you don't completely get it don't worry.
We're going to use it the whole time so you can get it by practice.
So the state it's an object that serves us like a database so we can be can stored values we can check
for events you can pretty much control how the application behaves through state.
So remember we talked about functional components and class based components.
Well every time we create a class just like this one we have right here we get by default from re-act
a default state.
And if we have a functional component not like this one we don't have the ability to get a default state.
The functional components don't have state and they are stateless.
And you're going to hear that term a lot stateless but classes classmates based components have a state.
So how can we set a state.
So I'm going to say state just like this.
Just use the keyword state and this one is going to be equal to.
And we open and close an object.
So right here we can put whatever we want to say keyboard's just like an object and keywords is going
to start with.
Hello.
OK.
So the class starts.
We're going to set a default value for keywords inside the state.
So inside the render what I could do I can do a console log of this that state that keyboards just like
this.
So when the application starts it's going to recognize the state that's going to read the function and
then it's going to do the render.
And we can get the keyboards.
Hello.
So we get hello.
That's good.
But if you notice this is just it looks like an object.
So what's the difference between in between using this state and a regular object.
The thing is that if we change the state re-act is going to recognize that you're changing the state.
And since this is a special property it's going to render the application is going to say Oh OK.
So the dude changed the state.
So I'm going to re render the application because now for this keyboards we have a new Ballew.
That's the main idea of state.
So I'm going to commandeer the console and right here instead of doing the console log from the change
handler you know if I type something we are not getting anything on the console.
I want to change the state.
So in theory if I changed the state every time I type something on the input this render should render
again and we can get the new state of keywords.
So to set States we need to use a pretty fine method.
We need to use a special method but re-act is going to give us is going to be this dot and we use the
set state and of course Methot inside we need to pass an object.
And now we need to make a reference of whatever value we want to change.
So we are going to say keyboard's now every time we type something keyboard's is going to be equal to
event the target value which is equal to whatever we are typing right here.
So I'm going to copy this and paste it down here.
Now if I type something we're going to get an error.
And remember I told you about the bind property.
OK.
I'm going to use it right now and at the end of the section I can explain why I'm using bind and then
this.
So the application reloads.
So if I type something is going to go to the change handler This is when it's going to set the state.
And since you're setting a new state the application is going to read render.
OK.
So I'm going to type an F and we are getting the value it's doing this cancel.
So he's doing the render again.
Let me make this a little bit smaller.
Not like that.
There we go.
So right now if I type something else f a and this console log it's doing the FAA.
If I type on our air on our sorry.
We're getting far.
OK that's good.
So every time we type something and we set the state react we renders it's not reloading the page is
just rendering the.
This piece of code.
Good.
OK.
So now let me explain you a little bit about the scientists.
OK so let me explain you what the mind is doing right here.
So we are.
Let me just first delete this and see that error message again.
I'm going to type a name and we're getting cannot read properly set state of undefined.
OK.
We're just invoking we are calling this function whenever we make an odd change.
That's good.
So it's going to go all the way to the top.
Inside the function and it's going to say this.
Now whenever we use a function just like this whenever we make a reference to this it's not going to
be declasse.
It's not the class header is going to be this function.
So whenever we use bind does we're telling that function that whenever we are saying this and this function
we are saying that whenever we use this keyboard inside of the function.
This means the actual class you know means the parent component and not the actual function.
That's why we're doing bind this.
So we're telling that whenever we use this inside of the function it means the class.
So since the class has the said State method we didn't get an error message it's working because the
said state it is defined.
OK so now the thing is that you're going to crawl the Web maybe in the future you're going to see some
other examples of react and you're going to find this on a different way.
You're not going to see the bind this and you're not going to understand why.
So I'm going the mind is.
And of course it's not going to work again.
So what can we use we can to use a fat Aro function instead of a function.
Now with iOS 6 the fat Aro functions are really really smart.
They know that whenever you make a reference to this you're meeting the class and not the actual the
actual function.
So if I just check again it's going to work.
So this is working.
So in the future you should avoid using bind and use the new method which is going to be a arrow function
bind.
It's from the old call.
You can still use it for a few other things.
But if you can use a find arrow function that it's better.
Now I'm telling you this again because you're going to find some examples with mind and you're not going
to know what to do if you don't know this.
OK so what's next next.
All the things that you can find inside the Web is going to be something like this you're going to find
a constructor then inside you can have a super And then inside you can have the set state just like
this and inside it instead of a state you're going to find this that state.
So OK.
And inside here I'm going to have something like probably going to be talking about props in a minute.
Don't worry.
So if I try this something like this it's still going to work.
So what this is doing and this is related to the previous section with when we were when we spoke about
IOS 6 constructor.
So this class it's starting and we are extending component and right here we are creating our own constructor
and right here we are bringing whatever prompts whatever values we get from components.
And this case prompts and then we are setting a new property for this constructor.
So we are adding this state to the prototype.
Now the thing is that whenever you react the state it's already on the prototype of whatever you are
extending.
So there's no need to do set state.
So I was I use this a lot in the past and I'm not using it right now not just using it a lot it's because
state it's already defined inside the components.
It's already in size so there's no need to do the constructor unless you really need for some reason.
So if we type this it's going to work.
So you can manage and you can use state for whatever you want.
I'm going to delete the hello I'm going to leave the key words empty and I can add a title just like
this.
Let's say that whenever the application loads you want to have some content text right here that maybe
it's going to come from a database.
So this title is maybe the key words something like that something really dumb.
The keywords are common.
So instead of of course coma because this is an object.
So instead of putting right here maybe creating a div that says the title is whatever you're going to
just call this that.
Probs sorry not prop's this state and that title just like that and this is going to print whatever
you have inside the state it of course if the state changes the application is going to render and you're
going to have that does that state just like that this state and then keyboard's.
And whenever I type something we renderers type anay type something is going to rerun under anti-body
and so on and so on.
So no state it's really useful for us.
But the thing is that whenever you use state it's kind of a it's going to be a little bit harder to
maintain.
So you should always avoid using class components with states because they use more memory and they
are hard to maintain if you can use a functional components if you can use a functional component that's
better.
No that's less code and less logic for you or for your application but of course it's not bad using
class components.
If you really need it you can use it.
No problem but you always try to think a little bit more about what you're going to do and what you
need instead of using a class or instead of using a functional component.
OK that's good.
Let's keep moving forward.
Remember I said props right here.
And then I made a mistake saying this that prompts well on the next section we're going to be talking
about props.