OK so now we could be talking about props.
But first I'm going to do a few things.
I'm going to go to the header dodgiest and I'm going to delete the title state because we don't need
it to delete the cancel log.
You're not going to eat it.
And then we are going to delete the dips right here.
And of course to cancel right here we're going to save it.
And if I check it now everything works that's good.
So now I'm going to go to index Yes and what I want to do I want to bring the news and went to bring
a file some Jason data that it's going to be the news.
Right here we're going to have the news.
So first US Prosit project resource is said this section resource I've added a DVD.
Jason so you can download it download the file and put it inside the source.
We're going to be using it right now.
So this DVD that Jason is going to contain just a few Jason data with and the title of which is going
to be the title of the news.
And then just to feed with some some larm Epsom.
So what are we going to do.
We're going to fetch this DVD that Jason and then we can pass it to a different place so we can render
the news first.
We need to fetch Jason.
So I'm going to go right here and I'm going to say import Jaison from.
And then we bring it from Dodd forward slash D-B the Jason.
And remember that we are inside the source but so now this DVD that Dasen is going to be converted to
to an object.
So what we can do.
I'm going to say console log and we're going to say Jaison.
And if we check it on the console we have the objects.
So now what we need to do we need to grab all this information and pass it to the different component
which is going to be the news list.
But first inside the up the app right here what I wanted to use is going to be a class based component.
So this one it's a stateless functional component.
I went to change that.
So first I'm going to delete this.
I'm going to say class and then it's going to have the same name and then extends just like we did before.
I'm doing this right now because now we know how a class based component works and that we can use state
so we can do it right now and extents and then components and open close are going to leave the console
to Jason and remember that whenever we use a class we can just return something.
We need to use the render method open close and then we put everything inside of this
OK I'm going to save it.
And of course nothing works component.
It's not to find we're calling component right here but we're not bringing bringing the component from
react just like we did before.
So you can just copy this and bring the component coma and then components.
And if we reload everything still works just fine right here.
Jason is defined but never used.
We're going to use it right now.
So what we need to do we need to pass this Jason data to a different component which is going to be
the news list.
We didn't have a component inside the news list.
So we're going to do it right now.
I'm going to say import re-act from and then react of course.
And this is always the same motion you need to port something.
So a good advice for me just I'm going to give you an advice right now.
It's going to be having a template or having some snippets because you're going to be typing this manually
every time you do a project.
I'm doing it right now because I'm giving you a course some explaining what to do.
So I need to type everything but in real life you can have snippets.
OK.
So we're going to create this component and this component for now is going to be a stateless component.
So I'm going to say Konst functional component and this.
This one is going to be called newsiest.
So I'm going to say use list just like that.
And this way it's going to be equal.
It's going to be equal to a function Burguet.
So this one whenever we call this one is going to return some GSX and this GSX for now is just going
to be a dev with news list whatever.
So now we need to make this component available inside other components.
So if you remember we need to say export than default and then use list just like that.
OK.
So this component it's ready to be included inside all their components but first we need to call them.
So we're going to put a right here to say import import and then we're going to be importing news list
just like that.
And then from and then we do DOD forward slash components for was slash and use list.
So now just like we did with Hetter if I include this news list right here use list and we close it.
In theory we should be getting useless.
And that's what we are getting.
So this works just fine.
Now the thing is that I'm fetching a Jason right here.
And what I want to do whenever a fetch does Jason I want to store it inside the state of app.
You know this app.
So OK so I'm going to go right here and I'm going to say state and the state is going to be equal to
an object.
So now I'm going to create a new property that is going to be news and use is going to be called to
day sign just like that Jay song.
Again if we do cancel the blog just to make sure that everything works council lock we have the Jason
and the news available inside the state of this app.
So we say does that state that new and in theory we should be getting the logs so we get it.
Let's get to.
Everything works fine.
Now the problem and it's the main point of this section is to pass the news to pass the Jasen to a different
component.
And in this case it's going to be useless.
So we need a way to pass this.
And this is going to be called prompts and it's very important just like the state we can pass data
between components using props.
How can we do it.
Well first inside this reference to the components I'm going to say news and this could be whatever
you want it doesn't matter.
Could be could be news could be donkey.
You can you can do it whenever you want.
So I'm going to call it news because of course it makes sense.
I'm going to say news and then opening close curly braces.
So right here we need to specify what we need to pass to this component.
So what we need to pass is going to be does that state that news.
And let me make this smaller.
There's the state that news.
So this is going to pass the decent data to the news list.
So now inside the news list how can we catch this information.
Well this information is going to be passed to this component which is it's just a function inside the
arguments.
So whenever you create a component you have some information available called prompts just like that.
And it's and you get this prompts by default whenever you use react with any component any type of component
if you use a stateless component a functional component just like this.
You can get some props if you're going to use a class based component.
You're going to get some props too.
You always get the props.
That's the one of the key features of react.
So in theory if I go right here at the bottom and say console log and then counsel log whatever information
I have inside prompts just prompts and go right here I'm going to get it and notice that this one this
one is kind of different is giving me an object with some news.
And inside the news they use property.
I have my news good.
So you know you get a lot of information.
What happens if I want to pass something else.
Not just news what I can pass is say donkey and donkey just like that donkey.
And it's going to be equal to me whatever.
And then I get to go to news list and of course we get a new object from the consulate prompts an inside
probably have news and we have dunky So in theory what we can do since we have that information inside.
Probst I can say console log and then prompts and then instead of a user you can say donkey donkey.
So we get me OK no that's good.
It's really really awesome if you think about it.
We can do a lot of thanks for this.
We are just passing a lot of data and we can catch that that data inside prompts and right here of course
we can use this prompts that Dunky.
Let me go right here.
We use the curly braces and we make a reference to props and Dunky.
So if we go below the page we get me.
OK.
So you know really really really easy to use.
We pass props and then we use it.
So now what we need to do and begin to go to the next section right now we need to create some markup
for this.
Grab the props bring the news of course it's not going to happen right here because we have an object.
So it's not going to display it.
Objects are not valid as a react child.
You cannot pass some object inside the return Sunia the Jason the I'm sorry the object data is not valid.
GSX so I was going to give you a fat error message.
So we need to do something else right here.
So let's go to the next section and check how can we render how we are going to be able to render this
news object.