All right.
So now we have the data inside props and that news and this is going to be an array of objects.
So now we need a way to loop this array of objects coming from props and display data right here.
So first I'm going to just remove this from here.
I'm just going to say items for now.
And OK I'm going to go right here at the top and it can create a viable that is going to be called items.
So this verbal is going to be looping whatever information we get from prop's the news.
So I'm going to first begin to be X accessing prop's then we're going to say Dot and I'm going to access
news because you know the data it's inside there.
And then since we have an array of objects are going to be using map and you're going to be using map
the whole time.
This could be your best friend.
So OK.
So now what we need to do we need to pass whatever we want to loop which is this.
And in each iteration we're going to pass an item.
Now I'm going to say item.
Now if you have a news pleural where you can say is new or whatever but you know there's no Singler
of news.
So for now I'm going to say item and this this is going to be an anonymous function.
Now on each iteration that on each key that we find inside prop's news each object begin to run an iteration.
If we check the Jason Jason that we have right here we have four different news.
So this loop is going to loop four times and in each iteration is get it past the item.
The first iteration is going to pass the first one.
The second one the third two is one and the other one this one and this going to this is going to be
ESX.
This is not react.
So now on each direction we pass the item.
So what we can do we can return some GSX going to say return opening close just like that.
So now inside the return remember that whenever we use data sets we need to pass a single element.
And this one is going to be each item of news.
So first thing going to add a title the title it needs a title.
If we go to the DVD that Jason we have the title right here.
OK.
I'm going to go right here and bring the title now.
On each iteration we have each element inside item.
So what we can do we can say item dot and then title just like that.
And if we go right here of course we're not getting anything.
So now what do we need to do is to pass the feed.
So I'm going to create a viable that is going to be I'm sorry a div that is going to pass the actual
feed.
So I'm going to say item and then feed.
OK.
Of course nothing is going to happen.
So now this Barville is doing all the logic rendering some markup with the title and the feed.
This is what we need.
So now what we can do inside the return we can make a reference to this Vrable.
So we're going to go right here and enclose everything inside curly braces.
OK.
And re-act is going to do the job for us is going to notice that we have something that calls items
is going to find the items and this item it's items this verbal it's returning some GSX So it's going
to go and paste and put the GSX inside here.
You know it works.
Everything works really nice.
So this map again it's C-s ESX and it's kind of doing kind of a for loop.
It's actually a loop of course but it's kind of a doing I equals zero if you come from the yes world
than I is less than our array that lang.
You know all the logic that we used to do back in the day plus plus And then inside begin to access
each array.
And then of course we passed the iteration and then we passed the item.
And in this case we wanted to get the title we say title.
So this is the same logic than this one.
You're not going to use that you're going to be using iOS 6 because iOS 6 is awesome and begin to be
using it the whole time.
OK so this works we still need to do a few things.
If you remember we are using news list item so this should be rendered inside use list item on each
item.
So let's go to the next section and see how to include that include this code inside news list item.