OK so we are rendering all the items.
But the thing is that we have one component right here use list item that needs to grab this information
and show each news each post.
So we need to do that right now.
First we don't have anything inside news list items so we need to create a component for this.
So first I'm going to do import I'm sorry import react.
Yes react from.
And then of course we need to bring it from react right go.
So now we're going to create a functional component because we don't need classes right here.
We don't need to state it's going to be Konst.
And then of course it's going to be equal to news something that makes sense.
News item.
OK.
So this news item is going to be equal to a function just like this and this function is going to be
rendering something.
So we're going to say render Oh sorry not render return.
So this news item is going to receive the props that begin to be passing from the parent component which
is going to be on your list.
So this return for now is going to be just death.
And what I want to do I want to console log the prompts that we're going to pass just to check that
everything works OK.
OK.
So now we need to make this component available from other components.
So we're going to say export the font and then news item.
So this one it's kind of a rating right now.
So we need to import this useless item inside here inside US list.
OK.
So I'm going to bring it just like we did before.
I'm going to say import and the name was news news item and we're going to bring this one from from.
And then we're going to bring it from Dot.
Forward slash and use this item just like that.
So now instead of passing this I'm just going to cut this and paste it right here at the bottom and
common this out to be going to be using it later.
So instead of passing some data what I can do I can make a reference we can make a reference to this
new list item and we can pass on each iteration the actual item.
So are going to be returning one single element on each iteration.
So we're going to go right here and we're going to say news item.
Okay.
Let me close it like this.
So this news item is going to go to the news list.
It's going to for example read the first iteration.
It's going to go to a news item.
It's going to go to this file and it's going to pass it as props.
So if we look a lot of the props we can see that we have four different objects so we calling it four
times.
No we are constantly we are doing the console of Propst But of course Propst it's still empty.
So if we go back to the news this can pass the props.
Now we can choose whatever name we wish to say item makes sense.
The item is going to be equal to item just like this.
So now this news item this item is going to be inside props.
So we check props we have four different props on four different iterations and on each one we have
different data.
First one is going to be the ID number one two three and four.
Okay that's good.
So now what we can do we can grab this this inside Propst and we can make a reference to what we are
whenever we're doing great here at the bottom.
You know we are exporting we are rendering some templates so it can get cut and paste it inside the
return.
Make this a little bit nicer.
So now we're going to get an error message fades Kampar item it's not fine.
And it's because item it is not defined item.
It's not inside item.
We're not using a map right here.
You're just passing the data inside prompts.
So what we need to do we need to make first a reference to Propst and then item and then again prompts
that item and it's going to reload the page a few seconds on the Internet it's a little bit slow.
And OK we're getting it.
OK that's good.
So now we're going to get a different error message and begin I'm sorry.
Let's go back.
We can make this a little bit better.
Instead of using prompts when I can do I can bring the item and instead of doing prompts that item you
can say like before item and it's still going to work.
So what is happening right here what what I'm doing.
So this is going to be ESX is going to be called.
It's called destructuring.
It's the same idea that we're doing right here at the top beer we have access to a big object and we
are say OK I did from that big object.
We only need components so bring me components.
So we're doing the same thing right here from prop's which is the argument that we're getting.
I want to just get the item and right here we make a reference to that same idea.
OK.
So we got an error message is going to say each child in array or iterator should have a unique key
or Propp.
Now this is from re-act now.
Whenever you work with a map or maybe some iterator oil Luper or whatever you want to call it you need
to pass a key on each element on each iteration.
If you return this element this element needs to have a key.
Now a key is going to be an ID.
And this from react.
You can pass whatever key you wish as long as this is not repeated.
So I'm going to say key and it's going to be equal to and then curly braces if you remember inside to
give you the Jasen for each news each post.
We have a different ID.
One two three and four.
So what we can do we can pass the key of that.
So we are going to say item that ID and the error goes away a little bit slow today.
OK the error goes away.
Let's get.
So remember to always add the key if not react is going to is going to give you that error message.
OK.
So that's good.
So let's go to the next section.
I want to talk about something else that is kind of related to props.
Let's go.
Let's go to the next section and talk about the children of props.