OK so now I want to talk about something that is small but it could be really really useful.
So right here we have only three different components.
I'm sorry four components the index the news list and this list it's calling the news list item.
So now I'm going to do this I'm going to just code something and then I can explain you what's going
on.
I'm going to this.
This was the news list right here.
It's a self-closing tack.
I'm not going to do this.
I'm going to go right here at the bottom and I'm going to say Newsless I'm not going to pass a self-closing
task any longer and a reload that will reload us.
So it's loading again.
You know we get the same result.
It's still going to work.
OK.
So now what I'm going to do I'm going to say hello dudes whatever some passing a text and putting a
text inside the news list.
And if we checked right here we don't have that text.
So whenever we call this component we are passing some props right here.
So whenever whatever information we put inside here you know inside the TAC is going to be passed as
props as well.
So if I go right here of course we didn't have access to that information because we are not calling
it.
But if I go right here at the top and say prompts I make reference to this prompts right here and I'm
going to say Dot and I'm going to use a very special keyword.
It's a reserved key word is going to be children.
And we go right here at the top case loading it's a little bit slow.
Wait for it.
OK there we go.
So now you're getting.
Hello doods.
OK.
So this works.
Whatever information we put inside the tag it's going to be passed as Probst.
And then children and this is just some dumb text that we can put whatever we wish we can put.
For example an H3 taxation the news are whatever.
And then of course this is going to be passed as props right here.
And we are accessing through prop's the children you can put whatever color you like.
This can be like a thousand cold thousand lines of code doesn't matter it's going to still be passed
as props.
And even though you're passing attack like H3 or dev it's not going to be rendered as text.
It's going to be rendered as an actual death in this case an actual three tag.
OK.
So you can have these access to props children.
It's a really small feature but you know it could be really really handy.
And one more thing before we go to the next thing.
Why are we doing this.
Why are we passing this news item when we were just doing the GSX right here from with the map we are
in Boeken we are creating more code and doing a news item to render that data.
But it was working right here with the map.
Why are we doing this.
Well this is modular javascript.
This is the main idea of doing this.
You always need to chop everything into a single piece of code because then it's going to be easier
to work with.
Let's assume that this application is going to get a lot lot bigger.
So you're going to have tons of Marvel's tons of functions doing something something different right
here.
So maybe in the future you just need to modify something real slim inside each item.
So you're going to need to if you're going to need to look after this file look all the functions find
the one that's returning that data and then make diea change make that modification.
But in this case you know that you have an item on each news and then you can go to this element that
is going to have just a few lines of code and you can make the make the change make the adjustment.
OK that's good.
That's enough for now.
We're going to move forward to the next section and we're going to be talking a little bit more about
styles.
We're going to extend our knowledge about styles and of course we can style this because it's really
really fugly.
Let's go to the next section.