OK so we are going to talk a little bit more about stylings and if you're going to use styles as an
import just like the head or digests or with a link inside the HD L that is cool.
That's good anyways.
But sometimes we can use the SS and we need to fall back to some javascript logic.
So I'm going to show you some different ways and this is not react this is just javascript logic programming
Gloc logic.
So OK so what I want to do I went to add a background to the header right here.
I went to change it to no read.
I going to say Konst style.
And then I just create an object with the style of the background.
It's going to say background and then this one is going to be equal to red.
So now we want to pass the style we say style equal to style just like that.
So that's good.
You know it's working.
We know this.
Well what happens if what I want to do I went to check if the keywords are empty.
If this impot it's empty and leave it at one color.
But as soon as I start typing something I went to change the color to something else.
So then we need to go and fall back to some javascript logic we could say if the keywords are empty
remember that the keywords we have them on state when whenever we change them so we could change the
state of that.
And if they are empty We're going to do something.
If not begin to do something else.
So I could do something like this.
State that keywords.
It's different than this than empty.
And we're going to say style that my background just like that it's going to be called to do.
OK.
Let me match it and then if not we're going to do else we're going to do the opposite of this.
So I'm going to say read whenever there's a matter.
So if I type something is going to change to blue if I go back to empty it stays as read.
So we could use some logic like this using the state of physics.
OK so we're OK we can do something else.
Let's do something different.
I'm going to just comment this for now just for now and what I want to do I want to say that the style
of the header is going to be read.
So right here inside styles what we can do we can pass styles directly.
And what we can we need to do we need to use double curly braces.
So now right here what I could do I could say background and it's equal to read something like that.
And of course we can get the background read.
So most of the time you're going to be using this whenever you have some dynamic data and you need to
put the background image and then you are l where you can do something like this.
Now again if I type something this is not dynamic so I need to change this this value dynamically.
So how can you do that.
Well we can use the state for example.
I'm going to go to state again to say active and whenever the application starts this active it's going
to be false.
So now what I can do right here I can check if the state that active it's true and show red and if it's
false show Blue they're going to delete this and they're going to be using template strings.
Simple strings are really really cool.
We can do operations inside.
So I'm going to do door sign open in close curly braces.
So now read here what we can do.
We can do some ternary operation.
Does that state that active stuff like that.
And if it's false We're going to set it to read and if it's not begin to set it to do
something like that.
OK.
So let's see if it's working.
I'm going to do this and type something and delete and nothing happens.
And this is because we are not changing the state of active.
Remember that we are doing it right here.
So to do this we'll have to go to the input change handler and create a viable that is going to be checking
if it's empty or not and said the new state.
So I'm going to say Konst style makes sense.
Now let's change it to value something different.
So we're going to catch that event or target that value and begin to check if it's empty or not.
So if it's 3PL equal to empty We're going to say that the state is going to be false.
If not it's going to be true.
So now we have the True or False inside of a marvel.
Whenever we type something and we pass the event to change handler.
So now we need to change the state of active to whatever value we are getting out of this.
And they're going to do coma.
And of course the state is going to change if I type something it's changed.
And if it's not if it's empty we go back to blue.
So you can use some logic like this using the state and changing state.
OK.
So let me let me give you one more one more.
Let's say that instead of just passing the inline styling just like this what I want to do I want to
change.
You know just a class.
OK.
So I'm going to delete all of this.
I'm sorry for the deleting and not deleting so I could say this that state that active.
So this in fact is going to be a class and not some styles.
So I'm going to go to active right here at the bottom of the top sorry and I can say that this act if
it is is going to be equal to active just like that active the default state it's going to be active.
So now right here instead of changing to true from true or false.
What we can do we can swap classes.
We can say that the new state of active is going to be active or non active is going to say active and
then we change it to non active makes sense not to.
OK.
So now it's going to reload up.
We get the message.
I a mistake right here.
The bottom.
What am I doing this state active.
Of course it's not a style it is going to be the class name for that.
OK.
So everything works if you type something.
Of course it's not working.
But if I changed if I check the console let me check the class name of this for now whenever we start
is going to be active.
But if I type something is going to change to not active.
And if I go back to zero we get back active.
So we're going to be swapping classes right here and we can do the same thing.
We can add the CSA as we can add that active and not active class to this time elsea says.
And it's going to work its a different way of doing things.
You know you have three different methods to do this.
Of course we have a lot more methods and that's the main point of this section and the next in the next
century in the next section so we can change all of this just like this.
Again it's up to you but we have tons of libraries for stylings and they are really really cool.
So let's check them out.
OK so I'm going to show you how to use applying for this.
We have tons of plug ins to work with CSX.
So yes that's the first I'm going to delete all of this because we're not going to need it at all.
Let me just delete this.
Just go back to lead.
Or I was done and to this state.
So now I'm going to go to the useless item and begin to test this library from you list item.
So I get to go right here and I'm going to say react and the library is going to call glam or not when
you just glam or something like that.
And we're going to get it right here 3.1 clamor.
So with this with this dependency with this module what we can do we can use CSSA inline Lycia says
just like this.
And then clamors is going to work it's going to do its job and we can pass the rules we can pass holders
we can we can use we can even use media equerries.
And then it's going to pass that as a rule or as a class name or whatever.
It's really cool.
So let's install this first and we're going to show you how it's going to work on the kill the server
of course and we need to do NPM install and then it's going to be called glam or Glam or so just like
that.
And then minus minus safe.
So this one is a little bit slow.
It's going to take a little while to install it.
When was done OK it's done.
So I'm going to do clear and I'm going to do NPM start again.
So no to use it.
First we need to require the library.
So I'm going to go back to the project and in say in say import any curly braces.
Say yes yes.
So this is actually the instructions from glummer I'm not making this up right here.
So it is going to be CSSA.
And then from.
And then glam or.
So now what we need to do we need to create a rule to pass it right here to this news item.
This one right here.
So I'm going to go before the return and get a career viable that is going to be called news underscore
item something real simple.
First we need to invoke the method that we are requiring on top and this method is going to take an
object right here.
We can pass whatever class we want.
So what I want to do going to make this a little bit better just a little bit better.
I to add padding and the padding is going to be pixel's something like that.
Of course it's an object so we need to do coma that we need to use box sizing.
So I sing good.
And the sizing is going to be border you know the box in a coma and I'm going to add a board there and
then bottom of one pixel pixels solid gray that makes sense.
So now we have this now.
We are not getting any errors you know.
Looks good.
It says that we have this Vrable and it's not being used.
We're going to use it in a minute.
So now to pass to you to use this class because we're pretty much creating the class what we can do.
We go to the actual elements where we need that class and we can say in curly braces that oh sorry dot
dot dot.
And then the name of the class which is going to be news item.
So I'm going to do that and if a reload.
You know we get it it's working it seems like a mistake right here.
The bottom should be working now.
There you go.
You know it works really really really cool.
So OK what happens if I want to add two different styles to different classes right here.
Well again we could create a new variable that is going to be item and grey or something like that.
And then of course we need to use the CSSA open the method and pass an object.
And I could say background something like that of gray lets use light gray.
I believe it's like a light gray Burguet.
So now if I went to pass a second class what we can do is the same process dot dot and then am gray.
And we get it it's using both classes this dot dot dot that we're using right here.
It's ESX.
It's not you know from the from Glenmore it's.
It's saying grab all the properties that we have inside that element and put them inside of here.
That's what pretty much it's doing.
So we can use a we can use more things.
What happens if I went to add a homer you know just a Hoover right here on each element.
Well I'm going to do comb I'm going to go below here.
And what we say is corn and then Hoover just like that.
And then of course this is going to be something else.
And then color.
And we're going to change it to read make sense.
Good.
So whenever we do however we are going to change it to red.
And you know it's working.
It's really really nice.
So what else we can do we have a few more things and what happens if we want to check.
We went to work with media queries again just like the Hoeber right here.
We can add a media query for this element.
So we are going to say and then media.
Then of course we need to open it close and I'm going to say Max what you can do with it's up to you.
This is just yes and they're going to save 500 pixels whatever.
And then of course we say calm and we pass the tiles.
And this chair in this case I can change the whole color to blue whatever but it's going to reload the
page of course going to make it.
And there we go.
You know it's catching that media Querrey.
So OK we can do a lot of thanks.
You can check the condition.
We have it all right here we have the docs.
It has some demos.
So you can you can check this out.
But don't do it just now.
We're going to be doing some all this stuff.
Let's say that for example right here we are creating an instance.
So this is going to be kind of a kind of a class name and right here we're kind of injecting a data
attribute.
Let me just do an inspection and show you.
Let's go and make it bigger.
It's going to go to elements and select each elements.
So you know right here we didn't have the class in the name of this.
We have a data attribute and if we go to Hetter we can see that it's a pending Goldstein's right here.
But this is a data attribute.
So again this library is going to give us the ability to use classes.
They're going to read all of this and I can add a class name.
So instead of a data attribute what we can do we can pass a template strings with the value of whatever
class you're creating right here at the top.
So I'm going to say this.
And then of course I'm going to be adding the item gray.
So we do the same dollar sign open close and then I'd say this is template strings.
OK guys if you are you're getting confused with this because you need to learn a little bit more about
ESX.
Remember that the last module of this discourse is going to be a whole course with ESX.
OK you know we are still getting it and now we are getting a class of this.
And if you check the head right here we are getting you know the classes.
So you know this works right.
So what else.
You know what you can do.
You can use this approach if you like this one you can use it.
It's not bad.
You know this methods are not bad.
They work really good.
So we are going to be talking about something else we're going to be going to the next action because
this video went too long and we'll be talking about S as modules.
That's kind of a new concept.
Can you show you how to how to use it.
It's going to get a little bit confusing but don't worry we're going to begin to do it right.
Practically do it on the project and begin going to be using that one.
OK.
So let's go to the next section.