Right so now we're going to be using C Ss modules and this is going to be you are going to show you
what we can do and then I'm going to show you how to do it because this can be confusing.
First I'm going to delete all the things that we have inside news item.
We're not going to use Glenmore.
So just going to go back to the previous state of things.
So now what we can do after we do some set up what we would we could do is to import maybe a variable
just give it a name.
I'm going to use classes you can use the styles or whatever it is that you want to use.
And then from and what we're going to do.
We're going to import the CSSA from the source folder just like here.
So I'm going to be an Access dot dot for Slash then CSSA for Slash.
And then of course it's going to be a stylus that assess.
So I'm pretty much including this style sheet instead of this just like with a header.
You know over here know it's a little bit different.
Right here we are importing the styles directly and right here we assign here we assign you know a name.
So now what we can do after we enable modules.
What we can do is just go to dev where we want to use the class and we can use class name and instead
of passing some text what we can do we can pass the class that we have inside styles the class for this
is going to be something like I don't know dot news item or something like that news item.
And for now I'm just going to say background and then just read something like that.
So now what we can do since we are importing right here were pack and we.
They're going to compile everything and you're going to have access to that class inside classes and
then dot and use underscore item and it's going to go ahead.
In the style right here.
Par's everything and just do it you know here.
I know it sounds kind of confusing but it's going to be a little bit confusing.
But it can show you how to do it and you will get it.
Now here's the downside.
We need to do a lot of tweaking and whenever we choose to use this method the modules including the
module we cannot use this one.
This one is not going to work.
So you're going to see in a minute why.
So the first step is going to be enabling the SS modules using this method.
So we need to change the configuration of how or how our app is rendered.
And I'm talking about what happens inside create re-act app and web pack.
So you need to touch the configuration files.
So by default the configuration files inside our project are hidden from us.
So we are not allowed to touch the files.
This is by default with Create we act up but react gives you the control over this.
We can run a command and have all the configuration files available.
Now here's a warning once you disabled the feature of Hanney having the folders hidden.
You cannot go back.
So if you make a change on the configuration you make a mistake the application is going to break and
you cannot go back to a previous state.
You can add to it is not going to let you.
So if you make some changes.
Make sure that they are you're doing the right changes.
And if not are you going to have to just inspect what you change and just you know fix it.
So I would recommend to use version control just like get to save a branch would you default state of
your app.
So if you make a mistake you can always go back.
All right.
So the first step to do this to enable and this is going to be in the package to Jason can go right
here right here you have the dependencies and this is what we care right now.
The scripts when we use NPM start it's creating the development server for us so you can see it on screen.
But then we have the build whenever we need to deploy the our application to production is going to
create a folder with all the required files.
You know the bundled non-jazz.
So then we have the test begin to see the slitter.
And then we have eject.
What why what is it ject why.
No it looks like a dangerous name.
So with object what we can do is say to create re-act app to disable the hidden folders.
So it's going to give us back access to all the configuration files we're going to do it right now.
Remember to save something and get to save your project and get going to declare I'm going to say NPM
run.
Just like that.
It's going to take a little while.
And are you sure you want to eject.
This action is permanent.
So yeah we now going to say yes or no.
OK.
So now the package that Jason is going to change is going to show you right here all the he's got the
Create re-act app.
It's using that we didn't have access but now we do.
And of course we have a lot more logic right here.
And notice that we don't have the eject so we didn't have we cannot do eject again.
OK.
That's good.
So now let me show you right here.
You have the public you're going to have access to scripts you know source the same source.
But now right here we have a folder that's going to say Confect.
So this is the folder where all the configuration happens.
And right here we have a web pack and a web pack prod.
You know the dev and the prod.
So whenever we use NPM start he's going to use the configuration we have for web pack inside config
that dev.
But if we do the built MP and ram build it means that we begin to go to production.
So we're going to use this one this prodigy is going to use this configuration and not the dead.
So if we want to make some changes here we need to make it on both files.
Okay that's good.
So now we need to enable the modules right here in the wet pack.
So we're going to go to well-packed Web let me make a little of this a little bit bigger.
I'm going to keep scrolling down.
You can have a lot of configuration.
Really confusing.
Whenever we hit the web pack configure it what pack section of this course.
This all this logic is going to start making sense.
Don't worry I'm going to keep scrolling down until you see something that says see SS inside test and
then see it says so right here we have the options.
So we need to add some extra features right here.
So what do we need to do.
We need to go right here and say modules and modules is going to be equal to true.
So now modules are available for our project but we need to add to to add an additional feature.
Now whenever these modules is working is going to create names over the classes.
So we need to specify which names are we going to be using.
So we're going to say local Just like that ident and then name all income case and right here I'm going
to do something we're.
So we're going to be saying is that we want to use the original name of that class and we want to add
an underscore underscore begin to use the local then underscore underscore and begin to be using a hash.
We make just trim this down.
So what we can say is hash and we need to pass which hash and begin to use base 64 and then Kong and
the number 5.
So this is pretty much omentum stake right here named local hash.
Let's get.
So this is going to convert the CSSA to.
So it can use it in the project.
Don't worry I know this doesn't make sense is going to make sense.
UNAMID B we can actually do it on screen.
So I got a copy of this and we're going to go to the Web config but not to death.
But the production we going to do the same thing.
We can find that the SS.
The images and then CSSA.
So if you notice we have some other options.
And this is because whenever the web hack it's creating the bundle and everything else we have more
options because it's going to create a minimized version of everything.
It's just compressing everything.
So it uses more options.
We don't need it for development so we can be a little bit faster because we don't really need it.
So after import loaders we're going to do this and are going to paste modules true and local IDN name
and the same thing we have inside that.
So no same options.
So this it's ready so we can use modules right now.
So I'm going to close the dev of the close Prod. and right here we are importing classes from CSSA styles.
So let me go right here.
Of course this is not working.
I'm going to do NPM start we're going to start a development server all around so that it's done and
notice that some things are going to break.
So the logo is breaking and we didn't have an stylings right here.
OK.
So I'm going to go back to a news list item and we import the classes we assign a name from the C S.
So now again classis a news item and what we can do we can pass a name.
So I'm going to go styles.
We have a news item that's good and right here.
Class name use items again which has the same name because I was using a different name.
If you go to the project it's going to reload and we have a background for this.
And notice the notation right here.
It's having that class putting it inside each element with styles underscore underscore.
This is the local and underscore underscore the hash.
And if we go to the head we have it right here.
You know it's just importing the CSSA and it's putting the same names describing that class changing
the name so it can match the one we have inside the element.
So this is the main idea of using modules you know it's really nice.
So again if we notice that right here the logo it's breaking.
So inside the head are not just we are importing this on a different way so we need to import classis
from and then you know from here we need to use the same methods inside our project.
Now right here you're using a logo and we are using the class for the header you're not using a class.
That's why it's not breaking.
It's giving us a background of blue because we're not using a class but logo it's breaking.
So we need to do the same thing we did with the Newsless item instead of passing class of Logo.
We need to pass an object that is going to be classes because we have it on top.
Classes dot and then logo.
And if we reload the page.
In theory should should be working.
So you know it's working.
All right.
You know that's good.
So I'm going to be adding rowboat so I'm going to be going to add some styles to this because it's really
really actually going to go to the index that HD mail is going to add a new phone sized new phone style
no font going to be adding Roboto.
You can skip this if you wish.
Doesn't matter.
And then of course in the body I'm going to be going to adding add fun style font style and then it's
going to be rebozo course.
Let me make this better.
And then we're botto and of course we're going to be adding some styles to news item.
We don't need a background.
I'm going to add a panning of 20 pixels.
What else.
The same thing we did before.
Can add a box sizing just like that make it better.
Box izing and the box izing of course is going to be for their box and begin to be adding border bottom.
Sometimes when you switch between javascript and says you get confused with the cons and the coma because
you know this is not an object.
So we can use a bother Barnham and it's one pixel solid and the gray makes sense.
Never reload the page a bit at stake right here and see.
We go.
I was using like an object that was adding the single quotes.
So OK.
So right here we get the style.
So this is working beautifully.
So again you can choose whatever method you wish.
You can import it right here.
You can import it without the class just like with it on the header.
Or you can use modules.
This is up to you.
There is a world of discussion of which one we should use.
Some people support this module some other people support the link.
You know at the end of the day it doesn't really matter if this works for you and you're comfortable
using this method.
You know you should use it just go ahead and use it.
All right so let's go to the next section.
We're going to go back exit the CSSA world and go back to the Dow components and what you're going to
be doing going to be filtering the news.
Remember that right here we have an input and what we want to do I want to say for example I went to
look for react.
This is going to go to the parent components.
It's going to check all the titles and it's going to show only the the the documents right here the
news with the keyboard we act good so we can show this to for example and the other ones are going to
be hidden.
And of course we're going to be using States and everything else.
So let's go to the next section and start work working on the Filcher.