Right.
So now we're going to be filtering the news on the U.S. has been a mistake.
I put font style in cinema instead of from family.
So now we are using botto.
That's good.
OK.
So we are not going to go we're not going to go back to styles.
So OK so now that we know props we could take a different approach with Hetter.
So with prompts we can share functions values or objects or whatever and you know we can share them
with chyle components just like we are doing with news.
We're just passing the whole list of news and then the job of that users is just rendering the news.
So now I'm going to just start doing something and then I'm going to.
You can see why I'm going to create a function to go to the index that is going to create a function
that I'm going to be sharing to a child component.
In this case the better.
So I'm going to say I'm going to create a function that is going to be called Get keyboard something
like that it's going to be equal to a fat R-OH function then open it close and you know which is passive
function.
So this one when when it's going to get triggered it's going to just cancel log key.
You know just a text it's going to say hey something real simple.
So now I'm going to go to Hetter and get a pass this function as props.
OK.
So the name for this is going to be keyboard's is going to be equal to.
And of course we say this because we mean declasse and then we pass get keyboard.
So now this function is going to be available inside Hetter.
In theory.
OK.
So I'm going to go right here and I'm going to do console log and remember that whenever we pass something
through props.
If you're using a class it's going to be available inside.
Inside this that props that keyboards in this case.
So if we reload You know we are getting the console log.
Hey it's telling us that we have a function that does this.
So we are successfully sharing a function between parent component and child component.
So what is the point of doing all of this now.
In theory if we have this function available we can call it from within whatever.
You know our code and we can trigger at this function we can do that.
So instead of doing that.
What I'm going to do I'm going to copy this.
They're going to delete the console log and I'm going to go right here to the On Change.
So every time we input a text instead of triggering the input change handler I went to trigger that
prompts you know the this that prompts keyword that function that we have available.
In theory it should be working.
We should be getting counsel luck hey.
OK.
So going to type something and you know we are getting it.
We get like hey.
So OK if we think about this we are just triggering a function that we have on the parent component
from within the child component.
So what is the point of doing all of this.
Why are we using a function in a class we could just make this smaller and create a functional component.
So you know right here we do the onchange.
It runs this function but we need to pass the events we need to catch the events.
So if I go right here and say event and then do the cancel log.
But instead of you know doing the consulate Hey I call the event I say event that target that value
theory again we should be getting the value of what we are entering.
So if I say Frances we get it.
So it's still working.
So again there is no need to do this.
If I combine all this out you know I just can't comment all.
And we tried again.
It's still working.
So there's no need to use the state and this is what and what I've told you before that if you can avoid
using states start using class based components.
You know you should avoid it avoid this and use a functional components.
So we can change this back to a functional component.
I'm going to do this because we're not going to need it.
I'm going to delay this again because we are not going to need it.
I'm going to say Konst and I'm going to just refactor this to a functional component.
It's going to be Hetter.
And then of course it's going to be equal to a function and this function is going to receive some props.
You know the props that keyboards now says you're using a functional component there there's no need
to use the render.
We don't need it since we're not using component right here.
There's no need to bring it.
And right here we are making we are making a reference to this and we didn't have this.
We're not using a class based component so we can say only prompts.
Let's see if it's working.
At least we are not getting any errors.
So if I type Francis you know it works.
So now again you should always take five minutes when you're whenever you're building your own application.
Take five minutes and think you're really need a functional component or a class based component.
Now again if you decide to use a class based component because you like it more that's fine.
You can use it.
It's still going to work.
No one is going to say anything to you.
But you know we're using less code and you're using less logic and not using state twice.
Now we are using state only once.
So you know less code.
It's going to be a better performing application.
OK so now we need to do more things we need to.
The idea of doing all of this or.
This refactor is to get the keyboards inside the state of the main app.
We're going to get the keywords right here are we going to store a new state.
So let's do that right now.
OK so let's filter the news.
I'm going to tell you what's the logic with this.
So where we are getting the keywords right here whenever the user enters something on the impot.
So we are catching that.
That keyboard if Icesave react.
For example we can catch react.
So we're going to grab that keyboard begin to filter the news Jason.
All the news and we can it just get all the news with the with the title react.
We're going to search the title and if we can find a match between the keyboard and something.
Some want some keywords in the title.
We can never return the whole news and we can store them in a new array.
So in theory if we type react we'll loop all the news is going to find the second one it's going to
store it on an array.
It's going to find the second one is going to pass through.
And it can store it in array and then it's going to be done with that loop.
And at the end we can have only one tray with only two use.
So OK.
So I'm going to delete them.
Just common this is going to use it later.
So we have access to the keyboards good.
So now we need to create something a function or whatever that is going to loop all the news and it's
going to just grab the noose with the keyboards.
OK.
So I'm going to say let creative are all there's going to be let.
And I'm going to call this filtered something like that.
So this viral is going to filter the news and we can use an E-6 helper that is going to be called Filcher.
So we're going to say this that state that news just like that can to grab this state of news with all
the news and then we're going to use the helper filter.
This is not react.
This is ESX.
So this filter is going to be running a function and this on each iteration is going to pass an item.
This is just like doing the map is going to run the loop and on each iteration is going to pass each
news just like we did with the Newsless item right here with the map and find it right here.
Same idea same idea.
So going to go back to the.
Now what we need to do on each iteration we're going to be doing some checking right here we're going
to be checking if the the title of each item we have a match for the keyword.
OK.
So this is again just raw javascript I'm going to save return.
We always need to use the keyword return whenever we use filter just like we did with the map.
So first we can access the item which is each new then we're going to say title dot begin access to
title.
And now again we're going to be using a raw javascript you to check the index off.
So the index off is going to be the event targeted value.
So I'm going to go right here at the top.
I'm going to create a new Farmall that is going to be called Lead keyboard like that a lot keyboard
is going to be equal to event.
The target value which is the actual keyword and then going to past keyword.
So this is going to enter that use.
For example on the first iteration it's going to enter.
This is going to enter the title right here.
It's going to check the whole string.
It's going to check if the keyword that we are typing.
If there is some match with any of the awards we have right here.
So if we type ESX we're going to find a match right here is going to be returning true and it's going
to return the whole news.
OK.
So we have the index off the keyboard and we need to specify that this is true.
So if this is true it's going to return that news real simple.
OK.
So I'm going to go and cancel log.
This will this filter just to check that we're getting the logic with the right way.
OK.
So I'm going to go to the main application.
I'm going to type E and noticed that we are already getting three and it means that it's not finding
we have one title and that you know you're not getting an E letter that's good.
So noticed that there is right here I'm using caps.
We didn't have it's for example when we match it right here in the off it's not going to match it between
lower case and upper case if it's uppercase is going to match this lower case.
It's not going to match.
Let me give you an example.
If I say E-6 with capitals we're getting one match which is Title 6.
And this is the match upgrade of eval.
So we're filtering the news and we are bringing the only news where we get.
Yes six on the title.
Now if I do six of course that's happening not happening it's not finding that one.
Of course we will need to do more logic right here.
You know we can do that later.
Maybe so OK.
So we're getting the filtered news.
That is the main point of all of this.
So now since we have the filtered news we need a way to tell the news list to render the filtered news
instead of the of all news.
So what I'm going to do I'm going to go right here at the top I'm going to get to I'm going to put a
coma and I'm going to create a new state.
It's going to be filtered and filter at the beginning when the application starts it's going to be empty
of course because we don't have a filter.
It's going to start as empty and then as soon as we get the filtered we get a new state of filter begin
to set the state of this filter with whatever result we have right here.
OK.
So I'm going to go right here to say this.
That said state opening close and we're going to say that this felt heard it's going to be equal to
whatever we get right here after we type the keyboard.
OK.
Since we're using Year Six there's no need to do this.
We can use past Filcher.
And this is going to be is going to pass.
Is this going to all happen behind the scenes.
Right.
So now we have the new state of filters.
So now we need to specify right here what we want to do it to output what we want to render.
So it's going to be it's going to look a little bit where we could do it just just right here and I'm
going to use a turnaround operation.
I'm going to say this that state DOT will be going to be AXS accessing the filtered begin to check on
the filter whenever the application renders for the first time.
If we have something inside if it's if it's empty.
So going to check the length of it.
So if the length is going to be equal to zero which it means that it's going to be empty we want to
do something right here.
And if it's not empty which means that we have the keyboard and we have some result we're going to displace
something else.
So if the gas filtered is empty going to say render this that state that news can render all the news.
But if they felt her state has some data we want to render that one instead.
So we're going to say does that state that filtered.
All right I made a mistake.
I may go back but so know the fonts are really big.
So for so you can the you can see right here the code if I trimmed down.
You're not going to be able to see it on screen that fonts are going to be small.
That's why you know I have this.
So we're going to trim this in a minute.
So what is happening right here.
The application renders for the first time is going to be checking if we have something inside filtered.
Of course we didn't have anything because whenever the application starts the state of filtered is going
to be nothing but just an empty array.
So since this is going to be passing it's true we're going to just return this that state that use this
state contains all the news.
Now the second one if this is the slang the filter length has some use which means that we made a filter.
And we get we salts.
It's going to render the filtered.
OK.
Let's see if it's working.
I'm going to go right here.
I'm going to say e as sex.
You know it's working.
Let's try something else.
If I delete everything and leave it to empty.
It's going to fall back and go to this state.
So now the made him sick.
So now Newsless is going to be rendering all the news.
You know it's working.
Let's say re-act for example.
Of course not going to work because his lower case and we have our case right here.
If I do upper case react we get two.
So it's working right now in this line.
It's a little bit long.
It's not human to human readable.
So what we can do we can create an alias for this and this is you can find this kind of kind of common.
You can find it in a lot of re-act projects.
So if we can have left can you create a viable that is going to serve as an alias for this.
This state that Filcher And you know it makes sense for this application.
This code could get could get much much longer.
So we are always using this date and something.
So you can create an alias just for this.
I'm going to say news filtered and this one is going to be equal to this state that filter and then
are going to say let And I'm going to say news and then hold something like that.
Going to be instead of this state that filter it's going to be news.
OK.
There you go.
So instead of making a reference to this because it's a long string I could just say use.
Replace this with news filtered and right here going to copy the news hole and make reference to news.
Whoa.
So you know a little bit better a little bit better.
So I'm going to go right here and just going to say sex and it works.
And if I delete everything it works OK.
So everything works as expected.
Now let's recap something right here.
I'm using whenever the application starts I'm storing the Jason data inside News I'm storing all the
news inside news.
And then we are running something to filter and we're storing the filtered news inside something else.
Why am I duplicating this.
It's always a bad idea to mutate the original state of something that it's really really important in
this case we are rendering all the news we get all the news right here.
If I filter the news and I store it inside News I'm going to be mutating the or regional data.
And then the next time that we need to use dysfunction you're not going to get this data.
You know we are just mutated the data.
We don't have access to this.
So we will have to find the news again and do something else OK that's good.
So you know we could take a different approach in this we could use life cycles but we're not there
yet.
We're going to get there.
So OK.
This is the final section of this tiny tiny project.
It looks really really ugly but that's good.
It's practicing you know the main point of this it's not making a nice application a good look like
a good application with good looks.
It's not the main point of this.
The main point is just learn the basics of react.
We're going to be going to be doing more sections with react.
We need to all we are going to be learning a lot more things and we're going to be talking about life
cycles.
We need to talk about broader.
That's going to be really interesting.
So we still need to do a lot of things.
So let's go to the next section and start with something new.