Right.
So on this section we we'll be talking about re-act router.
What is re-act router.
Well maybe in the future you want to build an application that has more than one view.
For example just to give you an example.
I'm going to go to facebook page and if I go to Home let me just go to home.
The application is going to load.
And of course you can it get home.
But of course you have different options right here.
For example if I go to Iowa this is going to go to a different view and notice that the u r l is changing.
So react is to create single page applications.
We don't have this behavior we cannot achieve this ride out of the box.
We didn't have the ability to do it.
So we need to add a middleware or extension or library whatever you want to call it.
So we can achieve this behavior.
And this is going to be called re-act router is to create routes.
So we will start with a clean project we're going to start all over again and we're going to go to the
terminal.
Notice that I've created a new folder to react live cycles writer say router and then life cycles at
the end of the section will be it will be we will be talking about life cycles don't worry we will get
there is going to blow your mind.
So navigate I'm navigated to the to the same directory so we can do the Create react with it before
we're going to say create re-act app.
And then since I'm inside the directory I'm going to do space and the DOD just like that are going to
press center.
It's going to take a few minutes.
So I'm going to pass the PTO and be right back.
OK so everything gets installed.
And just like before we get to do is just delete all the files we have right here and start from scratch.
So I'm going to go to the public folder.
I'm going to delete everything but the indexed DML going to send it to trash.
Then we're going to go to the source folder and I'm going to delete everything but the index that jazz.
So OK so I'm going to just oh I made mistakes or we're going to delete everything.
Move to trash.
We only get the index digests.
And I'm going to go to the index dodgiest it again.
We're going to delete everything.
We're going to start from scratch.
Burguet so we can you know we can practice a little bit.
So we you can be using re-act Browder and this is a different module.
So we need to install it.
So we're going to go to the terminal I'm going to do clear and begin to install the router.
Me make this bigger.
I'm going to say NPM install and then re-act dash router dash and then Dohm and begin to use a very
specific version.
It's going to be the for that to that zero.
This is the latest version up to date.
You know the date of course.
So this module keeps updating the whole time.
That's why I'm using an app specific person to keep consistency of course.
Of course if there is a breaking change I'm going to just update this.
So we're going to do space and minus minus save going to press center and it's not that heavy so it
should take just a couple of minutes maybe less of course a couple seconds minutes.
It's too much.
So OK it's going.
Almost done OK.
So OK so installed and we got no errors.
All right.
So you know we have a different process between how the web works today or how we've worked.
A while ago and it works in a different way so let me explain what happens when we get a request for
our application first.
OK so this is what's happening outside of the world of single page apps on let's say multi-page apps.
So you're going to get a request for docs that come it's going to be your domain your Eurail you're
going to have your application.
So this is going to make a request to a server.
The servers can find a file that belongs to that URL and then it's going to return that it's going to
give you or give you a response with that file and it's going to reload the browser and you're going
to have your application.
Now for example let's say that the user clicks on a link and goes to a different page.
Inside are our domain our application.
So then again who's going to repeat the same process beginning to enter to the Shittu page of our application
and it's going to make it detect a change and the you are all going to go to the server the server will
find the file will reload the browser and display the file.
So this is how it works how we know that it works on multi-page applications now on single single page
applications.
It's going to work a little bit different.
So let's go right here.
So we have our application inside docs that come.
So of course we make a request that this server is going to it's going to go to the server and the server
is going to return our application.
Now our application is going to be a single page and it's going to have different parts.
So first we can have a history.
Now this history is going to keep a log of when the world changes.
So for example if I go to docs that come dash should sue.
The history is going to be listening for that.
It is going to grab your L and store it kind of like a big Jason with all the bells.
So then we have the re-act router.
So the router is going to be checking the history it's going to be listening for changes.
So whenever we get a change on the Ural it's going to detect it.
And then when it's detecting everything is going to go and find Dimanche those that are linked to that
you are l.
So let's say we have a Shittu.
We're going to go to the model that belongs to Shittu.
And then is going to say react.
We have a we have a change on the history.
So we need to you need to show this component.
So was the reactors going to say OK so I'm going to grab the component laying to that Eurail and then
I'm going to show that components.
And of course it's going to give you that view.
So this is what's happening behind the scenes with re-act router and now we're going to begin to learn
everything that we need to learn to use re-act router and create kind of a multi bew single page apps.
OK.
Let's go to the next section and start with router.