All right.
So since we have a clean clean project we need to have of course an index base index page.
This is what we have in this Digest.
This is going to be the starting of our application.
Of course we need to do a lot of set up.
First we need to import just like we did before.
Let's create the first template for this.
It's going to be import the first components componentry import from Riyadh and we're going to be doing
this a lot.
Then of course we are going to need import to react on.
We need to bring react Dom to the equation and then we act on from.
And then of course react down just like it's all before.
So it is good if you have a template now.
Our main application the main start of the main component of our application is going to be of just
a functional functional of components.
We don't need a class for this so I'm going to say Konst and it's going to be app and it's going to
be equal to a function.
And of course we're going to return something.
And for now you're going to return some dumb dip just like that and is going to say home whatever.
Good.
OK.
So now we need to use this re-act Dom.
So I'm going to go right here and I'm going to say react and then Dohm dot and we need to call the render
method the render method it's going to be displaying the app that we have on top.
Good.
There you go.
So then coma in which you specify what we're going to be rendering this.
So we say document dot Querrey selector.
And then of course we select the route remember route on the H.T. now.
Well that's it.
OK.
In theory if we run this we should be getting at least home.
So I'm going to say NPM start and it's going to go is going to give us 3000 not post just home and we
get home so that it's working great.
So now we are going to be practicing with routes.
So we're just going to go ahead and create the routes I'm going to create a folder that is going to
be components just like that.
Just like before and from the start because we have just three different routes.
I'm going to create one file that is going to be home that jast going to create a new one that is going
to be posts that jazz is going to create a new one that is going to be profile that jazz.
So most of the times when you create your projects you can just do it like this and look at what we
need to do.
We need to create some at least a little bit of this to create the components or at least whatever we
rendered this posts we can get some text.
So first we need to import react and then from you guessed it react.
This is going to be a functional component so we don't need to do much right here.
I'm going to say Konst posts because we are inside posts and is going to be equal to open close and
just to function.
So this one of course is going to return open close and we need to return a dev.
Just like with that before and this one is going to save posts so we can know at least which component
we are rendering.
Of course we need to make this component available from all other components.
So we're going to say the font and then we pass posts.
So everything is good.
So in theory of course it's not going to work.
If we change it right here we need to include this.
But first we copy all of this and I get to go home.
I'm going to paste it and I'm just going to change the names.
That's the only thing that we are going to do right now.
Home then home.
And of course home.
Then we have profile so we get to paste it up sorry when you copy paste it.
And this one is going to be profile OCHA profile.
And then again profile.
So OK so we have all the buse ready now we need to start using.
Finally we are going to be using re-act router.
So again we installed we've installed and router as a dependency.
We have we have it right here.
So what we need to do we need to bring the package and begin to say import and then open it close curly
braces because you're going to be bringing things from re-act Rotterdam that we're going to say from
and then we passed re-act then router and then of course Dom.
Now the first thing that we're going to be bringing is going to be something called browser router.
I know sounds kind of funny.
Browser router.
So this this is going to be an object that it's going to interact with the history and it's good to
know know pretty much it's going to know what's happening on the your l.
OK so this one is the first one that we need and we need to bring something else we need.
We need to bring something that is going to be called route with a capital R.
So this route is the one that knows what to do when the browser router is saying that the world changed.
OK.
Again this one interacts with the you are l with history and this one is going to go and execute whatever
the browser router is going to pass.
OK.
That's good.
Now we need to import the components we just created.
So I'm going to put a comment I'm going to say components just like that components.
We need to import and we need to import first home.
It's going to be from and we're going to go forward slash components and then home.
OK what else we need to import.
And then we need to import posts posts.
We need to import it from DOD for Slash components and then posts.
Right.
We have one more to go.
It's going to be profile then from and then dart forward slash components and profile.
You know we did all this in just a couple of minutes.
Is you get the idea of how to how to do it.
You're going to do it really really fast.
OK so now we need to start using routes.
We brought this browser router and the route now inside of the app when we're going to do.
I'm going to delete this just for now and whenever we have an application and we want to use routes
our main application the starting of our application which is in this case is going to be app.
It needs to wrap everything whole up to application inside the router.
So we're going to be using this browser router I'm going to open and close a tack just like this and
then open and close it.
Of course you're going to get some errors but that's fine.
Oh model can resolve components and Profar maybe made a mistake.
It's going to be profiles on the make sure profile look at.
That's good.
I made a mistake with an aim but you know we're just going to leave it like that.
So now whenever we use a browser or router we can pass routes.
So this route is going to be just like that.
Now each crowd has a path the path is going to be whatever this router is going to be listening on the
history.
So I'm going to say path and it's going to be equal to something.
In this case I'm going to I'm going to pass the posts right here.
So what we want to do we want to listen for the your L for Slash posts.
It's going to be localhost three thousand four slash posts.
And whenever you use something you see it you use it like this is going to always mean that you want
the absolute roud which is the domain and then immediately after the fourth slash posts.
So that's going to be where you're going to be using why you're going to be using the the path.
Then you have a different option a different attribute and it's going to be components.
Whenever we use components we need to tell react and to tell react router which components we want to
render whenever we get this route makes sense.
So right here we are putting posts.
So I'm going to copy posts and put it right here.
So I'm going to go right here at the bottom and I'm going to create the route for the profiles.
OK.
So I'm going to say route.
We're going to take a path and the path is going to be profiles called Profiles singler.
And then of course we need the components and the components it's going to be just profile.
And then of course we need to close it.
Let me close this so you can see the whole code.
OK.
If I go to the browser we can get you if you're going to get a router may have only one child element.
So this means pretty much that inside browser router we can cannot have different elements.
This is just like returning some GSX.
We need to wrap everything inside something and that something could be whatever you want.
In this case I'm just going to use it if something simple.
If I wrap everything inside of the it passes.
OK.
So we are getting around four posts and profiles.
So in theory if I go to posts we should be getting something going to say posts.
OK.
You know we are getting posts if you go to the post component's this one is just returning posts.
OK let's go to profiles and see what happens.
A go to profile.
It's profiles and we get profile.
Let me change it.
I don't like profiles plural.
Let me just bring profile.
It's going to be profile and ok we get profile.
So you know it works.
Now let's do the home.
Because right now if we go to home you're not getting anything.
And we have a component for to render the home.
So I'm going to go right here and I'm going to say route.
OK.
Let me make it self self-closing tag.
And now for the home we're going to be passing the path.
And you know whenever we go home it's going to be pretty much the main domain the local host 3000 in
this case so to specify home we're going to use force slash then we're going to specify the components
and it's going to be home of course.
OK.
So if we go home you know we are getting home now.
Let's go two posts again and see what happens.
You can go to posts and we get home.
So why are we getting home if I go to posts.
Let's go to the correct route.
We're getting home and posts.
So what is going on right here.
Let me make this a little bit more.
Whenever we load the router we are saying that whenever you get the path of force slash you want to
render home.
So we're getting a fourth slash right here.
So it's rendering home.
Then we past posts and you know we are saying right here that whenever you get posts read their posts.
So this two routes are valid.
That's why we are getting we get we are getting both.
Now there's a way to fix this re-act router is going to give us one more option.
It's going to be the exact that we're going to do something different with this but for now EXACT is
going to work.
So if I go to post you know you're not you are now getting on the posts and if you go home of course
we get home.
So exact is going to say OK I need to listen to this Pat and it needs to be exact and if it's not render
something else OK.
So it's going to the second one in the chain which is this one and it's only rendering posts just like
this.
So that works now right here before the routes or after the routes you can output whatever you want.
In this case it is going to create a header tag just like that.
And you know again to see Hetter so reload the page we always going to get better the magical thing
about this.
And if I go to posts where getting better.
If I go to home we get we still get Hetter And if we go to profile we're still getting beheader.
So whenever you go to different routes you're always going to get the better because you know it's inside
the components.
Now if we look at this this kind of a make sense this is going to be the whole view which is the whole
window.
We have Hetter on top that it's going to be rendered no matter what.
And then of course we have the route.
If we have this case if we are inside home he's going to render whatever you have as a component.
So after the header.
So that's what it's doing.
We go to profile First we get the letter and then we get the profile.
So this works like this you're going to structure this in different ways.
We're going to be creating different routes inside the project we can create different projects and
we're going to be using this and different ways.
So you're going to have different ways to be to use it of course not.
Not this one.
We could create a file that is going to be routes and then import it and use it from there.
That's a different way to use this.
OK.
That's fine.
This lecture went too long.
Let's go to the next section.
And I want I would like to do is to add some links right here so we can click the links on the on Hetter
and go to different routes.
Let's go to the next section.