OK since we don't expect for the user to be changing the Ural manually just like you are doing right
here changing to profile the posts or whatever we need to do something first.
No you must be thinking Dude we need to add a link.
I'm going to put a than a ref and whatever we want ad will react.
This is not going to work.
We cannot use an ailing ATAC just like that.
So what we need to use is we need to use a property that is going to give us a router is going to give
us a model that is going to be called Link.
So this link is going to create a link.
So I'm going to go right here inside the header and I'm going to say link now.
Open and close this link is going to take us to home.
Now with each link we have a property that we need to use that is going to be too.
Now the two is going to be of course like the ref.
So it seems we want to go to home.
We're going to pass a four slash and we go to home so we are getting a link of home and it's taking
us.
OK.
So MacCready the other.
All the.
All the other links are going to go right here instead of home.
It's going to be posts and of course we want to go to posts.
And then of course we can have the profile and begin to say profile and then take us to profile.
And at the end I'm going to add just a ruler just a line so we can split everything up.
OK.
So to get home we go to home.
If you go to posts it's taking us to posts profile profiles.
Everything works fine.
You're getting home inside profile.
Maybe I'd change it by mistake muse profile again profile profile.
So everything works as expected.
Now with this link we have some additional options.
We can do some settings right here.
We can use them settings.
So I'm going to delete this route and instead of passing chess with a text string with double quotes
going to pass an object and then inside I'm going to pass an object.
So the first curly braces it's not an object.
Actually it's you're making reference that we want to use something from react and then inside of course
we pass a set of rules inside an object.
OK.
So this right here the options are going to be the pathname a hash and a search.
I know that it doesn't make sense but it's going to make sense in a minute.
I'm going to say hash and of course then search.
So the pathname is going to be equal to whatever we are using inside the two.
So it's going to be the actual route.
So it's going to be profiled.
OK.
Now the second one the hash whenever we use around is going to take us to profile and it's going to
add at the end of the Al is going to add hash in this case let's say that I want to add.
I don't know.
Hash tag Francis whatever it's going to go at the end and paste it and just put it at the end.
You're going to say coma and then the search.
So the search is going to be just a crazy string.
So if I do chest like this and say profile and that equal to true if we go right here to the profiles
your dating profile then the query string and at the end of the URL we get the hash tag.
So of course this is really useful but it depends on which that what you're building which kind of application
you're building.
Maybe you can use search to pass properties between you or else since we are using re-active just a
single page job.
You're not going to use it that much but it's cool.
You know it's good to know that we have access to this.
OK.
So let's keep moving moving to the next thing.
Now what I want to do I want to catch it say let's pretend that I am inside profile.
Let me just delete this for now.
Just delete it.
Just leave the pathname.
OK.
So if I go to profile we go to profile.
Now what I want to do I want to add a link inside of posts but this link should be taking me to slash
profile for Slash posts.
OK so let's pretend right here.
That said that I have a domain is going to be my awesome app outcome and I whenever I click this dad
is going to take me to user but I'm sorry to profile just like that.
Sorry.
Posts are going to use posts.
But since we are inside profile what I want this link to do is to take me to forward slash profile for
Slash posts just like that one for the link to know that we are inside profile and instead of taking
me two posts just take me to profile for snatch posts.
We can do this by hand.
You know we need to do something kind of dynamic right here.
So OK so I'm going to go to profiles and first we're going to be using.
We're going to be using a link right here.
So whenever we need to use a link we need to bring re-act road or dom.
If not you're not going to be able to use it.
So I'm going to paste it and the only thing that we can be using from here from here the reground Dom
is going to be link.
So I get to copy paste and say link.
So right here I'm going to create a link real simple link open close and then take me to forward slash
profile for Slash posts so I can know that this is clear.
OK so I'm going to say to open close and I'm going to say posts whatever.
Of course it's not going to happen.
If I click right here it's going to take me two posts.
I don't want this.
I want to do something else.
Now whenever you use react to writer Dom Rianne router and you have the browser router this parent component's
is going to pass a set of options just like what you're using prompts.
Well same thing this browser router is going to give you some probs with all the information about the
routes and whatever you're using.
OK so if I go to profiles I'm going to catch that.
I'm going to catch the prompts and going to see props and they're going to cancel out the proms and
see what we get.
And sorry props I don't know why I say bedposts props but going to reload the page.
And of course going to have that check the console.
And of course there we go to profile and we have a history inside probs a location and a match.
So you know we have a lot of information inside the props whenever we use Riak router we have a lot
of things we can use.
So what I want to do I want to get a dynamic Eurail from here and you know we check prop's we have the
information right here we know that the path its profile.
So what we can do we can get the Euro dollar the you are l from there.
OK so I'm going to go right here and I'm going to pass a set of rules just like we did before with pathname
and I say pathname open close and the path for this one is going to be using tempera strengths open
close.
And what I want to get is going to be inside props inside match.
Inside you are all going to go right here and going to say prompts that match dot you are l and then
whenever you get the parent directory which in this case is profile I want you to take me to posts.
So in this case we are always getting a dynamic Eurail you know dynamic directory.
If we use it this way whenever we are inside profile it's going to be profiled force posts and if we
are inside posts it's going to be for Slash post for Slash posts.
Ok so if we click this it's going to take us to profile and then post.
So that is working.
OK let's get let's talk.
Talk about something else right now.