Right.
So what happens if I'm inside posts and right here inside post.
I'm going to get just a list of posts.
Let's pretend that we want to build it.
Why not.
So I'm going to have the post number one.
You're going to have the opposed number two for example and then maybe post number three.
Just three simple posts.
So whenever we load the supplication I'm going to have this list I'm going to bring the link Madill
right here just like we are doing it right here.
Just get a copy of this go to posts and paste it down here.
I'm going somewhere.
Don't worry.
And then what we need to do we need to link to this specific post.
So this post list is going to come from a database lets say whatever database.
And this of course is going to do the linkage to the actual post.
So are we going to use a link We're going to rappel ink just right here.
We're going to say Lenk and then just you know link link.
Let me finish.
But this of course is going to be it's going to have to property and this is going to be two forward
slash posts and we already have that that path which is going to be posts right here posts and it's
going to be post for Slash and then maybe number one and they're going to have the two and the three.
So I'm going to go and paste it.
It's going to be two and three.
OK.
So let's go to home.
Going to go home.
I want to go to posts so I'm going to get my post-box number one post number two and post number three.
Of course we need to add a break just to make it a little bit better.
And there we go.
So OK we have this list so I'm going to click and post number one and it's going to go to local host
for I-Slash posts for Slash and number one.
This is going to be the idea of our post.
Now the thing is that whenever you go to this route I want to fetch the data that belongs to this post
to the ID number one.
And if we go right here we are only getting whatever it's inside post.
We're getting the on the route.
This route.
So what we need to do we need a way to create.
We need to create a model that it's going to be listening for this route and then it's going to render
the data that we have for post number one.
OK.
So I'm going to create that route.
And again I'm going somewhere.
Don't worry we're going to create a new file and this one is going to be on no post item makes sense.
Most of that has got so inside post item pretty much we're going to have the same thing than this going
to go to post.
Item the lead and right here and going to say post detail.
We don't need the link right here and we need to pass to create this to put a different name.
So let's put.
Post item.
Of course we need to export it and we need to require this file from the index so we can require the
path.
So I'm going to say import and then post post item.
Very good.
It's going to be from and then dash components and then for Slash and then post item.
Okay.
So this route is ready.
So now I'm going to create a post I'm sorry I'm going to carry it around for this.
I got a copy of this pasted at the bottom and we're going to say whenever we get a post with ID and
in this case let's pretend that we won the one the number one begin to be using the route for post.
And we're going to be using this component but it's just an out.
So if we go to post one you're getting posts and we're getting one but you know we are getting the PPOs
detail we are getting that component.
We are getting that text but we're still getting the post the main parent component.
And the thing is that both routes have posts.
So what we need to do to this one we need to say exact.
So now we are getting the post detail.
Now the thing is that right now this ID it's hard coded in and realized this ID is going to be dynamic
you could be receiving a request for a post number one post number to post 56 or whatever.
And notice that right here I'm doing 56 but this is not working because I'm the we have the number one
hardcoded.
So we need to find a way to make this field dynamic and this are called Perhaps we need to be use of
feature from react to use perhaps.
Now to past dynamic data to listen for dynamic data right here we're going to use the common currency
con and then whatever we want to listen.
In this case we are passing an ID so I'm going to say Id Now if I do id I have 6:56 56 right here but
I'm still getting the post detail.
If you go to post detail you know we just have a text it's a loading this.
So you know it's working.
Whenever used con you're meaning you're saying that you want to use that dynamic value right here and
this could be whatever you want.
Let me say that first we wanted the I.D. and then for example a user name something like that.
Of course nothing is going to happen because we need a user name.
I'm going to say the username of this guy is going to be Francis and it's going to load that data is
going to load that component because we have a match right here.
So another thing is that OK we are passing dynamic data.
How can we catch it inside here.
How can we get that data.
Because whenever you get a request for this you're going to enter this component this view and you need
to grab the fifth the sixth the Francis and then you need to go to the database do whatever you need
to do and render that post.
Well remember that we talked about the browser router and everything else that whenever we use re-act
router is going to pass all the options inside prompts.
Well same idea are going to go right here and say props and of course if I do console log and then prompts
me bring the console.
Make this a little bit bigger.
No that's fine.
So I'm going to be doing log the prompts an inside match right here just like before we have all the
data for this and right here you have perhaps you have the ID and the username.
So right here what we could say OK to do just render the prop's dot match dot programs dot ID in this
case and I I to do the same thing for the username.
Let's put it right here.
It is a DOS and then perhaps and then username.
So in our time we load around with dynamic data we are catching that data and then you can do whatever
you wish right here.
Let's put something else let's say 8 8 8 and then Janice whatever.
So we get the data you always get the information you're getting.
You said we are router is going to pass the information inside prompts.
So you know prompts are really really important for us to pass information between components.
So you're going to be using this the whole time.
We're going to be using this the whole time.
So let's go to a different topic right now.
OK so now I'm going to show you some additional features of re-act router.
Now instead of using browser router just like you're using right here we could use an alternative wave
to manipulate the L.
We get on top for example instead of bringing the browser router I'm going to say hash router just like
that hash Roder.
So this one is going to make the URL a little bit different and notice that you're getting an error
message browser router.
It's not defined.
And the thing is that if we use this one we cannot use browser router right here.
We need to replace this for hash router.
And if it were the page you're getting it and notice that at the end of the year you're all the domain
domain domain.
So we are getting a hash stack and then for Slash.
So whenever we use this the u r l is going to be built just like this.
If I go to posts after the hash tag then you get the Euro.
If I go to profile you know we get profile hash tag and then profile.
So this is the way it works with this.
So you know again it depends on what you're building and what you want to do if you want to use the
normal your L or then hash tag for Shlash of L.
This was very common with the first versions of angular I use this lot.
So OK.
We have another one that is going to be called Memory router and by the keyboard memory you can guess
what this is going to do.
So whenever we use memory router instead of getting a urinal you're not going to get anything.
Everything is going to be stored in memory.
You know it's not going to change the L or is not going to show you what you're getting.
If I go home we get home if I go to posts we are getting the posts new posts but nothing is going to
happen to the euro.
When got it just like I told before.
This depends on what you're building.
In my opinion the the browser router is the best because now everyone it's familiar with this with the
L and is certain that most people whenever they use change something or do something.
They look at the out and having the Ural with the directories and everything else.
It's really really useful.
So most of the times you going to be using browser Roder But it's it's good to know that we have different
choices right here.
OK so moving on instead of just using rgle links for the header to right here we have a different option.
We have Browder's gonna give us something that is going to be called nav link if you want to.
We want to use a navigation bar just like this.
We can bring something that is going to be called Knobloch so Napp link is going to create a navigation
for you.
Just as with the link.
The option to use links with that link.
But you have some additional options I'm going to change all of this to now blank and then same thing
right here.
OK.
And of course if I were the page nothing happens.
Everything stays the same.
But for example with nobbling you get some additional options.
Let me just break it down so instead of.
Well besides the two you have one option that is going to be active style so you can choose which color
this link is going to show whenever it's active.
In this case I'm going to say color.
Sorry I meant a mistake inside the double curly braces.
I'm going to say color.
I'm going to say read it of course.
Notice that this is just a.
So if I go to home get nothing if I go to posts.
Notice that the posts it's highlighted so is changing the color.
Lets me inspect this.
We get the color color red and if we go right here we have style and color red.
So this is just the styling for this.
But you know it's a nice option that we can use that we can use the styles we can use classes instead
of active style.
Going to say active was active class name I believe active and then class name so same thing.
We can pass a class the name of class.
So in this case I'm going to say select it just like that selected.
Of course if we were little the page and I inspect posts link are going to get the class of selected
whenever it's selected.
And if I go home of course we don't have that class so that's good.
This is good.
To use nice to use and nice to know that we have this feature.
Would react router.
OK so let's move to the next topic.
We're going to be talking about Riak routers switch is going to be short a short one.
It's really useful.
So if you know about Riak routers switch just go to the next section.