Right.
So so far we were getting a tiny problem but we fixed it using the exact keyword.
I'm going to leave the exact I'm going to go back to that problem.
I'm going to give you a different solution for this.
So of course if I remove the X act and we go to the main application to home we get home.
But if we go to posts we get home and we get posts and this is because the route is pretty much the
same right here.
We have four slash and right here we have four slash.
So this passes through and it's rendering the home and the same thing with posts is going to go to the
next one.
And we have four slash and then posts is going to render that of course you know this makes sense.
Now the thing is that if we put ex-addict just like here we are telling we are prouder that we want
to rendered this route only if it matches everything that we have in the path.
And of course that is fixing the problem.
Now a router is going to give us a different solution for this.
We're going to have the ability to use switch.
So I'm going to do coma and I'm going to bring switch to this just like a majoris crypt switch.
Well same same idea.
I'm going to go at the bottom and I'm going to wrap all the routes inside the switch statement but not
statement so much good.
OK.
So everything is inside switch.
So how how is this going to work.
OK.
So in theory if I just really love the application and I made a mistake is going to be switch just like
that or reload the application.
Everything works good.
You know we go to home.
We go to posts profile and everything works great.
But the problem is that we're still using Excel.
So if I remove this it should be working right.
OK.
So that's really the application.
If I go to home we get home if I go to posts we get home.
We are not getting posts at all at all.
And if you go to profile.
Same thing.
We are just getting home.
So how this switch is working.
How does this work.
So if this switch is just like a switch statement just vanilla javascript switch is going to start checking
the route is going to get around right here.
It's going to start checking the routes is going to say OK.
Does this match the criteria.
Yes because we have a latch.
It's going to be rendering this one which is home which is what we get and everything else.
It's not going to be rendered.
It's just a rendering.
The first one that matches the criteria.
OK.
And if you go to post of course not that's going work.
Let me just remove this just like this.
If you go to posts of course we get posts we get home.
We are of course we are not getting home we will get nothing because we didn't have that route.
If you go to a profile you know it works.
But the thing is that we need a home.
So how can we make this work.
OK so I'm going to grab this one.
It just says just chop it and paste it at the end of the switch.
Of course if I do this it should be working well.
Yeah.
We go to home.
If you go to posts we are getting posts.
If you go to a profile of your getting profile so the the logic behind that is is that this works like
a switch statement.
We need to send all the less specific routes.
At the end of the chain and the more specific routes at the top.
For example if we start checking posts Let's go to posts.
Going to go to posts.
Number two and remember we added a username.
I'm going to say Francis whatever.
If I go right here you know you're not getting the ID and Francis it's because this one matches this
one so search is going to render this one but not the other one so it's not going to go here.
So again same then before we need to put this one at the end of the chain because it's less specific.
And if we notice of course this one it's really really specific.
OK.
With that logic let's just check it out.
If you go to two and Francis we are getting the tomb Francis we go to posts we get posts and profile
and home.
So everything works remember with search send the less specific routes on the bottom and the most specific
routes up top.
And that way it's going to work just fine.
OK so let's move forward.
Let's go to the next section.
We're going to be talking about the red redirections and the 4 0 4 page because of course you always
need for 0 4 pitch.
Let's go to the next section.