Right.
So now we're going to talk about something that could be very important for your applications and it's
going to be how to re direct users.
So Riak router is going to provide us a component we can use to do this.
And if you're thinking why would I redirect you user.
Well let me tell you is one of those things that we are going to use it at least once in our projects.
So first we need to import this.
This module can do coma and then redirect.
So how can we use this one.
OK.
We have different ways to use this.
I'm going to go inside the router and notice that I am inside the switch and the router and I'm going
to say read direct.
Now this redirect is going to take a few options.
If you're are inside the router first we have the from me make a space from.
And then we have the two.
And if you think about it it can make sense from is going to be from where we're going to get from which
request and then do that too.
So if we get a request from profile that the user is trying to enter the profile we're going to kick
the user back to home make sense.
So if I go to home.
Good.
If you go to post works if you go to profile it's going back to home.
So it's kicking the user back for good.
And if you see it right here at the top you can see D L flashing.
You know it's just flashing.
But this is one way to use it.
Now the thing is that this is not very realistic.
What you're going to be doing most of the times it's keeping the user back if he's not authorized or
something like that.
So I'm going to delete this now I don't need it right now and then I get a go at the top and just delete
this one as well I'm going to go to post.
I I'm going to go to profile.
I'm going to bring this module this direct.
So now inside the return what I can do is just use this redirect just like we use it for redirect opening
close.
And of course we don't have the option from because if you think about it from where we are already
inside that route so we can use just the two.
So whenever the react it's a rendering this component's is going to be days and it's going say OK OK
we want to kick the user back no matter what.
And it's going to kick the user back if I go to profile again to post it works profil not happening
just clicking the user back.
And again most of the times are going to be using this in a different context.
If the user enters profile you want to check if the user is authorized and if it's not then it's going
to run this code.
So OK just going to copy this and I'm going to say redial and whatever just going to create a function.
So right here at the top I'm going to say Konst reader or whatever.
Open and close up.
Sorry.
I'm going to make it fun.
Our function are very close.
And this one is going to do this.
So right here we are both in this function.
The function should be running and after the function runs we're going to get this.
Of course you know a reader let me see if we reload the page everything is working.
We get no errors.
This is a warning because we need to do some links.
We are not using the link in the header.
You're using that link.
So you know but don't worry.
So if you go to a profile it's passing.
And so this code it's not being executed.
And again if you think about it this is just.
We are not doing anything.
We're just putting the attack right here.
So what you can do.
You can just say return opening close and what it's going to do this function is going to inject this
GSX inside here.
So of course if you go to a profile not happening is just going to kick the user back again.
OK.
That's good.
This works is a good method but I'm not a not a very big fan of just doing this.
Now inside props if you remember whenever we use re-act router inside prompts we get a lot of features.
A lot of methods we can use with you or else and with routes.
So inside prompts you you have one that is going to be history.
So we're going to enter prop's then enter history history then dot.
And what I can say is push just like that.
Push opening close and I'm going to specify.
I want to kick the user back to which route in this case is going to be home.
And this is not react this is just pure javascript or going to be interacting with the history of the
browser and say OK I want to put this at the end of the list inside the browser.
So of course the last element on the list is going to be executed.
So it's going to go to this route.
Now if I go to a profile you know works is not letting the user end.
It's executing the function and the function it's just changed the history of the browser.
So you know this one it's a little bit better because you're not using this module if you want.
I can just delete this one and we're going to be including the one last module inside our application.
OK.
So it works good.
So no we need to talk about in how to create a 4.
0 4 that's something really important to read so how to create a 4 0 4 page that say that the route
that the user is trying to enter it's not defined so it's going to be whatever route of course you should.
That should give the user a component for this that it's not home.
Notice that I'm typing whatever it's taking me to home.
Why is it doing this.
Because we have one rule that it's matching.
Remember that our our last drought says that whenever you get a path for home it's going to take you
back home.
I'm sorry for Slash and then take you back home.
So again this is just logic.
If I do route right here and then open it close what we can do.
We can just say if route nothing.
If none of this criteria is are matched we want to fall back to this one.
So we create kind of a fallback right here going to say render inside that we.
Every route we get a method that's going to be called render.
And we can render whatever we want right here.
I'm going to open it close and just pass some GSX some some dumb GSX going to be oops four or four.
OK.
So if I go right here to this route of course this one is not right.
That's not going happen it's not going to lead it's not going to show oops four or four because this
rule the one before 400 for this condition is matched.
So again we need to fall back one more time to the exact.
So if I reload the page we get four four.
And if I go home of course it works OK.
So this is just the simplest way where you have how you can use for for using a fallback.
Let's say that you want to render a component right here for a for for going to delete the render.
I'm going to say whenever the around the user or the application is not finding a route for this we
want to send the user to post whatever.
So if you go to Home With works posts works profile works and if I type what ever taken is taking be
taking us to posts.
Ok so that works.
So in real life you should be creating a component that is going to be for or four or not found something
like that.
OK.
That's good.
Let's keep moving forward.
We need to do some other things.
Really important things are the next section going to be talking about re-act life cycles.