So whenever reacts reactor starts the application and starts building a component or updating or receiving
prompts or whatever re-act is going to do everything in steps inside a component.
So this steps are going to be called re-act life cycles.
So OK I have I've created a class based component just rendering just some GSX you know just a normal
class based component nothing magical right here.
And I've created a route for this.
So since now you can use you know how to use routes you can create one in your own you know right here
and go to live and I get lifecycle is really simple.
We know how to do this.
So now I'm going to go right here and look at I've created the class re-act is going to be using this
component and then just rendering some.
So of course we are just rendering this but a lot of things happened before we render something so re-act
is going to do everything in steps.
The first the first step is going to be get default prompts just like that.
When a reactor starts that component is going to get the default prompts.
That's why whenever we go right here and we say cancel log there's the props.
The props are available for us to use inside the render.
Because this is the first thing that we act it's doing.
It's the setting that default prompts inside the components.
So if I go right here we have the prompts that we have router it's passing remember that we react router
we get the prompts.
OK so that's good.
That's the first thing that it's going to do going to come in this.
The second thing that re-act is going to do is going to set the default state.
Right now we don't have a state.
So we're going to do it right now said default and then state this is the second thing that re-act is
going to do.
We're going to say state equals to something and then it's going to be equal to title.
And I get to do this get a copy and paste it.
So this is the second step.
And that's why whenever we go to render and we say this that state that title is going to be available
for us inside this state OK.
So I'm going to say this that state that title just like that.
And of course you're getting.
We get we are getting the title and this is the second thing that re-act is going to do.
Then we have a third step that is going to be before render just like that.
And I'm going to go back in a minute.
So the fourth step is going to be the actual render.
You know just renders Jim.
Sex sex and make this right.
This is the fourth step and that we have an additional step that is going to be five after GSX we have
access to before and after the render method.
OK.
So that before render we can have access to some default some built in methods just like render if we
think about it.
Render is a default method method from react inside here we have one that is going to be called component
will mount going to say components just like that component and then well and then mount open it close.
So this component this code this method is going to always render before something gets rendered is
going to get called before we were under something.
So right here is going to say cancel log opening close and just going to pass this tax so we can view
it on the screen.
And after re-act is going to render this re-act is going to run this first is going to render this and
that it's going to run a different method that is going to be called instead of component will amount
it's going to be components components did mount open and close.
Now I'm going to do the same thing after GSX after render let's call it after render makes more sense
to say console log opening close.
And then after render.
Right.
So if we go right here we are getting the life cycles and then we get three before render and five after
render.
So re-act is going to start the component is going to set the default.
So the state is going to run this code and notice that I'm not running this code and I'm calling this
method is running by default is going to be executed by react.
So we get three before rendering then is going to render the GSX.
That's why we get life cycles.
And then of course we get five after render.
It's going to go and by default run this component it mouth.
OK that's good.
So no.
Notice what happens if I'm going to copy and it's just going to chomp it and put it before the component.
Well now we know that javascript executes executes everything in a single order.
So if I put it before the computer it will mount.
This is still going to be executed after that component will mount still working.
So let me let me do something else.
I'm going to go right here.
I going to say on the component will amount I'm going to say documents just like that document dot then
query selector and I get to select the three TAC right from the Dom can say age 3 and they are going
to change the style is going to change the color to something else style that color.
And then it's going to say that it's going to be equal to red.
So let me come this.
Now if I copy this let me just read the application.
I'm going to mistake.
I meant to type a get one second let me copy this.
Just gonna delete it.
OK.
So if I paste this on the browser we are changing the color of the three tag right directly from the
DOM.
Now if I run this code on the component will mounth we're going to get an error just like we were getting
before and reloaded and cannot read properly style of no.
So we are trying to change something the color of something and H-3 task that doesn't exist.
Remember that component will mount.
We'll run before the render so we don't have this inside the Dom just yet.
And of course we get the error and nothing gets rendered.
Now if I do the same thing just going to copy and paste on the component did mounth we are doing it
because this code was rendered and then this method was executed.
That's why we're able to change the color so we have a lot more of this we can do a lot more thanks.
Let's go to the next section and just move forward this.