OK so now we know that something happens before we render the end the day of sex and after we render
the GSX gut so we know this we have available we have this methods available but of course we have more.
I'm going to go over here inside the render.
I'm going to cancel.
I'm going to cancel law and then render just like that.
Make it Kappes render.
OK.
So going to reload the application and I'm going to I'm going to get three before render.
Then we get the render and then after render.
We know this.
I'm going to add a click and I'm going to be changing the state.
I have the code ready so we don't have to lose time doing this and we're going to make it just like
that and they begin to be setting the state.
So what is happening right here I just added a button that whenever we click it begin to be changing
the state of title to something else.
Real simple we just change the title right here.
So if I click it we change the title we know how to do this.
We're just sending the new state of something.
Now notice that we get rendered twice whenever we change the state of the component re-act is going
to be listening for that.
So he's going to detect a change on the state and it's going to really render whatever code you have
inside.
And that's why it's able to update the contents of this.
Right here we are rendering the title whenever we click change.
It's going to update the state is going to rerun under.
And now this state the title is going to be equal to whatever title we put right here.
So that's why we get the render twice.
And this is what single page applications do.
They re rendered the content the whole time whenever they detect an update.
This is what they do.
That's normal.
Now the thing is that right here we have two methods that are going to be listening before rendering
and after rendering.
That's good.
So we have some additional methods right here.
There are going to be checking that we can use to detect whenever something before something gets updated
or after something gets updated.
Notice that I click click changed changed state and I'm only getting the rendered so.
Before render and after rendering are not running.
This only happens once.
OK.
So what I'm going to do.
I'm going to call two different methods.
I'm going to do component just like that components.
And then we'll just like compound when.
But it's going to be compliant and we'll update.
So this method is going to it's going to run before we update something and then we have another one
that is going to be component and then that and then update just like that and this method is going
to be used after it gets updated.
So if I go right here and again to say console log and then before Before Update make sense before updates
and I do I'm going to do the same thing and this one is going to be after update of course I'm going
to rerun the whole application just from the start.
We get first the component will mount then the render and then component that mounth I'm going to click
and change and we get Before Update render again because we are rendering the application.
And then after the update.
So we have access to this so we can know when something whenever something is happening in our application
that's good.
You know it's good to have this once.
Of course we have more.
Let's let's we have the component should component update and then we have the component will we see
props.
This ones are not that easy.
So let's talk about this once.
So we have the shoot component up that we can use this one to check the changes of the props and the
state.
And this one it will return true or false.
Told you that this one is going to be a little bit confusing.
So let me I'm going to say should let me just show you the code and we will we will build from there.
I'm going to say should component and then update just like that opening close.
Now from the start this one is going to receive two arguments just going to put it.
And then we can add this because this is going to be next and then prompts and then the second argument
is going to be next.
And then at this function this method it should be returning true or it's going to return false.
So now whenever we received an update we make an update on our application.
It's going to go to it's going to fall to this one and it's going to be checking the next state of prop's
or the next State of the state.
So if we are changing the state is going to enter here and inside next date we can have whatever new
value we are passing not the previous one.
So if I say counsel law and then we counsel logged the next state.
Let me just copy this and remember that this function which this method meets to return true or false
are going to return true.
Just for now return true by default is going to return true.
But we're going to do this for just in case.
OK.
I'm going to click to change and it's going to change something else.
And notice that right here at the bottom you're getting title something else.
So we're getting the new body the one that we are passing.
You know the update one got here.
It's just doing the consulate and of course we are returning true.
So everything gets the normal behavior.
I've noticed what happens if I say false.
Going to reload the application I'm going to click to change.
And we're getting the title something else the next state of things.
But you know nothing's happening.
We are not getting an update.
So right here what we can do what we could do is to check the previous state and the next date.
And if if something happens that we don't want it to happen we can just return false and the application
will never update the render will never we render.
So let's do it right now.
Going to do the lead counsel law and of course are going to say the consulate.
First let me just show you.
So let's say that we can we can now put the consulate that we can do.
View the next date.
And of course if you wanted to see the previous state remember that we have it available inside this
state and that title and the next date is going to be title again and the will of the page if it clicked
change we have life cycles which is the current one and the next one so what we can do we can evaluate
right here with whatever code we wish to check the first pre-state and the next state.
And if it matches we let the user lead the component update or not.
Let's see in practice I'm going to say if you're going to be checking the next state title.
OK.
So if the next state title matches something I want to not move forward.
So I got to say it's going to be triple equal to something else.
And if it's of course if the next State of the title which is going to be true it passes.
I want to return false.
I don't want to update the components.
I'm going to say return and then false.
Now if it passes I'm going to return true.
Just like that they're going to reload the application.
I'm going to click the change and of course since we are passing something else the component will not
react is not going to really render the application.
If I change something right here of course this rule will not be met.
So it's going to do the update.
It clicked change.
And we are getting something else is doing the update.
So this way we can control what comes inside our application and decide if we want to move forward with
the update or not.
You know it's really useful.
And we're going to be using this a little bit in the future.
OK so we have one more to go.
Let's see that one and then just move forward.
So we have a couple or a couple more to go.
We have component will we see prop's says we know why the what the all the ones do we kind of know what
this one is going to do.
I'm going to say component's component and it's going to be well received and then props open and close
as a method.
So this one is going to be checking for new props because they cancel longer than opening close and
then before receive and then props and admitted typo receive props.
So this one is going a little bit hard to check.
So let me tell you what's going on.
We go to live.
We really the application is going to show was the components and of course we get the will mount the
render and the mouth and the only props that we are getting are from Briac router.
That's good.
We know that the only prompts we get are from re-act router.
OK of course if I go to profile nothing happens because we're not inside the life component.
And if you go back to live we get the will mount and then the render and then after render.
So this one is going to be listening for new props.
So if I go to profile and then alive this component is going to have some default props and this case
the default prompts are going to be from re-act router.
So we are not receiving new props.
They are the default one.
Now we are already inside the component life components.
So if I click on life again we are not going to reload the component component.
Its already mounted.
But what it what is going to do is going to be reloading some things.
So if I click on life again we are going to get before we see props the components it's already mounted
but whenever we click right here we are saying re-act Browder to reload this route and it's passing
the prompts again to this component.
And that's why we are getting before we see props.
So right here you can just you know maybe just check whenever whenever the apparent components it's
sending you props and this could be you know whatever could be a fetch from the urinal or maybe some
new data from a user or a socket or whatever.
Ok this one it's kind of a simple.
So then we have one more to go.
And again this one is going to be really simple.
We have the component will and mounts says we have the component will mount.
We have the opposite of this component that mount is going to be listening whenever the air component
gets unmounted.
So components component and then of course dead mounts knobs will amount just like that on Mount opening
close.
And again just like before I'm just typing this by hand I've disabled all the plug ins.
But you have tons of plug ins.
At least with the code to do the out of typing.
You can have some templates to use right here so you don't have to type it every time you need to use
it.
I'm just doing it right here by hand because I'm just showing you.
So I'm going to say cancel long and then on mnze.
Right.
So whenever we mount we do the reload and reactive scheme because this component which triggered the
component will mount that we have before render that we have the render and then the after render.
Now if I go out of this component we get the on Mount.
So it's unmounting the life component and it's mounting a different component of course.
But really we have access to know whenever a component gets unmounted.
So right here maybe maybe just maybe what you could do is maybe a netballer request to all to lock the
user out or to do whatever you need to do if the user goes out of that component if the user leaves
that component.
You can know when that happens and you can take some actions.
So this one could be really useful.
OK.
So that's the end of re-act life cycles don't worry.
We're going to be using them again to be using them on a real life scenario.
And we begin to be using them.
OK.
So you're going to get a lot of practice.
Let's keep moving forward.
I want to talk about some other things that we're going to be using maybe with the re-act life cycles
or something else.
Some other topics of react so let's keep moving forward.