So whenever re-act executes the render or the return with some GSX and so on we can make use of conditionals
inside of the statements.
So I'm going to create a new route to play with this just a little bit and create a simple route.
And I've tried to create the brand here with you so we can get familiar with this process of creating
routes.
So this route is going to be called conditional just like that.
I'm going to create a route that it's going to be conditional.
We didn't have this just yet conditional just like that in a go at the bottom of the copy.
This one going to go right here at the bottom.
Then paste it and I'm going to say conditional and you know same named right here.
Conditional.
OK so I'm going to go and create the round for this.
And again same thing conditional.
I get to go at the top and grab that component's real simple.
So we did this a few times already.
But we didn't have the component as yet.
So going to create it right now is going to be conditional digests and conditional is going to be just
a functional components.
So I get to go to home because we don't have much code right here.
I'm just going to paste it and rename everything conditional conditional.
There we go.
And same thing right here at the bottom.
And just to make sure that you're getting the correct roud I'm going to say conditional just like that.
OK he's going to rewrite under.
Everything is good.
If you go to conditional You know it's working.
We get that route.
So now what we can do inside here inside of the return we can make use of curly braces and right here
we can run kind of an IF statement.
And it's a kind of because we cannot really use this we cannot do this right here.
But what we can do we can use the ternary operator.
If you don't know what fernery is it's going to be just checking of Arbel could be whatever.
And then as you can to say equal equal or whatever you want to check you know in this case we want to
check.
It's true.
And if it's true you can have something like this.
So what it's happening right here is that it's going to check the value it's true and if it's true it's
going to pass.
So this statement just like NF is going to be true.
So what's it's going to be rendered this code with Will will be executed.
And if this is false which means that the rule the rule is there's no match with this rule begin to
be outputting this content.
So this is kind of a doing.
If and then value triple equals true.
And if it's true we rendered this one because it's this one and if.
Else which is going to be the calling we render the other one to you know just the same thing.
Then there's a shorter version.
So inside re-act inside the Rander or the return we can do this.
So I'm going to delete this.
Now if we do that this condition it means that by default the value is true.
We don't have a value right here.
So I'm going to create a variable.
There's going to be called value and it's going to be equal to true.
Now if this condition this value is equal to true we want to render whatever code we have right here
and what we can do we can return some GSX if you want it.
So I'm going to say div opening close and this let me put it at the bottom div is going to say hello.
It's true.
Now if this condition it's not math which means it's false.
What we can do we can say no nothing is going to be is going to get rendered.
So if we check this we get.
Hello.
It's true.
Now if I change it to false let me put right here this and see it change on the fly.
One second Almazan.
So if I save it it's going to reload and we are not getting anything because this condition is not met.
And again this is the same thing.
And in this just like that.
So if we change it to true of course it works.
Of course if you wanted to do the opposite we would we would have to to change the statement just a
little bit.
If you say that this one is false.
What we can do of course it's not going to work.
But what we can do we can add some more GSX right here at the bottom.
So we could say div and then hello.
It's false.
So if the values are not false we get.
And if we change it to false decoded the code that's going to run is going to be this one.
So we can we can make use of this.
I'm going to be using this the whole time you know this is pretty common right now.
So OK.
So right now we are just checking a viable what we can do we can use a function.
Let's say I'm going to create a function that is going to be returning a Boolean or whatever it's going
to say return value.
And that's when it's going to be equal to fat R-OH function just like that.
And you know you're going to do all your logic right here whatever.
Then at the end you're going to return something.
In this case I just get this function returns true.
So what we can do instead of checking viable we can check the function function returns true.
We get.
Hello.
It's true if it's returning false we get.
It's a false that mistake false so you know that's working.
So you know you can use a function you can do whatever function you want and then you just check this.
And now right here we are just returning this content right here inside.
But what we can do we can just make all of this logic inside the actual function.
It's going to create different function just to prove this.
It's going to see a concert and then show it of course is going to be a fat R.O. function just like
before.
And this one is going to be returning something.
So I'm going to grab this just copy and paste it down here and I'm going to copy all of this and then
just delete it.
So we are just calling this a show.
Show it.
So ink.
So here what we can do if you think about it if we do the same thing then before we say return and we
return this code just like this.
So you know this one will not work but it is a drag.
Here we are calling this function and we are returning something and we are returning something in curly
braces.
So whenever you try to return something inside of a function with react which means you want to return
some GSX this one.
Now it's not going to work.
So what I need to do we need to wrap everything in parenthesis this way it's going to work.
Now it is that we have the turn ready we need to address.
So I'm going to I'm going to use the same function that we have on top.
So if return value it's equal to true.
We want to to return this or we want to return.
Yes.
OK.
So I'm going to save it and look at we get.
Hello.
It's false because the return value is false.
If we change it to true of course we get.
Hello.
It's true.
So don't worry you will have the chance to interact and do more logic more complex logic using the conditionals
inside the actual render.
OK so let's move forward.
Let's go to the next topic.
We're going to be talking about pure components.