Right.
So there's a lot of confusion around pure components and they are real simple to understand and I guess
the confusion it's because we need to understand which problems pure components solve.
OK.
So first we can discuss the problem and then I'm going to tell you how to solve it.
So I'm going to go back to life to this route to the life route right here.
And of course we have everything else.
And what I'm going to do I'm going to comment all the code we have right here and I'm just going to
leave the state.
That's the only thing I'm going to leave right here.
So we have a state with a title which is the text that it's getting rendered right here.
If you go at the bottom we have the H-3 with this state title and we have a button to change the title
to something else.
OK that's reasonable.
Every time that we load this component is going to cancel log or render message right here.
So we get rendered OK that's fine.
So now if I go to click the change begin to change the title for something else and re-act will render
this component and show the new title which is something else could.
So I'm going to go and do click to change me on Mark this click the change oh nothing happens.
There we go.
So we get something else that's good and right here we get the first render with the first title and
then it's going to be rendered.
So we get the second render.
So that's good.
Now what happens if I keep clicking this click change I'm going to go right here.
I'm going to click it and we get the render again if I click it again we get render we get render and
we get you know we just keep getting render.
Now if we think about is about this this is the actual problem.
We're not changing the title the title it's always the same it's something else.
Whenever we change it for the first time so why is react.
Rendering the application since we have the same value.
So this is the problem.
Sometimes you can have a larger application with a lot of data going around and some things are going
to be changing some other things are not going to change but Riak will always be rendered whenever we
trigger something.
So with pure components we can we can add we could detect if the state changes and if the state changes
then it's going to render if not it's not going to be rendered.
So if you remember with the chute component update we can do this logic manually going to go in and
comment should component update.
We're going to reload the page.
So right here we are going to say if the next state of title is something else which is what we have
right here the bottom of the return is false.
So the application will not render.
So going a click to change and you know it's change you get first and then.
Then they save it again.
Sorry.
I'm going to go and click the change and of course nothing happens because this rule is met.
So we return false.
Now the thing is that this information it's hard coded.
How can we check the previous state.
So what we can do we can say this that state and then of course title and we're going to be comparing
the next title which whatever thing that we have inside the state.
So right now we have life cycles and we are changing.
And of course we are changing to something else.
So the state will not be the same so this will not happen and it's going to go and change the state
and we've rendered the application.
Notice that right here we get the first render.
OK so going it could change.
We change it to something else that's good.
So it's rendered for the second time.
So if I click it again it's not going to render this condition is met.
So he's returning false.
Now again imagine you have a lot of data a lot of state going around here.
A lot of information.
So what are you going to.
How are you going to create one scenario for every piece of state that you have.
Well that's kind of crazy.
So re-act is going to give us a component that we can use and this are pure components.
So right here we are doing class lab class life expense component.
So what we can do we can bring pure components.
I'm going to copy and paste it down here.
I'm going to go at the bottom and again and just comment this out because we are not going to need it.
OK.
So I'm going to reload the page and click to change it of course the change is going to happen because
we have something else right here.
Of course we have a different title than it click it.
And of course it's a rendering.
So we get something else.
Now if I click that nothing happens the pure components it's checking the state.
And since we don't have a real change inside the state it's not going to do anything good.
You know this is really really useful and pure components are really popular today.
You know the sense why reloading the whole application if the state it's the same.
OK that's good.
Let's go to the next.
The next lecture.