So ask for the latest version or react we are allowed to directly return arrays in the in the render.
So this is something that we could not do with re-act 15 but now the 16th version it's out so we can
do it.
So let me show you first with the old ways when they show you the old way and then we'll just refactor
to the new way.
And of course all the ways are valid.
So I'm going to go to the posts not just inside posts.
We just have three links you know same example than before.
Didn't change anything.
So I'm going to go right here and inside I'm going to create an object an array of objects.
So I'm going to say Konst and going to say IDS is going to be equal to an array an inside a created
you know the ID for each elements.
Right here we have the posed one to three and then the name of the link.
So I'm going to do that again to say id and the name is going to be equal to post 1 and we need three
links.
So I'm going to say coma paste.
And then of course coma and paste again they're going to change this.
Two and Three.
And same thing here.
You know we have our array.
So now right here what we need to do we need to do something else on this.
So we needed to create a variable that hosts a function and this function is going is going to return
the list is going to loop the array and then return each link.
So OK so I'm going to just say IDs and of course to loop a list.
We're going to be using map and of course map is a method and this one is going to take one item on
each iteration and then it will return the contents.
So I'm going to say return and then open it close.
So now here we need to return one thing.
So I'm going to wrap everything inside a span and right here we pass.
It's link.
So we're going to say link just like that.
And remember that at the top you're importing link from Brianne Groner Dom.
So going to say link and it's link each item that we return from a map.
In this case meets you have a key.
So we're going to say item that key item that Id sorry.
Then of course the space we need to pass it to because we have a link and we're going to say item dot
Id just like that.
OK.
So sorry I made a mistake.
The key is going to be inside the actual element know the parent element.
The one that it's containing.
So in this case is going to be the span.
So after that to what we would need to do we need to close the link just like that.
And right here we need to pass the name.
So it's going to be item that name.
And then I'm just going to add just to break me out right here.
Break open and close.
OK.
That's good.
So now what we need to do we need to make a reference to this loop is going to enter the map is going
to enter the IDs.
And for each each item is going to return a span with a link.
So with this in the past I'm going to go right here to open and close and make a reference to this OK.
So if I go to post we are getting we are getting each link post won.
You know post 2 and everything else so everything works this way.
Now we are using Riak 16 so there's kind of no need to create a viral to host a map.
What we can do we can do it directly in the return statement.
So we're going to go right here and get a copy.
The whole ID that map and then I'm just going to comment everything.
I'm going to go right here the return and what we do we just pasted we read the application.
You're getting the same exact result.
So you know that works.
So remember to always return the key of one of the main item on each iteration.
So now we can do more.
So I'm going to create a going to create a marvel me.
Let me just do this.
Either way do you have the code right here.
And again common the ID to as well I'm just going to delete all this.
So what we can do as well with the re-act 16 we can return an array.
So get to open and close an array after the return and I'm going to say hello coma and then just the
space.
I am just like that space.
You know just three values an array with three values a re-act app.
If I save this is going to reload it is going to render all the values we have on the array.
So this one works as well.
And if you think about it this right here is going to be it's a value.
So it's converting the value and outputting text.
So what we can do instead of returning this we could wrap everything inside a div and it's going to
be translated to GSX.
So let me just do it right now.
It's going to be dev and I'm just going to replace this and do the same thing with the other ones they
sold me out to space to save me.
Save it.
And you know we get the same thing.
Hello I am every act up and notice right here that we are getting an error message.
Each child in array should have a key.
So again whenever we are returning a list of things we always need to add a key for each elements.
So you know same thing I'm going to say key and the problem right here is that we need to hard code
the key and to do the unwon and just the old one and the keys are unique.
OK.
So you Fairouz save it reloaded.
We are not getting the error message.
And we get the actual result.
OK let's get let's keep moving forward.
We're going to move to h o C's.
It's going to be it's not going to be that easy to understand because we have many ways to use high
or other components overseas but we're going to do a few things.
It's going to get a little bit confusing.
So you need to put your thinking hat on.
OK.
Let's go to the next one.