Right.
So now we're going to be talking about h o C's day.
It stands for High or other components.
So this is another topic that it sometimes is hard to understand by developers because most of the time
we don't understand where to use it or why using it.
So I'm going to give you different different approaches are going to start with the easiest one.
So I'm going to go to profiles non-jazz and inside profiles.
If you go to profile of course is doing the direction.
So I'm going to comment this out OK.
So OK so we go to profile and we get take me to profile photos and everything is going to be tested
link.
Let me just delete the reader.
Rection good.
So OK so now what happens if this link you know this content we have right here that say that this code
is going to be something that is going to be using the whole time in your application.
You can repeat this GSX inside post maybe inside home you can do this a lot.
So we could use a high or other component just to try to show a template of this.
This is one way of using high or other components.
So what are you going to do.
I'm going to go to components.
I'm sorry to source.
I'm going to create a new folder that is going to be called a cease and right here going to create a
new file that is going to be called Card that jazz whatever it's going to you know I'm going to copy
the concept of home the template component.
And this one is going to be called car and then we're going to call this one current.
OK.
Got it.
That's good.
So now what this card it's returning it's going to be some diff.
But the thing is that what we want to do we want to call this to include this card component grab whatever
we have right here send that back to cart and then rendered that content inside that template that we
have right here.
Now if you remember we could use the we could do this with prompts the children.
OK.
So first include the card component going to say import that card from open and close that for Slash.
And we go back to H-how CS and we need to bring a card.
So now this component the card component it's available inside profiles.
Good.
OK.
So I'm going to go back to card and I get to create just desirable.
Can we just a marvel that you know we're going to be changing this style so it's out of style just to
you know just to check.
So I'm going to create a marvel that is going to be called style and there's one is going to be called
to background something simple background and light gray makes sense.
Light gray.
So now I'm going to go right here and say style then open and close and begin the same style.
OK so now what I want to do whenever I want to render this is going to be rendered within this template.
And this is going to be wrapped inside the car and it's going to change the background to light gray.
So right here and getting this component is going to be receiving some props and right here since we
want to rent or whatever we are going to be passing from profiles we always rendered Probst that children
just like that.
So this one is ready.
It's receiving some props.
It's returning a div and whatever contents we have inside props the children and we can have the background
of light gray.
So I got to go right here.
We are importing the cart so the only thing that I need to do right here I need to call this component
to use this component so I'm going to say cart and then just cart and everything is going to get rendered.
And we have the background of light gray.
So we're using this component as a high or there component of all the concepts we have right here.
So this is the very basic idea of a high or other component.
You know they're going to get a little bit difficult to understand begin to move forward right now to
the to the next topic which is a different way of using height or the components.
But this is the simplest way of a high or other component and you're going to be using again this the
whole time and we get when we hit the practice section of the course we're going to use this a lot because
we use it for pretty much everything.
OK.
So let's go to the let's go to the next approach of this.
OK so let's see a different approach of this.
Let's pretend that this profile section needs authentication.
So if the users have authenticated we want to let the user in if not begin to kick the user out or we
can you know just show an error an error message.
So we need to created high or other components to do this.
And I'm going to go right now to cosies and create a new file that is going to be called out just like
that.
So of course this is going to be just a component.
Just going to copy this and the markup and I'm going to call it off just like we did before.
No we're going to delete all of this for now we're just going to delete it.
And this one is going to this out it's going to receive some props.
And the only thing that it's going to do is going to return prompts the children
for now which is going to do this is the only thing that we can do.
So now we're going to go to profiles and I'm going to put this off and say import than all of that from
and we do dot dot for Slash.
H.O. sees forward slash.
And then we bring earth just like that.
And if you notice this is still working.
OK.
So we are not getting ours.
So now what I'm going to do I'm going to go right here and instead of doing dev I'm going to create
this out components and I'm going to wrap everything inside of it just like that.
There we go.
And close.
So now note notice that again this again is still working.
So we're bringing elth which is a component that is going to receive send children the job of all is
just to return the children.
So OK.
It's going to go to the next step then cart is going to get some children and child and car to Jarvis's
of cart.
It's going to be wrapping everything inside a div with this style and then return the children.
And then of course we get the link.
So everything is in kind of a in the casks cascade style.
So OK so now the job of off is not going to be just you know just returning the children begin to do
something else right here.
So the job of all that is going to be checking if the password is correct so I'm going to delete this
and get to make this a proper function.
So let's say that the user and of course we are pretending we're going to get to this part later.
This is going to get a lot more complex.
So let's say that whenever the user enters you're going to get something that it's password one two
three that's the password of the user right now.
So we're going to be doing an F and if else statement.
So if the user if the password of the user matches something we want to to let the user using if not
we are not going to let the user in.
So we're going to say if the past is going to be equal to you know password one two three if not begin
to do something else and then do the US.
OK.
So if the password is different than 1 2 3 what we want to do we want to return just an H-3 tax saying
you are not authorized something like that.
Now if the passport it's correct it which means that pass or one to three equals pass were one to three.
Of course we want to return and then prompts the children begin to move forward with that treat.
OK.
So this is going to reload and you know we get props that children if I add a number four for example
there's one are not going to be the same.
We're going to get you're not outthrust.
So what is happening right here.
Let's go again with whole process.
Including card which is an H O C an hour which is an oath.
OTOH Ozy.
So the first step is going to be going to the to the mouth component is going to be entering our component
and it's going to pass all the children's.
So off is going to check if the password it's correct or not is the password.
It's not correct.
Instead of returning all the children's which is going to be all of this code right here is going to
return just an H 3 task.
So the result of this instead of having this is going to be something like that.
So this is what we're getting right now.
Now if the passport it's correct is going to move forward and return prompts the children.
OK.
So inside props the children what we have is going to be the cart.
Now the cart is going to pass whatever children we have inside cart.
Is going to do the same process is going at first.
I did have an inside did this is going to return the children.
So we get all of this.
So now the result is going to be something like that and of course then we have the the the rest of
the children which is going to be the link to final cut.
You know we get the same result.
Let me save this reload we get not authorized.
And if you go off and match the passports it's working OK.
So this off as an h o c it's pretty pretty common going to be using this when we reach the authorization.
The out part of the course is security going to be using an agency and we're going to be using again
overseas for a lot of things.
OK.
That's good you know make sense but we need to talk about something else.
I could have skipped this.
It's a kind of a different approach of HFCS and I'm going to tell you how this works because maybe you
inspect someone else's code.
You can find and find an see with this kind of weird syntax.
So let's go to the next section.
It's going to be a little bit long.
So let's go to the next section and I'm going to show you the.
Show you this weird HLC.