OK so now I will explain you a different type of high or other component.
And at first it's going to look really really weird.
But don't worry.
Then we can stop and explain what's going on.
So you know you're going to get it.
Don't worry it makes perfect sense.
But it looks weird at the beginning.
I've created a route so we can save some times some time is going to be a user.
The files is going to be user Dodge's And you know we just have a route that's going to be user and
it's just returning a div with a user one.
OK.
So first I'm going to start doing this.
I'm going to start tape typing all of this and again is not going to make sense but then I will explain
you are going to go to H.O. CS and I get to create a new file that is going to be called user HAMC whatever
user H.O. see that jazz.
And just like always we need to import re-act from react just like that.
Is going to be a functional component so we don't need to bring components.
So now I'm going to I'm going to create a function that is going to be user a chose C and it's going
to be equal to a function just like we did before.
So this one is going to take some arguments.
First one is going to be the wrapped component.
Just like that.
And then it is going to receive an argument it's going to be argument one.
OK.
So again this function is going to return something and what it's going to be returning it's going to
be whatever with the prompts and then returned a new function say prompts and then it's going to return
a function.
So this function is going to have some code inside.
So this code to me make it right.
I mean it mistake right there.
There you go is going to right here it's going to return some code and this code is going to be just
a component with the wrapped component inside.
I know that it doesn't make sense so far but don't worry I can explain you're limited.
I'm going to say export and of course we need to make this component available.
So I'm going to say user H.O. C.
So now I'm going to go back to user and I'm going to import this file.
So it's going to be important.
And then I'm going to call it a Josi makes sense.
User HAMC from and then dot dot for Slash a chose C and then user H.M.S..
So now what are we going to do instead of purely putting this component inside of here.
I'm going to go right here at the bottom and I'm going to say user Tosi making reference to this user.
You change it user.
There you go.
And then I get to pass this the user as the first argument and then I'm going to say hello.
Just something simple just a string.
And if you notice again the application.
And this is still working.
So why is this working.
We didn't know this.
So OK.
So the application starts and we load the user components going to be showing the user components.
All right.
Well not really.
So what it's happening it's that it's loading this file and this function this component.
It's not exported.
You know we have the export default and instead of showing this what we're doing we are exporting the
user chose C.
OK.
So instead of doing this it's going to go and do this now.
User.
H O C is going to receive two arguments.
First it's going to be the actual component.
This is going to be the key component.
And then you know we passed some text just a string.
So it's going to go to HNC instead of rendering this is going to render HAMC.
So let's go to HAMC.
So H O C user HAMC is going to receive the wrap component which is going to be this component and then
an argument which is going to be this text.
So the job of this component is going to be returning just to function and this function what it's going
to return is going to be dead with whatever components we passed as an argument.
And that's why we're getting user 1.
So this is the you know it's a really weird right here and whenever we get to redux we're going to find
the same the same syntax right here.
But this this is the thing that's happening this function.
It's receiving a component and the job of this function is just return the component we get as an argument.
Okay that's good.
You know really really weird.
But why would we use this.
Well the cool thing about this is that we can we can call a component and we can pass that component
and then we can use different arguments.
So right here what I could do I can say arg one.
And you know everything is going to be it's going to get rendered Halo and user want.
So we are outputting two pieces of code.
First whatever argument we get on top and then the actual component that we are passing as an arguments.
And again this user H.O. C could serve as a template for one ever so we can go to a different a different
component right here and call that user HNC and pass the components as an argument and it will always
be rendered with a div and maybe with the arguments.
OK that's good.
You know it's nice to know that we have this available.
Now the weird thing.
The confusing thing is going to be the props.
Why am I doing this why am I passing this prompts.
OK let's go back to user.
Whenever we call this function we load this component instead of running this we run this.
So if we remember the component that wraps the.
This section is going to be rehang router so re-act router is going to give us some props.
Now if I go right here and let's go to a user going to go right here I'm going to say console log and
then prompts and right here at the top I'm going to say props OK.
So in theory this user this component it's receiving the react router prompts just like with that before.
Now if you go to the console we are getting nothing which is getting an empty object.
And again this make first it makes perfect sense.
The component that it's rendering it's not this one is going to be user hoc.
So the one that is getting the props it's this one.
So if I go right here and say console log and then prop's
reload the page a minute mistake sorry it's over that and the copier.
I to put it inside of course because you're getting the props right here.
So if we reload the page we are getting the props inside the props from Briac writer are entering this
user Haack.
And then we returned the function with the props.
Another thing is that what we need to do is to pass the prompts that we are getting from Riyadh Browder
to the next component in the list which is going to be the ract corrupt component.
Remember the ramp component is going to be this components.
So now how do we make this problem available within this component.
Okay.
So going to make a space and what we do we do a little bit of rest.
Operator It's going to be dot dot dot.
Then we pass props and whatever prompts we are we are getting We're going to pass them to the wrapped
components.
A middle of this.
So now remember that we have a user doing the console log of props.
So now we are getting it the prompts are available with this computer component.
So again we are as we see triggering this user Hok this one is getting to the prompts of from the router
and then we grab the props and we pass it to the next line of code to the next component.
OK.
So you know it's a little bit confusing but once you get the idea of what user I'm sorry the h o zes
do it's going to it's going to simple.
So again this whole logic using H-how sees when whenever we reach via the practice project it's going
to get really really complex.
We can have tons of code right here and they're going to be checking important parts of our application
so we can use and this is just a dumb example.
But you're going to be doing more difficult stuff don't worry.
OK so let's keep moving forward.
Let's go to the next topic.
Sorry guys.
I would like to add one more thing I forgot to mention.
It's actually something we call.
So right here the Whenever we are we are exporting the user Hok you're just passing user but something
else that we could do.
We can create whatever components right here.
We can do.
We can just do two.
We can have a lot of components and I'm going to say user 2 and then user 2 and now instead of just
passing one component we can pass as many components as we wish.
And then right here you're going to get them.
So I'm going to say wrap component is a second argument and this one is going to be the number two.
So we are getting the first user one component.
The second user to component and then the arc and right here do pretty much the same thing.
You're still going to get the problem you're going to say wrapped component.
So instead of just rendering one component we can render whatever component we want.
We could have 10 different components and you're going to be rendering all the components in at once.
That's it.
That's the only thing I want to add.
Sorry for that.
Let's move forward now.