Write so now you'll learn about transitions.
I've made a tiny template so we can start with this and not to lose any time in building a simple template.
So we still have a lot of things to learn so we're going to do a lot of coding in this section and it's
going to look weird at the beginning.
So first you will need to download this template.
This project I'm going to be adding this project as a download source inside the course inside this
section so download it.
Put it on a folder and then of course you need to go to the terminal navigate and do NPM start.
OK.
You just download that and do that.
So first let me show you what we get on this template.
We have three different routes one transitions CSSA incisions and transitions group.
If I go to transition's which is this one you know you're not getting anything just a div with the text.
Same thing with CSSA rescissions and inside incisions group.
We have kind of a function that it's going to be adding an element with a random number.
Every time we add elements that that's it.
And if Of course I add more I get more random numbers.
If I do we move is going to be we moving.
Real simple.
Now the main point of this is going to be to animate each and each enter on each dip.
No that's the idea.
So first we need to start with transitions is going to be the hardest one.
You know it's going to be the hardest one to do.
So we're going to start with that one because we know how to do transition we will know how to do all
the other ones.
OK so first the first thing we need to do is to add a div and then a button that is going to be adding
a div right here.
So OK I'm going to go to transition's and inside here going to delete transmission's and inside I'm
going to create new div just like that.
They're going to be adding some style.
Real simple.
Open and close and then open and close again to add a background so we can see good background.
And it's going to be read just like that.
Oh read.
And then of course I can add height just like that hide and it's going to be I don't know 100 pixels
sounds right.
That's fine.
Now there's not going to be anything inside.
At least we get the read.
That's what we want to do.
So to show or hide this element we need to state that it's going to be deciding if we want to show this
or not.
So I need to go right here at the top at the top and I'm going to say state it's going to be equal to.
And of course we add state and the state is going to be a show make sense.
And first it's going to be a boolean and it's going to be good.
So now to use the state to show the stev or not what we could do we can wrap everything in curly braces
and we can use a turn or operator to do this.
So that's going to be this that state that Schu just something like that.
And if states true this is going to be rendered and if not of course we will return.
No something like that makes sense.
OK.
So of course we have to.
It's going to be showing this.
But if we change it to false.
No it's not going to show it.
OK.
That's good.
So now let's keep moving forward.
The next thing that we will need to do have to get is going to be a button that it's going to be displaying
this.
So I'm going to go right here at the bottom and go right here.
Up first I'm going to tweet the function that is going to be tackling this state.
So if we click a button it's going to change this state to false or true.
And this is going to be rendered or not make sense.
It's not going to create mine is going to be show deaf.
You can call your function whatever you want.
Doesn't matter.
And then of course we're going to open and close.
So whenever I click it I invoke this function I'm going to be going to be changing the state is going
to be set state.
So it like that resemble and inside of course we want to change the state of show.
And of course if we click it and the state is false We're going to change it to true.
And if it's true we want to change it to false.
So what we do again is going to be a turnaround OPERATOR We're going to use ternary a lot.
So it's going to be if not this does that state that show we went to true and if not of course we Wonderfalls
get you go.
So now we need to add the button that is going to be the bottom for this.
It's going to go right here at the bottom and I'm going to say Dave just just a.
And this is going to say show or hide whatever doesn't matter.
OK.
I'm going to say.
Class name can add a class name or show of show something like that.
OK.
I'm going to add an unclick just like we did before.
You know with the with the events.
Same idea and this one is going to be this.
That show did something like that.
We're going to invoke that function.
So it's going to be show live.
OK.
So we don't have this class.
But inside the abseil says it's going to be right here right here.
I've added that just previous Kersley.
OK.
So if I save it and go to the project we have the button show or hide.
And if I click it it's going to be showing the red death.
And if I click it is going to hide it just changed it to states.
And when the application renders is going to be displaying the death or not so it is working.
That's good.
So now would we want to do we want to add a nice transmission to this maybe a slide or a fade or whatever.
So first we're going to need to install a dependency for this.
It's going to be called react transmission's reactive decisions.
So are going to do Control-C to clear the terminal.
They're going to be installing this.
So it's going to be NPM install and then react.
Dash transmission let me make this bigger just like that.
Write react transmission's and then group and of course don't forget to do the minus minus say I've
got to stand and are going to pause and be right back.
OK so everything is installed.
So since we install then component a dispensing what we need to do is we need to invoke that dependency.
So first we're going to say import and then this import is going to look a little bit weird.
You know it's going to be a little long.
So we're going to say import and then it's going to be transmission just like that.
And it's going to be from and then it's going to be a little bit long it's going to be re-act transmission
dash group just like that and then forward slash and then transmission and know you should have a snippet
for this.
OK.
That's good.
So we are importing transmission right here.
What we need to do we need to use it inside the return.
So I'm going to delete all of those.
You're not going to use it.
And of course I'm going to say transmission just like that.
And then I'm going to create a task we need to wrap everything inside the transmission tag.
No this transition is going to be using two main props.
The first one is going to be called.
And just like that.
And the second one is going to be called timeout equal to something.
So that in is going to be kind of the state of this transition component.
So we have a state right here that it's deciding if we want to show or hide it to change it to true
what we can do.
We can use this state.
So this one could be true could be false could be whatever it is we have it on the state.
I got to say this that stayed that show.
OK.
So this since this transition is going to be of course a transition we need a timeout we need to decide
how long the transition is going to take.
So I'm going to say two seconds.
You know so we can we can see the difference.
So we have the state of this Ellen decision and the timeout.
So I'm going to go right here and if I do something like that may be a tag that is going to say hello
just like that.
Going to reload.
And of course you know we get this do we get the halo.
But this one with transition.
It's not going to work this transition.
What it will return is going to be a function.
So are going to wrap everything inside curly braces and this function that transition is going to return
is going to have a state and that this is really important for us.
Now after we get the state is going to return whatever element we want to return in this case is going
to be a p tag if I go right here.
You're still getting halo so you know it's still working.
Now the funny thing is the state.
Why do we get the state right here.
Going to just output whatever information we get on the state just like that.
We're just printing this state and I go right here.
You know we get entered.
Let me make this a little bit bigger when we go right here and there we go.
So we get enter and when we load the application we get entered.
OK.
So I'm going to click.
It's going to say exiting and then exit.
And if I click again is going to be showing the data again in theory and is going to say entering and
then entered.
So what is happening right here.
So what we get with transmission and with the with this module which we acquisitions group it's not
DIAK The animation itself.
We're going to get a state so we can do the animations with CSSA or with whatever you want.
So in this case we get the state of what is happening with this dev or what should happen with this.
So we have.
And so when we click again it's going to say a thing and then exit.
So exit thing is going to be the Whenever the div is doing the transition and whenever it's done it's
going to be after two seconds we get a different class which is going to be at a different state.
And if I click again you know if it is this the state of this is going to be exit the div it's not it's
not there anymore.
It's going to it's not visible.
I click show is going to be doing the animation and then the animation complete.
Since we are getting the state what we can do we create we can create four or maybe two different CSSA
classes and you know just give it a class of or with the passively or with whatever we want with the
animation.
So OK let's go.
You know we're going to do it right now.
I know that it's kind of confusing.
It's not going to make sense.
But right now we're going to show you a practical example with a with a div and it's going to make sense.
So I'm going to delete this.
I'm going to delete that P-TECH and instead of returning a P are going to return a.
So I'm going to say div open and close resample are going to add style right here.
I'm going to add an inline style so we can see what's going on with this and open and close and then
open and close.
You remember that for inline styling we need two curly braces right here at the bottom and first are
going to be adding the same background with it before the read that Acoma are going to add height and
the height is going to be 100 pixels than coma.
And this one is kind of important going to say transition and begin to add the East for all all it's
going to be two seconds because we have the time out and this is going to be important if you're using
CSSA for the transitions.
If you put two seconds this one needs to match with whatever timeout you have right here.
If they are different you know you can have a tiny crawl is going to still do the animation but they're
not going to be synchronized.
OK.
So we are going to be animating whatever whatever we want.
So I'm going to say coma.
And what I'm going to be animating it's going to be the passing is something simple.
It's going to be state and.
OK.
Let me get started.
I'm going to say opacity.
What I want to do I want to hide.
Whenever we get a state of exit or thing.
So the opacity is going to be equal to zero if we have the state exiting or exit exit.
And if we have entering or entered we want to change it to 1.
So again we're going to be using turnaround and it's going to be state triple equal to exit it good.
And then I'm going to be adding the.
Or Oh sorry.
It would be adding the or 0.
Let me one second I just changed the key words.
So it going to be when you see if I can figure out because it changed keywords and right here have British
because I have a keyboard and you know it's going to be using possibly the R and find the or her source
for that.
I got it.
So it's going to be or.
And of course we're going to do the same thing is going to be state and 3PL equals to the all the other
state which is going to be exiting so exiting Burguet.
So of course we get this to states.
It's going to be equal to zero.
And if not it's going to be equal to what is going to be showing the dev.
So whenever the application starts of course it's going to be showing to true.
So this one is going to have the class of entered the state of Intrade and you know just let me put
this to the state right here.
All right.
So we're going to reload and you know the application starts.
There is no transition but we get the the state of this debate which is going to be entered.
They've already entered.
So it's like click hide or show it's going to do exiting the animation stops.
And the element is not there anymore.
And if I click it's going to change the state to entering and when it's done it's going to change it
to enter.
Good.
You know so this is how we use transition's group.
We're not going to do the animation.
The transition's group is going to just give you a state or a class something like that so you can do
the animation using CSSA.
That's how trance react transitions group works.
Of course we can do a lot of things with this not just this.
And you know this writing all of this to do a simple animation.
It's a real pain in the ass.
I know.
I know what you're thinking.
So we're going to be doing all the things and this is one is going to get a little bit simpler.
So with this transitions and pretty much with all the other ones you're going to get two different choices
begin to get options of course.
And one of the options is going to be mount on enter.
Let me delete it right now and let me show you.
So when does the application start.
You know we get the dip.
So if I hide everything.
So the state of this is going to be non-visible.
But if you take a look right here we have a big space so Divx.
It's hidden.
But of course it's occupying space right here.
The div..
It's inside the door.
OK.
So if I do this just like that me add there the the amount on enter or go.
And of course we have a different options which is going to be the opposite of Mount on enter.
Are going to be unmount on exit.
So we have the mount on guns or if I click show or hide.
It's going to be hiding this and when it's exiting it's going to be done.
But the div. it's not there anymore.
So if we have an unmount on X exit transition is going to know because it knows that the div it's not
there anymore it's exit it.
So it's going to be grabbing that element from the DOM and you know just remove the item from the DOM.
And if we click it is going to be mounting again.
OK.
That's it.
You know it's not that hard but you need to do a lot of coding just to get this simple thing.
But you know it's going to get a little bit better.
OK.
Let's go to the next section and see the other.
The other one.