Right.
So before we move to the next generation I want to show you how we can achieve the same the same behavior
and not to do inline styling to use classes.
So first I'm going to lead all of this to delete this one because we're not going to use it and we're
going to be adding just a simple div with a class code to delete all of this as well.
And for now I'm going to delete the state.
So now what we can do is we have the state available what we can do we can as a class name and the class
name we're going to be adding our custom class but we're going to be using the state as well.
So first I'm going to give a name to this to my to my component and make my div I'm going to give a
class and again and call you know square mixdowns square the square or not.
And then of course I'm going to repeat the same thing I'm going to say Square but now what I will need
to do only to add the state of whatever state we get right here.
So are going to be using template strings and going to be adding the state.
So now whenever we the transition is going to be entering this or exiting this we get the class of a
level inside class name.
So I'm going to do the same thing right here.
Just get a copy of this and paste it right here so we can see inside the div which classes we are getting.
So OK.
So we have square and square enter.
This is the first state going to click.
It's going to say Square exiting and square exit.
And if I click again we get you know entering and then enter.
So we're getting the classes right here.
And inside the class name of course we get the class on the inspect just to make sure.
And to make this a little bit bigger.
And I'm going to go go right here and you know we have square square entered.
And if I click it square exiting and exited and then entering and entered.
So we are getting the classes.
So the only thing that we need to do right now is to add the the CSSA for this.
OK.
So got to go to APS-C SS and they have three different transitions and this one is going to be the basic.
So going to be adding the classes right now.
Real simple.
The first one is going to be called Square and square.
If you remember we have a background off read what else we have the height of 100 pixels.
What else.
We have the capacity since this is the main state of the def is going to be one.
And then of course we need to add the transmission and the transmission is going to be all then two
seconds of course and then ease.
You know this is just an assessment.
Nothing.
It's not react or javascript.
Good.
So now we have the main state of this the next state is going to be entering then the entered and then
the exiting and then the exit.
So I get to say Square.
Just like before.
And again to be adding a class A square entering.
So it is going to be square and then entering and this class is going to be doing the animation of when
the device is going to be entering.
So we're going to be doing opacity just like that and it's going to be equal to one and it could be
adding one more thing to add a transform and it's going to be translate and translate X and we get a
good zero percent.
So now I'm going to do the same thing but with the square entered it's going to say square dot and square
and then entered and are going to be change in the background to blue so we can see that transition.
So first the the element is not visible.
It's going to have a visit I'm sorry it's visible is right here we can see it right here with you.
Has it your one and after the element enters.
And we get the state is going to be changing the color from red to blue.
So now we need to do the exit state.
So it's going to be square then Square and it's going to be exiting and going to be change in the background
to green.
And of course again I need to do the accident which is going to be the translite and the opacity and
of course is going to be the same idea so square and then square and it's going to be it looks like
that open close.
We get a pass city and you pass it is going to be zero and we're going to be removing the element from
the queen is going to be sliding to the left.
So we're going to be using transform and the same translate X but this time is going to be minus 100
percent.
So it's going to be hiding.
Hold it.
OK.
So in theory this should be working good.
So we're going to be reloading the application now.
We get square entered and enter it's going to be a positive one and the color blue.
If I click it it's going to be changing to green and it's going to remove the different screen.
And you know exiting.
And when we get X it is going to be moving so it's going to work.
If I click on show or hide again it's going to be doing and then change the color when we get to enter.
So you know it's working good.
It's just one more time.
OK.
It works.
So you know it's really simple once you get the idea of how this works with this state means what we
can do with the state.
It's you know it's really really simple.
So of course we get a lot of more options with this.
What we can do we can set the time out for the enter and the exit in separate mode.
Let me just delete this and I'm going to be adding an object and this object is going to be the enter
which is going to be 200.
Just like that.
And again at the exit.
And this one is going to be shorters going to be 50.
So whenever with the state it's enter or entering it's going to be it's going to be using the timeout
of two seconds.
And if redoing exiting is going to use half second.
So going to reload the application going to show you know it's a little bit faster.
And if I do it again same thing.
So we can do this.
We have a lot of options available.
You can check the documentation of course.
We have more of course.
I can say Enter it's going to be equal to.
And I'm going to set it to false so we can see the difference.
I can say Exod. and it's going to be equal to false as well.
So I'm going to be reloading the application OK.
So we have entered.
And if I click a show or hide it's just going to do it.
It's not going to go through the exiting option.
It's going to just do the entered Micheaux changed as you move reload and click hide.
And if you notice it's just doing the and the accident it's not going through the exiting it's just
going directly to the ad to the exit going to click again.
And we get it right here.
So it's not use it is only using the square entered the state of enter it or exiting or our exit is
not going through exiting or entering.
So this is the main purpose of this.
And if I do true of course it's going to be using all the states you know the entering and the exiting
exiting.
And then it's going to go and of course we do the same thing entering and entered.
So this is the main purpose of the enter and the exit.
Of course we can do a little bit more or are going to be adding on Antar and it's going to be equal
and it's going to be equal to a function.
This function takes takes a note which is going to be the arguments for this and then we can do whatever
we want.
I can say cancel log and then I don't know enter on the brink the council is going to go right here
the Bonhomme and if I click it of course nothing is going to happen.
But if I click it again we should be getting a console log of enter.
You know we get Enter So whenever the element and the div it's entering is going to do is going to be
executing whatever code you have right here.
And of course we have the opposite of this which is going to be on exit.
It's going to be on exit.
And same idea this one has a node and it's going to be equal to something.
And I always made a mistake here.
Just deleted.
No there's no mistake.
There we go.
OK.
So same thing are going to just copy the console log and it's going to be Exod. something like that.
And if I save it I click show it's going to be hiding.
So we get the exit and if of course we click again we have to enter it.
So this one is never going to be useful for us.
Going to see it later.
OK.
So everything's good.
Let's go to the next one to see a sister incisions.
And now since you know how this works the main logic of doing all of this.
This ones are going to be real real simple.
Let's go to the next one.