Read so now we know that transmission uses a state to do the transitions says your sister incisions
follows the same idea.
So I'm going to go to see our sister stations right here we get just a text so we're going to be needing
the same thing that with before the state and this show did function.
So I'm going to copy all of this.
Get a copy and then paste it right here.
OK.
I want to stay with the name but that's fine.
Just leave it fade.
OK.
So what else do we do we need.
We have to function.
And we're going to need the button that is going to be changing state.
So I'm going to copy and delete CSSA decisions and pays the bottom of the bottom.
So you know we get it.
So now we need to import and we going to import something else.
It's going to be import and the name is going to be CSSA just like that Sia says all in caps.
And then transmission.
No it's different.
And the other one the other one is called transition.
OK.
So this one is going to be it's going to be from and then react dosh transmission and then group Burguet.
Remember notice that right here we didn't have a forced slash just react rescissions group.
So now just like with it before we need to wrap everything inside these elements.
So CSSA transmission opening close.
And for now I'm going to I'm going to just show a dip print a dip.
OK.
So we get hello and of course nothing else.
It's not working.
So with transmission's what we get we get a function that has this state and then we use this date to
change the class names.
Now with the assistance missions.
This one is going to be it's going to work kind of a different way there.
First we get the same options then before we have the end which is going to be equal to this state and
then show.
And then of course we have the time out which is going to be five seconds.
I know it's a long time but it's going to make sense in a minute.
To put five seconds so the next option.
And of course with this rescissions is going to be required is going to be called class names in asset
class names.
And notice that this one it's plural.
So with this one I'm going to be using a class that's going to I'm going to give it a class.
So what your system is going to do is going to use this class to append the classes inside our dip and
it's going to do it for us.
There's no need to grab the state and do the class ourselves.
It's going to do it out medically.
So OK so this one is done I'm going to save and I'm going to go right here going to make a bigger of
course nothing is going to happen.
Going to do the inspect going to reload the page again and select that Hello.
So for now we don't have anything.
If I click it notice that we get square exit and it's quite exit active.
And then it's going to be deleting that.
So it's appending the classes for us.
And if I do show or click kind is going to do square enter and a square enter active.
So this is the class that you're getting.
So the assistance sessions is grabbing this square class that we passed inside class names and it's
going to pan the square and it's going to add and the dash enter and the active as well.
You know it kind of makes sense can be confusing but it makes sense.
So now we have the state of when the element is entering or it's active while it's entering.
Now the thing is that we have a tiny problem whenever the we have the debt you want to reproduce the
same example right here.
We didn't have a class that is going to be saying that the dev it's red you know we get no class at
all.
So what we can do we can add a class name manually.
It's going to be it's going to say class name.
It's going to be equal to something.
So first I'm going to be adding the class square and then I need to know when the element it's visible
or not.
If you notice right here after the transition is done it's going to be deleting the classes.
The state we didn't get anything.
So what I'm going to do we're going to make a reference of this text you know.
True or false is going to be this state that show.
So now when we reload the page the element is going to be right here and note notice that it's grabbing
the classes from this one from Square.
I'm going to go right here is going to say is square.
True.
So we have the classic square and we have true because the element is it's possible.
So if I click it is going to be adding the false and the square exit and the square exit active.
And then of course it goes back to square false.
So you know it's to working.
So of course right now nothing is happening.
You know you don't get a transition's because we will need to add the C Ss for this.
So let's go to AB That's the assess and start adding the transitions right here.
You know we have the square already so there's no need to add it so we can say Square and then I'm going
to be adding the false false and it's going to be a background of I don't know whatever color.
Let me do one two three and then three.
You know a nice orange and they're going to be adding the transform and the transform is going to be
translate X and then minus 100 percent just like that.
Then we have the square.
True it's going to be Doud square and then that true opening close and begin to be moving the dif to
the original decision.
So it's going to be translate X and then 0 percent.
And what else.
You know we are getting the state of square enter and then square are active.
So we can use these states to do something else.
So I'm going to say Square and then dash and tour and the dot and square dash enter dosh active and
this one going to be change the background to blue get the next one.
Again is the same idea is going to be the square that does exit dot and then square.
Same thing.
Everything is very repetitive except and then active.
And this one is going to be background over a..
Green good.
So in theory this again should be working.
Going to reload the page we get the rodef.
If I click at an exit and notice that is using the exit and it's quite active and is changing to green
and then it's going to change the state falls.
If I click it again we get the green and it's changing to blue because we have the enter and the enter
active and when it's done it's going to be going to the original state.
Remember that we are using five seconds for all and are going to be changing this to two seconds.
It's going to be a little bit faster just a little bit faster.
Wait two seconds it's a lot of time.
So I'm going to show hide.
It's going to do it.
And if I click it again.
No it works.
All right.
So you know it's it's real simple since we know how this one works.
We know how this one is going to work as well.
I mean save it again.
OK.
So let's.
Let's move to the next video we're going to be talking about the transition's group and we're going
to be using this tiny little function.