OK so we have one more to go.
It's going to be transition's group.
So just like this you know just like it's old before this component is it's just going to add an element
with a random number.
Every time I click an add element and it's going to remove it if I click Remove elements real simple.
Let's go to the code.
So we have two buttons.
Dinner number and remove number and right here we are just showing whatever we have an at elements of
elements.
It's just doing a map over the state of items.
So if we have on a number right here is going to be displaying this.
So if I do 56 or whatever it's going to reload the page and we get 56 so you know it's this rendering
that state.
So whenever we click on Add elements it's going to go to generate number he's going to grab whatever
state is going to add a random number and then of course he's going to update that state.
The application will be rendered with the new element and it's going to display the elements and the
same thing happens with remove number is going to remove the last number on that state and then is going
to be setting state again.
Real simple.
OK.
So I'm going to remove the five six I'm going to save it.
And now we're going to be using transmission's group.
Now the main difference of transmission is group the with the transmission and the CSSA condition is
that we use this one to render lists.
Right here we are rendering whenever we have inside the array items.
So we are going to be using transmission's group.
That's the main reason.
So first we need to import everything.
So we need to import two things we need to import the CSSA incisions group just like with it before.
Just as transition's concision trend will start again.
Tren session and then coma and we need to import transmission and then group just like that group.
So now of course everything is going to be from.
And then re-act transition and then group OK Breguet So now what we need to do just like that before
this element we need to wrap everything inside transition's group.
So I'm going to say transition's group opening close and I'm going to put everything inside.
So now this transition group is going to need you pretty much one thing are going to be adding to.
So the first one is going to be the component.
Now whenever we specify the component is going to be what this list is going to be.
In this case we're using a list makes sense that we can ever be using.
We should be using a UL because we're going to be adding lists but in this case I'm going to be using
a device.
So whenever the application renders is going to create a div that is going to be containing whatever
data we have right here.
So if I go out a class name as well so we can see the difference.
And this one is going to have a class name of list.
So I'm going to inspect are going to add an element I'm going to select 5:52 and notice that right here
we have diffs this class and we have the class of list and each side here we have a def and this one
again it's a.
It's not a UL.
This is because we said that the component should be a div.
So this one works.
So now how do we add a transition to each element.
Well now we're going to be using the CSSA transition that we imported on the top.
I'm going to go right here inside the map and I'm going to wrap everything in.
Inside CSSA transition.
Open it close.
And just like with it before this one there's nothing you write here inside the assessment session.
I need to start adding the props first one are going to add the class names.
So this one is going to have an item a class name of item and I need to put the time out and for now
the time out I'm just going to give it 500 seconds something fast.
Now since this is a list and each time we return something we're going to be returning in a list an
item of that list.
We need a key.
Remember that with lists we need to add a key.
So I'm going to say key and it's going to be equal to I which is the iteration on each iteration inside
the map makes sense.
Now one more thing we can have a problem if we render this we going to get the classes and get a good
five second so we can see the classes right here.
I'm going to add I can select and notice that we have item enter and enter active.
And if I add again item item enter an item active.
Now whenever this is done it's going to be moving and going back to item.
But I need to know whether this item is active or not.
So again we're going to be using the on entered.
Same thing we did before on enter it it's going to be equal to opening close and we grab that node and
we do something else with that node.
So it's going to be adding a class inside this element.
So what we can do we can access the node which is whatever information you have right here.
And again to say Dot and I'm going to enter the classis and then I'm going to say add and now we're
going to say no active access active.
So now we expect this going to add an element select selected and we have item item enter enter active
and then item and active.
You know this is working.
So this is ready we have all the classes and we have the cost whenever the element is not active.
If we move it is going to do the exit and remove the the element from the list.
Very good.
So the only thing left is going to be adding the CSSA.
So OK I'm going to go to app are going to be going to a transmission's group and outclasses the first
one is going to be the item and you can have an A pass city of 0.
What else we can have a transform of translate x.
Same thing with the for minus 100 percent.
And what else we can have the transmission and we're going to say all DOD can give it a half a second
and that is fine.
But then we have the DOD.
And then item and then dot active and we're going to put it all at once I can say item dosh enter and
the other class is going to be item Dasch enter Dasch active.
And this one is going to be opacity of one.
And what else a transform of translate x.
And this one is going to have a zero percent beginning.
HYDE we're going to show it.
So then we have the exit scenario so I'm going to say item that excess exit then dot and then item X
said and then dasht active.
Remember that you have when we have the option to put enter and then exit and set it a true or false.
So we didn't have to use the exit active and we can use the item active.
OK.
So let me make this right.
And this one is going to be opacity of 0 and then we're going to put transform and you know we can hide
it again.
So translate minus 100 percent.
And that is done you know this is going to make the transition.
So I'm going to click and add elements and you know it's doing the transition.
Let me check if we have 500.
No we didn't have it.
Can it put it put in 500.
And it click and add element you know doing the transition can add one more and it's working.
And if I remove it it's going to be removing the element and doing the transmission principle.
So you know it's not that hard to to use once you get the idea of how this works.
It's read resample.
But first it's kind of a weird to to learn how to use is why we can why we're using a class name or
why why were you using it state.
That's the tricky part of CSSA transitional transitional group.
But once you get the idea that you get all the states it's real simple.
All right.
So let's go to the next topic.
Oh before we go of course you have a lot of different dependencies for transitions.
This one is the one you know the one the main one from react but you have other or other dependencies
other components from different vendors.
For example you have one that is going to be called re-act move.
That's when it's really good going to go to get have and right here react move.
So again it's just like a library just like applying to do transitions and it's really really complete.
It's not that easy to use.
But of course you can check this out.
Let's see if we can get.
Yes.
Just a live example so you can see what you can do.
It's really really good.
So I'm going to go to examples and you know sort value.
And you know really a very good transition as we go to update.
It works really well.
But again it's not that easy to use.
Of course you need to do a lot of coding and resolved.
It's really cool.
But of course you need to do some work.
Look at this now.
It's good but it's kind of hard to use maybe at the end of the course if you still have time we can
add it can make a tiny tiny tiny section to show you how to use this.
All right so let's keep moving forward with react.
And we're going to be talking about Propp types.
Let's go to the next section and do that.