Right.
So now we're going to be talking about Prop types.
So prop times prop types was a built in ability of react for type checking.
It was included by default on earlier versions of react.
But now just like transition's group we need to install the add on and we're going to be using the same
templates and transitions.
If you didn't download it just download the main template and begin to be adding a route right now.
So before I start I start explaining to you what what to do with properties what we can do.
And if you express that you might never use prompt types in your life and your re-act application is
going to work just fine.
No it could I just could have skipped this prompt types from the course.
But you know in the future you might stumble with prop types and you're not going to know what to do
with prompt types.
So again if you want you can skip it.
Or maybe you can just stay and at least know what prompts what Prop types is all about.
OK that's good.
So let's start with Propp types.
First we need to create around to use this.
So I'm going to create a class based component and a child component.
So first I'm going to go right here to components.
I'm going to create a new file that is going to be called user digests and then I'm going to create
a new file again.
It is going to be called user underscore template make sense resemble.
So inside the user it's going to be a class based component.
And just for you to know I'm using B as code and I install I'm using a template or here is going to
be called reactive Yes code snippets and right here for example if I do re-act which are just the letter
are re-act class component RCC is going to create a class based component for you.
It's not going to be using this right now.
You will need only to install it or you can just create a class based component.
It doesn't matter.
So I'm going to say user and of course this one is going to be called user and this one this class based
component is going to have a state of something going to be adding something inside here in a minute.
And of course this one is going to be called is going to be calling child component.
From now on they're going to do anything just going to say component whatever and are going to add the
route of this.
So first I need to import I'm going to say import.
And it's going to be called user from and then dot forward slash components for Slash and user.
And again to create the route copy the Prete the previous one page then at the bottom say user and right
here for the name.
I'm going to say Propp types and then user are going to create the route.
So can it be user and then prob time user.
Oh sorry.
It's going to be just user OK.
Salmiya below the page.
You know we get to user and we get components so it's working.
That's good.
So now this one you're going to create a component right here.
So I got to do it right now.
The component was called user template.
So I'm just going to call it that way.
It's going to be called user and then template.
And then just close it.
OK.
So now we need to create a component first then go to import it is going to be called user template
and then from.
And we didn't have it to do it right here.
So it's going to be DOD force slash component.
Dot dot for Slash.
And it's going to be called user template.
So this user template it's not doing anything.
And again with the with the code snippets we can do re-act stateless components and it's going to create
for us real simple user template.
Okay.
And then just user template and then template whatever OK and we are getting templates so this is working.
We are just loading this user component this class component and calling that the user template component.
So with prop types what we need to do what we can do with Prop types is just type checking.
We can type we can check if we have the correct information.
I'm going to give you a practical example of course.
But before using prop types we need to install it.
So I'm going to go to the terminal right here going to kill it and I'm going to do and PM install and
it's going to be Propp heaven or score
Ivan types prop types.
Let me make this bigger crop tops.
And then of course mine is mine is safe.
It's going to take a second.
It's not that big.
Would be almost done.
OK.
It's taking longer than expected.
So I'm going to say NPM start to start the application again.
I'm going to go back.
You know it's a it's still loading.
So everything goes ok.
Works OK.
So now this component is user component is going to have a state with some fields inside and the going
to be passing as props.
The state of this component to the user template component.
So going to create some dummy data going to say name it is going to be called to Francis.
And you know last name of course it's going to be Jones.
And for now just the age and the age he's going to be 25.
That's good.
So I just have some dumb user data and I'm going to be passing all of the state to the child component
so I don't know if I mentioned this but if we want to past the whole state of this component to the
components we can do dot dot dot this dot state that is going to be passing everything all state as
props.
So now we need to import the Propp types going to go right here.
The bottom is going to say inport and is going to be prob. types Propp types and then from and then
promp types drop on the core and Piven and then types.
And am I making a mistake.
It should be on the other components.
I'm going to copy it and put it inside user template.
So now OK this component is passing the state to the char component.
In theory if I do props right here and do console log and then the probs I should be getting the prompts.
So I'm going to say console log and then prop's just like that.
And you know we get Francis last name and age.
That's.
You know it's working.
We know how to do this.
So now this component is going to be using Propp types to check the information we get and props.
So to use that just after the component the actual components we need to make a reference to the name
of the component.
In this case is user template.
And then we say Propp type.
OK Propp types on the like this right.
It's one.
OK.
Prop types
just like that it's going to be equal and it's going to be equal to an object.
Now right here we're going to be checking things.
For example this prop's is going to be receiving name OK and the name is going to be a string and it's
going to be Frances.
So I'm going to make reference to that name promp and I'm going to invoke Propp types right here and
then we're going to say Dot and this one is going to be equal to string.
Now if we reload the page nothing happens.
But if I go back to user and grab this Francis and change it to a number.
So this name it's not a string anymore it's going to be a boolean.
And if we go right here to the browser you're getting an error message is going to say fail Propp type
invalid Propp type name of type number supplied to user template expected string.
And this is the keyboard expected string but we're getting we are we are getting a number.
So that is a problem that that's how we can use Propp types.
We use it to check to check that we're receiving the correct information inside prompts.
That's the whole idea.
The application is still going to work.
Everything is going to work just fine if you don't have any other errors.
The only thing that does it's going to give you a warning.
And why use this maybe in the future you make an application and someone else is going to grab that
application and do some work on top.
So maybe you have some information that it's kind of a case sensitive and should not be change or you
need to make sure that that information has the correct type.
So we all use prop types.
OK let's.
Let's check the other ones because we have a lot of information we could have functions we could have
a race we could have objects and of course we have a way to check it.
So the first one is going to be a string of just going to change it back.
If I reload the application you know we are not getting any warnings.
The next one is going to be again just a string.
So just to complete the example going to the coma and I'm going to say last name and same thing prob
types dot string and you know it's going to pass.
Got the next one.
It's going to be the age right here.
The age so the age is a number it's going to different.
So we're going to do.
Koma are going to say age is going to be equal to prompt Times Dot and it's going to be a number.
So if we check it it passes.
If I change it to whatever.
No just a string.
It's not going to pass.
It's going to give you a warning.
Let's get.
So there's a lot of things that we need to check.
So we need to add more information right here.
For example we can check a race are going to say hobbies just like that.
And then of course an array and hobbies are going to be rond than coma and jump.
Let's get to check it going to go back to user template.
And of course we need to we need to make to make reference to that.
Going to be hobby's is going to be equal to prop types just like that and then dot.
And how do we check if it's an array of simple array.
If we reloaded it passes good.
So it's working.
So what else what else we can check.
We can check booleans are going to say I don't know Spanish than Koehn.
And it's going to be false.
So Francis knows how to speak English only not a spanish.
So in a coma and are going to say in Spanish Spanish or go and again is going to be Propp types dot
and of course to check for booleans is going to be Boole b o l real simple.
And it seems like even a mistake it's capital P reload.
You know we are not getting any errors and warnings it's passing what else we could use a function going
to do a coma and going to write a function.
It's going to be message something like that whatever it's going to be you know function.
So we're going to create a function and then this function is going to a log.
Hey whatever.
So this one is going to be passed as a function.
How do we check if we have a function.
OK.
First we need to make a reference to that to that function.
That's going to be called message and this function is going to be Propp types.
Again prop types dot and check if it's a function we check we check func and reload the page it passes.
That's good.
So what else we can check.
Objects of course to do coma.
And I get into car that can and are going to be adding an object and it's going to be brand of four
and then coma and the model is going to be of focus just like that.
So right here inside the car we have an object to check that we can do car of course and again prop
types or go prop types.
Doug Dant and to check if it's an object we can say object.
And if we reloaded it passes let's get know.
There's a lot of more things that we can do with Prop types more complicated things.
So let's get a possible deal.
And we're going to be checking the other ones.
OK so we have a few more we can we can use we can make use of one off.
I'm going to I'm going to write and run here.
Just going to delete the name the prompt type strings because we cannot check for one thing twice.
I cannot do we cannot do name and then check the name again.
We can get an error message.
So right here inside name what we can do we can make use of Propp types are going to give you a practical
example because it's kind of weird and it's going to be one off and one off it's going to it's going
to make is going to use an array.
So pretty much what went off.
We can check if the this about the value of name Francis or something else.
So if I say Francis is going to be is going to pass because we have Francis as name.
And if we have Steve for example is going to pass because we have Francis and if I change it to Steve
it's still going to pass because we have Steve.
But if we have something else different than Frances or Steve it's not going to pass.
So right here it's passing.
So if I do Jane some like that and reload the application it's not going to pass.
It's going to give you a warning for this.
OK.
Let's get.
So there's one more thing that we can do.
We can do we can check for several things inside the same property.
So right here I'm going to make use of prop types again.
It's going to be Propp types Dot and I are going to be using one off type.
So with one of type we can check for several things is going to be is going to be using an array just
like here it's just an array.
And we can check for four different things.
For example I want to check if this is a prop types and is a string.
So if a string is going to pass if I reload the application it passes if it's a number I'm going to
say Propp types and then dot and number and if I write a number inside user is going to pass anyways
because it is allowed.
No no warning.
And of course we can use something more more complicated like prop types and one off.
And again you know same example before.
Even Ray and it's going to be Francis or Steve just like that they're going to change it to I don't
know Francis or the application it passes.
And if I change it to Jane of course it's not going to pass because we have this but since Prop type
String it's valid is it still going to pass.
You know we're not getting an answer.
Our message if one of this matches the criteria of what we are getting it's going to pass around.
Remember that.
OK.
So we can we have more more more things we can check if you're getting on a rate of something.
I'm going to go to hobbies I'm going to just delete this.
I'm going to say Propp types that dot and Auray off so Araik off is going to be checking what with what
kind of information you have inside this array.
So we have strings we can be checking if you have strings going to say Propp types dot and a string.
And of course it's going to pass because we have strings.
But if I change it to number for example or boolean whenever it's going to put numbers is not going
to pass because we are expecting a string.
You know there's a lot of things we can do if we can check if something it's required going to go wrong
here.
But on the bottom we're going to say Mother and Mother and then prop types dot and then required just
like that.
Oh sorry.
It's required.
So this one is going to be checking that we have the motter right here mother is in Balad must be a
function of the properties but received on the find.
This means that motter mother it doesn't exist and it's required.
OK.
So that's good right here.
I'm getting something different from Hovis is giving me the error message because you're expecting a
string.
So I'm going to change it to string and begin to get the message from Mother.
Now if I do coma and say Mother and then I don't know Martha something like that.
It should be.
Oh I'm sorry.
I made a mistake.
I'm going to say I'm going to delete this.
I'm going to mistake I just omitted to do something right here inside monitor a mother.
We are we are just checking the prop types and we want to check if it's string.
And this one is going to be required.
We always need to do it at the end of something.
So first it's going to load.
You know it's going to pass.
Sorry for that.
Forgot to put this.
There there's one more thing we can do.
It's a little bit complicated.
So we're going to go to the next video.
It's going to be really short and we're going to be moving forward with the next topic.