All right so we have one more we can use.
It's going to be a custom custom prop type are going to be I'm going to be using the mother promp I'm
going to delete everything inside.
I'm going to create a custom function that is going to be checking.
So first we need to create a function.
OK.
Just a function.
So this function with Propp types is going to be getting three different arguments.
First is going to be it's going to be Propst then begin to be receiving the props and the name this
case it's proper name and then coma and then the component name is.
These are the arguments that we get by default.
So just to check what we're getting I'm going to say console log and are going to be canceling doing
the console log on with prompts.
So OK so if we cancel all the prompts you're getting the props.
Let's get if I do it grab the prop name we get the name.
In this case it's going to be mother.
It's the name of the prom that we are checking.
And if we put the component name of course we get the component name makes sense.
So right now Mother it's given back just a string with the name Martha.
So what we can do we can check for something since we have the access to the value we can check for
that.
So I'm going to I'm going to write just an if statement something real simple and first are going to
be ugly.
Grab the props which is the actual object the actual array and are going to be accessing the product
name which in this case is going to be mother.
So this is going to access the mother and it's going to be checking the values we have access to the
value what we can do.
We can check for us for things.
So I'm going to say if this value is not equal to Jane we're going to give back an error message.
So I'm going to say cancel log and then no that's good.
So if I reload the application I'm getting no.
And that's good because as value of mother I have Martha.
So you know should I be working.
So if I say Jane if I correct this we're going to because it's going to pass.
Let's get so now right here.
Something else what we can do we can return our own custom error message.
So I'm going to say return just like that and then knew and then error and this one again I can pass
right here whatever I want.
In this case just going to pass.
Attempt to strings.
I'm going to say the name.
And then of course I'm going to make a reference to props and then prop name just like that prop some
prop name and then I'm going to ride is incorrect should be.
And then Jane says we have Jane right now is going to pass.
But if I change it back to Martha just like this is going to give us our custom our message didn't Martha
Martha is incorrect.
Should be Jane.
So this is a way where you can use you can write your own custom messages and of course it always depends.
Depends on what you want to do or which kind of a message you want to output you have to have a lot
of more options for this going to go to the browser and I'm going to go to and be NPM J.S. and then
package and then prop types you know is the NPM Web site and then we're going to go to these to these
pensee.
So you know you have a lot of more options right here.
You can check things is going to give you the the information of what you can do you can change.
We we would you just covered most of them.
You know the most used prop types.
So let's go.
OK.
That's good let's keep moving to the next topic we're going to be talking about something else completely
different topic.