OK so now we're going to be talking about drafts but we're not going to spend much time with drafts.
And if you ask why it's because we should not use it you should not use it now because I say it because
re-act gives you the chance to use them to use refs but they advise not to do it.
So it's kind of a link or reference we can attach to an element and then we can use the ref to do things
in the dorm directly and that is the keyword Dom and directly with refs we can bypass react and interact
with the DOM ourselves not through state or whatever directly.
And if you think about it you can have a Riak discourage you to use it because why use in react if you're
going to use refs and interact with the DOM directly while using Bre-X.
So OK it's going hard to explain with words with words how to use a ref.
So I'm just going to give you a simple simple example.
I going to go right here.
I'm going to be using the user view.
We're going to be right here Peetie user and Jabir of returning the template.
So it is just not to not to create a new project for this.
Going to use this one.
So I'm going to go right here.
I'm going to create an H for an inside the H for I'm going to output the mother.
No Access does not state.
And the mother.
If I go right here we're going to get Jane let's get.
So we know that that's that's working.
I'm going to be adding a style so I'm going to say style equals two and then style just like that.
We don't have a verbal with with the style for this.
So I'm going to go right here on the top.
I'm going to say Konst style and just going to add some inline styling skin color.
And then there's that state DOT and then color.
OK.
Good.
So now I'm going to go right here in a coma.
I'm going to add a color and this one is going to be red.
So when the component really read were renters begin to get Jane.
And with the color red and of course this one contains an inline styling.
Me and make it bigger.
Right here we have style and color red.
But you know we know how to do this.
I to go over here at the bottom and it can add a div.
And with this div whenever we click it begin to be change in the color.
We'll be updating the color to something else.
So are going to add text change color right here I need to go to use an event.
So it's going to be on click and this one is going to be equal to and I'm going to a chest book function.
It's going to.
Does that change color
so that we can have this function.
I'm going to go right here at the top and get a chest created can we change color.
And it's going to be a function open and close and right here are going to be updating the state.
This is the way we know how to do things.
So I'm going to make a reference to the collar and I'm going to change it to you know how to do this.
So I'm going to click and change color so the color changes to blue.
Let's get your.
We are just changing the color through the state overreact but to do this we can use reps are going
to say ref right here it is going to be equal to name who's going to be my caller.
So now this element this 8:04 tag has a ref or reference to something called My caller.
So instead of updating instead of updating the state what I can do I can make a reference to this that
refs dot and the name of the ref in this case is going to be my caller.
And then again to add the style property which is this one and then I'm going to access the caller inside
and change it to blue get to reload the application and you fight click and change color it's working.
So you know Same same with salt.
And we even get the style and the color blue.
So this is good.
You know it's working.
We are gives us the ability to do this directly to the Dom but not through the state.
But again they advise you not to do it this way.
If you can use state the only use in Aereo they they give you that it's kind of a good idea to use refs.
It's going to be with forms and with maybe with the on Blar change on the on the input.
That's the only the only place where they kind of allow you to use it.
And again you have the ability to use it but you should not use it.
You should use state in this case.
All right that's good.
You know something really simple.
Let's go to the let's go to the next section.
We're going to be starting with new project and we're going to be applying all the things that we learned
so far is going to be really extends and we can do a lot of things is going to get really complicated
but it's going to close to a real life scenario with the project and we react.
So let's start with the project.