All right so now we're going to be talking about forms.
We're going to be talking about controlled and uncontrolled.
So first we're going to be using a template I've made so you need to download it.
You can find it in the project resource.
So downlow the project put it inside a folder whatever folder doesn't matter.
And then of course you need to navigate to that folder.
I've called mine 0 5 forms and then you need to do NPM install so you it's going to go and download
all the dependencies.
And after you are done you need to do and pm start just like that.
I'm going to run it right now because everything is installed for me.
So it's going to show it's right here.
So this is what we're going to get.
It's going to reload in a second.
So this is what we get.
We're going to have three different routes right here.
We have a do we have a controlled controlled and then a user is going to be doing something else right
here.
Right from the start we have an uncontrolled component and are controlled by you.
Sorry not component.
So first we're going to be using the control we're going to build a controlled component so going to
close everything I have right here is all I'm going to go to controlled.
So inside control we just have a class based component with the state and you know with render really
really simple.
So remember to download and run it.
OK.
So OK so a control component.
It's whenever we use re-act 100 percent.
And you know we don't bypass react just like we do with draps.
So the best example comes directly from the playbook and it's of course working with forms.
So right here we're going to have a just component.
OK.
And the Whenever we work with the form whenever we use control component everything has to go through
state.
You know nuts just like ref.
We don't put the things directly into the DOM.
So let's build a form that's really the form for this and to begin to be changing everything else and
passing the functions so we can know and see how a control component works.
So OK so first they're going to have a div that it's going to have a class name of container inside
the the up the CSSA you all have already have the styles so you don't have to worry about that.
So we have a class named container and inside of course we can have a form.
So I'm going to open and close the form.
Right.
So inside a form we can have two different elements one for a name and one for last name.
It's a very simple form.
So inside form I can have one element that is going to have a class name of form element just like that.
OK.
So then we're going to have a label of course because we need a label just to be correct and my label
is going to say Antar name makes sense right.
OK.
What else you're going to have an input and the input is going to be I'm going to put it down here is
going to be equal type.
And of course it's going to be equal text.
And then for now I'm just going to close it.
Begin to do more here in a minute.
We're going to have a different a different container just a different div.
It's going to be the same class opening close just like this and we're going to have a different level
on going to copy this and paste at the bottom because I'm lazy and it's going to be.
Enter last name.
Makes sense again.
Then we can have a different input and this input again is going to be type text.
So I'm going to copy the one we have on top and paste it down here.
So I'm going to delete this again to save the form.
And you know we get the Leavell and the input Frigga.
So now the thing is that whenever we use a control component because we are in the control view everything
needs to go through react.
If I type something right here this for example let's say Francis this Francis.
Being put by the by us inside the actual input.
So we put it directly into the DOM right.
We're putting the data inside the input ourselves.
And so this is not controlled because this Francis is not going through state.
So what we need to do we need to do something right here create a couple of functions and this function
will detect when we type something inside here.
And instead of putting it right here is going to add the state is going to read render with this value
and it's going to putit react is going to put that value for us around.
So OK so first what do we need first we need a value right here in this input we don't have a value.
So I'm going to say value is going to be equal to you know something else and we're going to say this
that state that name we don't have it we're going to create it in a minute.
I'm going to copy this one.
I'm going to put it at the bottom and this one is going to be last name last name.
We're going to have the state.
So let's create it right now.
We're going to go right here and we're going to say name and it's going to be to Francis whatever coma.
And then last name Jones.
So now if you reload the application we do have a stading site value so react it's placing the values
whenever the application Lute's you know makes sense.
Now of course we don't want to do this.
We want to pass an empty stage and have re-act put the data that in pass since begin to be typing things.
We need an event listener.
So we're going to do on change now whenever we the emptiness re-act is going to run a function.
So I'm going to say this dot handle and you can choose whatever name you want right here handle name
change makes sense.
OK.
I'm going to do the same thing going to copy the onchange and I'm going to paste it down here but this
one instead of name is going to be last name.
All right going to save it for now of course we didn't have this functions.
We need to create them.
OK.
So I'm going to go right here.
And at the top going to get it just create two different functions.
I'm going to say handle name change is going to be equal and we can grab that event that is going to
be provided by the change even listener.
So OK I'm going to say event now.
First thing it to do console log and check the event dot target dot value just like that.
OK.
And I'm going to do the same thing and again copy this and paste it at the bottom and this one is going
to be last name.
So we're going to have two functions for two different inputs.
OK.
Now if I'm going to open the console let me put it at the bottom.
Now this one let me make a bigger because I see the options.
There we go.
I'm going to put it at the bottom.
Good.
I'm going to be opening the console.
There you go.
So now if I type something we get an F and if I type something else we get an F and if I type a letter
we get a name.
So we get one character individually because we are typing only one character.
The thing is that whenever we do this you know re-act is going to grab that the letter is going to show
it right here.
But the thing is that nothing gets placed right here.
So this function the main purpose of having this function is going to be updating the state.
So the next time we type we can have all their information right here.
So let me show you how to handle change.
I'm going to say this that said state said the new state and this one is going to be equal to name.
And we pass the same thing.
Event the target the value.
OK.
So let's try again.
So if I type an F the F stays right here inside the input.
You're right and this f is going to be placed by the state.
Remember that we are the state then the application is going to read render.
And now the Baalu is going to be equal to f..
Now if I type an e d e it's still going to get there because the application is going to add that E
F and that e is going to abduct this state the obligation will we render.
And now the value is going to be f e.
And the same thing as long as we type No the information is still there.
It's not getting delete.
And OK so what is the point of doing all of this whenever we type something we are not entering the
information directly into the input re-act is doing this through the state.
You know whenever the we we render is going to output whatever we have inside this state and whatever
input you know that's the main idea of using a control component.
You don't do things manually re-act is going to do it for you.
So I'm going to say last name just like that.
An ok and everything should work and if I say Frances we get Frances and if I say last name we get the
last name.
So you know this is the main idea of using a control component.
And if on the future in future you will work with the forms.
This should be the best approach working with state and you know using a control component.
We have the other way which is an uncontrolled component and we're going to be talking about this right
now.
OK so now let's see how an uncontrolled component works.
We know how a controlled compound works.
So let's talk about this one.
I'm going to be going to controlled and because I don't want to type all over all over again I'm just
going to copy the whole container.
This is going to copy go to control and just paste it down there.
There's a few things that we need to delete.
We don't need the on change and we don't need the values are going to go ahead and just delete those
ones.
OK good.
We're going to save it.
Let's go to our control and inside of control we get the same result.
The Enter name and enter last name.
So with an uncontrolled component we don't use the state.
There is no need to use the state because we are going to get that information devalues directly from
the DOM.
OK.
So how do we use an uncontrolled component how do we make it an uncontrolled.
Well we use refs.
We talked about refs in the future in the past.
So we're going to be using refs to catch the value of each input.
So I'm going to go ahead and just do it.
I'm going to say ref.
And now this is going to look a little bit weird.
Let me type it first.
I'm going to say input is going to be equal to this name.
And then it's going to be equal to input.
So that's pretty much what we're doing.
We're creating a variable called this that name and that this that name contains whatever information
we have inside the input.
No just like event this input this variable right here.
It's just like an event.
We catch it.
We create desirable and we put inside this marble whatever we have inside this event.
This is the main reason.
So now whenever we use that name it's going to store this viable that there's that name inside the class
so we can make a reference to that wherever we are and you know and get the values of this input.
Of course right here we could use something else but we're going to lead the state doesn't matter.
So we have the this name that contains all the information about this.
OK.
So we need to do the same thing with the last name.
So I'm going to copy all of this in a copy and then just paste it at the bottom and I'm going to say
last name.
So now we have a variable called this last name that contains all the information about the template.
So now I'm going to be adding something.
We're going to be of course extending this a lot so I'm going to say button and now whenever we submit
the form I want to get the values that we have inside ref but I need a way I need something that tells
me that the user submitted the form so I'm going to create an unclick for now.
We're going to do this in a different way in a minute.
And this button is going to be opening close and we're going to say button.
There we go.
And this button is going to say don't no sign and good because we have a user and last name whatever
it did register you know.
So this unclick is going to be running a function.
So again we're going to call it handle self.
And then just click you know make sense.
So the main purpose of this function is going to be grabbing whatever we have and this ref.
So going to go right here at the top of me just copy the name going to go right here.
The tab is going to be creating a marble I'm sorry a function that is going to be doing all the logic
with this refs so I'm going to say Handels of Klegg is going to be equal to the event because we are
using any vandalism were going to be grabbing that event and then say prevent and then default.
Of course we need to prevent the default behavior of this form because if we click on this it's going
to be made in the form and the application will reload.
And we don't want that.
With this we prevent that.
This is standard Javascript.
So now we need to get the information that we have inside this name and this last name.
OK so I'm going to go round here and going to say Konst values.
It's going to be it called to name and last name.
You know the two inputs we have last name.
OK.
So the name is going to be equal to this the name.
And now we need to get the values since we restored this.
We're going to save value and there we go.
We can't get the value of this that name.
And the same thing with this that last name dot value.
All right I'm going to do Cancellara just like this and I'm going to get values about values.
Let's make it plural bodies.
There you go.
So now I'm going to go to Control of course I'm going to type something it's going to be Frances.
And the last name is going to be Jones.
Now this information we are entering the characters and you know Francis and Jones inside the input
directly inside Dom react is not doing this job for us.
We are just entering the information.
So now whenever we click on sign n this handles of click is going to grab the formation stored inside
an object and then begin to get it.
So if I do sign and we get named Francis and last name JONES So this works.
But this of course is an uncontrolled component.
We don't have a state and re-act is not entering and just ruling the information for us.
We are just doing it directly with drafts.
So this is an example of uncontrolled and control component.
And of course in the future whenever we you work with forms you can use whatever you want.
You know you can use a control and you can use an uncontrolled.
And of course the main difference is that using a control component needs more logic a lot more code
you know right this way you could do this directly you know which is much much simpler.
But again if you're using react to y bypassing react if you're going to use re-act use we 100 percent
not just half way.
OK.
So bear on this course we're going to use the correct way to encode the correct way.
We're just going to be using a controlled component.
Now this set up right here you can choose to do something like this.
It's still going to work of course and I'm going to do one more thing I'm going to go to control components.
And now the thing is that right here you're clicking the handles of click to get the values.
OK.
So how do we do to get the data from this one.
You know from the state if you remember right here in form what we can do we can say on SIFF med just
like that.
And then we're going to be passing a function then I'm going to be calling this that on as handler or
whatever doesn't matter.
So this on as handler the main job of this one is going to be stopping the form from submission.
So I'm going to go and copy the event prevent default.
And now where do we have the information about the inputs inside the state.
Right.
So if I do console that law then this opening the the server that stayed we should be getting the information
about the form.
So ok me.
I made a mistake for the user and whatever.
Ok so I'm going to say event I forgot to do that.
So going to reload the application.
I'm inside control.
I do Francis and then Jones.
And then of course I don't have a button but I'm going to press enter.
OK.
When we just do it like this I'm going to do Bunin and then I have met and that type is going to be
Superman of course
reload again.
It's going to be Francis and then Jones and then SIFF mad.
You know we get the same information we get the name and we get the last name.
So the way to get the information about your form and all the inputs is through state because we are
using control.
So with these on submit you get to know when the user is submitting something.
So you just get to the state of whatever you have inside the form and then you just do the network request
to store the information or to log in the user or whatever is that you want to do with with this information.
All right of course this is a very very simple approach.
On the next sections we're going to be discussing kind of a I wouldn't say better but it's a more complete
and complex way to work with forms.
Because of course whenever you were forms you need to validate the information and you need to do a
lot of things.
OK.
So we're going to be doing that.
We're going to be building a template inside the user where the user is going to enter something formation
and we're going to be using a template to validate everything to show the inputs.
And you know we're going to be using a lot of logic.
So it's going to take a little bit of time.
So grab a cup of coffee and let's begin with that.