OK so now would be going to be doing is going to be creating a template that it's going to be adding
the all the inputs of a form for us is going to be using a different component and we're going to do
better.
We're going to do everything else but we're going to be doing everything kind of in a different way
with control and control.
We're going to do something else and we're going to do this is going to be a little bit hard to understand
if you can.
It's going to be a little bit confusing.
But this is going to be an approach a more realistic approach.
OK.
So OK.
So let's begin build on this are going to go to the user buse and go to user.
I get just nothing you know as user are going to do this and I'm going to be starting doing this.
I can see a class name and I'm going to give it a class name a container just like the all the ones
container.
And inside here we're going to have a form and this form will have an on submit.
Of course we didn't have that function but we will create it in a few seconds.
So it is going to be calling whenever we submit the form we're going to use a function that calls on.
So sorry is going to be called Mid form.
That's good.
What else.
We need a button right here.
So we're going to say Bunin and this one is going to be saying have met and right here we can have the
type off the bottom which is going to be met.
Right.
So now in the middle we should be getting all the inputs.
If I check this we get nothing but we're going to be doing something different right now.
The main idea of doing all of this is to call to a component to include components that is going to
be receiving some state.
Now inside the state we can have all the inputs that this component needs to create and to go to state.
And I'm going to create a new key that is going to be called Forum data just like that.
And this form data is going to have a bunch of information.
So let's say we want to add a name and a last name just like with did before.
OK.
So going to say name and then I'm going to pass a lot of values.
So this name first I need to specify which type of input we want to add.
So we are going to say elements and this is going to be kind of the name of what we want to add.
So it's going to be input.
And of course don't worry this is going to make sense in a minute.
This input is going to have a value of nothing.
Whenever the application renders.
Now we can have each input.
It can have a label.
So I'm going to specify if we want a label for this one so I'm going to say label true.
We're going to do koma.
What else do we need.
Even if the label is true we need to have a Leavell text.
So I'm going to say label and text and the text for this one is going to be name right.
OK.
So now impled contains a configuration just like a name the imperative type and maybe a placeholder.
So I'm going to create a new value that is going to it's going to be called config and this config is
going to contain all the options of what we need.
So this input is going to have a name and I get to give it a name of name.
Input makes sense in a coma.
This input is going to be of type and it's going to be of typed text.
What else are we going to be adding a placeholder.
So it's going to be place holder and this placeholder is going to have a placeholder.
Enter your name.
So pretty much all of this information is what we need to create an input right from a template.
Right.
We have the name the tax the placeholder the value the label and you know the type of the element.
This cases in input are going to be creating a new one.
Right here we have a name.
So I'm going to go right here at the bottom get a copy of this I'm going to paste it at the bottom.
Remember to put a coma because it's an object.
And this one is going to be called last name.
OK.
Now we need to change things here just change it a little bit.
This one is going to be last name last name and the name of the input is going to be called last name
and then enter your last name right.
So now what do we do.
What why are we doing this.
So now the main idea of doing this is that we can create a function or a component that is going to
be grabbing this form data is going to be looping.
Whatever we have in the form data is going to create a template for each input out magically.
So if we have 100 inputs at the end we can have 100 inputs right here.
And the only thing that we need to add is going to be just a new element inside for data.
You know it is kind of different because the all the way we have to enter each input manually.
Right here inside the render.
So the advantage of using this is that you know we have a more controlled way to enter inputs to create
inputs.
So you're kind of creating a template function to create the the form elements so now we don't have
that function.
So we can be created right now.
I'm going to go to source and inside source just like with did before going to create a new component
that is going to be called with widgets but inside these widgets are going to have you know a new folder
that is going to say forms just to make it a little bit more correct.
And inside forms I'm going to have a new file that is going to be called form fields.
You know you can call them whatever you want.
So form fields of course is going to be just a function that is going to be receiving whatever we passed
right here inside form data is going to create the inputs.
So I'm going to say import react when you make it right react from and then react good we need to created
you know the actual function is going to be called form fields form fields and this form fields is going
to be receiving prompts you know the state of whatever we want to create and then are going to do export
default.
And then of course you know form fields.
It can be form very low form fields.
So now this form fields it's going to be rendering something of course.
So I'm going to be doing this space and I do return opening close.
And what we do on this return we want to return you know a div with something inside.
Now we need to create a function that is going to be having this form data and it's going to be creating
the inputs I'm going to say render and then.
Fields that say the name of function.
We don't have this function.
We get it created in a minute.
Now you know for now we're going to read right now so we can skip that error.
So I got to say Konst render feels it's going to be equal for now nothing opening close and begin not
going to do anything.
Now we have this component so we need to include it inside users so we can use that component so I'm
going to go right here at the top.
I'm going to say import and then form fields.
From.
And then of course we have dot dot for Slash.
We enter widgets and we enter forms and we enter from tails.
So now this components it's available for us to use.
OK.
So now the next step would be to use this component and start passing all the props that we need.
We're going to go right here.
I'm going to be you know just creating this is going to be form fields opening close.
You know self-closing tag that.
So what do we need for this form fields to work.
We're going to need all the information about our form our inputs are going to go right here and are
going to be passing a prompt.
So it's going to be form and I'm to call form data.
We shouldn't skip this but you know whatever we're going to see later.
So I'm going to say that the form data the information that we have inside this group is going to be
this DOD State DOD and then form data which is equal to all of this.
Right.
Where are we going to be adding more more stuff right here.
But for now this is all we need.
So this one feels is going to receive a prop called forms data.
So let's go to form fields and let's start creating this render fields because it's really important.
So okay.
So let me tell you what I'm going to do.
I'm going to create a function I'm going to create a viable that is going to be storing all the information
that we have inside here.
Now if you notice this one it's not an array of objects object.
So what are we going to be doing is going to get that Propst.
And there's this form data and you know structure the information in the way we need.
So I'm going to go right here at the bottom and going to a concert and then form and then array is going
to be equal to an array.
So now what we need to do we need to kind of create a way you know we need to run a function that is
going to be grabbing whatever we have inside form data and it's going to be putting the information
inside the form array.
So going to use of for now for its ESX they're really really good.
You know they are really good to use is really useful for us.
So first I'm going to create a viable that is going to be called element and then name just like that
element name.
And what are you going to be looping.
It's going to be the information that we have inside form data that we're in.
Can it be you can see this and it is going to be prop's that is going to be looping form and then data.
So now we're pretty much doing we're looping this prop's form data and in each iteration we're going
to be storing that particular item inside element that name.
So what I want to do I want to grab the item and store it inside form array.
So I'm going to say form array dot push open it close.
And what I want to do first I want to know the id of the elements I'm going to put name of ID which
is going to be the element name.
So I'm going to copy and paste it right here.
Now I'm going to do coma.
I'm going to do settings just like that settings and settings.
It's going to be equal to props that form data from data and are going to be putting the element name
I know that this doesn't make sense.
I could explain it in a minute.
Don't worry.
And then what I'm going to do I'm going to do console log the form array you know just to see what we
get.
OK.
So let me tell you what is happening right here.
We are calling this form fields and we are passing forward form data.
So it's going to be this is when is non-array.
So we have to have two different inputs.
You know that name and the last name.
So then of course we render feels is going to go to this function is going to create an empty form array
viable.
Now there we're going to be a looping this form data.
Now on each iteration of course we have the data that we have inside each element and then we have the
name of the element you know the key.
So the main idea of doing this is that we want to create one specific item just one item for each input
that contains an ID which is going to be you know the name of each input and then inside settings we
can have the rest of the information which is going to be this one.
All right.
So let's go right here and you know just below the page and right here since we're doing consul lawk
form array we got an array of objects and each arrays can to each area.
Each object contains an ID of the name of the input and then the settings.
Which is all the configuration that we need to create this element.
So now the the the next thing is going to be running a function to doing something that is going to
be looping this form array and it's going to create one input for each ID.
Right one with ID of name and then another one with the last name.
OK.
So I'm going to do this and delete this.
And this one is going to be it's going to be returning the information that we need to render right
here of course they're going to say return again to be accessing this form array.
We're going to be looping in a loop over it.
Now each iteration contains an item you know and then the iteration number going to run a function right
now.
So this function is going to be returning something and what we are going to be returning is going to
be the actual template you know the actual input.
So I'm going to say dev open it close and remember that when we iterate over something we need to pass
a key and the key is going to be the iteration number are going to be adding a class name of form underscore
element.
Good.
And now inside here what we need to do we need to pass the information we need to create the actual
input.
We're going to be doing this in a minute but for now we can decide to make sure that we are looping
everything correctly.
So if I say input input and we are passing two different inputs we should be getting input twice so
you know it is kind of working.
So now OK let's go back to form fields.
Now this whenever we look we need to create the input.
Now what are we going to be doing.
Are going to be creating a function that is going to be entering the data that we have the configuration
and is going to check for each element.
What type of element we have in this case we have an input.
So is going to access a switch just like that before is going to access that template.
It's going to be returning a configuration that we have for a type of input.
Now for now we just have two inputs.
It's going to be the same template but then we're going to be adding a text area and the select.
So we can have a different type of elements if we have a select.
The element is going to be select.
So it's going to be entering a different template.
So OK so let's you know start creating this.
So now I'm going to be creating a function of course the video is going to it's going to be going to
long.
How are be going to be going to the next section.
But you know I'm just going to start creating it right now.
So this function is going to be called render templates make sense.
And on each iteration I'm going to be passing the item.
You know this item equals to whatever information we have right here on each iteration.
So I'm going to go right here at the bottom and I'll be going to be calling this rendered templates
that is going to be equal to you know a function.
And you just open and close it.
So this render templates is going to be receiving some data which is the actual item.
Now whenever we do this and we find that we create a search and switch and we find the template that
we want to render we need to access the information that we have inside you know inside config.
And if you remember the item contains the information about item dot setting's dot and then config.
So just to make make everything less full I'm going to create a viable that is going to be called values
and it's values it's going to be equal to data that settings.
So now instead of doing inside the template data that settings that config and then whatever we're just
going to say.
Right.
Just creating an alias for this.
Now we need a template so I'm going to say let and then form a template that is going to be null at
the beginning.
OK.
It could be empty.
Doesn't matter we are going to say this does matter.
And now right here we need to create a switch that is going to be checking the data that setting that
element and it's going to be deciding if you want to render an input or select or whatever we want to
render.
So if we were going to create a switch that is going to be accessing values dot and then the element
now the elements remember is the time of the.
So it's going access input.
OK so I'm going to say OK if the case is that we want to render an input we can enter this scenario
scenario.
Of course we need to do a break open and close and now after this.
Of course we don't need a default case.
I'm going to go right here at the bottom again to say the fault.
Now whenever we have a default we need to return or at least something.
So I'm going to say form template is going to be equal to normal.
So you know same thing we could use right here at the top and a the.
And whenever we are done with a switch we want to return the form template.
Right.
OK.
So now what we need to do we need to create a template for inputs.
So for now just going to say there and this one is going to be an input.
So if I save it and we go right here we have rendered templates OK.
So it's not defined.
I made a mistake with the names.
I'm pretty sure about that rendered templates won second.
Oh because you know it's a Stigler's component.
So in concert sorry for that.
So OK.
Switch values and that template.
So we have data that settings values and element.
Let me just change it right here.
We have data that's setting and it's plural of course remember that we say settings right here.
OK.
Let's get you know we have nothing so far.
But don't worry we're going to be getting something right here.
So let's go to the next section.
And you know start building the actual template.