OK so let's continue with this.
So right here you're are just looping the information we have right here so we need to at least display
something.
Nothing is happening because we need to do this.
We need to make a reference to form template.
That's the thing that we are returning.
And it's again say this when it's equal to you know some GSX.
So opening close just like that.
So if I save it we're going to get to IMPA it's because we have two different templates that's good.
So I get to go back to form fields that begin to be you know adding all the logic for this.
So now on each iteration we have the items you know each item which is going to be each form element.
So now inside data we have access to data settings and we have all the information about that item.
Let's go to the first one let's go bit by bit.
Now the first element says that we want to label and the label is going to be a name you know we have
a label text and right here we have the ability to you know to to include the Leavell or not.
So I'm going to go to a form fields and I'm going to be creating a function that is going to be checking
all this data and return a Leavell if we need it.
So he's going to be show level just like that.
And this show label is going to be receiving values DOT level.
Remember we made reference to values which is equal data that settings.
Now if we don't do this each time we pass a value we need to do data that settings that level something
like that.
You know it's just pretty boring.
So OK so I'm going to do this you know do something else going to do values that label.
Now then we to do a coma and we're going to be passing values DOT level text.
So pretty much we are passing this Balis.
OK so this is going to go to a function that calls show level.
We didn't have this function begin to create it right now.
So this show label is going to be you know just checking if we have a label or not.
So I'm going to say Konst show Leavell this show label's going to receive two prompts me.
Make it nice and it's going to be receiving the arguments that if we want to show it and then we're
going to be getting the actual labels are going to call it show and label now are going to be returning
something of course dysfunction is going to be returning believe it or not.
So I'm going to say return now if we have a show which just means it means that we have true.
We're going to do something.
And if not we're going to do something else.
We're going to be returning No because we don't have a label.
OK.
So I'm going to go right here at the bottom I got to say level.
So in the case that this one is true we want to return a label that has you know the label text on going
to say label.
OK.
So if we go right here we get name and we get the last name again.
We are just looping each item.
It's matching the type of the element it's entering the template.
It's creating the template.
And then at the end it's going to it's going to return that specific input right here.
So the application it's including first name and then the last name because we have two different elements
now make sense so far.
So let's you know continue creating the actual input you know the most important part.
So I get to create an input because we have an input.
If the case is select instead of input begin to do select you know we can do this later so we can have
a whatever I'm going to have an impact and this input is going to be a self-closing tag.
This is going to be requiring some configuration.
If you remember inside user inside form data and the name of input inside config we have all the information
about that.
You know that input the name the text and the place holder whatever.
Ok so I'm going to go.
But back to form fields and are going to be adding all the information that we need.
I'm going to atomistic right here let's go back.
It's not text it's not it's type.
Maybe you notice this and you were saying do you mean it was day.
Well yeah I did.
So the type is going to be type text you know type text make sense are going to be going to go back
to form fields.
And now we need to pass this configuration.
How do we pass it.
One way of doing it is just creating a type.
It's going to be equal to values.
You know config and then type something like that.
But since all the information that you have you have it inside you know an actual object.
What you could do is something much simpler.
You can do that dad.
And then values that config.
So now react.
It's going to be creating a property for each data that we have inside config.
So if I go to confect if I go to the view we have.
Enter your name and enter your last name.
You know we are getting the placeholder me make this bigger let it go go.
So we have the type which was text the name name empathy and then the placeholder remember that if you
add something right here that should not be included inside the actual input as a property.
You know it's going to get included.
So remember that the only information that we need to get right here inside confect is whatever we're
going to be putting right here.
OK.
So let's go back to form fields.
Now what else do we need.
We need the input we need to value.
This is going to be a control component.
So we're going to be adding value.
It's going to go right here at the bottom and save value equal to values.
DODD And if we check right here we have value.
So I'm going to say value of course value.
So now this impede the value of this input it's going to be whatever we have right here.
If I save Francis the application will reload and we're going to have a pretty fine value right here.
Let me save it.
There you go.
So we have Frances that's good.
So that is working.
OK.
So everything is ready.
We are creating and we are creating the inputs are going to be creating a text file and we're going
to be creating a select feel but we're going to be doing that in a minute.
Now what do we need to do next.
Well it's really important for us whenever we submit the form we need a way right here when we submit
we need a way to pass a function right here that is going to be catching the new state of the ballot.
Remember you are going to be using a control component.
It's going to be grabbing the value that we are typing here.
It's going to access the form data updating information update the value.
And then the application is going to be read rendering.
You know with the new value maybe then a and whatever we need to do that right now is going to be a
little bit confusing.
But don't worry.
You know again telling you how to do it step by step.
OK so now let's read that on change.
So we can update you know the news date.
So first I'm going to go to user and of course what we need to do we need to pass a function that is
going to be receiving the new state after we type a new value.
It is going to be adding you know updating the state.
So I gotta go right here to form Phil's and at the beginning this is not going to make sense but don't
worry it's going to make sense in a minute.
I'm going to say change is going to be equal to something.
So now whenever we get in book form fields begin to be passing a function that is going to be called
change.
So change is going to be equal to use date because we need to pass the new state.
And again Don't worry is going to make sense.
So it's going to be whenever we do this whenever we trigger this change function is going to be calling
to a function that is going to be called update up date.
And then four and then you state and let me make it right.
You state.
So the main job of this update form is going to be grabbing the new state of the you know the inputs
and do set state of whatever new state we have.
So if we go right here the top I can call this update form going to say update form.
It's going to be equal to this new state that we're going to be getting on the ride new state and this
new state.
Of course we're going to be running a function with this.
And this of course is going to do this this this.
That said state and whatever data we have right here for now I'm just going to do Konsole long.
And then again a console log you know hello whatever.
So oh sorry instead of doing hello I'm going to show the new state now we don't have this function.
We don't have something that connects to this change and we get it created right now.
But notice no that whenever we Boag we never call it we call the change within the form fields is going
to be running a function that it's going to be expecting a.
You know an argument with some data and then it's going to be passing whatever we're getting from the
other component is going to pass it to that form you know with the new arguments.
So this one this ones are just the same.
The only difference is that you're getting it from a different place.
This one is receiving from foreign fields and this one this one right here.
It's passing the update form as an argument.
All right.
Don't worry you're going to see it in a minute.
Senators and now whenever we change of an input when we trigger a change whenever we type something
just like with did before we need to run an event.
So it's going to be on change and the change is going to be equal to something.
Now this change first is going to grab the event because we need to grab the value and they're begin
to be running a function that can be called Change hand or good.
Now this change handler is going to be passing the event makes sense.
You already did this in the past.
So we don't have dysfunction that's created right now.
Going to say change handlers going to be equal to make Konst right here.
Maybe it was like the pope.
So this change handler is going to be receiving and event it's going to be called to a function opening
close.
So now whenever we type something we have access to the event.
So what we can do is say console log event that target that value.
And if we go right here to the component I type f so we get the T.F. we get whatever.
OK.
So it's working.
We are getting the data inside change handler.
But the thing is the problem is that whenever we type something we are not updating the state.
So we only get you know the letter I'm typing the character I'm typing.
So we need a way to catch that information store it someplace and then pass the new state of form data.
That's the main point of this.
Now the thing is that we are getting the event right.
So now whenever we have this component loads we have a prop and inside probably have something called
form data which is you know the current state of the application.
So what we need to do we need to access form data find the name of the input that we want to change
because at this point inside event we don't have that.
So we need to wait to pass the the the name of the input.
We want to change and then access that modify it and pass the new state.
OK.
Going to delete this.
Now I'm going to need it now so far.
Whenever we call change handler we're just passing the event but you are also going to need is the name
of the Emperor that we want to modify.
If you remember whenever we do right here for example whenever we pass prompts we have right here inside
the template.
We have data.
So if I do console log and data let's go one more time to N.F..
Now we get ID name which is the name of the input and then settings and then we have an ID.
And then last name.
So what we need to do we need to catch this ID and password to change handler so gay.
So I'm going to say coma and then data that ID.
So now this function is going to receive two arguments the actual event and the ID of the elements we
want to modify.
OK.
Now what do we need to do we need to update the new state.
So I'm going to say Kunst and are going to create a novel that is going to be called new state and this
one is going to be equal to prop's dot form data now form data its going to be equal to all of this
to all the inputs that we have.
Okay.
So now inside the new state since we have the ID of what we want to change what we can do is going to
say let me go right here is going to be going to new state you know access that variable then fine the
ID find the ID and then of course we can be access in the value and the value is going to be equal to
event that target dot value.
Okay so now let me do the console log and then you state so we can see what we get is going to reload
the application any file type.
NF We know we get the new state viable and if I do go to name inside value we have a neph.
OK so this is working we are adding the value inside the correct place.
So now since we have the new state of things what we need to do is we need to pass this new state to
the user component and the user component is going to be doing that.
That said stayed with the new state.
Okay.
So if I go to form fields going to delete this can save it and I guess the video is going too long.
So we're going to be doing this on the next section where we're going to be doing is just passing the
news tade to the other component so we can update that state.