OK so let's finish this this first.
So here we have the new stage in this new state equals to all of the inputs.
No the whole state now and you might be thinking why updating the whole state.
So right here we go to user the top.
We have one key.
It's going to be equal to form data.
And inside we have all the information about the inputs and what we are updating what we're going to
be at.
Dating is going to be all the information.
Again it's one key one value which is calls form data.
The thing is that inside form fields we cannot access you stayed that form data or that name and then
just update one value inside this because the application will not take it.
You know we not render.
So what we need to do is we need to pass the whole new state.
You know the value of this form data key but to pass that we need to pass all if not it's just going
to be updating the value and form data is going to be equal to value and not name and last name and
everything else.
So that's why we need to pass the whole object.
They're going to go back to form fields and we know that whenever we type something you're getting the
new state.
In this case if I type an h an H.
Right here we get the name and the values going to be h.
OK.
So we have the new state so we need to pass this new state to the user component so we can update the
state right here.
If you remember we have a function called change and this change receives an arguments of a value whatever
Marmol and then it's going to be calling to a new function call update form.
And is going to pass that argument that we are getting.
OK.
So I get to go back to form Phil's going to delete this and since we're passing as Probst called change
what we can do we can access prompts and we have that function available and it's going to be called
of course it's going to be called Change open and close and we're going to be passing as an argument
the state.
OK.
So now this change is going to get triggered.
And this is going to receive the new state as an argument and it's going to be running this update form
and it's going to pass the new state and right here inside update that form we are getting that argument
and we are doing the cons..
So pretty much we are doing the same thing we are we're doing right here doing the council lock.
So if I go right here and type a G we get name a last name and name is going to have value.
OK.
But now we are inside the user component and we have access to update the state of this one.
So what are we going to do here.
And the lead This is going to be doing this.
That said state.
Does that set stayed open and close and begin going to say that form data is going to be equal to the
new state can save it going to go right here and now if we type something since it's going to be updating
the state whenever we trigger on change we should be able to get the values right here.
Going to say F R and C as Frances.
So this is working.
It's updating the input with whatever value we have inside form data.
And the same thing right here.
Last name.
Good.
So you know this one works.
Now the thing now the problem is that if we want to submit something we want to submit the form.
We just need the name of the key and just devalue everything else for us.
It's going to be relevant.
You know we we cannot use it.
So we need a way to loop through all the continents and just get the key and the value.
OK.
So right here we have this submit form.
We don't have a function that does that.
So we get it created right now going to say serve med form is going to be equal to an event opening
close and of course we run a function.
Now we pass the event as an argument and submit form needs to do just like we did before events prevent
and then default.
All right.
So this is going to stop the form for from Mitton.
So now what we need to do we need to loop the current state and get the name of the key and just to
bother you this portion of code.
Okay.
So first I'm going to create a viable that it's going to store all of this.
So I'm going to say data to see if med makes sense it's going to be equal to open and close.
Okay.
So now we need to loop the information that we have and create this data to submit.
So I'm going to create a for open close and then just rerun the for now the 4 needs.
The key is going to say let key and remember that key is going to be equal to last name and name I'm
good.
And then of course we need to do space and in and we say this that state and since we want to look at
the state of form data we say form data.
So now on each iteration on each iteration it's going to be access and the key.
So I'm going to say OK so what I want to do I want to create inside data is have made a key that is
going to be equal to the key on the first iteration the is going to be equal to name.
So now data is made is going to have a key of name something like that simple like that.
And now the value of name is going to be equal to this.
That state DOT formed data then we pass the key that in this case its name.
And then we passed the value.
So in the first iteration this one is going to be equal to whatever value we have.
All right.
And then on the next iteration is going to say last name is going to be equal to whatever.
So I'm going to delete this.
You don't need it.
Me make this a little bit better.
OK.
So this is pretty much done now.
If I do a console log do console not log opening close and I console the data to SIFF med.
We're going to get the information we need to make a network request are going to type Francis are going
to type Jones whatever and I'm going to do med.
Ok we get name Francis and last name of med so we have all the data we need to make an ad for request.
And now in the future if you want to add more inputs what you need to do is just copy one to one of
the one of one of the ones we have right here.
The koma do something else something some something like that something is going to be unempowered you
know something we just need to change something simple right here and then something whatever doesn't
matter.
And the template that the function is going to pick this up and it's going to be rendering.
So if we type Francis then Jones then else and we submit the form.
You know we get it we get that.
So this is ready to submit.
So now inside the you know the submit form we can make a network request just like we did before with
Acciona than posed.
And the your well then coma and then we pass this data to submit.
And that's that's all you need is going to do a network request and post the values you have inside
data databases of mid.
Of course we don't have x years we are going to do something else right here in a minute.
OK so everything is ready.
We're going to do.
Quick you know conclusion of all of this because I need you to make sure that you know what we are doing
that kind of make sense to you and then we're going to be doing validations.
And of course this form data all of this rules are going to be going to be changing a little bit.
We're going to be extend this.
So again it's going to be getting a little bit more confused.
So we're going to do a little recap and all the all of this logic right here.
OK so let's review let's recap what we have so far.
So first we have a component that it should be rendering a form element some form elements just like
this.
We have a state with like of non-indexed like a manifest of the inputs that we want to create the first
input is going to be a name and it's going to be a type of input.
And the second one it's a last name and it's going to be a type of input.
OK.
So then we run a component we make we call to a component called form fields and we pass the information
you know the state of form data which is all of us.
OK.
So that form fields is going to be entering right here and it's going to be calling render fields.
Now this component this form fields is going to be receiving some props you know with all of this data
we have on top.
OK.
So the first function that is going to be running it's render fields.
Now for you if you notice inside here the this object is not good to us because we need to create one
input for each of the elements we have inside form data.
So this function is creating a new type of array we are restructuring everything.
So we can lump the information.
So for each elements we are grabbing this.
And we are pushing inside form data array.
So now we get the information on a different manner.
So we get four Morais save it.
So now we get just like this an array of objects with an idea of name and then settings is going to
be you know the actual information on each key.
So once we have this form array is going to be looping this form array.
And for each element we have inside form data on you know name and last name.
In this case it's going to be calling to render templates to render one input and it's going to be passing
the item on each iteration.
So this read the job of this rendered templates is going to be checking what type of element we have
on each iteration and it's going to be checking the input the type of element which in this case input.
And if we have an input it's going to render one template.
And if you have something as an input is going to render a different template.
So far we have only one.
OK.
So render templates is going to pass the all the information about that item.
So render template is going to be going right here is going to grab that data.
You know all the information about that is going to be checking what type of element we have right here.
Values element in if the case is impot is going to be returning this template.
So in conclusion if you have 100 types 100 100 values right here you know different inputs if you have
100.
This function is going to run a 100 times one for each element on that list.
So now it's going to be returning this template.
Now this template checks if we have a label and if we do is going to put it and then it's going to be
rendering an.
Because the case is impot of course.
Now inside config on the manifest inside config we have all the configuration about that type of input
which is the name.
You know they type text and a placeholder.
So it's including all of that config values that is going to be adding a value which is going to be
equal to this value but at the beginning it's going to be empty of course.
And then of course it's going to be adding those elements inside the screen.
Good.
So now what do we need to do.
Of course what it does is to trigger a function every time that we need to change that we change something.
So we can update the state.
So we have this function on change.
Now the on change handler is going to be running a function and it's going to passing is going to be
passing the event type that contains the information of that input of the values that we're typing right
here and it's going to be passing the ID of the element.
Now this is going to be equal to the this part of the code to the key of whatever we want to be updating.
Let's say that we want to update name.
So this data ID is going to be equal name.
OK.
So the job of change handler is going to be entering creating data Barville of new state that it's a
copy just a duplicate of prompts that form data.
And at this point if nothing gets entered right here form data is going to be equal to all of this not
just the input to all of this.
So then we access since we have the ID which is in this case let's assume that we are changing this
one equals to name we access that new state name and we access the value and we change it with the one
that we are typing right here.
OK.
And every time we change something we type something is going to be calling a function that calls change.
Now we passed this function inside probs.
If we go to user whenever we both form fields we have a function called change.
This change is going to be running a function and now this function is going to be expecting the new
state.
You know whatever we are just updating right here inside this marvel and right here we call it change
and we pass an argument.
We pass the whole list of all the elements you know but the updated version.
So OK.
So inside user this function is going to receive that and it's going to be calling a function and it's
going to pass those arguments.
Now update form the job of update form is getting that new state and it's going to be doing this said
state and now is going to update to the new state with the correct values.
OK.
And at the end whenever we submit the form we create a viral that contains only the name and the key
which is going to be only with the ballot you know because of course we cannot post this to the server.
We just need that name of the key and this valley right here.
So what we do right here we create a for loop that is going to be getting the key in this case on the
first loop is going to be name and on the second is going to be last name and to each key is going to
be adding the value that we have on the state and this is going to generate an object with what we want
to post to the server.
OK.
So this is pretty much all the logic we have so far.
So and again just like I told before this works good if we add more inputs is going to be adding all
the inputs of medically.
Now the only thing right now is that you know we could have more we could have different inputs.
So we're going to be adding a couple of more it's going to be real real simple.
It's going to short we're going to be adding a text area and we're going to be adding a select select
and put with options inside.
We're going to be doing that.
And then what we're going to do we are going to be adding validation to this because validation it's
really important.
Well let's do that right now.