OK so now what can you be doing.
We're going to be adding different scenarios.
So so far we just have an input.
You know we an 11 type of input.
So what happens if we want to add a text area or maybe select.
So that's what we're going to be doing or doing right now.
Let's say we want to add Selecta I'm sorry a text area one so I got to go right here at the bottom after
the last name and I'm going to be adding and using Harry for this.
It's going to be message.
The message is going to of course contain some configuration.
I'm going to copy the one on top and you know paste it right here.
The type is not going to be an input.
We need a different scenario so it's going to be text area.
But then we have a value.
The label is going to be true the label text is going to be message whatever then the config and the
config it's going to be a little bit different because you know we have a different configuration for
text areas.
So but the name is still still the same.
We're going to say message.
Now we don't need the type and we don't need the placeholder but inside a text area.
What we can do we can use rose and we can use calls.
I'm going to say rows and calls.
It's going to be equal to 36 something big.
So far so good.
You know everything is looks nice.
The only thing that it's missing right now is the template part inside here.
We only have a case for inputs.
So we need to add a case for text areas.
So I'm going to say cased opening close and then text area now text area.
Of course never forget to do the break inside text.
Arianne what we want to do we want to catch this scenario scenario and return a template.
So it's going to be formed template equals to you know some GSX.
Now the data sets for this is going to be really really simple.
So I'm going to backspace and now what we need to do first we need to return a dev you know one element
now inside the diff.
We still have a label song to copy the one we have on top and pasted.
So now we want to do.
And if I say this note is that I begin to get the label.
So this is working.
So what we want to do we want to return a text area got to open and close the text area.
You know I'm going to just not make an self-closing tag text area in the text area and received some
configuration.
And again we have the configuration inside config Raheel config.
We have the name the rows in the calls.
So we're going to do just like with it before Bally use that config going to go right here and paste
it.
What else do we have.
We have a value so I'm going to copy the values and paste that right here.
We have an on change so we can paste the On Change event so we can update the state of this one.
So the next thing is going to be you know nothing else.
That's the only thing that we need to do.
I'm going to delete the text area and then not make it a self-closing tag.
So all this is what we need because of the configuration we have the value.
And we have the onchange handler.
So everything is ready.
So if I go right here we get the message and the text area is working OK.
So going to reload the page and go back to user.
Now what I want to do I want to cancel logged the date it's met.
So whenever we submit I want to check that we are getting all the information correctly.
So I'm going to go to the form and I'm going to say Francis I'm going to say Jones and for the message
I'm going to say hello guys were going to submit and if I check the data to submit we get last name
Jones message.
Hello guys and name Francis.
So it's working.
So again it was really easy.
The only thing that we needed to do of course add the template in this case.
But if you from the future we've already have this template now for a text area.
The only thing we need to do is to add a message here and that's it.
It's really simple once you.
You were done with as you create all the logic for this.
Just at this and maybe on the future you're going to be working with different projects you can make
a lot of Web applications and you can copy all of this logic to this works like a template.
And you don't have to code all over again you just copy paste and you pass an object.
And since you did this you did all the logic to make this work.
You know how it works.
OK.
So OK so we have a text area.
Let's add a select.
It's going to be a little bit different.
So I'm going to go right here at the bottom and are going to do coma and I'm going to create a select
for age.
Really real simple I get copy all of the things we have the top and paste it.
And now the element of course it's going to be something else.
We're going to say that the values still empty label true we can have a label but it's going to say
age.
Now the config is going to be a little bit different.
The name is still going to be age but we don't have rows and cause what do we have on the Select.
We have options.
It's going to create a viral that it's going to be hosting all the options.
We want to show.
And the starters start is going to be an array.
Now inside the array we can have an array of objects.
So then whenever we create select we can loop the options and show the options inside.
So I'm going to save Vau and the first one is going to be equal to 1 and then I'm going to do something
real simple instead of putting the actual H.
One two three four five until one whatever are going to say the value one equals to 10.
Tilt swing makes sense.
The next one I'm going to just copy the one on top and paste it at the bottom.
And of course it's going to be de-value number two but it's going to start from 20 and 30 and they are
going to do one more.
It's going to be the last case the volume number three.
And instead of 20 is going to be Plus than 30.
Now something real simple.
OK.
So everything looks ready.
So now we need to create a scenario for a select.
So I'm going to go right here.
The bottom I'm going to say case open close.
And of course it's going to be select.
Never forget to do the break.
If not nothing is going to work.
OK.
So we have we need the form template.
Let me copy this one on top and it's going to be equal to you know some GSX and that's why we use parenthesis.
So this one is going to be real simple.
First then it's going to get a little bit of you know we need to use more logic whenever we need to
return the options.
But first at first it's going to be the same and the other ones we have a div we show a label if it's
enabled and then we return a select.
Let me make it like this.
Select So this select has some configuration just like the other ones.
But if you notice the other ones have the information inside config and all of this is going inside
the actual attack.
But this one inside the Select we have the name that it's going to go in the tag but then the options
are going to go in a different place.
So if we do just something like this inside the select just like this is going to be adding that object
inside the actual sled.
And we don't want that.
So what I'm going to do first I'm going to create a value because we need a value and then for the name
I'm going to make it manually it's going to be name.
And then we access use dot config dogs name and then begin to get the name with all of the options.
Of course we need to non-chain on change.
So I'm going to page the on change OK.
So you know we're getting the select and everything else but we don't have options.
So far I'm going to create.
Right here.
Going to be accessing the options inside config.
We're going to loop this because we have an array of objects.
We can do that.
So going to open all the braces.
Going to make a reference to values that come Feg DOD options options plural.
And then I'm going to map overhead.
Whenever we run a map we each have an item on each iteration and we have that each number and this one
is going to be equal to a function just like this.
All right.
You know looks good.
Now if we do this if we return a function with curly braces we have to make a return right here since
I want to return some GSX.
I can just delete this and just use parenthesis.
And this by default is going to return some GSX you know we know this.
So inside here we're going to be returning an option real simple.
Now the option is to needs to have a key because we are using a loop.
So we need to add the key.
So we have the I the number.
So everything looks it's going to be fine it's going to just output it.
So we get a net getting an error.
But don't worry you're going to check it in a minute.
So we have a key.
And what else.
We need a value for each option.
We have a value and if we check it right here we have Bahau.
So we are going to say item dot Val.
Now inside the option again we have a text and if we have read if we check it's going to be text.
So we say item dot text you can save it that's going to reload the application and we get an error cannot
read properly.
Map of undefine.
And this is pretty much maybe because I made a mistake with the name.
Let's go to values config options key item you know everything looks nice and you just don't check.
So I made a mistake right here.
I say option and or in reality makes sense that it's going to be options.
Because we have more than one.
And I was going to work.
OK.
So we get age turned 20 30 20 30 and Plaza 30 that looks really bad because I don't have a style for
this.
I'm going to be adding this in a minute.
I'm pretty sure that in your version of this template you're going to get this styling but don't worry
that's fine you're getting the the options 10 20 20 30 plus then 30.
So in theory if I select one and submit the form with the other things Francis then Jones and they make
this little bit bigger and a message of hello if I submit this you're going to get an object with the
age of the value which was number two last name message and name.
So everything works as expected.
And if in the future you want to you know at a new select you just have to copy the previous one paste
it and change the names of course and the options.
That's the only thing that we need to do.
OK.
So this is good.
Now the only thing that we need to do right now everything it's done but you know we need to validate
things.
We are not going to let the users enter the information that they want.
Know we need to regulate this when we do this a little bit.
So we're going to be adding some validation.
So we're going to be you know start doing that.
So again it's going to take a it's going to take a couple of lectures.
So grab a new cup of coffee and just come back.