OK so now we're going to be adding some validation.
And just like we did before we are going to do everything from the template you know that's the main
idea of doing all of this.
So right from the start.
Each of each item you know each input it's to have inside the manifest you know inside the schema a
rule for validation.
So I'm going to add a coma and I'm going to say validation and this one is going to be called to you
know an object.
Now at least we don't need to have the of what we're going to be doing.
You can change this in the future.
You know it's up to you.
We need to have at least one validation that is going to be required.
And this could be either true or it could be either false so if this one is false it's not going to
validate anything.
But for starters when it's going to be true the name is going to be required good.
So then I'm going to do koma are going to be adding more things are going to be adding a rule for Barlett.
So if this after we do the validation if this impot it's valid we're going to be changing this property
for now whenever the application start is going to be false.
So then coma we're going to be earning it touched and get it about.
Talk about this later.
But don't worry just as you just need to add it and then we can have a validation message after we validate
everything.
We're going to check if it's wrong.
And if it's wrong begin to return a message so we can say valley Dacian and then message could be shorter.
But no this name mix makes sense.
And when the application starts of course this message is going to be empty.
We don't have an actual message.
OK.
So this is the the start the starting point begin to validate first the name.
Now the rest of the inputs need to have at least ambulation just like that right here.
So just get a copy of this validation required and everything else.
I'm going to paste it on the all the ones I'm going to do koma paste.
This one you know koma paste.
And of.
Let's leave the message and the H because first we're going to do the validation inside the template
so we can test the inputs for now.
So just to make it a little bit faster.
So OK so this one is going to be false.
For now just false.
And again if we start false we didn't have any rule.
It's going to be valid equals true of course.
OK let's get we're going to just do the inputs first.
So now whenever we the application is going to is going to create this input we need to start checking
whenever we add something inside the input.
Whenever I type something I want to run the validation and check it.
So if we go to form fields right here we have.
Now we have a function that onchange and we just run the change handler.
So inside change handler we could check the information that we are typing and then just decide if this
information it's correct or not.
No that's the main idea.
OK.
So I'm going to go right here at the top and I'm going to enter the change handler so I'm going to go
here at the bottom.
And now I need to start checking things first.
I'm going to create a variable that is going to be called valid data there's valid data is going to
be equal to true or it's going to be equal to false or it's going to be equal to something.
So right here I to make a reference to Valley date and this one is going to be a function that is going
to be checking if this input and the value we have inside it's true or false given the rules that we
have right here.
So OK so this validate is going to run some checks on this impot for example on the name.
So right from the start is we need to pass which impot we want to check.
And if you remember we have the information inside new state and Id say if we pass to validate the name
and the all the information about that input this Band-Aid is going to receive this input in particular.
And of course then it's going to receive this one and then this one and everything else.
But right now we can focus on this one.
OK so Vulg. is going to be receiving the you know that data we don't have this function.
We're going to create right now.
So I'm going to say Konst and then Byerly date.
And this one is going to receive that elements are going to say element.
And then of course we run a function.
Okay that's good.
So first I'm going to do a console log and then elements just like that are going to save it for now
we can get now going into anything.
But if I type f we can get that discount lock elements.
So you know we have the config the element input level and we have touch and valid and everything else.
So now we have access to this element and we can check the validation and valid and whatever.
OK we're going to do that right now.
So right from the start is whenever we check if it's valid or not if it's invalid We need to return
something.
So we're going to be returning if it's valid.
So this one is going to change.
True.
And if it's invalid of course it's going to be false.
And then if it's false you know it's not valid.
We need to return a message for this.
OK.
Whenever the applications start and we type something inside this and put this function is going to
run and right from the again this input is going to be valid.
So I'm going to return an array and you can see in a minute why it's going to be true.
And then the second session in the parade is going to be something empty.
So this one this position it's equal to the valet's message.
So we fight save this and run this right now this input it's going to be always true you know.
True because it's the ballot and then the message.
But then what are we going to do.
We're going to be doing some checking right here.
And at the end we can turn this error.
All right.
And this is going to be equal to this.
But if we do some checking right here and this element it's not valid.
We're going to return false and we're going to return the message.
So this data is going to receive an array with true or false.
And the message or no message no.
That's the idea make sense.
So right here and going to start doing the check in and we do this with just simple gifts.
There's nothing magical right here.
So we need to access that element and Dot and I are going to be access validation the Dacian just like
that.
If I go to a user we are entering these key.
And now we're going to be checking if I have a required rule.
Are going to be creating the validation for required.
So if we do have an element that calls required and it's equal to true we want to run some code right
here.
So first I'm going to create a variable that is going to be called valid.
This one is going to be checking if the elements it's empty or not.
So I'm going to say elements that are going to access the value dot.
I'm going to trim it.
So if you have a white space it's going to remove that and begin to be checking if this elements it's
equal is not equal to an empty string.
So if you have an empty string there's one valid is going to be returning false.
Ok so I'm going to say Konst and message and it's going to be equal and I'm going to be returning some
template strings because of course we want to return a message.
We could do this differently.
Just going to do it this way.
So I'm going to return some template strings.
So if they are valid it's not true.
No it's not valid.
We want to return a message but if it's not you want to return something empty.
So the message for a required is going to say this field is required.
Make sense.
Ok so I'm going to go right here at the bottom and I'm going to say error and it's going to be equal
to not valid.
I'm sorry if it's not valid.
The error is going to be equal to something or is going to be equal to no error which is the one we
have on top.
So OK let's go again if we can to check.
I'm in mistake right here.
Me.
There we go.
So we're going to be checking if this is valid.
This is going to be returning true or false.
If it's not valid begin at every turn this message inside the barbel message if it's valid begin out
not going to return anything.
Then this error of Will just the same we have on top it's going to be checking if it's valid.
So if it's not now that we want to return an array with the new values not with this once but if it's
valid we want to return error which is equal to true and nothing.
So OK so I'm going to go right here.
And first we return valid which is true or false.
In this case it's going to be of course false.
It's not valid.
And then we return an error message which is going to be message.
Let me make this better.
OK.
So now when I'm going to do.
I'm going to do cancel long do right here and I'm going to be just doing a console log for the Bali
data.
All we have right here at the top are going to reload the application.
And of course I'm going to be going to type and Neph now since we have a N.F. it means that this input.
It's not empty.
So we have about you.
So this input is true and we have a message of none.
Nothing.
OK an empty message.
Now a five day lead.
If you're going to get false because it's not valid.
And you know we get this field is required.
OK.
So this valid data is getting an array with whatever we want to render.
You know we want to update the state of the form.
OK.
So we're going to be doing the same thing we did right here.
We're going to access the data we have right here and begin to change the values that we have inside
New state and I.D. and that it's going to be of course updating the state.
So OK.
So first we need to access the valid right here we have that valid.
We need to change it to true or false depending on what we have inside valid data.
So I'm going to say and use new state new and then state then I make a reference to the ID.
And then again I'm going to check I'm going to access the valid and now the information that we have
right here.
It's inside the array of valid data.
So I'm going to save valid data and it's going to be equal to the first position on the array.
So now I'm going to copy of this because we just need to change some things are going to be accessing
the news state ID and are going to be accessing the validation message and going to be changing that.
So hollidays message and I'm going to be passing whatever we have on the second position of the array
of ballot data.
So now I'm going to go right here I'm going to do a console log for the new state.
So if I do new state I'm going to get guns like a lock of the state to begin to be updating you know
this new state is going to go to change and change is going to be updating the whole state of the application.
So if I type in f I get name and name is going to be ballot true and validation message nothing.
Now if I go back it closes if I go back and deleted the next state of name is going to contain valid
falls.
So it's not valid.
And we have a message inside validation message.
This field is required.
OK.
So it's kind of working.
So now what we need to do we need a function that is going to be checking if we do have a message and
the input it's not valid and it's going to be showing a message right here because that's the main point
of this.
OK.
So I'm going to go back to form fields.
I'm just going to just going to delete this for now.
I'm going to save it.
Now where can we check if we have a message on the state.
We can do it on the template we can check on the template if we have a message down there and display
something or not.
So right here at the bottom I'm going to create a function that is going to say show validation we're
going to open and close and we need to pass whatever data we have inside each item inside the state
of each item.
In this case we have it inside values remember that we do data that settings.
So I'm going to be passing values.
We didn't have this function so far.
So going to be adding the function for now.
The function is going to be call Konst.
Again show validation and show validation is going to receive in arguments and then just you know just
render the information.
So the arguments I'm going to call data.
You can call it whatever you want.
You can pass values or you know it's up to you.
So right here what we do we are going to be returning a message an error message if we do have one inside
the state.
So I'm going to go right here and creative a marvel that is going to be called for and then message
makes sense right.
And it's going to be No.
For now it's going to be no.
So now what we need to we need to do we need to check if we have an error message an actual message.
So we are going to be checking data and then validation right.
Going to be checking if we have something inside validation if this one is true.
OK.
And then we're going to check something else we're going to check if the data is valid.
So if it's not valid it means that we have a message.
So we're going to be returning an error message.
We're going to say error message is it's going to be equal to return some GSX.
And then of course I'm going to be adding just one class name and I call that legal error.
It's going to be on the CSSA styles.
And inside here we need to add to pass whatever error message whatever message we're adding from the
validation right here.
And this one since we are getting right here the new state is going to be equal to this field required.
So if I open and close and say data dot and then validation message is going to be rendering whatever
message we have there.
And then at the end of course we need to return something.
So we return error.
And then message.
OK.
Look sermonize should be working.
So if I type f of course we didn't have an error message.
This is good but if I go back and deleted you know we are passing the information to the state.
The application read renderers.
And on this new render we do have an error message.
So it's going to detect it right here and it's going to be showing the validation message that we have
inside the new state.
So we get this field is required.
And if I type something this is State you know it's going to be valid.
So it's not going to be showing a message anymore and it's valid.
True.
So OK.
It works if I delete it.
We get the same result.
All right that's good.
So we're going to be adding more more things right here.
But you know again this video went too long.
Let's go to the to the next section.
You know the next video and going to be kind of finishing all of this.