OK so now we're going to be doing is going to be adding a new validation rule for this so we can you
know just add more rules on the same statement.
So are going to go right here to users.
And what I want to do I want to add a rule that it's going to be checking if we have more than five
characters so are going to do coma and I'm going to do an ad men land something like that you can call
it whatever you want and I want to get at least more than five characters.
OK.
So now we have a rule for this how can we you know check add a rule for this piece of code.
Again right here we haven't.
We have a function that is going to be checking all the rules and do something if we have something.
So you know we can add the rules right here.
We're going to go right here at the bottom.
They're going to be adding the rule and if you remember he was called Mean lenge.
So I'm going to say if open it close and if element validation and I'm of course going to change require
and then we do mean lenth we want to run some code.
So first we need to check if this is valid.
So it's going to be valid it's going to be equal to something are going to be assaye accessing the elements
that value dot and then the Lang because of course we want to check how many letters we have how many
characters.
And this one needs to be greater or equal than something and that something is going to be this number.
So again we just access that.
It's going to be elements darte then validation that and then mean Len.
So now this one is going to be true or false depending on what we have in the closet.
And then we need to add the message so it's going to be message it's going to be equal then.
And I'm just going to copy the one we have at the bottom so we can spare some time.
So if it's not valid we're going to be adding a message she's going to be must be greater than and and
going to be a plus and then make a reference to these elements validation mingling and of course if
we don't have an error message it's not going to pass anything.
OK so now we need to return the error and the validation message is going to copy and paste it and then
that is all.
So let's check it.
If I type enough we're going to get a message must be greater than 5 5.
Keep typing things is going to go away because we have more than five.
And if I delete some we have less than five so we get the error message.
So you know that can work.
And there's one problem right here.
Let's go back to reload the application now.
If I type of character just like why I'm instantly getting must be greater than five.
So it would be good if we get this error message whenever we do the on Blur's.
You know whenever we focus on a different place and if we are right here you're typing and I go out
and this is not valid.
Then I should be getting the error message and not before that.
That's why inside user we have touched property so we can create something that is going to be changing
that touched to True or false depending if we deal with it on blur.
And you know that kind of stuff.
OK.
So let's begin this.
First we need an event listener that is going to be listening if we you know we focus out and that of
course is going to be called on blur.
We didn't have that function.
So this blur what it's going to be doing is going to be just running the same function we have right
here whenever we do we move outside.
It's going to run this function.
You're going to see in a minute why so right here going to be passing a new action right here that is
going to be triggering the same thing.
OK so I'm going to say on blur.
This is not the end listener.
This is just a prop.
It's going to be doing the same thing that we do on change.
OK.
Paste it down there.
So now right here if you go to form fields we didn't have something that listens for that on Blar on
Blar listener so I'm going to go right here.
I'm going to be adding this on blur.
It's going to be a mistake.
This is the correct one and this is the re-act event listener right.
So this on blur what it's going to be doing is going to be triggering the change handler whenever we
focus out of this input.
So again we just copy the same thing we're going to be running the same function and we have one problem.
Whenever we we do the ampler we focus out that elements we need to tell the new state that the state
that we're going to be updating to.
We need to tell it to tell if this blur right.
Here is this property right here.
The touch should be false or true you know.
So right here whenever we are triggered this we need to say true.
And then this one we need to say forms.
It's not going to be passing a third argument.
This one is going to be true.
True.
And the other one is going to be false.
So this could be could do this you know many many different ways.
When we hit the the second part of the NBA project we're going to change a little bit of this is going
to change it a little bit.
OK.
So when whenever we have an umpire we're going to run the change handler and begin to pass a third argument.
So I'm gonna go right here at the top and we're going to be changing this function.
So this change handler now is going to get a third argument.
It's going to be the blur which is going to be true or false.
And we only want to validate whenever blur.
It's equal to true.
You know if it's true it means that we did the on focus and we want to do something.
So I'm going to say if blur than we want to run the validation.
All right.
Now this blur is going to be always changing.
So I need to pass news to access in you state of this element and change that touched property we have
right here because after we do the focus out this touch it's to go to true.
So this could be a blur or that could be true.
Doesn't matter for now.
For now I'm just going to put a player that's fine.
So I'm going to save it and I'm going to just check checking this.
I'm going to answer here.
I'm going to stop typing.
You know we're not getting the error message.
Now if I focus out we get the error message and if I keep typing you know and focus out it's going to
be it's going to go to true.
So this one is going to be called true.
You can just check that we get the same thing.
If I focus out we get the message and the fight type something you know I'm not getting the error message.
If I focus out we get the error message.
So you know this is can working.
That's the main idea of having that touched property.
OK so we are pretty much done.
So we need to get the last thing we need to do is to check the the information in the form it's valid
before we submit.
Because if I type for example just to this one it's an error and I typed the other ones and actually
passed them values and now I do SIFF med I'm going to get you know the values and the name.
It's not correct it's not valid but it's still submitting devalues this council log.
It's coming from a sieve for data to submit.
So we need to do something right here to check on the state.
If all the inputs are valid and if we're going to be looping all the inputs inside the state and we
need to check if they have a property of valid true.
Now all of the elements we didn't have the ballot property so we need to add at least now we are going
to be requiring at least the required falles validation.
It's going to be copping this one and I'm going to be changing this one too.
True.
This one is the last name.
Going to make this required and valid.
It's going to be false.
They're going to be copying everything else over here.
The message is going to be koma validation.
It's going to be required true and I'm going to copy this one as well and it's going to be required.
I'm not going to make this one required.
And right from the start this one it's valid because we don't require validation and the same thing
with the with the select right.
We make this nice.
OK.
So now whenever we submit what we need to do right now we have all empty.
So this one it's not good.
This one and this one are not valid.
So we need to do some checking right here to check if we have the value prop the value true inside all
of this right now from the start.
This one the last name and the name are false.
So this shouldn't be submitting.
OK.
So let's go to submit form and I'm just going to do this at the top right here.
So now what do we need to do.
We have the data to submit and we need to check before that if that does that state that form has the
property value valid true inside all of the inputs.
So I'm going to do a for just like we did before.
So for let key.
Same thing with it at the top.
And this state that formed data.
OK.
Once we are inside here we want to check if the form is valid.
So I got to create a new viral that is going to host of Boullion.
So it's going to be form is valid just like that.
So this one is going to be equal to true or it's going to be equal to false.
Right from the start when whenever we submit the form it's going to be true but if it something happens
right here it's going to be changed to falls and we are not going to submit it.
So inside the form are going to be accessing this form valid and they're going to do some checking right
here.
So what I want to check is does not state that form data.
And then we check each key on each iteration and we check if it's valid.
So if this one this key has the valid of true this form ballot it's going to be true.
If not it's going to be false and then are going to be adding one more rule.
We want to check if the form is valid.
OK.
So no this this one it's false formatted it's going to be false.
So we are not going to submit.
So I'm going to say if opening close and I'm going to be checking for Malad and if we do have a valid
form I'm going to be doing the console log.
All right.
Going to save this.
OK.
That's a test.
You know this should be at or are going to be adding a name.
You know I'm going to enter the wrong name of this impot it's not valid.
I'm going to do last name which is you know JONES And you know a message of hello this one.
It's not required.
And then I'm going to be adding an age.
So now if I submit nothing happens I'm not getting a console log.
So that is good.
So what happens if I put the correct information and I submit I get the data that we need to post.
All right.
So you know that is that that is working.
So this is it.
You know this is all we're going to be doing pretty much the same thing on the NBA project begin to
be adding users on a database.
They're going to be doing a log in and we're going to be entering data inside a real database not the
Jason server and we're going to be using a template just like this to you know to enter the information
to create inputs and to validate everything.
But we're going to be doing it on a different way we're going to be changing this a little bit.
So if you think about it what is the downside of this.
You know this logic.
So right here.
Calling to form fields and form fields is entering this state and generating all the inputs.
What happens if this form we need to have some text between last name and message.
I cannot add it because form fields is just rendering all the inputs in a list.
So I cannot just chop this down and put some text in the middle.
We can use this way just to render all the impetus we have in the list.
We cannot add anything in the middle on the MBA project begin to be doing something else instead of
rendering all the fields inside of different components.
You're just going to call to an input feel that has some property and this one is going to be in charge
of rendering won input.
We're going to do that you know before that we need to discuss a lot of things.
So in the next sections we're going to be talking about firebase you're going to be going to be talking
about how to authenticate users how to log in and how to log out.
We're going to be adding all the data we're going to be adding data inside a database and once we know
how to work with firebase we can grab that NBA project we're going to add firebase and we're going to
be adding users log in log out.
We can to create a backhand you know a dashboard of register user so we can add a new post.
So we're going to be doing that.
So let's go to the next section and start with firebase.