OK.
So now we hit the redux section of the course and it's going to be challenging for sure.
So what is redux.
If we check the redux documentation redux dodgiest that org is going to is going to save relex is a
predictable state container for javascript apps and you know that it's nice but it's not very clear.
So let me show your chart and explain you what that redux is going to do.
So let me bring the chart up to go back.
There you go.
So let's pretend that you have three different things.
Redux your application and the browser.
So first we have the Rydex data.
And for example let's pretend that this is something that we can see and we can search we have Rita
we have react and then we have the actual browser.
So we realize what is going to happen someone is going to enter to our domain to our web app and you
know the application is going to start.
So re-act is going to be starting and it's going to request for a list of movies because of course home
needs to render a list of movies.
So we need that data.
So redux is going to do the process of going to the server fetching the information and then it's going
to be stored someplace inside redux.
So then of course we have the list of movies is going to be passing to the component that needs that
list of movies and the component it's going to be rendered on the screen.
That's what's going to happen pretty much.
Then of course if the user selects a movie it's going to go to relax read it is going to fetch the information
about that movie that was selected.
The components are going to receive this.
And then at the end it's going to show the information we need of course is going to go to the next
few with the data.
So this is what happens inside a redux.
In a nutshell.
So the critics and creators of Rydex describes redux as a state management library.
Right here we have the developer experience and it's going to say my goal was to create a state management
library.
So if you remember we work we react and we used a lot of est.
So the idea and the main idea of redux is to make the usage of state a little bit easier.
OK so we think about this.
So the state is an object where we store data.
So again redux going to be kind of a big object where we stored data inside and this data will advise
we act in how to behave.
OK.
That's good.
That's fine.
We need to start with this.
Of course we need to create a new project so go to your computer or your main directory or whatever.
Create a new project do the Create re-act app and delete everything in sight just like we did previously
at the beginning with the before.
So just create a new project and are going to be going to be doing that and I'll be right back.
OK so I have my clean clean project.
The only thing I left you know the untouched is going to be the index that is which has the import react
and the reaction.
That's it.
Then they went there of course.
I don't have an I don't have a file that it's going to be rendering the app going to be doing this in
a minute.
But first we need to do a few things.
Reac or redux.
It is a third party library.
You know it's not from the same developers is not from re-act from Facebook from us from someone else.
So we need to install that.
So we're going to go to the terminal just navigate to your project and first begin to do and PM install
and we need to install redux just like this.
Relax.
We're going to install the latest version is going to be 3.7 2.
And then of course we need to install something else.
Think about this redux is Fruma.
It is a third party library.
So you know it's not related to read to react so we need to install something else that connects redux
with react.
So and that that's going to be called re-act redux.
Just like with with we react router Dom we need to connect something we need to use something to connect
that.
All right so we can react Dasch then redux and it's going to be apt.
And the Bushin is 5 0 6.
That of course mine is mine is safe.
I'm going to press center and then just possibly deal whenever this is done.
All right so everything was installed.
So now we need to do a lot of setup redux is going to use a lot of fans.
It uses a lot of fancy words fancy keywords.
So it's going to be a little bit over whelming.
First one is as we repeat the process many many times it will become natural to us trust me.
So to connect redux we need to import from Briac redux something that cold's provider it's going to
go right here at the top and I'm going to say import just like this opening close and then provider.
Now this provider is going to come from react and then rejects just like this.
So just like we did with re-act router we need to wrap our main application the main starting point
of our application inside of this provider just like we did with re-act router.
So going to go over here the bottom going to you know just make it a little bit better.
And I'm going to bring something that calls provider just like this open and close now inside of the
provider.
I was just you know the app got of course if I do NPM start I need to mention this if I need to do NPM
start you know nothing is going to happen.
We're going to get a lot of errors.
And of course we don't have a nap right here.
App is not defined.
So I'm going to go around here and create just a function functional component that is going to be just
rendering some div just a div so I'm going to say Dev and then hello or something like that just I'm
going to save it.
The application should we render and we get.
Hello.
And of course I'm going to check the inspect.
You can do that as well.
So I fail prop Taieb the props.
Smart as required in provider.
So again again in the provider we need to do something else.
Remember that this provider comes from re-act redux not redux.
So this is a connection between them.
But before we can connect them we need to bring GUI docs to our application.
Right.
OK.
So I'm going to go right here.
I'm going to import something else I can open and close.
Now first we need a couple of things from redux.
We're going to be needing something that cold calls create just like this and store create store and
then we're going to be using something that calls apply middleware.
Remember that we have the apply no cap and then you know caps right here.
OK.
And this comes from redux.
So first what we will need to do is create store but this is a kind of a something that we could keep
right now.
But the thing is that in real life you can be using redux with middleware and you know I'm just going
to jump a step and tell you about a middleware.
I have a chart right here.
Let's bring the chart.
OK so again you can use relex without using mere words.
But again real life you can use them.
So it's just going explain you what we're going to be doing with words why we can use it.
So first again let's pretend that we have an application you know with main the user is going to enter
here then the server is going to go to the server Maker Faire a network request and we will bring the
data whatever data we need to render the actual component.
So this one is going to be stored in redux and then it's going to be passing the information to the
actual component and the component is going to be rendering whatever we need on the screen.
So what could happen is that what happens even after you make the network request and read X receives
the information we need to grab that information before it goes to the component and we need you know
to change the name or maybe to check something or maybe multiply a number and then pass it to the component.
So for this reason what we're going to be doing is we're going to be using Minner wares so middleware
just like the word middleware middle we can use something in-between redux and the data flow you know
the actual component we can grab this information mutated change it whatever.
And then of course do something before it goes to the component that is the main idea of using Mynor
wares.
And again just like I told before you're going to be using this in there in the real live the whole
time.
You're not going to be using read X without made whereas I assure you that of course we can use discreate
store just with the provider and use it.
I'm going to show you right now.
So now we have the interest a provider and we have this keywords from redux.
So again we are using the providers so now we need to grab this provider and we need to tell the provider
that begin to be using redoes.
So we need to connect the re-act redux with redux.
So for this would be can to be using begin to pass.
We're going to be using something that calls store.
So this store is going to be the connection between them.
Now again just like I told you you can do this.
You can create a store and that's it.
But again we're going to be using middleware.
So I'm going to go right here at the bottom and I get to create a viable that is going to be called
create store just like this store.
And then with middleware this variable can be called whatever you like.
Doesn't matter.
I'm just writing something that makes sense create store with middleware.
So again just like it's old for we can pass the create store right here but we want to pass it with
middleware.
So how do we include this create store inside this apply middleware function.
So what we do we call and apply middleware.
And of course it's going to be a function and then what we do we pass the create store just like this
and now create store is going to be it's going to be created.
It's going to be working.
But with men Wheres that we're going to be adding things inside of here.
But don't worry we will get there.
So now since we have this viable that it's create that it's creating a store with the middleware we
need to pass it to the provider this provider needs the connection.
And this one is the connection.
So I'm going to go right here and they're going to say create store with me where I'm going to be passing
this viable.
And of course this is going to be a function we're going to be adding some more things right here.
But for now this is the the first thing that you need to do whenever you work with redux you need to
call the dependencies create the viral that binds the middleware with the create store and then pass
the store to the provider.
That's the first thing we need to do.
If I go to the browser a fight checker on the screen you can get a lot of errors.
And you know we need to do a lot of things before we can see that.
Hello.
Now we are used in redux.
We are doing a lot of things but read ads it's going to need more things.
In this case it's going to be expected there we douceur to be of function.
Now everything works but now this store discreate store it's expecting for a reducers expecting for
something that calls reduce hurt.
OK.
So now we're going to need to stop to make pause and talk about actions and reducers and other big keywords
but this ones are really important.
OK so don't don't skip the next video.
Let's go to the next election next letter and talk about actions.
And we do cers.