OK so you might be thinking updating the redux state or making a network request should be real simple
but not really.
There is a lot of logic and setting up we do.
So we need to discuss now we do series and action creators just like we.
We spoke in the previous on the previous lecture.
So the action creator is going to be the one that is going to be called at first the action creator
will do something and then return an object with a type and a payload.
This object is going to go to all the reducers and is going to search for the reduce or we manually
create for this action and that is going to be Abdy updating the redux state and once the estate gets
updated re-act is going to rerun under and display the information we need on the screen.
So I know its really confusing.
And again sorry but Im going to bring a chart to explain this a little bit better.
And don't skip this chart.
This one is really important.
So let me bring the chart.
OK so again our application someone is going to be entering our domain and our application should be
starting and home is going to be rendering a list of movies.
Right.
OK.
So the first thing that is going to happen is that in our code we said that we want a list of movies
or a lot of movies.
So first what's going to happen.
Are we going to be using in-action creator Now this action creator is going to go of course to the to
the actual server is going to bring the data we need.
And at the end when this action creator it's done is going to be returning an object.
So what is going to be returning is this object we have on screen now this object contains a type and
a payload the type.
If you noticed it's just the keyboard.
So the type could be ID.
Right.
So it's just an ID.
And then the payload contains the information we fetched from the server.
You know the list of movies.
So again but it's just an object with a type and a payload to ride with it.
When an ID and a list of movies but of course we call it type and payload inside the redux world.
So OK so this action creator is going to be returning this object so the action creator will return
an object of course with the action and the action type and the pillow.
So whenever we have this done redux it's going to be sending this to all the reducers.
Now the main job of the reducers is going to be receiving this object with the type in a payload.
So it's going to match the type is going to look at the type.
In this case it's going to be movie and it's going to be searching to all the reducers with it to find
a reducer that it's assigned for this job.
OK so we have a reducers a search for the movie.
All right.
So it's going to take a look at the object take a look at the time.
It's going to see a movie and say OK I need to find the reducer with the type of movie is going to search
all is going to find one and after finds the the correct we desire the reducer is going to be updating
the redux state is going to grab whatever we have inside the payload which is the list of movies and
then it's going to be passing this to the to the state and we can restore everything of course.
And now since it's updating the redux state the redux state is going to be telling the application that
we have the movies the list of movies ready.
So now you should be rendering the actual queen.
You know the actual you know this is what happens with between action creators and we do.
That's why they are so important.
Without them redux is not going to work.
So now we need to learn how to create action creators and how to create reducers.
So let's do that right now.
OK so now what we need to do we need to create.
We do so we're going to be doing that make sense.
You know maybe you're thinking oh are we going to do an action creator because is the first step on
the list.
Well now we're going to be starting with reducers.
It's easier that way.
So this provider it's using redux is creating a store and this creates store uses this middleware.
Now this creates store with middleware.
It's going to be using.
It's going to be a list of all the reducers we have inside inside our application.
And you might be thinking OK just greeting reducers in obtaining the state it might it should be real
simple right.
Well not really.
If there is a lot of things we need to do just to get this starting now just to get this started.
So the reason why we Duc's is so popular it's because when you learn to do all this process it's always
the same goes to the action goes to the reduce or update the state and that's done.
So in a large scale application where you make a lot of network requests and updates read it's going
to make it really simple.
That's why I saw part so popular.
You repeat the same process and it works really good.
So first before we can do anything this store and create install with middleware is going to need a
list of all the reducers inside our application.
So what we do as a convention we create a new directory in your folder inside source that in this case
is going to be called reducers.
So we do Sir's is going to have one file in this case that is going to be called index that jazz This
file is really important.
And then what we get inside this folder is going to be files for you know whenever we do what you need
in this case we are going to be receiving movies.
So I'm going to be calling this movie reducers Danja at reducers singler.
So again right here we're going to be receiving whatever reduced we get.
We're going to be putting whatever we desire we need for movies.
You could have a lot of reducers you could have used a reducers.
I don't know actors directors or reduce or doesn't matter.
You could have a lot.
Now the thing is when we go back to index digest this create story with men where it's going to be receiving
the reducers and it's going to need a list of all the reducers since we could have a lot of reducers.
We need a way to combine all the reducers we have inside our application into one.
So we need to combine all the reducers.
So that's why we are using this index.
Non-jazz next and next is going to be combining all the reducers and then pass it to the create store
with men where it's going to go to digest.
And since we need to combine reducers are going to be importing something that calls combine and then
reducers just like this.
Let me make it right.
Combined we juicers.
And this one comes from redux because now we are working with redux not with the re-act weeks.
So we're going to say redux.
OK.
So this combined with Dysart's is going to be passing something that calls core root.
We do serve.
And again it's a convention.
It's going to be equal to and we're going to be using this combined reducers.
So this combined reducers is going to be receiving a list of all the reducers in this case we have a
redo for movies so we can say movies right.
So this is a viable This concept is going to it's going to go to index.
And this is going to be using this and this would reduce our contains a list of all the reducers since
we need to make this Marvel available for other components.
We're going to do export than default.
And then of course we do sir.
OK.
So this is done.
This is the only thing we need to do right here hear you have more reducers you just add them right
here.
Actors you know directors whatever.
Ok since now we just get one just movies.
I'm going to go back to yes and these create store with middleware is going to need that list of producers.
So going to go right here at the top I'm going to say in port reducers from.
And it's going to be dot for Slash and then reducers.
There's no need for us to do index because you know it is an index.
It already knows.
Since we have the reducers sorry.
What are we going to do.
We can grab this reducers and we're going to be passing this to the store and the create store with
middleware.
So we pass the reducers good makes sense.
I hope so.
OK.
So okay everything looks there.
The only thing is that right here we are not including anything we are saying that you know we have
or we do series that cause movies.
But you know there's nothing inside and we are not importing anything to movies.
It's not that fine.
I'm going to go right here at the top and I'm going to say import movies from Dad forward slash and
then movies we.
So now of course it's going to be receiving a valid valid component.
Now at least we're getting halo.
OK.
It's the least rendering something.
But of course we have an error message stored does not have a ballot reducer.
Make sure the arguments pass and you know whatever it is you know it's right because inside movies reducer
we don't have a ballot reduced or we don't have anything to add.
We do so right now.
So let's do this right now.
OK so let's create a valid reducers.
So a few things are going to happen.
First I'm going to you know I'm going to pass this right here.
So the first thing that's going to happen and action is going to be returning an object.
So whenever the action returns an object is going to be entering here.
The second thing that is going to be happening is that instead of here a reducer is going to be trying
to find a match with whatever we pass we have inside the type of the action are going to get to paste
something something like this and paste it down here.
So whenever we have this action triggers and returns an object is going to be just looking like to look
something like this.
This action is going to be equal to an object and this onda object is going to contain that type and
a payload.
So now this file contains contains an action with a type and a payload.
So now what we can do we can go right here and try to find a match.
So this reducer of course this is not real.
OK we are going to be splitting this in a minute.
So this reduced or what it's going to be.
It's going to be it's going to be just a function and this function is going to have a switch inside
so we can find a match.
Right.
OK.
So I'm going to say oh sorry going to delete this.
And first I'm going to say export the default and what we export is going to be just to function right.
OK.
So this function needs to have to do just two arguments and they are really important arguments and
arguments is going to be the previous state.
And then the action.
And this is equal equal to whatever we are receiving right here.
You know this action with the type and a payload.
So this state is going to be the previous state.
Let me mix in space right here.
So let's pretend the the state know whenever the application starts.
Of course the state is going to be empty or you know you can have just a default state.
So you know the application start starts and we have a state of zero.
So then you're going to be receiving an action which is an object and we're going to be searching right
here with a switch for that action and then that type.
So whenever we find a match what we want to do.
The main purpose of doing all of this is going to be updating the state so the state is going to be
equal to zero.
You know right now it's equal to zero.
So we enter here we find a match.
And what are we going to be doing.
We're going to be returning the state which equals to zero.
But since now we have information we're going to be changing the state.
So it's kind of a look doing like this begin going to grab the previous state which is zero and we're
going to be adding one.
OK.
So maybe later on the application later the user is going to enter to a section where we need to fetch.
We need to trigger this action again.
So we're going to be fetching the list of movies again.
So again we're going to do the same process is going to return an object with whatever data is going
to be entering this function.
And now the state equals do one right.
Not zero.
So when we find a match we return this state which is one and then plus one.
So now the state equals two.
That is why we have the previous state right here.
So we can add to the previous state the new state.
You know we can modify the state and then returned the actual state of course this is not real.
We can do something else.
Now if you think about it right here the state is just the system Arbel.
We don't have anything just yet.
But whenever we see it whenever the application starts this state is going to be just an object so what
we do.
We set it as a default object.
So whenever it starts it's an empty object.
Of course we're going to be doing something right here and we're going to be changing this.
So again the main purpose of this function is to receive an action match a type and then change to take
it.
Right.
OK.
So now what do we do.
What are we going to be entering break here and what we do is just a switch just like we did with the
with templates inside react same idea.
We do a switch.
We match a template and we do something in this case the switch is going to be always listening for
this object.
Right.
And inside of this object we're going to be trying to find a match for that type.
And again this is just an idea a keyboard.
So again since we want to match the type we say action that type you know it's an object we can enter
to the action just like that.
So now this type is going to be equal to something right.
OK.
Now in the case and right here we need to do it manually of course if the case is that we see an object
with the type of movie at least we want to do something right here.
Just do something.
Now we have a default case so we need to do default and what we do we return the previous To say you
know we are not changing the state so we return state.
OK so nothing is going to get changed.
Now if the case is that we find a match you know we have a type of movies list we want to do something.
So what we do we return something and what are we going to be returning is going to be again just an
object to replace the state.
Now remember we have the previous state so we kind of need to include the previous state inside of this
one just not to mutate information you know just not to mutate an object.
So what we do we say that this thing that we're going to be returning this object is going to be equal
to dot dot dot state.
So this object is going to contain all the previous information right.
So it's like having an app application where you have a state or something like this that is going to
be equal to an object and maybe right here you have name.
Maybe you have no one ever parents and this one is going to be an RE whenever.
Right.
So whenever we entered this scenario the state it's equal to this.
If we find a match of movies well remember that inside the payload we have the data we need.
So what we do we pass this object with the previous state that contains name imperent and then we added
something we added whatever we are getting from the payload.
So we say now that that movie is going to be called to action DOD payload something like that.
So now this is going to be returning a new state and now the state is going to be equal to movies just
like this with you know the list of movies or whatever.
So let me delete all this.
You're not going to need it.
We just need this.
So if I save it we're going to go right here and we are not getting an error message.
So that is good.
This is a valid reducer.
Again just it's just a function with a previous state and an action.
And whenever we find a match for the keyboard inside the action we returned the previous state and whatever
data we get from the action that payload that is the main purpose of having this reduced.
This is the only thing that we can do.
And this is going to be updating the state inside redux OK that's good that's enough for now.
So now what we need to do we need to create a Nachum creator that you know does this that that connects
to this every douceur and passes all the information we need to do that.
So let's go to the next section and add an action creator.