OK so now what we need to do we need to add an action creator the action creator is going to be the
one in charge to connect with the producer.
And you know just like with it with that we do so we need a place where we can be hosting all the action
creators.
So I get to go inside source Negre create a new folder called actions just like this.
And now just like reducers we going to have a new file inside of actions called index that Jay has.
All right.
So this is going to be changing this structure is going to be changing in a little while.
So inside actions we're going to have a list of all the actions and you can have multiple actions not
just one.
Right.
So this actually creator is just going to be a function just like the reducer.
So I'm going to say export and then function and notice that I'm not using the default because we could
have many functions.
So going to export a function and this one is going to be called movies list.
Right.
OK.
So the real world for example if we want to make a network request we're going to be using x make that
requires then whatever whatever.
And at the end remember that X just returns a promise.
So whenever we get the promise we get the data we need.
You know the list of movies.
So whenever we get the data out what we do we return an object.
The main the only thing that that this function needs to do is just to return an object.
Now we're going to say Return going to hard code.
For now we're going to be of course doing an ad request and everything else.
For now we're just going to learn the basics.
So it's just going to be returning an object.
This object needs to have a type.
And if you remember this type is the one we need to use to match with the reducer.
In this case the user has a type of movies list.
It's going to go and put moves list.
The second thing that this object needs to have is going to be a payload.
Now the payload is going to be just the data we get from the server.
You know the list of movies have an object right here so you don't have to type I'm to paste it.
So we're going to have just a just an array of objects with three movies both fiction because I love
that movie.
Then a Pacific Rim because I love it.
I know it's a stupid movie but I love it.
And then we have Rambo.
But the first one first blood.
The other ones are really shady.
OK.
So now this is it.
This is our action Creator.
At the end it always returns an object with a type and a payload.
So now what's going to happen is that for example the application starts in our app function.
This component is going to call this function.
This function is going to go to the reducers and it's going to be finding a match with the movers list.
The producer is going to be returning the previous has stayed with the movies we have inside of the
action creator right action that action that payload.
So now the combined reducers we have right here is going to be always listening for what happens inside
the reducers.
So it's going to be detecting a change you know it's going to know that something happened and it's
going to be connecting to the application right to the provider is going to say OK I do it.
I just received new data.
So I have and you stayed and it's going to be passing and storing the new state.
The application is going to know that something happened and you can a new state and of course you're
going to be able to access that state from within the components.
And there you go and you get the at the information that you need it.
So now if you notice there is no connection at all between this action creator and the actual reduce
her user and it's combined with the combined reducers and they combined reducers with the actual store.
But the actions it's not related.
So what we're going to be doing next.
It's going to be creating just changing this app to be a state state component and begin to be connecting
an action see how to use the actions to connect with the reducers.
And you know and update the store and the state.
So we are going to be doing that right now.
OK so how to connect the action creators with the producers and the actual component.
OK we're going to be doing that right now so I'm going to delete this Konst app.
Just going to delete it and I'm going to create a new components right.
A class based component.
So I'm going to go to source create a new file that it's going to be called app.
Yes.
Now app that jazz is going to be a class based component.
So first we need to import re-act from Bre act.
Then we bring components just like this then from and react to.
So then we need to create a class that it's going to be called app and then extends and then component
and this one is going to be render it's going to be going to use the render method.
And of course we always need to return something.
So we say return and for now which is going to return a simple simple dev saying hello whatever.
Now I'm going to go at the bottom I'm going to say export then default.
There we go.
And then of course he's going to be app and are going to delete this time.
So we have our class based components.
So I'm going to go back to index and I'm going to import the app and then from and it's going to be
a dot forward slash and then app.
Right.
So if I saved the project reload the application.
Oh sorry.
We should be getting hello so we get.
Hello.
That's good.
So it's working.
So OK.
So how do we connect we bind redux with the actions and the users and everything else.
OK.
So first we would need do we need to bring something from re-act redux.
Remember that redux.
It's not react.
OK.
Not from the same developers.
So we need a way to connect them both.
You know this re-act notation and the re-act code and and re-act redux.
So we bring import and what we do we can use something called connect and we bring it from react and
then redux.
So this connect is going to be in charge of connecting whatever logic we have from redux with this application.
With this class.
So how do we use it.
OK so I'm going to go to the export default.
I'm going to delete the app.
I'm going to use the connect instead of this connect it's going to be using two different arguments.
Right.
Two different arguments begin to be talking about this.
But for now I'm going to pass.
No you get changes.
Change it.
Change this in a minute.
And then what are we going to do.
We're going to be just rendering the app and the application reload.
And we are still getting Coloe So you know we are not getting any error messages.
So this is working.
So now this connect takes this this arguments.
The first argument is going to be something called Map state prompts which show something else and to
save it we're going to go right here on the East Coast plug ins.
You have to find if you want of course there is something called re-act redux.
Yes six snippets.
So the this one it's true to use snippets of redux.
Right.
They're going to show you why it's good to install it.
So what we need to do right here and I'm going to be typing after the class I want to do map state prompts
and you know it's good to have a snippet because if you have to type this by hand every time you have
to use it you go crazy.
So right here we just have a Condes which is a map state to prop's is going to be just a function.
For now I'm going to delete this.
The second argument you're just going to use one.
So we get one argument and then we run a function and we turn something really real simple.
So I'm going to call this data.
And for now it's just going to be empty right now.
That's good.
So now what is the purpose of doing this.
So what are we going to do we can copy this the name of the barbel and we pass it as a first argument.
It's always the first.
So this is redux quote.
So whenever we connect this one is going to go to redux and it's going to be working with the maps state
to props.
Now what is the main function of my state to props.
Now if we dispatch an action we triggered this this is going to go to the producer and update the store.
So this one this maps state probs is going to be always listening for an action and when the action
happens and we have a new state this one is going to run and it's going to be passing the new state
with the movies.
Right.
OK.
And then what it's going to do this map state to Probst is going to grab the new state and it's going
to inject the new state inside this component as a class.
And now and then we're going to be able to enter this that Probst the data.
And we will have the list of movies now just going to go right here I'm going to say Konsole law and
it going to cost a lot of props to see what we get.
So inside this that props of yours we are getting data and empty so it's going to be injected.
But of course we don't have any data.
And then of course we have this patch we're going to go there later.
So now this second one is going to be the second argument.
It's going to be the actual This patch the one we have here for now we don't have anything.
But the main point of using this is that whenever we import an action we're going to trigger this and
begin to inject this action that that which is dysfunction inside this process.
So we are pretty much doing the same thing that Mab's state Propst.
But with the actions.
Right.
So first it's going to need to import the actions begin to import everything manually.
We're going to change it of course.
So I'm going to import all these actions from.
And then the actions.
So this is going to bring this function right.
OK.
So now all the functions all the action creators are going to be inside this Vrable called actions are
going to be copying this I'm going to paste it as a second argument.
So now the actions are going to be inside maps state to probably notice that right here we have movies
that list and it is a function.
So in theory if now we can do this this stuff probs and then movies list just going to be triggering
this action.
There is a special way to add the actions begin to do it in a minute.
No no just like this because right now we are just learning.
So we're going to go right here and I know that this is going to weird and makes no sense but you're
going to see right now why and how it works.
So I'm going to say component will mount this function is going to be triggering we going to trigger
this before we render everything.
So now remember that we are injecting the actions inside this stuff props.
So in theory if I did this that props and then the name of the action.
This one is going to run whatever function we have right here.
This one is going to it's going to run.
It's going to pass the payload to the reducers and they're reducers will return the information and
it's going to be running the maps state to.
Now with the maps that prompts contain a new state you know with the actual data with the movies and
everything else.
And now let's go back and then map state to prop's is going to inject whatever state we get inside this
props.
So inside here we can have this that props that movies.
So I'm going to go right here and say state that movie is going to save it and go to the application.
So the first time that reloads of course we get no data.
You know the database senti then map state to prop's is going to receive new data in the state.
It is going to inject everything.
So the application will rerun under for a second time.
And inside data we have movies and we have the rate of movies.
So now inside here what we can do we can say this that probably that data that movies
and of course first begin and find because it doesn't exist.
And the second time we get the data and this is why we are going to be using redux.
First we connect and we passed the maps state to prop's that injects the new state inside the component
and then we pass the second argument the actions so we can have the actions available inside this stuff
props.
Right.
And then of course what we can do.
We can just create just the function that is going to be rendering the movies.
I could say I don't know something like render and then movies stuff like that.
And of course it's going to be this that rendered movies and I hear what we can do is just to marvel
and just our function that's going to be called render movies and it's going to be called to a function
opening close.
And this one this render movies is going to be receiving some data and the data is going to be whatever
we have inside data and movies.
So it's going to be render movies and then it's going to be this that prompts that data that movies.
So this is going to be passing the movies this to this component.
So here we're going to say movies.
Good.
OK.
So this one is going to be returning some GSX some are going to change it.
And this this one is going to be just doing a map with the names.
So I'm going to say movies that map open it close we get an item on each iteration and then we're going
to return something.
So let me go back.
Going to be returning this and what we will return is just a div with the with the name.
So I'm going to say item that name going to save it and it's going to fail.
It's ok cannot properly map often define.
And this because it's not finding anything called movies if you remember the first time that the application
loads movies is empty.
We don't have this.
So what we can do we can say if movies we get if for movies is not empty we want to do this.
If not we want to return.
No it's not going to return anything.
So if I save it we should be getting the list of movies Pulp Fiction Pacific Rim and Rambo.
So that works again.
What is the point of doing all of this.
Well whenever you have a large obligation you can have a lot of factions.
So right here what you do you create different actions for different things whatever.
And then whenever you need them you're going to be go into the app import the actions and then just
trigger the action trigger the moves list and then of course maps that to prompt is going to be always
listening.
So this is going to work and you're going to get the information inside.
It's really easy to work with.
Once you get the idea how everything works it works like a charm and you want you will want to use it
the whole time I assure you that.
OK so now we know about the maps stick two props and we have a few more things.
Right now we are importing the actions as a file when we're just passing the actions just like this.
But there is a special way to pass the actions.
So let's go to the next Berio and see how to pass this patch in action.
Probably.