OK so now we're going to see the proper way of using action.
So whenever we want to trigger an action we're going to do it in a different way not this way.
So whenever we trigger an action we say that we dispatch something we dispatch an action not trigger.
So again that is the redux of lingo that we need to use whenever we we want to use an action we dispatch
it.
OK.
So how do we do it.
OK so I'm going to go out the top.
And as you notice we are importing all the actions from within this file.
So right here we're going to get all the functions we have right here but maybe in the future you're
going to have a lot of functions a lot of action creators and you just need to import this one.
So in this case what I'm going to do.
I'm going to delete the actions and I'm going to use destructuring and I'm going to bring just this
one.
OK.
So I'm going to copy and paste.
So now the application is going to fail because we don't have auctions anymore.
We have just one that is going to be called movers list.
So now the proper way to this patch in action is just like doing map state prompts we have a different
way that it's going to be called map.
This patch to prop's make sense.
Yeah.
So we're going to say Consta and then map this patch just like this.
And then two and then prompts.
So this one is going to be just a function and just like we did with the maps that props this one received
state.
This one is going to be receiving this patch just like this.
So the main purpose of this map this patch to props is to return the actions.
So first I'm going to copy the keyboard map this patched props and I'm going to be passing it right
here.
A second argument.
So now the second thing we need to do is to return something inside the map state prompts.
This one is going to be returning whatever action we want to use in this case.
We want to use.
We want to use it to use one that calls movies list.
So I'm going to copy the name and I'm going to paste it Frank right here.
This is an object.
So this move is list at the end.
It's going to be just a function.
So whenever we trigger it we need to refer to this as a function.
So this is a key name right.
So now this one is going to be equal to a function.
Open and Close.
Now this function is going to be using this this patch we have at the top and again is going to be a
function.
So what we pass is going to be the movies list that we have at the top.
It's not the same name.
I'm using the same name.
I get it.
I'm going to change it.
I'm going to say get movies.
Makes more sense.
Get movies.
So whenever we triggered this get movies from within this that Probst is going to be using this.
You know it's going to be dispatching this movie's list that we are importing at the top.
So now instead of using this the props and movies list we used to get movies and we're going to get
the movies right.
So this is the proper way of this patch and in action.
Now the other one you should always use this one.
All right so there's a second way of doing this.
But for this I'm going to need to complicate things a little bit.
What happens if you have a second action creator.
So let's say get director's going to do that.
Just going to copy.
Going to go to index inactions actions are going to copy movies list and are going to say Directors
list right.
Makes sense and for the time I got to change it to death list and payload.
Tarantino mini me cried termer Encino Well you know and then I know a different director Scorsese Argo.
I don't know if this is the correct way to write this.
Maybe like this.
Whatever doesn't matter.
So we have two directors on the Directors list.
So now what we need to do we need to create to reduce her for this.
So I going to go to movies producer or get a copy to case we have on top to paste it down here.
We are using a different type.
So I'm going to just change it.
Copy and then paste it right down here.
Now we're going to be returning instead of movies directors.
Right.
So now our application is just rendering the movies what I want to do.
I want to bring this action creator Directors list inside the app components.
First I'm going to go right here to the Render I'm going to say console that block.
And then this stuff prompts to see what we're getting.
So I going to check in inside data.
We just get movies.
Now I'm going to go at the top and I'm going to bring the all the action creator which is going to be
director's list I'm going to paste it at the top.
OK.
So now we are still getting the same thing of course.
So now what do we need to do we need to trigger this director's list.
We need to dispatch this action again right here.
We only get we have to get movies.
But since this is an object if we want to add another action what we need to do is just create a different
scenario for this so it's going to be get directors just like this open and close and then we pass the
action and it's going to be again this patch open close and we get the directress list and we execute
this.
So now at the top if we do this that prompts and then it get I believe get directors we're going to
be getting that data and maps state to.
Is going to be listening for the state and inside the state inside data we're going to have the information.
So I'm going to save it open and close and inside data.
We have directors and we have movies.
So this is the again the main reason of why redux is so popular ones.
If you want to add something you want to add a function right here just an excellent reader.
You add it then the reducer and then you request it right here at the top.
And you know and you put it right here and that's it.
Then you get the data and it works really fine.
Now there is a second way of doing this.
Now imagine that you have I don't know seven or maybe 10 or 15 actual creators and you need to use them
all.
What are you going to.
You can copy paste right here on the list of 15 times.
No it is not that fun to do this.
So we have a different way.
We have something that calls bind auction creators and bind auction creators.
It's from redux.
So I'm going to delete this for now.
Delete this to save it and I get it all of this.
So we don't get any mistakes.
So right here we are still importing the movie's list action creator and a direct just list.
That's good.
I'm going to bring something else that is going to be called import.
We use destructuring and we say bind bind.
And then action and then creators.
So bind.
Action creators is going to be Fromm redux a from and then redux.
So what does this bind auction creators do for us.
So with this one what we can do we Compounce all the actions we have on the top that all the actions
we are importing is going to just create all that functions.
Notationally we have right here.
So what we can do we first we do the Cong's and then map and then dispatch to prompts map map this patch
to prop's is going to be equal to we are still passing the dispatch just like this.
And then we just return a function.
So what we return is going to be the bind action creators.
This action creates this bind actually.
Creators is going to take two different arguments.
First is going to be an object with all your actions.
And the second one is going to be this dispatch.
So right here seems we have two actions what we could do we just copy the ones at the top and then just
paste it inside.
And if I save it of course it is going to happen.
I need to make the request right here sorry.
So we going to make a call to this that prompts that prompts and then just the name of the of the action
creator and thats it.
Now let me copy the other one directorates list
the application is going to reload and we are still getting the same thing.
And inside data we were still getting directors and we are still getting movies.
Now the thing is about a bind and creators what he's doing is just creating all that logic for us.
And then at the end he's going to be passing to Matt this patch to Probst just the object with the same
key we had as in actions.
So this one is going to be equal to function.
And you know just this patch and that coma and we can have the director's list which is going to be
again a function.
And at the end is going to create all of this for us and it is going to be passing to match dispatch
Propst.
And then at the end begin to be able to access them as a key value pair.
Makes sense right.
So again if you have a lot of actions the other one is kind of a pain in the ass but if you have if
you want to use bind action creators that's going to be better no less typing right.
Lets get this looks nice.
So lets move forward to the next topic we're going to be talking about container's.