OK so so far we've been using keywords like component's imbues and that is fine but we read with three
ducks we need to use something else.
Whenever we have a component that is strictly related to the redux store we need to say that this component
it's a container.
All right.
So whenever we have this type of components we need to put them on a different place.
So I'm going to go to source code and create a new folder called containers and inside containers.
I'm going to grab the app that is going to promote this to containers.
Right.
OK.
Of course the application would crash.
We need to change all the routes.
So now is not going to be in app anymore it's going to be in DOD containers and then app and then app
is going to fail because we know we don't have the correct pack path for actions.
So we can do that for I-Slash actions.
Right.
And if I save it it's going to work just fine.
Now there's one more thing right here.
Well we shouldn't be rendering a lot of data.
You know it's not meant to do that.
What we need to do right here we just need to be passing the props so to some other component that is
going to be just grabbing the prompts so rendering here just a lot of HD M-L and that thing is not recommended.
So what are we going to be doing.
I'm going to go to source and are going to create a new folder called components.
We know there's one components.
Now these components that we see probably from a container up awfully They are called in a different
way just like this one just like this one which is a container.
There are going to be called the presentational components but it's FAE's just a component.
I'm going to name it.
So you should be may name this movie this list makes sense.
Yeah.
So I'm going to say.
And this one is going to be just a functional component so I'm going to do re-act stay list component
Precentor and it's going to create that snippet for me.
This is a different plugging I have installed.
It's going to be you let me find Ed there react Jasc code snippets.
That's pretty cool.
So I'm going to go right here and I'm going to just put movies list movies and then list right.
And then of course I'm going to export this.
This component is going to be receiving props of course.
And I'm just going to do the console log just to see the props console log and then props.
So now this one is going to be receiving the props from the parent component.
This one is a child and the parent is going to be the app.
So now get a copy this function because begin if needed.
On the other components and it's just going to paste it here at the bottom.
So now inside app what we need to do.
Let me do Konst of course.
So this is going to be just receiving the movies and right here we can make a reference to render them
movies and then we're going to be passing whatever we see inside props the same thing with it right
here.
Now we don't have this anymore.
Now we need to include the presentational component.
It's going to be in port then we can call the movies and then list the Make It Right.
There we go.
And then it's going to be from the forward slash components forward slash and then movies list resemble
going to grab this movie Liz and I are going in the lead of this are going to make her reference to
this component.
And since this one is going to be receiving props I'm going to do this.
I'm sorry Dad.
Dad this dad props just going to pass all the props for now.
I'm going to go back to movies list and read this one.
It's going to be rendering let me say right here inside movies list.
We are getting the props now with all the data.
So now what do we need to do is we need to pass a reference to render movies.
So we're going to say prompts dot data dot movies.
And you know we get the same results as just the the index with the array.
So let me just fix it right now.
There is no need.
No I just don't like this.
Error messages are going to be adding just the index is going to be key.
And then the key is going to be called to.
I just like with it before that is done.
So this is the last thing we're going to be discussing in about a redux the most basic redux on the
next few sections we're going to be doing a lot more redux.
And we're going to be starting a tiny tiny application.
It's going to be just just for practice.
Not like the MBA app is just going to be something for practice.
I can create a template with all the routes and everything else so we don't lose time doing that.
And then what are we going to be doing is going to grab that project template and we're going to be
putting redux on the top.
All right.
So let's go to the next section and start doing that.