All right so we can be doing our practice product for four redux.
It's going to be really small.
We are not going to spend a lot of time.
I'm going to give you the template of what we're going to be doing because then at the end of the course
we're going to do a real big project with the redux we react and we're going to be using a real server.
We're going to be using Mongo and mongoose.
So it's going to be is going to be long and I don't want to spend a lot of time on this.
Are we going to do this right now so you can practice redux a plane redux and react on a real kind of
a real live environment so you can have a little more practice and you can go to your project and apply
redux on your own.
So okay I'm going to give you a I'm going to give you downlow to go to resources and download this package.
And you only to of course navigate to this to that directory and do NPM install.
This is going to give you the node modules right after you do that do NPM start.
Just like always and if you go to the package to Jason we have Jason server right here.
So we're going to need to be running Jason's server so go right here and do NPM run Jason and then serve.
This is going to star Jason server right.
If I read the page you should be getting something like this.
All right.
So whenever we click on an artist it's going to take us to the main page of The Artist.
This comes from the database.
And of course if we type something this of course is not working yet.
If we type Hendrick's is going to filter all the results from the database and give his chest.
Hendricks that's the idea and everything of course is going through redux.
All right.
So this is what we're going to be doing.
Let me give you a recap of what we said inside source.
We have the index you know with the router and we are calling routes.
So routes we have two routes we have home and then we have the artist list which is going to be the
index page of each artist.
Now inside home if you go to home and we go here we have a class based component and we have we are
importing two components.
We have a state of artists and whatever the application this view gets mounted.
We're going to be doing a fetch for the artists.
So that list is going to go to the state.
So right here artists list this component is going to grab that list is going to map it and is going
to show this we can know it's real simple.
So then we have the search components the search component.
The only job of the search is going to be passing the On Change event.
You know the the actual keyboard tell me to go back and to go back home.
So this search has a function that calls this and key keywords.
So get keywords is going to be grabbing that event and then the event target value.
So if I do comes along by check the log there we go if I type something I'm I'm going to get that event
right.
So that is working.
So what else.
Well let's say we have the search nothing else.
So we can grab all of this and convert everything to to redux.
Right.
We're using redux.
So let's let's begin doing that right now.
OK so before we can start anything we need to install all the redux dependencies so we going to go to
the to the tabouli have the server reacts over running.
We could kill the process and we're going to do.
Clear right we're going to be installing a lot of things.
So we need to install three main things we need re-act redux we need redux and they begin to be using
something else.
Didn't show you we're going to learn it on this project that cause redux promise.
So first we need to do NPM install.
Let me make it right and PM install and then it's going to be called react just like we did before redux.
That's the first thing I'm going to be using a specific version which is the five that 0.6.
OK.
That's that's what they're going to do space and we to install readouts.
And again I'm going to use a version it's three that seven the two this is the latest version so far
for this course.
So going into space and we're going to be installing redux promise.
Make it bigger.
It's going to be redux and ops or dush and then promise and again 0 5 0 $0.5 3.
And of course we're going to do mine as mine is safe.
So is going to be installing all of this dependencies are going to present or possibly deal and be my
back.
Okay so everything was solved.
Remember to do NPM start back again.
So I'm going to close it.
And go back to the project since we have the Penzeys everything else what we need to do now is to start
connecting redux.
Okay.
So we need to we need to do a lot of things a lot of configuration.
So first from Briac redux I'm going to split it just like this.
You need something called provider.
The provider comes from Briac redux.
So it's provider.
And then of course is space and then from and then react and then redirects.
So what else we're going to need in a create store so I'm going to say import open and close and it's
going to be create and then store.
Now we're going to use something else because we can apply we're going to be applying middleware be
installed redux promised.
So we're going to be doing that.
Could we be using that.
So I'm going to say apply and then middleware.
Okay.
So this one is going to come from redux it's going to say from.
And then Rydex.
There we go.
What else are we going to use that promise.
So import and then it's called Promise and then middleware.
We're going to see why we are using this in a couple minutes.
So we're going to bring this one from redux and then promise but what else.
Nothing else.
This is for now the the only thing we need.
Okay so now I don't want to I don't want to that's that's a little bit better.
So I don't want to render an app.
I want to render everything inside the render whenever we redux we of of don't like to do this.
It depends on what we are doing so I'm going to just copy this browser rudder and again it just delete
it.
I'm going to go right here to the bottom and I'm going to put it right here.
So now if you remember we need to wrap everything inside the provider.
We need to wrap everything with the provider.
So first I'm going to be calling of creating a provider.
So it's going to be provider open and close.
And inside we're going to put the browser router.
So this provider needs a store.
So in say space store equal to something.
Now what we need to do we need to pass the connection between the create store and the API with middleware.
So going to go right here at the top I'm going to say Konst Konst Konst and then create then store then
with and then middleware.
This one is going to be equal to apply middleware.
Same thing with the Priem Priestley is going to be using this promise made aware and the create store
just like that.
Let me move it just like that.
So now this creates store with where is going to be used it is going to be used by the store inside
the provider now of the creature store with middleware.
Oh sorry.
It's going to be is going to be passing something which is the actual reduce.
We don't have it just yet.
That's why we get an error message so we can to fix it.
Let's go to source and create a new folder is going to be called reducers just like that.
Reducers and each producer folder is going to contain an index non-jazz.
Now if you remember we cannot pass a lot of reducers you know just all of the producers inside here
we cannot import all of them.
What we do we import an index that contains all the reducers to do that we need to combine reducers.
So we need to do import opening close and then combine and then reducers and this one comes from redux
from Redux I know this the setting up is boring but you know it's something that we need to do.
So what are we going to be exporting.
It's going to be the route we do sir.
And then we would reduce or he's going to use combined we do sers now combined with juicers of course
the method.
And it's going to need an object I'm going to go right here to the bottom and export it default and
then it's base and rude reducer.
Now this combined reducers is going to need a list of reducers.
We're going to have only one for now.
So I'm going to say artists because you know we're working with artists we didn't have this file just
yet.
I'm going to import it right now and we're going to create it in a minute.
So we're going to say artists from opening close and then Dopp for Slash and it's going to be on the
same directory.
So we say artist and then we do sir.
We don't have the file that's created right now.
I'm going to copy the name.
Go to reducers create a new file and then you put that non-jazz.
So this one the actual reducer is going to return just to function with an action right.
So we're going to say export default and then function open and close.
So this function has two default arguments the first one is the state and by default it's an empty object.
So then we do coma and this reducer is going and we see an action.
So we can do right here we can do a switch checking for the action type match the type and do something.
So we can do switch just like that open and close and begin to be checking the action dot and then type.
Now for now we didn't have a real action we don't have a type.
So we're going to say just by default default opening close and begin to return and then state and that's
it for now this is get we don't have anything we're going to created create this.
The the cases as we go.
So I'm going to save it and if we reload the application we're still going to get this.
And it's because we didn't import.
We are not passing a valid reducer.
So we need to do that.
So I'm going to go work here at the top and I'm going to say import reducers from and then dot for Slash
and then we do hers and say we want to bring the index.
There's no need to do for Slash and index.
So going to save it.
We're going to reload the application.
Oh sorry I forgot to do this.
We need to pass it to the create store with midways.
So we're going to reload it and everything works right.
So everything works fine.
Now of course we have the provider and we have a store we are using redux.
We are not using any actions in anything else but everything is connected.
So the next thing is going to be going to the actual components and start creating containers and creating
the actions and everything else so let's do that right now.