OK so now we need to modify the structure for home.
So right here whenever the application loads we need to fetch a list of articles we to fetch.
So whenever the application slows again is going to show some default articles so we can have something
on screen then we need to dispatch a different action going to dispatch an action for this and we're
going to dispatch a different action for whenever the user type something and begin to do a search with
the keywords.
So we need two different actions are going into this.
For now I'm going to go right here to source and create an action directory.
So I'm going to say actions have this just yet.
So I'm going to say Index stodginess.
So now again each action is going to use Actio so I'm going to import X-ers from X-ers.
That's the first thing.
Now since we are using Jason's server we need to we need the actual R L and we are using local host
3 or 4 so I'm going to create a viral is going to call your L and we're going to host everything inside
of a barbel so we don't have to type it every time we need to make a request to this.
So an action is just a function.
So I'm going to say export than function opening close.
And each each function needs a name.
All right.
So we can call it.
So I'm going to call it our artists list and then all because you know make sense before getting all
the artists.
So each action whenever we dispatch an action is going to return return an object and this object contains
a payload and a type remember.
So we going to say type and then we can say payload.
Now the type is going to be the actual name.
So we can begin to call get artists and then or again because it makes sense to do a coma.
And now the redux promise comes into place whenever we Imbolc this whenever we call this action with
dispatch and action with this name.
The application is going to go here and it's going to immediately return this.
The problem is that we are making a request and a request might take some time.
We remember with ASIO's we make the request and then returns the promise and then might take a few seconds
or milliseconds or whatever.
So this act this return it's not going to stop for the requests you know for the promise.
So we need a way to stop everything until the promise gets resolved and then return the payload and
thats what the promise middleware dust is going to stop everything until the promise is done and then
its going to return this with the actual payload and the response from the database.
So how does this works.
Real simple we can say Konst going to create a viral and I get a call request could be any name.
So I'm going to say X-post dot get open close and I'm going to use template template strengths and first
we need to use the your L we are including the top forward slash and then artists.
Now what are we going to be doing.
Are we going to be limiting this.
So I want to limit everything to six results.
So I'm going to do going into space.
And then of course this returns the promise with the response of response that is going to do something
with that response.
Now since the only thing we are doing is just returning the data and that response there's no need to
do this and to do this return what we can do.
We can just pass response that data.
So the only thing that is going to get returned to this Marvel is going to be this right.
There is no need to do the old thing.
Okay.
So after the the ex-CEO access is done and the response that the promise gets resolved is going to return
whatever data we get from this request.
Okay so I'm going to copy their request and I'm going to paste it down here.
So now promise it knows that we have a promise right here and it's going to wait until everything it
gets resolved and then it's going to return this.
That is the main point of using this is really you know great because it fixes a lot of issues for us.
So I'm going to save it.
So now this action is ready.
What we don't have yet is going to be the actual reduce or we didn't have get artists or reduce her.
So let's go to the we do hers and create one.
We're going to go over here and say case open it close and it's going to be called get Artest all this
one is going to return something but it's going to be returning.
It's going to be first.
That thought and the previous state and they were going to do coma.
Well this one is going to be doing is going to be honest and then list is going to return a of artists
and the contents of this artist's list is going to be the action that payload right so this is pretty
much done.
US it's working.
We are not getting any errors.
But for now we need to do we need to go to Home and convert this home promoted to our container.
So I'm going to go right here to source create a new file.
Sorry not in your file new directory that is going to be called containers.
Now this container is going to be the actual home.
So I'm going to create a new file and I'm going to call it Home.
Home container.
You can call this whatever you want.
And then that jazz.
So this home container is going to pretty much have all have all the logic we have home.
So I'm going to copy all and again paste it there we're going to be modifying this don't worry.
And this one.
Delete it all.
Yeah sorry for that.
Just begin to delete everything.
So now what are we going to be doing is just create a functional component and you know include this
home container.
You're just delegating.
So I'm going to say import and then react from react just like that.
And we close it and we want to import home container and that is the key word.
We know that home is a container because it's related to is going to be related to redux.
So it's dot dot dot for Slash containers for Slash and home container.
This one is going to just return a function that is going to be called home opening close again return.
And then we return some GSX.
We're going to be returning a dev with this home container inside.
And of course we need to do export default and then home for this one is going to fail because it's
outside.
We are making.
We are requesting this views from components and not we are just behind us.
So OK first I got to get rid of this compound with mouth for now and again to get rid of this artist
list and then just delete it going to use it.
Use this in a minute.
We are going to be changing and using this one for now.
So first we need to change.
We need to change some things we need to change the search and the artists because we have the wrong
directory right here.
So this one is going to be inside dot and then components for Slash and the same thing with the other
one its components for latch on to copy this and paste it.
Right.
OK.
So at least we get something that's good.
We're not getting any data but you know we get something you're not going to use this state and get
it delete the state.
That's good.
OK so the first thing we're going to do.
We can fetch the articles whenever the application loads.
OK.
So we need a few things we need to first connect with redux and then we need to bring the actions and
use find action creators.
So I'm going to say import and the first thing is Connect and then it's going to be from and then react
and then redux.
That's the first thing that we need to import the actions we're going to be using.
For now we have only one we have this artist list or so I'm going to go back to home container and bring
that one.
So it's going to be from and then dot dot dot for Slash actions.
We're going to be using bind action creators because you know for now we know that we have one action
but to be using another one in a minute.
So it's going to be behind action just like this and then creators from.
And then redux.
I should be getting the snippet I'm not getting the snippets I know.
I don't know why.
Sometimes it doesn't work the way he does what he wants.
OK so now we have the artists list all.
And we have the by action creators and we have to connect.
So what do we need to do now is to convert the home to use redux.
So I'm going to delete it all.
I going to say export the default and instead of exporting the home default or go.
OK Verio export default and we can just connect.
Now connect is going to use the map stage props and the map dispatched to props for Navigon Noga uses
I'm going to say.
All right.
OK.
So if I say this of course nothing is going to be working OK.
So now what do we need to do with the connect we need to pass the actual components.
And in this case it calls home but we already have a home.
So I'm going to call it home container.
OK.
So I to copy and past the home container.
I know that that's working.
So now the first thing we need to do right.
The next thing we need to do is to do the maps they do props and the maps dispatched to props.
OK.
So first I'm going to do function and then map sorry.
Map state 2 and then props.
Now the map states prop's uses a state and at the end is just going to return something.
Right.
OK.
So what is going to be returning is going to be the artists.
So I'm going to say artists just like this.
Now inside artist is going to be going can host whatever we get from the state DOT artists.
If you go to the artists reducers this one is going to return an artist list.
But on the index of artist it's going to be called artists.
So this is what the name the name will be going to be using inside Home is going to be inside St..
And then the name whatever name we are passing if we are creating this with dogs this one should be
thanks.
So we're going to say state and then artists Okay.
And just for fun I'm going to console log stick open close state now we are not dispatching any action
so you're not really going to get anything.
So I'm going to create the map this patch to prop's you know the opposite of this map.
This patch and then two and then prop's opening Kotz.
So this one has this patch just like that open and close again.
So what are we going to be using is going to be divined action creators.
We have the top.
We only have one action but we're going to be using another one in a minute.
So we're going to say return and then bind action creators.
The first argument and this one is going to be the actions.
So we are we've only have one which is the artist list all sound going to be passing that one.
The second argument is going to be this this patch this patch.
So we have the maps the props and the dispatch the props are ready.
The thing is that you're not really using them.
So I'm going to copy maps maps tipped props and it's the first argument and then the second one is going
to be the dispatch.
Right.
Going to reload the page.
And of course at least it's not failing.
We get the actual view.
So OK so inside state inside this state to Propst we should be getting this function.
So what I'm going to do just just to check me not do this.
Oh sorry.
Now do this and on the Render I'm going to do console that law.
And then this that prompts just a check if at least we get the action inside.
Props.
OK.
So let me make this bigger and go to cons. I'm going to remove this.
We don't really need it.
So we have an object and we have artists which is the object and then artist on which is the function.
This is our action.
So we have it inside props.
That's very good.
OK.
Let's get.
So now let me let me just leave the console open.
We're going to use this in a minute.
So just going to leave it open.
OK.
So now we have the actions the action the artists list all inside this component.
So we need to make to use it.
We need to dispatch an action.
So what we're going to be doing is doing on the component will now the application will start and begin
to do a request for it.
I don't know.
6 6 6 buse 6 articles.
Just like with it here.
So we say this that prompts dot artists all because we have it inside props.
This one is going to dispatch an action is going to go to the actions it's going to dispatch it is going
to get the data we need.
It's going to trigger the get artists on.
Art is always going to go to redux update the store and then we're going to be getting everything inside
the consulate.
So this is the second time right this is the second request after we dispatched the action.
We get this an inside artist.
We have the list of artists so that let's recall and we have sex of course.
Right.
So the next thing is going to be passing whatever we are getting inside artist and then artists list
to the actual component that renders the information which is going to be on this list.
So I got a copy on this list and go right here at the bottom.
And you know include that component open it close.
It's I'm going to be passing a prop with the you know the list of artists that of course makes sense.
Right.
So it is going to be artists just like this artists.
It's going to be equal to opening close and it's going to be inside this that prompts that artists just
like this dot and then it's going to be called Artist list artists list.
It's with a capital L..
It's OK.
Everything kind of looks nice.
Let me just double check the artist reducers is artist artist list.
It's going to be singler.
So let me just change it.
It's going to be artist list.
Everything looks nice.
So now we're going to be getting in there.
Now if you remember the first time we do the consulate this prompts that there's a props artist.
It's empty.
You know.
So we are trying to map something that you know has two keys is that is empty we cannot map it.
So what we can do to fix this in this case what we can do we can just add some checking right here so
we can add we can check if the you know the list it's empty or not and do something if the list is not
empty.
If it's empty of course do nothing.
So I'm going to say if props Dodd artists just like this it's it's of course it's true.
We're going to do something and I'm going to be adding an additional checking.
I'm going to say props that artists just like this dot and then lenge.
And it's greater than zero.
So this way we are sure that we have something decide that props that artists are and if not if it's
empty What are we going to be doing.
You're just going to return.
No we're not going to show anything.
So if I say it we are going to be getting the list.
And we're getting six.
So this comes from burritos right.
Really cool right.
So everything works as expected.
OK so the next thing is going to be dispatching an action whenever we type something right here we are
getting the data inside the console lock because we have an event listening for this.
But we don't have an action that listens for this.
So let's go to the next section and add an action an action for that for the for the search.