Read so the next thing would be for us to add an action that it's going to be fetching for us it's going
to do an actual request for whatever we type here.
You know we do a search.
OK.
We don't have an action for that.
So we're going to go to actions and create a function that it's going to be doing that.
So inside actions is going to be export and then function.
And then the name of function is going to call it artist and then list whenever.
Now the difference the difference with this with this one.
Then the artists list all is that this one takes in arguments.
We need to catch.
We need to be we need to receive the keywords we are typing right here so whenever we read dispatches
section begin to be passing the keywords.
So at the end there's one rich received an argument I'm going to call it keywords OK save it.
Now this one works just like this one right.
We do a request and then we pass the payload.
And because I'm lazy I'm going to copy and paste it right here at the top.
So this one is going to do next.
Actually I was request to the same Ural to the same path but this one is going to be changing a little
bit.
What we do we pass a Q and equal.
This comes from Jason's server to make a search.
We pass a Q An equal to whatever is that you want to search and the information we have it inside keywords.
So I'm going to say key words.
So this one is going to do it's going to go promise and when they promise gets resolved it's going to
return to data just like this one.
Right.
OK.
So again we're going to be returning a type in a payload.
So it's going to be return opening close type and then pay load.
Now the type for name again it could get artists just like the skins is an object we need to do in Tacoma
and then we passed the request actual request.
So our action is ready.
We need to add a get artists to the reducers.
So let's go to Nichols's Let's go to artists reducers and add value readers are for this.
So it's case opening close and again called Get and let me just make sure get artists OK.
So this one is going to return something.
And what is going to be returning is going to be the same thing than this one.
Why.
Whenever the application loads this component does view graphs.
Whatever we have in the list of artists list whatever we have down here and renders everything then
whenever we want to change it we are changing the same list.
So this component is going to get We've rendered but we know with maybe one resoled or maybe two results
here.
All right.
That's the main point.
We're using the same one.
OK.
So the reducer.
It's ready.
So let's go to the home container and include the action so I'm going to copy the name of the action
artist list.
I'm going to put it on the top.
They're going to go at the bottom and include it in bind.
Action creators.
OK.
So now how can we use it whenever we type something this search keywords and this dysfunction gets executed
right here.
So we're going to get the keyboard.
So all you can do instead of console law is to this to this petty action right here.
So we're going to at this.
I'm going to say this that prompts dot and then artist list and this one of course receives a key note
which is the argument.
So if I save it and test that should be working.
So I'm going to say Hendrix and works.
You know we are getting everything.
So if I delete it of course we're going to say Madonna and Madonna works.
Let's say cash.
OK.
So that works.
Now of course there's a lot of improvements we can do here.
If I delete everything it's fetching the whole database again this is how we are Jason's are works.
But what we can do instead of what we can do of course more checking right here we can check if the
value eats empty and triggered the list all again.
And you know it's going to bring just sex.
What else instead of just doing something whenever I type maybe two characters I could wait until I
get I don't know five characters or maybe three characters and then triggered search so we can do a
lot of improvements.
We're not going to spend time doing that because that is just javascript.
It's not of maybe re-act redux it's just javascript.
So I'm going to leave that right you're not going to do it.
Beginner spend time on the final project not this one.
OK so everything's ready for the home.
So the next thing is going to be building this.
Modifying this this one.
Still using Jason's server is doing how request an actual request from the component will mount.
So we going to be changing all of all of this logic and adding we do source inactions of course.
So let's begin doing that.
OK so let's add redux to the artists list.
If I go to components and artists list we can see that we have I'm sorry to the artist that yes we have
again the same thing as home.
A caste based component with the doing the request or the component will mount and then we render the
template from this that state up artist real simple.
So we're going to do the same thing at home.
This one is going to be using RE redux.
So we need to promote this one to a container.
I'm going to create a new file.
It's going to be called Artist underscore container.
Jack's got going to go back to artist copy all and then pasted down here.
Going to go back to artist and delete everything.
Yeah sorry for that.
So inside artist it's just going to make a reference to artists container just like with at home.
So if we import re-act from and then Riak what else we need to import the artist and then container
from that that forward slash container's forward slash artists container then we need to of course we
need to return function.
It's going to be called Artist equals to a function.
And this one we'll return opening close ups open it close and we we need to return artist container
right make sense than we export and default and we export artist not container just Arzt.
So this one should be working.
If I save it it's going to reload.
But it's not going to work.
It says cannot read properly.
Paramo of undefined and this is because artists container to make the request is searching for the program's
and the ID.
But since now this artist container is a child container it's a child component.
We don't have this information.
We have it in the parent but not on the child.
So what we can do we can request the props.
Right.
And we can say dot dot dot props.
So now are just containers is going to receive whatever props artist has.
And that's why it's working.
We have the programs and ID available here.
OK everything's good.
Now we need to modify this to use redux.
But first we need to create the actions and the reducers we didn't have that.
So pretty much what are we going to be doing is just create an action that is going to be receiving
this ID.
OK.
And then of course there are going to be doing pretty much this.
So I'm going to go to actions and inside actions I'm going to create a new one.
It's going to be called export and then function.
And we're going to call it artist and then detail expense.
There's what is going to receive the argument of the ID.
And again Sims and Lacey are going to copy this and paste it down here.
Now again the request is going to be the same.
Your RL is going to be artist but this one is going to be changing it's going to change.
We're going to we will request for an ID a off and whatever we get as an argument.
Right.
So then it's going to return to promise and then the data.
So now the user instead of going to get Artest all is going to go to a different place so we say detail
right.
And we pass.
Whenever we get from that request we don't have this but this reducer So let's go to reducers and create
a new one is going to be case open opening close get Artest detail begin to return return and then we
pass that state coma.
And now we need to create a new one.
We are not going to use this one.
We want to do something else.
So I'm going to call it artist and then data and this artist data is going to be equal to action that
payload.
All right.
So now on leave after we trigger this action after we dispatched the section is going to go to the producer
and all the information we need for this artist is going to be inside artist and data artist data.
Right.
Just like with with the other ones I told you that we'd read us when you get the first one.
Everything else is just redundant.
Its pretty much the same you just change the ID and the name of the key.
Right.
OK so everything looks ready.
We have the action and we have the reducer.
So now we need to change this artist container to use redux around.
So what do we need to do first.
Is this going to be requesting importing all the the connect and the creators and everything else.
So I got to say import make it ride import and then connect is going to be from react and then redux
the next is the action.
So import and if we take a look at the actions the action calls artist detail so art is detail is going
to be from.
And then I believe its not that force and then actions but going to use mind action creators we get
to use a second one.
We can discuss this in a minute import and then bind action and then creators from redux that looks
nice.
So now we need to use the connect so I'm going to go right here at the bottom.
I'm going to delete this and we're going to start again.
It's going to be export then default and instead of exporting the actual component we export connect
begin to say no no because we didn't have the maps state and the map dispatch.
And we're going to be using the components This one calls artist and the parent component cold calls
artist as well so I'm going to I'm going to cut I'm going to change it to container.
OK.
So there we go.
So at least we should be getting something at least.
OK.
So everything is good.
Let's create the maps that props and dispatched the props.
So I'm going to save function map date too.
Props to all of you again redundant.
Everything is the same opening close and we say state.
Now the argument that map state prompts going to be using.
So of course this one is going to return something and it's going to return the artists.
It's going to be equal to star state DOT artists just the same thing with the home component.
OK.
Looks nice.
It's really this patch.
So I'm going to save function and then map this patch to props.
Let me make it right this patch too.
And then props open it close.
The argument is going to be this patch.
Right.
So we get to use bind action creators so we use return and then bind action creators.
The first argument is going to be whatever action we are importing at the top right.
And the second argument is going to be the actual dispatch.
If I save it nothing's going to happen of course but what we need do we need to use the maps state to
probs and get this patch to Propst down here.
Right mobs dispatched props and as a second argument right again everything looks nice now.
Right here this component is rendering whatever data we have on this that's data art.
So we're going to need to change this a lot.
But first I would like to check if the action works.
First I'm going to go to the render and I'm going to do console that blog.
And then this stuff prompts just a check for least we get this action on the prompts.
So if we check it we have match location.
We have our justi tell Let's get.
So we are getting the we are getting this.
So now what I'm going to do since I went to this patch to S..
I'm going to say this that prompts dot artist and then detail and what we are going to be passing is
going to be this that props that match that harams that ID.
So in theory in the console log we should be getting the artist right here we have artist artist data
and we get the artist data.
So everything works.
Everything works really nice.
And how easy was this was the same process then home.
And we are getting the data.
This is why redux is so popular again after you get the process.
Everything is the same.
Right.
OK.
So now we're going to need to change this component a lot to render this data we get from here.
You know we are getting inside artist state data right now is rendering everything from state.
If I delete the state of course and delete the X-posts everything is going to fail because we don't
have state.
OK so let's see how to fix this.
All right so let's see how do I fix this problem.
Again the first time that the application loads we didn't really have an artist's.
We have it on the second time.
So we again we need to do the same thing at home.
We need to check if this data exists.
And if it exists we wonder if we're under said this.
If not you're not going to run anything.
So first I'm going to delete this.
You're not going to use it.
We're going to host the template inside of a function.
So I'm going to say artist and then template just like this.
Open and close.
We're going to say we're going to be receiving some data and then we can of course do something.
So what we're going to be checking we're going to be checking if data inside data we have something
that cold calls artist data which is you know the information we need.
The one we have on the actual producer is data.
So I'm going to say data dot and then artist and then data is available.
We want to do something.
If not we do know.
All right.
So get to put it right here.
I get to go to the template right here.
Copy all can to cut it and paste it in.
Inside of here if you select this and make right click and then form selection is going to pretty fine
everything.
So this looks nice.
If we have data inside artists that data this is going to get Brender right.
So now we need to make a reference to this function.
And of course pass the information we have in this the prop's that artist remember that all the information
is inside of here.
So I'm going to say open it close and then this dot and we make a reference to this function artist's
template.
So it's going to be artist template.
And what we will pass is going to be whatever information we have inside artist.
This props then artists right.
Same thing we have here.
Now this one is not going to work because re-act doesn't like this.
We need to do we need to wrap everything inside of a div.
OK so now we're going to make reference to this template and we have a different message.
We're passing this the props that artist the first time that this Lote's this that processed artist
and artist data.
It's going to be empty art stated doesn't exist.
So nothing is going to happen the second time.
Artist data is going to be avail for us.
But right here inside of this template we are making of reference to artists so artists doesn't exist.
What exists is going to be Deda dot artist data.
And remember this is not an array of objects is just one.
So we're going to do this.
We can do zero to access the first the first object.
All right.
So I'm going to copy data.
I'm going to copy this paste it right here whenever we get artists.
So artist artist albums artists albums everything is good.
Right.
So now the application will reload.
And we have a different plan right here.
We are returning just to function.
We are not returning some GSX so I'm going to remove the curly braces again to go right here at the
bottom and change it for a print and print piece.
And now the application is going to reload and we get the information.
Everything works just like before.
So everything works really cool.
I'm going to show you a different problem.
Maybe it just let me double check maybe you have time maybe get time maybe not.
OK.
So I'm going to go right here to the network tap and when we make it open open open it I'm going to
go back to home.
Going to reload the application and now right here I'm going to make the application slow.
I'm going to put up faster G.
Is it still slow for us.
I'm going to click and Jimi Hendrix is going to go.
You see the white page.
And then it's going to of course show Shumi Hendrix going to go back home.
I'm going to click Madona.
You see Jimi Hendrix and then you see Madona.
The thing the problem is that on the previous has stayed right here on the Get artist detail since the
first time you clicked on the on an artist the information of Hendrix is going to be before the application
app updates everything with the Madona information.
That's why whenever you enter a new artist first you're going to get the old information until the action
gets triggered gets the information from Jason's server and updates the story.
So if a click cache we see Madona and then we see cache.
So we have that problem.
This is the last thing we're going to do.
So let's go to the next section is going to be real small.
Right.
But just go to the next section and fix fix this problem.