OK so how are we going to be fixing this.
So the solution is going to be dispatching an action whenever this component and mounts.
So if I exit there we trigger a function or an action dispatch an action that is going to be deleting
whatever data we have inside artist and data write is going to set it to nothing to null.
So that is that's the solution if you want it you can do it alone at home.
If not of course I'm going to do it right here with you.
So first we need an action for this.
So I'm going to go to actions and incite actions are going to create one that is going to be real simple
to say export than default the fault and then I'm going to call it clear.
And then Art is detail going to copy and paste it and make the capital A.
So there you go.
So this one is going to be real simple.
You're not going to do pretty much.
You're not going to do anything.
It's just return just like this.
Open and close.
And instead of default sorry my mistake is going to be function and inside the return we pass the type
and I'm going to call it clear underscore artist's artist and the detail and the option that payload
is going to be nothing.
You know we want to do lead to make it.
No.
So we say payload and it's going to be equal to null.
So whenever we triggered this actually is going to go to the reducers going to find it and begin to
be changing that artist data to nothing to know.
So the next time that it floats the data is not going to be available.
Right.
OK.
So I'm going to save it.
I'm going to go to the artists.
Reduce her and create a new case for this.
First I'm going to copy the clear detail keyword so I'm going to say Kate case open it close and pass
the name and we say return return.
Well return opening close and first one is dot dot dot state.
And then we make her reference to artist detail with the same information with the action that payload.
So whenever we dispatched this section it goes to this producer artist data is going to be equal to
null.
So the next time that it floats nothing it's going to be showing or shown on the screen.
Right.
Makes sense.
So going to save it.
And now we need a way we need to dispatch the action whenever the component component and mounts.
All right.
So I'm going to go over here at the top and this this will get triggered on the component will unmount.
So we say components just like this then will and then unmount component will unmount.
So we didn't have the action we need to bring into the top so I'm going to go to the to the index copy
the name and go back to artist container and paste it on the top.
And it's of course to do it on the on the Byne action creators as well.
OK.
So that is ready.
We're going to have this function available.
So now this is available I'm going to go right here and say this is that.
Probs dot and clear detail.
That's it.
That is the solution.
I'm going to go back to home of course we are still with fast 3G so I got to go back to home when we
load the application.
OK Scott it's going to take time while we're going to go to Hendriks I get to go to Hendriks.
OK.
Why Paige.
And then if I go back home and I go to Madona we are not going to get Hendriks you know empty page and
then Madona and same thing if I go to Pink Floyd nothing.
And then we get pink floyd.
So that is the solution for this.
All right.
OK.
Just like I told you before with redux everything is redundant after a while after you know how to do
this.
You can have some snippets available.
You're going to trigger certain commands and it's going to do everything for you just like this one.
The only thing you will need to change is going to be this if you're going to be using maps or prompts
or just this patch and the name of the container of course and the actions but everything else is just
just the same right.
It's always the same idea.
You are.
This map stage probs you'll dispatch an action update the prompts and then you use it on your application.
It's always the same idea.
All right.
So in the next section we're going to start with.
We're going to start with something else.
It's going to be really really fun.
Then at the end we're going to do kind of a big project beginning could react beginning called servers.
And of course we are going to be using redux.
And yeah we're going to use redux on a a default on a different level.
Right.
OK so let's go to the next section and start with something else.